<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1000319-ditte-dennisor]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1000319-ditte-dennisor" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2013 21:29:40 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7879-either-kill-me-or-take-me-as-i-am-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2013 21:29:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditte add a quote by marquis de sade]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7879-either-kill-me-or-take-me-as-i-am-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Either kill me or take me as I am, because I'll be damned if I ever change." -- marquis de sade]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221968-you-re-in-a-car-with-a-beautiful-boy-and-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 12:52:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditte add a quote by richard siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221968-you-re-in-a-car-with-a-beautiful-boy-and-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You’re in a car with a beautiful boy, and he won’t tell you that he loves you, but he loves you. And you feel like you’ve done something terrible, like robbed a liquor store, or swallowed pills, or shoveled yourself a grave in the dirt, and you’re tired. You’re in a car with a beautiful boy, and you’re trying not to tell him that you love him, and you’re trying to choke down the feeling, and you’re trembling, but he reaches over and he touches you, like a prayer for which no words exist, and you feel your heart taking root in your body, like you’ve discovered something you didn’t even have a name for." -- richard siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/330164-eventually-something-you-love-is-going-to-be-taken-away</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 12:52:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditte add a quote by Richard Siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/330164-eventually-something-you-love-is-going-to-be-taken-away]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eventually something you love is going to be taken away. And then you will fall to the floor crying. And then, however much later, it is finally happening to you: you’re falling to the floor crying thinking, “I am falling to the floor crying,” but there’s an element of the ridiculous to it — you knew it would happen and, even worse, while you’re on the floor crying you look at the place where the wall meets the floor and you realize you didn’t paint it very well." -- Richard Siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256382-i-ve-been-rereading-your-story-i-think-it-s-about-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 12:54:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditte add a quote by Richard Siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256382-i-ve-been-rereading-your-story-i-think-it-s-about-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’ve been rereading your story. I think it’s about me in a way that might not be flattering, but that’s okay. We dream and dream of being seen as we really are and then finally someone looks at us and sees us truly and we fail to measure up. Anyway: story received, story included. You looked at me long enough to see something mysterioso under all the gruff and bluster. Thanks. Sometimes you get so close to someone you end up on the other side of them." -- Richard Siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101504-you-go-to-work-the-next-day-pretending-nothing-happened</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 12:56:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditte add a quote by Richard Siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101504-you-go-to-work-the-next-day-pretending-nothing-happened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You go to work the next day pretending nothing happened.
Your co-workers ask
if everything's okay and you tell them
you're just tired.
And you're trying to smile.  And they're trying to smile." -- Richard Siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308623-here-is-the-repeated-image-of-the-lover-destroyed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 12:57:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditte add a quote by Richard Siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308623-here-is-the-repeated-image-of-the-lover-destroyed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here is the repeated image of the lover destroyed." -- Richard Siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/579054-imagine-that-the-world-is-made-out-of-love-now</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 12:58:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditte add a quote by Richard Siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/579054-imagine-that-the-world-is-made-out-of-love-now]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine that the world is made out of love. Now imagine that it isn’t. Imagine a story where everything goes wrong, where everyone has their back against the wall, where everyone is in pain and acting selfishly because if they don’t, they’ll die. Imagine a story, not of good against evil, but of need against need against need, where everyone is at cross-purposes and everyone is to blame." -- Richard Siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/657363-you-re-waiting-because-you-thought-it-would-follow-you-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 13:02:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditte add a quote by Richard Siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/657363-you-re-waiting-because-you-thought-it-would-follow-you-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...you're waiting because you thought it would follow, you thought there would be some logic, perhaps, something to pull it all together but here we are in the weeds again, here we are in the bowels of the thing: your world doesn't make sense." -- Richard Siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/796430-i-am-the-wind-and-the-wind-is-invisible-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 13:04:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditte add a quote by Richard Siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/796430-i-am-the-wind-and-the-wind-is-invisible-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the wind and the wind is invisible, all the leaves tremble but I am invisible, blackbird over the dark field but I am invisible, what fills the balloon and what it moves through, knot without rope, bloom without flower, galloping without the horse, the spirit of the thing without the thing, location without dimension, without a within, song without throat, word without ink, wingless flight, dark boat in the dark night, shine without light, pure velocity, as the hammer is a hammer when it hits the nail and the nail is a nail when it meets the wood and the invisible table begins to appear out of mind, pure mind, out of nothing, pure thinking, hand of the mind, hand of the emperor, arm of the empire, void and vessel, sheath and shear, and wider, and deeper, more vast, more sure, through silence, through darkness, a vector, a violence, and even farther, and even worse, between, before, behind, and under, and even stronger, and even further, beyond form, beyond number, I labor, I lumber, I fumble forward through the valley as winter, as water, a shift in the river, I mist and frost, flexible and elastic to the task, a fountain of gravity, space curves around me, I thirst, I hunger, I spark, I burn, force and field, force and counterforce, agent and agency, push to your pull, parabola of will, massless mass and formless form, dreamless dream and nameless name, intent and rapturous, rare and inevitable, I am the thing that is hurtling towards you…" -- Richard Siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
