<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1000504-tricia]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1000504-tricia" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2009 07:03:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11500-i-would-be-most-content-if-my-children-grew-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2009 07:03:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tricia add a quote by Anna Quindlen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11500-i-would-be-most-content-if-my-children-grew-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would be most content if my children grew up to be the kind of people who think decorating consists mostly of building enough bookshelves." -- Anna Quindlen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157063-her-face-was-round-and-rosy-with-a-healthful-downy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 10:58:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tricia add a quote by Harriet Beecher Stowe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157063-her-face-was-round-and-rosy-with-a-healthful-downy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her face was round and rosy, with a healthful downy softness, suggestive of a ripe peach.  Her hair, partially silvered by age, was parted smoothly back from a high placed forehead, on which time had written no inscription, except peace on earth, good will to men, and beneath shone a large pair of clear, honest, loving brown eyes; you only needed to look straight into them, to feel that you saw to the bottom of a heart as good and true as ever throbbed in woman's bosom.  So much has been said and sung of beautiful young girls, why doesn't somebody wake up to the beauty of old women?" -- Harriet Beecher Stowe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157069-for-twenty-years-or-more-nothing-but-loving-words-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 11:01:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tricia add a quote by Harriet Beecher Stowe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157069-for-twenty-years-or-more-nothing-but-loving-words-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...for twenty years or more, nothing but loving words, and gentle moralities, and motherly loving kindness, had come from that chair;--headaches and heartaches innumerable had been cured there,--difficulties spritual and temporal solved there,--all by one good, loving woman, God bless her!" -- Harriet Beecher Stowe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30327-it-was-the-first-time-that-ever-george-had-sat</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 13:03:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tricia add a quote by Harriet Beecher Stowe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30327-it-was-the-first-time-that-ever-george-had-sat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was the first time that ever George had sat down on equal terms at any white man's table; and he sat down, at first, with some constraint, and awkwardness; but they all exhaled and went off like fog, in the genial morning rays of this simple overflowing kindness.

This indeed, was a home, - home, -a word that George had never yet known a meaning for; and a belief in God, and trust in His providence, began to encircle his heart, as, with a golden cloud of protection and confidence, dark, misanthropic, pining, atheistic doubts, and fierce despair, melted away before the light of a living Gospel, breathed in living faces, preached by a thousand unconscious acts of love and good-will, which, like the cup of cold water given in the name of a disciple, shall never lose their reward." -- Harriet Beecher Stowe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121252-i-will-give-you-this-my-love-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 19:01:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tricia add a quote by Donald Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121252-i-will-give-you-this-my-love-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["  I will give you this, my love, and I will not bargain or barter any longer.  I will love you, as sure as He has loved me.  I will discover what I can discover and though you remain a mystery, save God's own knowledge, what I disclose of you I will keep in the warmest chamber of my heart, the very chamber where God has stowed Himself in me.  And I will do this to my death, and to death it may bring me.
  I will love you like God, because of God, mighted by the power of God.  I will stop expecting your love, demanding you love, trading for your love, gaming for your love.  I will simply love.  I am giving myself to you, and tomorrow I will do it again.  I suppose the clock itself will wear thin its time before I am ended at this altar of dying and dying again.
  God risked Himself on me.  I will risk myself on you.  And together, we will learn to love, and perhaps then, and only then, understand this gravity that drew Him, unto us." -- Donald Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90648-i-ll-tell-you-how-the-sun-rose-a-ribbon-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 19:04:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tricia add a quote by Donald Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90648-i-ll-tell-you-how-the-sun-rose-a-ribbon-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'll tell you how the sun rose 
A ribbon at a time... 

It's a living book, this life; it folds out in a million settings, cast with a billion beautiful characters, and it is almost over for you. It doesn't matter how old you are; it is coming to a close quickly, and soon the credits will roll and all your friends will fold out of your funeral and drive back to their homes in cold and still and silence. And they will make a fire and pour some wine and think about how you once were . . . and feel a kind of sickness at the idea you never again will be. 

So soon you will be in that part of the book where you are holding the bulk of the pages in your left hand, and only a thin wisp of the story in your right. You will know by the page count, not by the narrative, that the Author is wrapping things up. You begin to mourn its ending, and want to pace yourself slowly toward its closure, knowing the last lines will speak of something beautiful, of the end of something long and earned, and you hope the thing closes out like last breaths, like whispers about how much and who the characters have come to love, and how authentic the sentiments feel when they have earned a hundred pages of qualification. 

And so my prayer is that your story will have involved some leaving and some coming home, some summer and some winter, some roses blooming out like children in a play. My hope is your story will be about changing, about getting something beautiful born inside of you, about learning to love a woman or a man, about learning to love a child, about moving yourself around water, around mountains, around friends, about learning to love others more than we love ourselves, about learning oneness as a way of understanding God. We get one story, you and I, and one story alone. God has established the elements, the setting and the climax and the resolution. It would be a crime not to venture out, wouldn't it?" -- Donald Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205243-when-you-stop-expecting-people-to-be-perfect-you-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 19:04:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tricia add a quote by Donald Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205243-when-you-stop-expecting-people-to-be-perfect-you-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you stop expecting people to be perfect, you can like them for who they are." -- Donald Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124340-even-our-beliefs-have-become-trend-statements-we-don-t-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 19:06:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tricia add a quote by Donald Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124340-even-our-beliefs-have-become-trend-statements-we-don-t-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even our beliefs have become trend statements. We don’t even believe things because we believe them anymore. We only believe things because they are cool things to believe." -- Donald Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208956-i-fell-in-love-with-books-some-people-find-beauty</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 19:06:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tricia add a quote by Donald Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208956-i-fell-in-love-with-books-some-people-find-beauty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I fell in love with books. Some people find beauty in music, some in painting, some in landscape, but I find it in words. By beauty, I mean the feeling you have suddenly glimpsed another world, or looked into a portal that reveals a kind of magic or romance out of which the world has been constructed, a feeling there is something more than the mundane, and a reason for our plodding." -- Donald Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2614-it-occurs-to-me-it-is-not-so-much-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 19:14:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tricia add a quote by Donald Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2614-it-occurs-to-me-it-is-not-so-much-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It occurs to me it is not so much the aim of the devil to lure me with evil as it is to preoccupy me with the meaningless. " -- Donald Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
