<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1002943-jackie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1002943-jackie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 12:06:47 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/592860-far-outside-the-city-the-tree-frogs-were-calling-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 12:06:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Ann Patchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/592860-far-outside-the-city-the-tree-frogs-were-calling-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Far outside the city the tree frogs were calling her, and the deep, rhythmic pulse of their voices set the blood flow to her heart." -- Ann Patchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/592867-i-saw-it-myself-an-endless-succession-of-mongrels-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 12:25:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Ann Patchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/592867-i-saw-it-myself-an-endless-succession-of-mongrels-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I saw it myself. An endless succession of mongrels and malingerers, the laziest dropouts who fancied themselves explorers. He made his policy clear: he was not responsible for their food, their shelter, their safety, or their health. He didn't waste his time discouraging them because frankly there was no discouragement they could not withstand. All of the energy they could have put into their intelligence they had used to develop their tenacity. But what I quickly learned was that their tenacity was for going, not for staying. Once they were out on the trail they fell like flies. Some took a day, two days, others were gone in a matter of hours, and Dr. Rapp never stopped for them. He remained beautifully consistent: he was to work and he would continue to work. He would not ferry back the weak and the lame. They had chosen to get themselves in and they would simply have to figure the means to get themselves out. People were quick to accept these terms until they themselves were weak. Then they changed their tune entirely, then they said Dr. Rapp was heartless. They couldn't slander him as a scientist but they said no end of scurrilous things about him as a man. He hadn't rescued them! He hadn't been their father and mother! I will tell you, none of that troubled his sleep. If he had made them his responsibility, either by dissuading them from their ambitions or by bailing them out of their folly, the greatest botanist of our time would have been reduced to a babysitter. It would have been an incalculable blow to science, all in the name of saving the stupid." -- Ann Patchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11268-it-makes-you-wonder-all-the-brilliant-things-we-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 12:26:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Ann Patchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11268-it-makes-you-wonder-all-the-brilliant-things-we-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It makes you wonder. All the brilliant things we might have done with our lives if only we suspected we knew how." -- Ann Patchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80728-there-was-such-an-incredible-logic-to-kissing-such-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 12:27:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Ann Patchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80728-there-was-such-an-incredible-logic-to-kissing-such-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was such an incredible logic to kissing, such a metal-to-magnet pull between two people that it was a wonder that they found the strength to prevent themselves from succumbing every second. Rightfully, the world should be a whirlpool of kissing into which we sank and never found the strength to rise up again." -- Ann Patchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279293-thank-god-roxane-coss-had-not-fallen-in-love-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 12:29:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Ann Patchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279293-thank-god-roxane-coss-had-not-fallen-in-love-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thank God Roxane Coss had not fallen in love with one of the Russians. She doubted they could make it up the stairs without stopping for a cigarette and telling at least one loud story that no one could understand." -- Ann Patchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
