<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1003770-anne]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1003770-anne" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 08:04:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41134-fortune-may-have-yet-a-better-success-in-reserve-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 08:04:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Cervantes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41134-fortune-may-have-yet-a-better-success-in-reserve-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fortune may have yet a better success in reserve for you, and they who lose today may win tomorrow." -- Cervantes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3670-it-does-not-do-to-dwell-on-dreams-and-forget</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2008 08:36:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3670-it-does-not-do-to-dwell-on-dreams-and-forget]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It does not do to dwell on dreams and forget to live." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44160-it-isn-t-necessary-to-have-relatives-in-kansas-city-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2013 19:28:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Groucho Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44160-it-isn-t-necessary-to-have-relatives-in-kansas-city-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It isn't necessary to have relatives in Kansas City in order to be unhappy." -- Groucho Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422874-there-is-a-certain-kind-of-pain-that-can-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 13:50:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Adam Gidwitz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422874-there-is-a-certain-kind-of-pain-that-can-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a certain kind of pain that can change you. Even the strongest sword, when placed in a raging fire, will soften and bend and change its form...
   Trust me on this one. I know this from personal experience. I hope that you never will, but, since you're a person, and therefore prone to making horrible, soul-splitting mistakes, you probably will one day know what this kind of guilt and shame feels like. And when that time comes, I hope you have the strength...to take advantage of the fire and reshape your own sword." -- Adam Gidwitz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122689-but-the-mahommedan-religion-increases-instead-of-lessening-the-fury</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 20:32:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Winston Churchill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122689-but-the-mahommedan-religion-increases-instead-of-lessening-the-fury]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...But the Mahommedan religion increases, instead of lessening, the fury of intolerance. It was originally propagated by the sword, and ever since, its votaries have been subject, above the people of all other creeds, to this form of madness. In a moment the fruits of patient toil, the prospects of material prosperity, the fear of death itself, are flung aside. The more emotional Pathans are powerless to resist. All rational considerations are forgotten. Seizing their weapons, they become Ghazis—as dangerous and as sensible as mad dogs: fit only to be treated as such. While the more generous spirits among the tribesmen become convulsed in an ecstasy of religious bloodthirstiness, poorer and more material souls derive additional impulses from the influence of others, the hopes of plunder and the joy of fighting. Thus whole nations are roused to arms. Thus the Turks repel their enemies, the Arabs of the Soudan break the British squares, and the rising on the Indian frontier spreads far and wide. In each case civilisation is confronted with militant Mahommedanism. The forces of progress clash with those of reaction. The religion of blood and war is face to face with that of peace." -- Winston Churchill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6979-i-am-trying-here-to-prevent-anyone-saying-the-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 09:18:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6979-i-am-trying-here-to-prevent-anyone-saying-the-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am trying here to prevent anyone saying the really foolish thing that people often say about Him: I’m ready to accept Jesus as a great moral teacher, but I don’t accept his claim to be God. That is the one thing we must not say. A man who was merely a man and said the sort of things Jesus said would not be a great moral teacher. He would either be a lunatic — on the level with the man who says he is a poached egg — or else he would be the Devil of Hell. You must make your choice. Either this man was, and is, the Son of God, or else a madman or something worse. You can shut him up for a fool, you can spit at him and kill him as a demon or you can fall at his feet and call him Lord and God, but let us not come with any patronizing nonsense about his being a great human teacher. He has not left that open to us. He did not intend to." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
