<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1003783-c]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1003783-c" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2009 13:43:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126260-long-after-her-death-i-felt-her-thoughts-floating-through</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2009 13:43:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126260-long-after-her-death-i-felt-her-thoughts-floating-through]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Long after her death I felt her thoughts floating through mine. Long before we met we had had the same dreams. We compared notes. We found strange affinities. The same June of the same year (1919) a stray canary had fluttered into her house and mine, in two widely separated countries. Oh, Lolita, had you love me thus!" -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2481-there-must-have-been-moments-even-that-afternoon-when-daisy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2009 13:43:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2481-there-must-have-been-moments-even-that-afternoon-when-daisy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There must have been moments even that afternoon when Daisy tumbled short of his dreams -- not through her own fault, but because of the colossal vitality of his illusion. It had gone beyond her, beyond everything. He had thrown himself into it with a creative passion, adding to it all the time, decking it out with every bright feather that drifted his way. No amount of fire or freshness can challenge what a man will store up in his ghostly heart." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72771-i-believe-the-poor-fierce-eyed-child-had-figured-out-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 14:29:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72771-i-believe-the-poor-fierce-eyed-child-had-figured-out-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe the poor fierce-eyed child had figured out that with a mere fifty dollars in her purse she might somehow reach Broadway or Hollywood - or the foul kitchen of a diner (Help Wanted) in a dismal ex-prairie state, with the wind blowing, and the stars blinking, and the cars, and the bars, and the barmen, and everything soiled, torn, dead." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66237-thus-neither-of-us-is-alive-when-the-reader-opens</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 14:29:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Vladimir Nabakov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66237-thus-neither-of-us-is-alive-when-the-reader-opens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thus, neither of us is alive when the reader opens this book. But while the blood still throbs through my writing hand, you are still as much part of blessed matter as I am, and I can still talk to you from here to Alaska. Be true to your Dick. Do not let other fellows touch you. Do not talk to strangers. I hope you will love your baby. I hope it will be a boy. That husband of yours, I hope, will always treat you well, because otherwise my specter shall come at him, like black smoke, like a demented giant, and pull him apart nerve by nerve. And do not pity C. Q. One had to choose between him and H.H., and one wanted H.H. to exist at least a couple of months longer, so as to have him make you live in the minds of later generations. I am thinking of aurochs and angels, the secret of durable pigments, prophetic sonnets, the refuge of art. And this is the only immortality you and I may share, my Lolita." -- Vladimir Nabakov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4853-in-spite-of-everything-i-loved-you-and-will-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 14:29:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4853-in-spite-of-everything-i-loved-you-and-will-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In spite of everything I loved you, and will go on loving you―on my knees, with my shoulders drawn back, showing my heels to the headsman and straining my goose neck―even then.  And afterwards―perhaps most of all afterwards―I shall love you, and one day we shall have a real, all-embracing explanation, and then perhaps we shall somehow fit together, you and I, and turn ourselves in such a way that we form one pattern, and solve the puzzle: draw a line from point A to point B... without looking, or, without lifting the pencil... or in some other way... we shall connect the points, draw the line, and you and I shall form that unique design for which I yearn.  If they do this kind of thing to me every morning, they will get me trained and I shall become quite wooden." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124677-there-are-gentle-souls-who-would-pronounce-lolita-meaningless-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 14:29:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124677-there-are-gentle-souls-who-would-pronounce-lolita-meaningless-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are gentle souls who would pronounce Lolita meaningless because it does not teach them anything.  I am neither a reader nor a writer of didactic fiction...For me a work of fiction exists only insofar as it affords me what I shall bluntly call aesthetic bliss, that is a sense of being somehow, somewhere, connected with other states of being where art (curiosity, tenderness, kindness, ecstasy) is the norm." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73227-although-we-read-with-our-minds-the-seat-of-artistic</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 14:29:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73227-although-we-read-with-our-minds-the-seat-of-artistic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Although we read with our minds, the seat of artistic delight is between the shoulder blades. That little shiver behind is quite certainly the highest form of emotion that humanity has attained when evolving pure art and pure science. Let us worship the spine and its tingle." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57424-and-i-still-have-other-smothered-memories-now-unfolding-themselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 14:29:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57424-and-i-still-have-other-smothered-memories-now-unfolding-themselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I still have other smothered memories, now unfolding themselves into limbless monsters of pain. Once, in a sunset-ending street of Beardsley, she turned to little Eva Rosen (I was taking both nymphets to a concert and walking behind them so close as almost to touch them with my person), she turned to Eva, and so very serenely and seriously, in answer to something the other had said about its being better to die than hear Milton Pinski; some local schoolboy she knew, talk about music, my Lolita remarked:
'You know what's so dreadful about dying is that you're completely on your own'; and it struck me, as my automaton knees went up and down, that I simply did not know a thing about my darling's mind and that quite possibly, behind the awful juvenile cliches, there was in her a garden and a twilight, and a palace gate - dim and adorable regions which happened to be lucidly and absolutely forbidden to me, in my polluted rags and miserable convulsions..." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always imagined that Paradise will be a kind of library." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148090-when-you-re-young-you-always-feel-that-life-hasn-t-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148090-when-you-re-young-you-always-feel-that-life-hasn-t-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you're young, you always feel that life hasn't yet begun—that &quot;life&quot; is always scheduled to begin next week, next month, next year, after the holidays—whenever.  But then suddenly you're old and the scheduled life didn't arrive.  You find yourself asking, 'Well then, exactly what was it I was having—that interlude—the scrambly madness—all that time I had before?" -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10086-brevity-is-the-soul-of-wit</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10086-brevity-is-the-soul-of-wit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Brevity is the soul of wit." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65051-all-at-once-we-were-madly-clumsily-shamelessly-agonizingly-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65051-all-at-once-we-were-madly-clumsily-shamelessly-agonizingly-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All at once we were madly, clumsily, shamelessly, agonizingly in love with each other; hopelessly, I should add, because that frenzy of mutual possession might have been assuaged only by our actually imbibing and assimilating every particle of each other's soul and flesh; but there we were, unable even to mate as slum children would have so easily found an opportunity to do so." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39101-in-a-nervous-and-slender-leaved-mimosa-grove-at-the-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39101-in-a-nervous-and-slender-leaved-mimosa-grove-at-the-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a nervous and slender-leaved mimosa grove at the back of their villa we found a perch on the ruins of a low stone wall.  She trembled and twitched as I kissed the corner of her parted lips and the hot lobe of her ear.  A cluster of stars palely glowed above us between the silhouettes of long thin leaves; that vibrant sky seemed as naked as she was under her light frock.  I saw her face in the sky, strangely distinct, as if it emitted a faint radiance of its own.  Her legs, her lovely live legs, were not too close together, and when my hand located what it sought, a dreamy and eerie expression, half-pleasure, half-pain, came over those childish features.  She sat a little higher than I, and whenever in her solitary ecstasy she was led to kiss me, her head would bend with a sleepy, soft, drooping movement that was almost woeful, and her bare knees caught and compressed my wrist, and slackened again; and her quivering mouth, distorted by the acridity of some mysterious potion, with a sibilant intake of breath came near to my face.  She would try to relieve the pain of love by first roughly rubbing her dry lips against mine; then my darling would draw away with a nervous toss of her hair, and then again come darkly near and let me feed on her open mouth, while with a generosity that was ready to offer her everything, my heart, my throat, my entrails, I gave her to hold in her awkward fist the scepter of my passion." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75343-but-that-mimosa-grove---the-haze-of-stars-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75343-but-that-mimosa-grove---the-haze-of-stars-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["but that mimosa grove - the haze of stars, the tingle, the flame, the honey-dew, and the ache remained with me, and that little girl with her seaside limbs and ardent tongue haunted me ever since.&quot;

&quot;this then is my story. i have reread it. it has bits of marrow sticking to it, and blood, and beautiful bright-green flies. at this or that twist of it i feel my slippery self eluding me, gliding into deeper and darker waters than i care to probe." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195996-i-will-be-very-careful-the-next-time-i-fall</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Richard Brautigan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195996-i-will-be-very-careful-the-next-time-i-fall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;i&gt;I will be very careful the next time I fall in love&lt;/i&gt;, she told herself. Also, she had made a promise to herself that she intended on keeping. She was never going to go out with another writer: no matter how charming, sensitive, inventive or fun they could be. They weren't worth it in the long run.  They were emotionally too expensive and the upkeep was complicated. They were like having a vacuum cleaner around the house that broke all the time and only Einstein could fix it. 
    She wanted her next lover to be a broom." -- Richard Brautigan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/783-what-is-love-i-have-met-in-the-streets-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Victor Hugo ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/783-what-is-love-i-have-met-in-the-streets-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What Is Love? I have met in the streets a very poor young man who was in love. His hat was old, his coat worn, the water passed through his shoes and the stars through his soul" -- Victor Hugo ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21873-i-realized-that-once-people-are-broken-in-certain-ways</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:33:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21873-i-realized-that-once-people-are-broken-in-certain-ways]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I realized that once people are broken in certain ways they can't ever be fixed, and this is something nobody ever tells you when you are young and it never fails to surprise you as you grow older as you see the people in your life break one by one." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158499-without-turning-the-pharmacist-answered-that-he-liked-books-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Roberto Bolano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158499-without-turning-the-pharmacist-answered-that-he-liked-books-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without turning, the pharmacist answered that he liked books like The Metamorphosis, Bartleby, A Simple Heart, A Christmas Carol.  And then he said that he was reading Capote's Breakfast at Tiffany's. Leaving aside the fact that A Simple Heart and A Christmas Carol were stories, not books, there was something revelatory about the taste of this bookish young pharmacist, who ... clearly and inarguably preferred minor works to major ones.  He chose The Metamorphosis over The Trial, he chose Bartleby over Moby Dick, he chose A Simple Heart over Bouvard and Pecouchet, and A Christmas Carol over A Tale of Two Cities or The Pickwick Papers. What a sad paradox, thought Amalfitano.  Now even bookish pharmacists are afraid to take on the great, imperfect, torrential works, books that blaze a path into the unknown.  They choose the perfect exercises of the great masters.  Or what amounts to the same thing: they want to watch the great masters spar, but they have no interest in real combat, when the great masters struggle against that something, that something that terrifies us all, that something that cows us and spurs us on, amid blood and mortal wounds and stench." -- Roberto Bolano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2136-the-covers-of-this-book-are-too-far-apart</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2136-the-covers-of-this-book-are-too-far-apart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The covers of this book are too far apart." -- Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4737-cut-out-all-these-exclamation-points-an-exclamation-point-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4737-cut-out-all-these-exclamation-points-an-exclamation-point-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cut out all these exclamation points. An exclamation point is like laughing at your own joke." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4619-i-wish-i-had-more-friends-but-people-are-such</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Bill Watterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4619-i-wish-i-had-more-friends-but-people-are-such]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish I had more friends, but people are such jerks. If you can just get most people to leave you alone, you're doing good. If you can find even one person you really like, you're lucky. And if that person can also stand you, you're really lucky." -- Bill Watterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11951-i-was-a-flower-of-the-mountain-yes-when-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11951-i-was-a-flower-of-the-mountain-yes-when-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was a Flower of the mountain yes when I put the rose in my hair like the Andalusian girls used or shall I wear a red yes and how he kissed me under the Moorish wall and I thought well as well him as another and then I asked him with my eyes to ask again yes and then he asked me would I yes to say yes my mountain flower and first I put my arms around him yes and drew him down to me so he could feel my breasts all perfume yes and his heart was going like mad and yes I said yes I will Yes." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135242-and-the-rest-is-rust-and-stardust</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135242-and-the-rest-is-rust-and-stardust]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the rest is rust and stardust." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15334-boys-and-girls-in-america-have-such-a-sad-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15334-boys-and-girls-in-america-have-such-a-sad-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Boys and girls in America have such a sad time together; sophistication demands that they submit to sex immediately without proper preliminary talk. Not courting talk — real straight talk about souls, for life is holy and every moment is precious." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41291-the-sense-of-unhappiness-is-so-much-easier-to-convey</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41291-the-sense-of-unhappiness-is-so-much-easier-to-convey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sense of unhappiness is so much easier to convey than that of happiness. In misery we seem aware of our own existence, even though it may be in the form of a monstrous egotism: this pain of mine is individual, this nerve that winces belongs to me and to no other. But happiness annihilates  us: we lose our identity." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217333-i-was-always-hungry-for-love-just-once-i-wanted</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217333-i-was-always-hungry-for-love-just-once-i-wanted]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was always hungry for love. Just once, I wanted to know what it was like to get my fill of it -- to be fed so much love I couldn't take any more. Just once. " -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268048-love-poem-it-s-so-nice-to-wake-up-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Richard Brautigan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268048-love-poem-it-s-so-nice-to-wake-up-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love Poem
ـــــــــ
It's so nice
to wake up in the morning
all alone
and not have to tell somebody
you love them
when you don't love them
any more." -- Richard Brautigan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69503-my-god-the-english-language-is-a-form-of-communication</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69503-my-god-the-english-language-is-a-form-of-communication]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My God! The English language is a form of communication! Conversation isn't just crossfire where you shoot and get shot at! Where you've got to duck for your life and aim to kill! Words aren't only bombs and bullets —no, they're little gifts, containing meanings!" -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104504-and-for-that-one-moment-of-freedom-you-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104504-and-for-that-one-moment-of-freedom-you-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And for that one moment of freedom you have to listen to all that love crap... it drive me nuts sometimes... I want to kick them out immediately... I do now and then. But that doesn't keep them away. They like it, in fact. The less you notice them the more they chase after you. There's something perverse about women... they're all masochists at  heart." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227358-i-loved-you-so-much-once-i-did-more-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 22:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[C add a quote by Raymond Carver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227358-i-loved-you-so-much-once-i-did-more-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I loved you so much once. I did. More than anything in the whole wide world. Imagine that. What a laugh that is now. Can you believe it? We were so intimate once upon a time I can't believe it now. The memory of being that intimate with somebody. We were so intimate I could puke. I can't imagine ever being that intimate with somebody else. I haven't been." -- Raymond Carver]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
