<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1003057-myridian]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1003057-myridian" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 11:42:43 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142661-it-is-my-conviction-that-there-is-no-way-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 11:42:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142661-it-is-my-conviction-that-there-is-no-way-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is my conviction that there is no way to peace - peace is the way." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125722-love-is-a-fragile-corruptible-thing-and-yet-i-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 11:42:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Brent Weeks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125722-love-is-a-fragile-corruptible-thing-and-yet-i-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a fragile, corruptible thing.  And yet I have seen it evince a curious strength.  It is beyond any comprehension Love is a weakness that once in a great while triumphs over strength.  " -- Brent Weeks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14028-all-paths-are-present-always-and-we-can-but-choose</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 12:42:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Jacqueline Carey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14028-all-paths-are-present-always-and-we-can-but-choose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All paths are present, always... and we can but choose among them." -- Jacqueline Carey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222721-when-the-stories-of-our-life-no-longer-bind-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 12:42:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Jack Kornfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222721-when-the-stories-of-our-life-no-longer-bind-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the stories of our life no longer bind us, we discover within them something greater.  We discover that within the very limitations of form, of our maleness and femaleness, of our parenthood and our childhood, of gravity on the earth and the changing of the seasons, is the freedom and harmony we have sought for so long.  Our individual life is an expression of the whole mystery, and in it we can rest in the center of the movement, the center of all worlds." -- Jack Kornfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105835-on-the-day-i-swore-to-uphold-the-hippocratic-oath</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:33:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105835-on-the-day-i-swore-to-uphold-the-hippocratic-oath]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the day I swore to uphold the Hippocratic oath, the small hairs on the back of my neck stood up as I waited for lightning to strike.  Who was I, vowing calmly among all these necktied young men to steal life out of nature's jaws, every old time we got half a chance and a paycheck?...  I could not accept the contract: that every child born human upon this earth comes with a guarantee of perfect health and old age clutched in its small fist." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55077-he-meant-the-kingdom-was-over-the-kingdom-of-heaven</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:33:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55077-he-meant-the-kingdom-was-over-the-kingdom-of-heaven]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He meant the Kingdom was over, the Kingdom of Heaven, it was all finished.  We shouldn't live as if it mattered more than this life in this world, because where we are is always the most important place....  We have to be all those difficult things like cheerful and kind and curious and patient, and we've got to study and think and work hard, all of us, in all our different world, and then we'll build... The Republic of Heaven." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122914-do-you-know-what-punishments-i-ve-endured-for-my-crimes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:33:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Brent Weeks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122914-do-you-know-what-punishments-i-ve-endured-for-my-crimes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you know what punishments I've endured for my crimes, my sins?  None.  I am proof of the absurdity of men's most treasured abstractions.  A just universe wouldn't tolerate my existence." -- Brent Weeks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79656-you-believe-in-god-demanded-billy-karma-i-believe-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:34:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Mike Resnick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79656-you-believe-in-god-demanded-billy-karma-i-believe-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You believe in God?&quot; demanded Billy Karma.

&quot;I believe in thirty-seven separate and distinct gods,&quot; answered Argyle proudly. &quot;That puts me thirty-six ahead of you.&quot;

&quot;It makes you a pagan.&quot;

&quot;It makes you a man of limited vision,&quot; said Argyle." -- Mike Resnick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79653-whatever-your-grievances-i-m-sure-we-can-address-them-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:34:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Mike Resnick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79653-whatever-your-grievances-i-m-sure-we-can-address-them-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever your grievances, I'm sure we can address them without resorting to war,&quot; persisted Argyle....
Nonsense,&quot; said the alien. &quot;Do you know how many laborers and industries we'd put out of work if we were to stop the war just because a few bleeding hearts think we can talk out our grievances?" -- Mike Resnick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222718-this-life-is-a-test-it-is-only-a-test-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 12:44:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Jack Kornfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222718-this-life-is-a-test-it-is-only-a-test-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This life is a test-it is only a test.
If it had been an actual life, you would have received further
instructions on where to go and what to do.
Remember, this life is only a test." -- Jack Kornfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120142-i-would-that-i-could-have-stopped-time-and-preserved</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:35:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Jacqueline Carey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120142-i-would-that-i-could-have-stopped-time-and-preserved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would that I could have stopped time and preserved that day forever.  It was a perfect day.  There was the shadow of sorrow, yes.  It would always be there.  But that was the nature of life.  The bright mirror and the dark, reflecting one another.  And today there was so much brightness." -- Jacqueline Carey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60306-how-different-would-our-perception-of-reality-be-if-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:35:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Robin Hobb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60306-how-different-would-our-perception-of-reality-be-if-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How different would our perception of reality be if... we discarded the mundane events that cannot coexist with our dreams?" -- Robin Hobb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64470-i-tell-you-lad-that-men-will-believe-is-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:36:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Sheri S. Tepper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64470-i-tell-you-lad-that-men-will-believe-is-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I tell you, lad, that men will believe is one says, &quot;The Gods say...&quot; They will believe if one says, &quot;I had a Vision...&quot; They will believe if one says, &quot;It was told me on a tablet of hidden gold...&quot;  But, if one says, &quot;History teaches,&quot; then they will not believe." -- Sheri S. Tepper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15334-boys-and-girls-in-america-have-such-a-sad-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:36:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15334-boys-and-girls-in-america-have-such-a-sad-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Boys and girls in America have such a sad time together; sophistication demands that they submit to sex immediately without proper preliminary talk. Not courting talk — real straight talk about souls, for life is holy and every moment is precious." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60310-a-terrible-premonition-washed-over-me-this-was-how-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:37:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Robin Hobb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60310-a-terrible-premonition-washed-over-me-this-was-how-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A terrible premonition washed over me.  This was how the whole world would end.... They would devour the forest and excrete piles of buildings made of stone wrenched from the earth or from dead trees. They would hammer paths of bare stone between their dwellings, and dirty the rivers and subdue the land until it could recall only the will of man. They could not stop themselves from doing what they did. They did not see what they did, and even if they saw, they did not know how to stop. They no longer knew what was enough." -- Robin Hobb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105824-i-could-never-work-out-whether-we-were-to-view</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:38:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105824-i-could-never-work-out-whether-we-were-to-view]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I could never work out whether we were to view religion as a life-insurance policy or a life sentence.  I can understand a wrathful God who'd just as soon dangle us all from a hook.  And I can understand a tender, unprejudiced Jesus.  But I could never quite feature the two of them living in the same house.  You wind up walking on eggshells, never knowing which... is at home at the moment." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82812-i-ll-pit-my-god-against-your-god-any-day-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:39:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Brunonia Barry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82812-i-ll-pit-my-god-against-your-god-any-day-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;em&gt;I'll pit my God against your god&lt;/em&gt; any day, I say to the Calvinists.  It's not their god I'm praying to....  The God I'm praying to is neither male nor female.  My God is the one who exists apart from all of men's agendas, the God who takes you away when there is no possible place you can go." -- Brunonia Barry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125947-above-all-we-pray-that-they-will-make-the-journey</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:40:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Jane Ross-MacDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125947-above-all-we-pray-that-they-will-make-the-journey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Above all, we pray that they will make the journey from selfishness to true love.  Whether together or single, this is a journey we all have to make.  In a sense it is the real journey of life." -- Jane Ross-MacDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120143-happiness-is-the-highest-form-of-wisdom</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:40:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Jacqueline Carey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120143-happiness-is-the-highest-form-of-wisdom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is the highest form of wisdom." -- Jacqueline Carey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64468-for-it-would-be-only-for-a-time-until-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:41:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Sheri S. Tepper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64468-for-it-would-be-only-for-a-time-until-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For it would be only for a time. Until what he knew and thought became no longer relevant or necessary and was forgotten. But that was the same with all of us. We were only what we were for a time, at that time. Then our own silver began to mix with the tin of our future to change us. I knew this to be so and grieved for Windlow while I grieved for me. In time I would not be this Peter, even as I now was not the peter of two years ago.... Yet that Peter was not lost." -- Sheri S. Tepper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105831-but-his-kind-will-always-lose-in-the-end-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:41:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105831-but-his-kind-will-always-lose-in-the-end-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But his kind will always lose in the end.  I know this, and now I know why.  Whether it's wife or nation they occupy, their mistake is the same: they stand still, and their stake moves underneath them....  Chains rattle, rivers roll, animals startle and bolt, forests inspire and expand, babies stretch open-mouthed from the womb, new seedlings arch their necks and creep forward into the light.  Even a language won't stand still.  A territory is only possessed for a moment in time.  They stake everything on that moment, posing for photographs while planting the flag, casting themselves in bronze....  Even before the flagpole begins to peel and splinter, the ground underneath arches and slides forward into its own new destiny.  It may bear the marks of boots on its back, but those marks become the possessions of the land." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82813-there-is-lace-in-every-living-thing-the-bare-branches</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:42:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Brunonia Barry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82813-there-is-lace-in-every-living-thing-the-bare-branches]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is lace in every living thing: the bare branches of winter, the patterns of clouds, the surface of water as it ripples in the breeze....  Even a wild dog's matted fur shows a lacy pattern if you look at it closely enough." -- Brunonia Barry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105837-a-choir-of-seedlings-arching-their-necks-out-of-rotted</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:42:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105837-a-choir-of-seedlings-arching-their-necks-out-of-rotted]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A choir of seedlings arching their necks out of rotted tree stumps, sucking life out of death.  I am the forest's conscience, but remember, the forest eats itself and lives forever." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125717-why-is-it-my-shadow-striding-friend-that-we-don-t-fear</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:43:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Brent Weeks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125717-why-is-it-my-shadow-striding-friend-that-we-don-t-fear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why is it, my shadow-striding friend, that we don't fear dreams?  We lose consciousness, lose control, things happen with no apparent logic and abiding by no apparent rules....  We don't fear dreams, but we do fear madness, and death terrifies us." -- Brent Weeks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64472-he-told-us-that-nations-of-men-fell-into-disorder</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:43:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Sheri S. Tepper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64472-he-told-us-that-nations-of-men-fell-into-disorder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He told us that nations of men fell into disorder, so nations of law were set up instead.  He told us that nations of law then forgot justice and let the law become a Game, a Game in which the moves and the winning were more important than truth.  He told us to seek justice rather than the Game." -- Sheri S. Tepper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64469-in-that-look-was-such-love-and-uncritical-adoration-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:44:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Sheri S. Tepper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64469-in-that-look-was-such-love-and-uncritical-adoration-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...in that look was such love and uncritical adoration as a god might instill into a new create.  &quot;Except, how boring at last,&quot; he thought.  &quot;To have one always, always adoring one.  But perhaps gods do not get bored..." -- Sheri S. Tepper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142660-to-dwell-in-the-here-and-now-does-not-mean</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:44:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142660-to-dwell-in-the-here-and-now-does-not-mean]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To dwell in the here and now does not mean you never think about the past or responsibly plan for the future.  The idea is simply not to allow yourself to get lost in regrets about the past or worries about the future. If you are firmly grounded in the present moment, the past can be an object of inquiry, the object of your mindfulness and concentration. You can attain many insights by looking into the past. But you are still grounded in the present moment." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105828-for-time-and-eternity-there-have-been-fathers-like-nathan</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:45:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105828-for-time-and-eternity-there-have-been-fathers-like-nathan]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For time and eternity there have been fathers like Nathan who simply can see no way to have a daughter but to own her like a plot of land.  To work her, plow her under, rain down a dreadful poison upon her.  Miraculously, it causes these girls to grow.  They elongate on the pale slender stalks of their longing, like sunflowers with heavy heads.  You can shield them with your body and soul, trying to absorb that awful rain, but they'll still move toward him.  Without cease they'll bend to his light.  " -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55073-seems-to-me--lee-said-feeling-for-the-words-seems</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:45:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55073-seems-to-me--lee-said-feeling-for-the-words-seems]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Seems to me-&quot; Lee said, feeling for the words, &quot;seems to me the place you fight cruelty is where you find it, and the place you give help is where you see it needed...." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125716-why-did-women-always-believe-that-talking-about-a-problem</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 12:45:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Myridian add a quote by Brent Weeks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125716-why-did-women-always-believe-that-talking-about-a-problem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why did women always believe that talking about a problem would fix it?  Some issues were corpses.  Hot air made them fester and rot and spread their disease to everything else.  Better to bury it and move on." -- Brent Weeks]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
