<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1003339-ruhegeist]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1003339-ruhegeist" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 16:18:26 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494991-interdependence-is-and-ought-to-be-as-much-the-ideal</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 16:18:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494991-interdependence-is-and-ought-to-be-as-much-the-ideal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Interdependence is and ought to be as much the ideal of man as self-sufficiency. Man is a social being. Without interrelation with society he cannot realize his oneness with the universe or suppress his egotism. His social interdependence enables him to test his faith and to prove himself on the touchstone of reality." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120143-happiness-is-the-highest-form-of-wisdom</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 14:11:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Jacqueline Carey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120143-happiness-is-the-highest-form-of-wisdom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is the highest form of wisdom." -- Jacqueline Carey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23101-pleasure-to-me-is-wonder-the-unexplored-the-unexpected-the-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 16:18:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23101-pleasure-to-me-is-wonder-the-unexplored-the-unexpected-the-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pleasure to me is wonder—the unexplored, the unexpected, the thing that is hidden and the changeless thing that lurks behind superficial mutability. To trace the remote in the immediate; the eternal in the ephemeral; the past in the present; the infinite in the finite; these are to me the springs of delight and beauty." -- H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214763-happiness-is-like-a-cat-if-you-try-to-coax</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 08:36:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by William J. Bennett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214763-happiness-is-like-a-cat-if-you-try-to-coax]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is like a cat. If you try to coax it or call it, it will avoid you. It will never come. But if you pay no attention to it and go about your business, you'll find it rubbing up against your legs and jumping into your lap." -- William J. Bennett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129363-guilt-is-a-good-friend-isn-t-it-it-will-stand</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 16:18:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Holly Lisle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129363-guilt-is-a-good-friend-isn-t-it-it-will-stand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Guilt is a good friend, isn't it?  It will stand at your back when every other friend has abandoned you, and in the face of all reason it will stay by your side, and even when you tell it, &quot;I am moving on now,&quot; it will say, &quot;I shall never leave you; never.&quot;  
If only I could find a lover as faithful as guilt." -- Holly Lisle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98671-grace-like-water-flows-to-the-lowest-part</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 16:18:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Philip Yancey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98671-grace-like-water-flows-to-the-lowest-part]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Grace, like water, flows to the lowest part." -- Philip Yancey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142727-it-is-astonishing-in-the-end-how-difficult-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 18:20:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Aoibheann Sweeney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142727-it-is-astonishing-in-the-end-how-difficult-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is astonishing, in the end, how difficult it is to know the things you know.  What I mean is that all I had discovered was everything I knew all along." -- Aoibheann Sweeney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410806-you-obsess-but-of-course-you-obsess-until-the-joy</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 18:33:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Beth Kephart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410806-you-obsess-but-of-course-you-obsess-until-the-joy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You obsess (but of course you obsess) until the joy is gone from that thing you'd loved, until your fury overwhelms your passion, until you no longer know how to sit with your back against a tree and write poetry that no one will ever see." -- Beth Kephart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460002-and-it-means-snapshots-because-that-s-what-all-stories-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 17:26:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Caitlín R. Kiernan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460002-and-it-means-snapshots-because-that-s-what-all-stories-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And it means snapshots, because that's what all stories I write come down to; each is a snapshot of who I was during however many days and weeks it was written.  A fictional reflection of my mind fossilized, set in paper and ink, instead of stone.  Memorialized, for better or worse.  This is who I was, and this, and this, and this, and that, and most times I look back and wince.  I'm rarely kind to who I was.  But other times, looking back is bittersweet.  Sometimes, I'm even grateful to the me of then who left a snapshot for the me of now.  Maybe I should let go and join those who pretend the past is past, but it's a falsehood I've never learned to spin." -- Caitlín R. Kiernan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158618-there-was-a-long-pause-you-know-he-went-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 07:16:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Jan Siegel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158618-there-was-a-long-pause-you-know-he-went-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was a long pause. “you know,” he went on, “I sometimes think mankind is dangerously arrogant. We do a few sums, and then claim we have the universe off pat. we measure the spaces between the stars, and declare them empty. We set a limit on infinity. We are like the occupants of a closed room; having worked out everything within the range of our knowledge, we announce that the room and its contents are all that exists. Nothing beyond. Nothing unseen or unknown, incalculable or neffable. This is it. And then every so often God lifts the veil—twitches the curtain—and gives us a glimpse, just a glimpse, of something more. As if He wishes to show us how narrow is our vision, how meaningless the boundaries we have set for ourselves. I felt that when Fern was talking. Just for a minute I though: This is truth, there’s a world beyond all the jargon of unbelief." -- Jan Siegel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508742-lougarry-was-waiting-over-the-brow-of-the-hill-lying</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 07:29:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Jan Siegel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508742-lougarry-was-waiting-over-the-brow-of-the-hill-lying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lougarry was waiting over the brow of the hill, lying so still in the grass that a butterfly had perched within an inch of her nose.  The stems bent and shimmered as she rose to her feet, and the butterfly floated away like a wind-borne petal.  Fern wondered if , like Ragginbone, the she-wolf possessed the faculty of making herself at one with her surroundings, not invisible but transmuted, so close to nature that she could blend with it at will and be absorbed into its many forms, becoming grass blade and wildflower, still earth and moving air, resuming her true self at the prompting of a thought.  It came to Fern that we are all part of one vast pattern of Being, the real world and the shadow-world, sunlight and werelight, Man and spirit, and to understand and accept that was the first step toward the abnegation of ego, the affirmation of the soul.  To comprehend the wind, not as a movement of molecules but as the pulse of the air, the pulse of her pulse, was to become the wind, to blow with it through the dancing grasses to the edge of the sky..." -- Jan Siegel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508745-they-slept-little-that-night-making-their-newfound-love-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 07:33:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Jan Siegel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508745-they-slept-little-that-night-making-their-newfound-love-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They slept little that night, making their newfound love like people for whom the world is running out.  Fern did not think of her Task, not because she had abandoned it, but because she felt it would present itself for her attention when the moment was right, and until then she had an intermission, a suspension of hostilities, given by whatever gods there were.  They lay in the cave while outside the tide rose and fell, and she thought that in this life and maybe in all lives she would remember that love sounded like the sea, and the beat of her heart was waves on a beach, and she would hear its echo in the nucleus of every shell." -- Jan Siegel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158628-as-the-chant-grew-in-volume-she-began-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 07:35:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Jan Siegel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158628-as-the-chant-grew-in-volume-she-began-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As the chant grew in volume she began to be conscious of the terrible potency of language, the sense that a name spoken is a summons and more than a summons, an act of creation, for a word shapes an idea, an idea shapes belief, and belief shapes the world. " -- Jan Siegel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508749-everyone-has-to-act-out-of-character-sometimes-it-s-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 07:38:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Jan Siegel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508749-everyone-has-to-act-out-of-character-sometimes-it-s-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone has to act out of character sometimes.  It's like taking your clothes off: you feel free without your character but very naked, unprotected.  Unfinished.  So you get dressed again- you put on yourself-and then you know who you are." -- Jan Siegel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158621-you-d-have-to-trust-in-hope-said-fern-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 07:38:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Jan Siegel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158621-you-d-have-to-trust-in-hope-said-fern-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You’d have to trust in Hope,” said Fern. “Is that it?”
No,” Ragginbone replied shortly. “Hope needs something tangible to sustain it. You would have to rely on Faith. Only Faith can endure in the teeth of the evidence." -- Jan Siegel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508751-advice-is-a-dangerous-thing-the-watcher-responded-it-should</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 07:41:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Jan Siegel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508751-advice-is-a-dangerous-thing-the-watcher-responded-it-should]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Advice is a dangerous thing,&quot; the Watcher responded.  &quot;It should be given only rarely and cautiously, and taken in small doses with skepticism." -- Jan Siegel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508752-once-people-needed-heaven-and-hell-elysium-and-faerie-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 07:45:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Jan Siegel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508752-once-people-needed-heaven-and-hell-elysium-and-faerie-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once people needed heaven and hell, Elysium and Faerie.  They believed.  Belief is the great creative force, the faith that moves mountains.  If Someone had not believed in us, so they say, we would never have been born.  I have spent my darkest hours wondering what kind of a Creator would have believed in me.&quot;   Kal" -- Jan Siegel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508753-i-have-often-dreamed-of-strangling-my-creator</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 07:46:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Jan Siegel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508753-i-have-often-dreamed-of-strangling-my-creator]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have often dreamed of strangling my Creator." -- Jan Siegel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508756-and-she-knew-she-was-not-sure-she-would-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 07:51:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Jan Siegel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508756-and-she-knew-she-was-not-sure-she-would-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And she knew she was not sure, she would never be sure, because uncertainty is the essence of the human condition, and death is the one barrier beyond which we cannot see.  There is no hope but faith, no knowledge but the acceptance of ignorance.
Yet still she hoped that one day she would know." -- Jan Siegel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508759-i-am-not-tormented-fern-responded-i-am-diminished-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 07:56:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Jan Siegel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508759-i-am-not-tormented-fern-responded-i-am-diminished-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am not tormented, Fern responded.  I am... diminished.  I have always believed that your soul grows when you do something that is good and brave, a right thing, a true thing, and when you do evil- no matter what the motive- your soul is eroded.  Well, my soul is less." -- Jan Siegel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162597-books-can-be-possessive-can-t-they-you-re-walking-around-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 19:19:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Sarah Addison Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162597-books-can-be-possessive-can-t-they-you-re-walking-around-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books can be possessive, can't they? You're walking around in a bookstore and a certain one will jump out at you, like it had moved there on its own, just to get your attention. Sometimes what's inside will change your life, but sometimes you don't even have to read it. Sometimes it's a comfort just to have a book around.  Many of these books haven't even had their spines cracked.  'Why do you buy books you don't even read?' our daughter asks us.  That's like asking someone who lives alone why they bought a cat.  For company, of course." -- Sarah Addison Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20603-it-s-like-everyone-tells-a-story-about-themselves-inside-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 17:36:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20603-it-s-like-everyone-tells-a-story-about-themselves-inside-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's like everyone tells a story about themselves inside their own head. Always. All the time. That story makes you what you are. We build ourselves out of that story." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299759-not-only-do-we-all-have-magic-it-s-all-around</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2012 08:09:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Charles de Lint]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299759-not-only-do-we-all-have-magic-it-s-all-around]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not only do we all have magic, it's all around us as well.  We just don't pay attention to it.  Every time we make something out of nothing, that's an act of magic.  It doesn't matter if it's a painting or a garden, or an abuelo telling his grandchildren some tall tale.  Every time we fix something that's broken, whether it's a car engine or a broken heart, that's an act of magic.

And what makes it magic is that we *choose* to create or help, just as we can choose to harm.  But it's so easy to destroy and so much harder to make things better.  That's why doing the right thing makes you stronger.

If we can only remember what we are and what we can do, nobody can bind us or control us." -- Charles de Lint]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/548830-she-wanted-to-tell-him-what-happened-wasn-t-really-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2012 08:16:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Charles de Lint]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/548830-she-wanted-to-tell-him-what-happened-wasn-t-really-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She wanted to tell him what happened wasn't really his fault, but she knew that wasn't the way this kind of guilt worked.  Intellectually, he already knew that.  It was his emotions that were tripping him up.  The tangle of love and memory and what might have been." -- Charles de Lint]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/548833-most-times-we-only-see-things-for-the-way-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2012 08:20:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Charles de Lint]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/548833-most-times-we-only-see-things-for-the-way-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most times we only see things for the way we are.  But we're good at lying to ourselves.  Sometimes we need somebody who's not living in our skin to point out how things really are." -- Charles de Lint]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361309-every-life-needs-a-little-space-it-leaves-room-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2012 19:52:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Sarah Addison Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361309-every-life-needs-a-little-space-it-leaves-room-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every life needs a little space.  It leaves room for good things to enter it." -- Sarah Addison Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/549616-agatha-had-declared-that-her-friendship-to-georgie-still-existed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2012 19:56:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Sarah Addison Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/549616-agatha-had-declared-that-her-friendship-to-georgie-still-existed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...Agatha had declared that her friendship to Georgie still existed, as if it was a living, breathing thing, something that came to life the moment it happened and didn't just go away because they no longer acknowledged it." -- Sarah Addison Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363929-why-were-girls-in-such-a-hurry-to-grow-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2012 19:57:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Sarah Addison Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363929-why-were-girls-in-such-a-hurry-to-grow-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why were girls in such a hurry to grow up?  Agatha would never understand.  Childhood was magical.  Leaving it behind was a magnificent loss." -- Sarah Addison Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/567738-it-wasn-t-as-if-the-flowers-themselves-held-within-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2012 20:33:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Vanessa Diffenbaugh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/567738-it-wasn-t-as-if-the-flowers-themselves-held-within-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It wasn't as if the flowers themselves held within them the ability to bring an abstract definition into physical reality.  Instead, it seemed that...expecting change, and the very belief in the possibility instigated a transformation." -- Vanessa Diffenbaugh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14404-real-magic-can-never-be-made-by-offering-someone-else-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 15:03:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruhegeist add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14404-real-magic-can-never-be-made-by-offering-someone-else-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Real magic can never be made by offering someone else's liver. You must tear out your own, and not expect to get it back." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
