<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1004133-michael-poteet]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1004133-michael-poteet" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 21:56:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512468-o-god-that-madest-this-beautiful-earth-when-will-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 21:56:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512468-o-god-that-madest-this-beautiful-earth-when-will-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["O God that madest this beautiful earth, when will it be ready to receive Thy saints? How long, O Lord, how long?" -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293637-it-is-a-world-of-magic-and-mystery-of-deep</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2013 21:35:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293637-it-is-a-world-of-magic-and-mystery-of-deep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a world of magic and mystery, of deep darkness and flickering starlight. It is a world where terrible things happen and wonderful things too. It is a world where goodness is pitted against evil, love against hate, order against chaos, in a great struggle where often it is hard to be sure who belongs to which side because appearances are endlessly deceptive. Yet for all its confusion and wildness, it is a world where the battle goes ultimately to the good, who live happily ever after, and where in the long run everybody, good and evil alike, becomes known by his true name....That is the fairy tale of the Gospel with, of course, one crucial difference from all other fairy tales, which is that the claim made for it is that it is true, that it not only happened once upon a time but has kept on happening ever since and is happening still." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
