<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1005529-kimberly-ann]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1005529-kimberly-ann" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 16:26:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362-if-you-don-t-stand-for-something-you-will-fall-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 16:26:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by Gordon A. Eadie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362-if-you-don-t-stand-for-something-you-will-fall-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you don't stand for something you will fall for anything." -- Gordon A. Eadie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71-the-fool-doth-think-he-is-wise-but-the-wise</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 16:26:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71-the-fool-doth-think-he-is-wise-but-the-wise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fool doth think he is wise, but the wise man knows himself to be a fool." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467-life-is-what-happens-to-you-while-you-re-busy-making</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 16:26:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by Allen Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467-life-is-what-happens-to-you-while-you-re-busy-making]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is what happens to you while you're busy making other plans." -- Allen Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1944-a-woman-is-like-a-tea-bag-you-never-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 16:26:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1944-a-woman-is-like-a-tea-bag-you-never-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A woman is like a tea bag; you never know how strong it is until it's in hot water." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 16:27:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The person, be it gentleman or lady, who has not pleasure in a good novel, must be intolerably stupid." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1958-whenever-i-feel-the-need-to-exercise-i-lie-down</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 16:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by Paul   Terry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1958-whenever-i-feel-the-need-to-exercise-i-lie-down]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever I feel the need to exercise, I lie down until it goes away." -- Paul   Terry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/778-it-is-not-a-lack-of-love-but-a-lack</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 16:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/778-it-is-not-a-lack-of-love-but-a-lack]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not a lack of love, but a lack of friendship that makes unhappy marriages." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 16:28:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 16:31:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know you're in love when you can't fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/660-i-believe-in-christianity-as-i-believe-that-the-sun</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 16:32:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/660-i-believe-in-christianity-as-i-believe-that-the-sun]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in Christianity as I believe that the sun has risen: not only because I see it, but because by it I see everything else." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 08:59:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He's like a drug for you, Bella." -- Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120467-i-figured-i-could-read-more-than-five-pages-tonight</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 11:22:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by Richelle Mead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120467-i-figured-i-could-read-more-than-five-pages-tonight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I figured I could read more than five pages tonight since I'd been deprived for the last couple of days.  When I finished the fifteenth, I discovered I was three pages from the next chapter.  Might as well end with a clean break.  After I was done, I sighed and leaned back, feeling decadent and spent.  Pure bliss.  Books were a lot less messy than orgasms." -- Richelle Mead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/453623-you-were-true-to-her-even-if-she-was-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 19:20:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by Laini Taylor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/453623-you-were-true-to-her-even-if-she-was-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You were true to her, even if she was not to you. Never repent of your own goodness, child. To stay true in the face of evil is a feat of great strength.”

“Strength,” she said with a little laugh. “I gave her strength, and look what she did with it." -- Laini Taylor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/452034-i-want-to-talk-about-creating-your-life-there-s-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 19:24:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by Laini Taylor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/452034-i-want-to-talk-about-creating-your-life-there-s-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to talk about creating your life. There’s a quote I love, from the poet Mary Oliver, that goes:

Tell me, what is it you plan to do with your one wild and precious life?

I so clearly remember what it was like, being young and always in the grip of some big fat daydream. I wanted to be a writer always, but more than that, I wanted to have an extraordinary life. I’m sure I dreamed it a million different ways, and that plenty of them were ridiculous, but I think the daydreams were training for writing, and I also think they spurred me to pursue my dreams for real.

Daydreaming, however awesome it is, is passive. It happens in your head. Learning to make dreams real is another matter, and I think it should be the work of your life. Everyone’s life, whatever their dream (unless their dream is to be an axe murderer or something.)

It took me a while to finish a book. Too long. And you know, it doesn’t matter how good a writer you are unless you finish what you start! I think this is the hardest part for most people who want to write. I was in my mid-30s before I figured it out. The brain plays tricks. You can be convinced you’re following your dream, or that you’re going to start tomorrow, and years can pass like that. Years.

The thing is, there will be pressure to adjust your expectations, always shrinking them, shrinking, shrinking, until they fit in your pocket like a folded slip of paper, and you know what happens to folded slips of paper in your pocket. They go through the wash and get ruined. Don’t ever put your dream in your pocket. If you have to put it somewhere, get one of those holsters for your belt, like my dad has for his phone, so you can whip it out at any moment. 

Hello there, dream.

Also, don’t be realistic. The word “realistic” is poison. Who decides? 

And “backup plan” is code for, “Give up on your dreams,” and everyone I know who put any energy into a backup plan is now living that backup plan instead of their dream. Put all your energy into your dream. That’s the only way it will ever become real.

The world at large has this attitude, “What makes you so special that you think you deserve an extraordinary life?” 

Personally, I think the passion for an extraordinary life, and the courage to pursue it, is what makes us special. And I don’t even think of it as an “extraordinary life” anymore so much as simple happiness. It’s rarer than it should be, and I believe it comes from creating a life that fits you perfectly, not taking what’s already there, but making your own from scratch. 

You can let life happen to you, or you can happen to life. It’s harder, but so much better." -- Laini Taylor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395657-hope-can-be-a-powerful-force-maybe-there-s-no-actual</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 19:53:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by Laini Taylor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395657-hope-can-be-a-powerful-force-maybe-there-s-no-actual]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hope can be a powerful force. Maybe there's no actual magic in it, but when you know what you hope for most and hold it like a light within you, you can make things happen, almost like magic." -- Laini Taylor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434907-i-don-t-know-many-rules-to-live-by-he-d-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 19:56:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by Laini Taylor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434907-i-don-t-know-many-rules-to-live-by-he-d-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know many rules to live by,' he'd said.  'But here's one. It's simple. Don't put anything unnecessary into yourself. No poisons or chemicals, no fumes or smoke or alcohol, no sharp objects, no inessential needles--drug or tattoo--and...no inessential penises either.'

'Inessential penises?' Karou had repeated, delighted with the phrase in spite of her grief. 'Is there any such thing as an essential one?'

'When an essential one comes along, you'll know,' he'd replied." -- Laini Taylor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7807-sometimes-i-feel-discriminated-against-but-it-does-not-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 11:11:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly Ann add a quote by ZORA NEALE HURSTON]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7807-sometimes-i-feel-discriminated-against-but-it-does-not-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, I feel discriminated against, but it does not make me angry. It merely astonishes me. How &lt;i&gt;can&lt;/i&gt; any deny themselves the pleasure of my company? It’s beyond me." -- ZORA NEALE HURSTON]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
