<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1005834-ebookwormy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1005834-ebookwormy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 06:27:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363-it-is-better-to-remain-silent-at-the-risk-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 06:27:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Maurice Switzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363-it-is-better-to-remain-silent-at-the-risk-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to remain silent at the risk of being thought a fool, than to talk and remove all doubt of it." -- Maurice Switzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11915-favour-is-deceitful-and-beauty-is-vain-but-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 06:32:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11915-favour-is-deceitful-and-beauty-is-vain-but-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Favour is deceitful, and beauty is vain: But a woman who fears the Lord,
She shall be praised.

(Proverbs 31:30 Modern King James Version)" -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42252-alan-grant-there-are-far-too-many-words-written-millions</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 12:29:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Josephine Tey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42252-alan-grant-there-are-far-too-many-words-written-millions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alan Grant: &quot;There are... far too many words written. Millions and millions of them pouring from the presses every minute. It's a horrible thought.&quot; 

The Midget (his nurse): &quot;You sound constipated." -- Josephine Tey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36501-perhaps-after-all-romance-did-not-come-into-one-s-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 07:29:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36501-perhaps-after-all-romance-did-not-come-into-one-s-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps, after all, romance did not come into one’s life with pomp and blare, like a gay knight riding down; perhaps it crept to one’s side like an old friend through quiet ways; perhaps it revealed itself in seeming prose, until some sudden shaft of illumination flung athwart its pages betrayed the rhythm and the music, perhaps . . . perhaps . . . love unfolded naturally out of a beautiful friendship, as a golden-hearted rose slipping from its green sheath." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42254-anne-walked-home-very-slowly-in-the-moonlight-the-evening</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 07:41:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42254-anne-walked-home-very-slowly-in-the-moonlight-the-evening]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anne walked home very slowly in the moonlight. The evening had changed something for her. Life held a different meaning, a deeper purpose. On the surface it would go on just the same; but the deeps had been stirred. It must not be the same with her as with poor butterfly Ruby. When she came to the end of one life it must not be to face the next with the shrinking terror of something wholly different--something for which accustomed thought and ideal and aspiration had unfitted her. The little things of life, sweet and excellent in their place, must not be the things lived for; the highest must be sought and followed; the life of heaven must begin here on earth.  

That goodnight in the garden was for all time. Anne never saw Ruby in life again." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42725-it-was-a-masterly-piece-of-work-but-once-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 17:14:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42725-it-was-a-masterly-piece-of-work-but-once-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was a masterly piece of work. But once you began admitting explanations in terms of purpose— well, you didn't know what the result might be. It was the sort of idea that might easily decondition the more unsettled minds among the higher castes—make them lose their faith in happiness as the Sovereign Good and take to believing, instead, that the goal was somewhere beyond, somewhere outside the present human sphere; that the purpose of life was not the maintenance of well-being, but some intensification and refining of consciousness, some enlargement of knowledge. Which was, the Controller reflected, quite possibly true. But not, in the present circumstance, admissible." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49640-one-thing-about-change-hasn-t-changed-it-still-fascinates-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 12:16:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Warren Wiersbe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49640-one-thing-about-change-hasn-t-changed-it-still-fascinates-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One thing about change hasn't changed: it still fascinates some people, frightens others, and provides a good living for a prophetic minority." -- Warren Wiersbe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51947-people-are-always-thinking-they-can-use-the-lord-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 19:55:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Lynn Austin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51947-people-are-always-thinking-they-can-use-the-lord-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People are always thinking they can use the Lord to get their own way-- all they have to do is pray and God's gonna take away all their suffering and give them what they whatever they ask for. But it don't work that way. God's doing His business, and it's up to us to be serving Him, not the other way around.&quot;

Then why do people pray at all? My papa asked Jesus to help him escape with me when I was just a little girl. But Jesus didn't help us.&quot;

Praying ain't about asking for your own way. It's all about talking things over with God, just like you and me are talking things over. In the end, you have to be trusting the Lord to do what's best.&quot;

So the Lord thought it was best that my papa died and my mama was sold?&quot;

Delia slowly shook her head. &quot;I don't know, honey, I just don't know. The hardest thing of all to understand is why a loving God keeps letting us suffer... I don't know all the answers myself. I seen my share of suffering, believe me. But there two things I do know for sure. One is that God loves us... And the second thing is that God's always in control of everything that happens. When bad things come our way and it starts looking like He don't love us, all I can say is that maybe we ain't knowing everything He knows.&quot;

Kitty's tears started falling again. &quot;I still don't understand.&quot;

Remember what you told me about the fighting up in Charleston? How you was standing on that porch, not able to see what's going on? This here's the same thing. We're standing in the smoke, hearing the noise [of the battle] all around us, and we don't know what God's doing because we can't see things clearly as He sees them. But He's gonna make everything turn our okay when the smoke clears. When it does, God's gonna be the winner and all our suffering here on earth is gonna finall make sense. We're gonna look in Jesus' face and say, 'O Lord, it was worth it all." -- Lynn Austin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54585-god-use-that-war-civil-war-to-show-you-southern</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 08:48:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Lynn Austin, &quot;Candle in the Darkness&quot;]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54585-god-use-that-war-civil-war-to-show-you-southern]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God use that war [civil war] to show you [southern] white boys what it's like to be a slave&quot; [said the former slave]. &quot;For four years, you sleeping on the ground instead of in your fine houses. You eating food that no one would feed a dog. You wearing rags and going barefoot and marching all day beneath a hot sun until you so weary you want to die. You ain't allowed to see your family or the woman you love. Your life ain't even your own anymore, with someone telling you what to do and when to get up and when you can go to bed. How you like it, Massa...? How you like trading places with me?" -- Lynn Austin, &quot;Candle in the Darkness&quot;]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107758-there-is-not-much-talking-now-a-silence-falls-upon</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2008 12:47:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Alan Paton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107758-there-is-not-much-talking-now-a-silence-falls-upon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is not much talking now. A silence falls upon them all. This is no time to talk of hedges and fields, or the beauties of any country. Sadness and fear and hate, how they well up in the heart and mind, whenever one opens pages of these messengers of doom. Cry for the broken tribe, for the law and the custom that is gone. Aye, and cry aloud for the man who is dead, for the woman and children bereaved. Cry, the beloved country, these things are not yet at an end. The sun pours down on the earth, on the lovely land that man cannot enjoy. He knows only the fear of his heart." -- Alan Paton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121192-consider-that-in-1800-western-powers-claimed-55-percent-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 17:38:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Edward Said]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121192-consider-that-in-1800-western-powers-claimed-55-percent-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Consider that in 1800 Western powers claimed 55 percent but actually held approximately 35 percent of the earth's surface, and that by 1874 the proportion was 67 percent, a rate of increase of 83,000 square miles per year. By 1914, the annual rate had risen to an astonishing 240,000 square miles [per year], and Europe held a grand total of roughly 85 percent of the earth as colonies, protectorates, dependencies, dominions, and commonwealths. No other associated set of colonies in history was as large, none so totally dominated, none so unequal in power to the Western metropolis.&quot; Culture and Imperialism, pg. 8" -- Edward Said]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144395-canaan-the-youngest-son-of-ham-genesis-9-20-27-the-bible</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 11:44:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Tokunboh Adeyemo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144395-canaan-the-youngest-son-of-ham-genesis-9-20-27-the-bible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Canaan, the youngest son of Ham
Genesis 9:20-27

The Bible tells us that Ham ridiculed his drunk father, Noah, by failing to cover his nakedness.  According to Deuteronomy 27:16, to treat one’s father or mother with contempt as Ham did was punishable by a curse. However, Noah could not curse Ham though he deserved it. This is because in Genesis 9:1, we are told that God blessed Noah and his three sons. Noah knew that he could not curse anyone whom God had blessed.  This principle would later be seen in Numbers 23:7-8, 8-22 when Balaam discovered that he could not reverse the blessing of God upon Israel.  
	But Ham had four sons: Cush (Ethiopia); Mizraim (Egypt); Put (Libya); and Canaan (Genesis 10:6).  Noah could not curse Cush because he was protected by another law, the law of the firstborn (Genesis 27:1-37; Deuteronomy 21:17). He, however, could have cursed Mizraim or Put but he chose to curse the youngest son, Canaan.  
	In the story, between verses 18 and 27, reference to Canaan occurred five times. Also, in Genesis 10 Canaan is singled out for particular attention in verses 15-19. Why? Because the Holy Spirit and the human author don’t want us to make the mistake of wrong or unsuccessful judgement.  Ham was not cursed, but Canaan was (Genesis 9:25).
	Thus for the first three sons of Ham, we have a good idea of the geographical locations of their nations and that is North Africa.  Genesis 10:18-19 also tells us of how scattered the families of the Canaanites have been : “And the border of the Canaanites was from Sidon as you go toward Gerar, as far as Gaza; then as you go toward Sodom, Gommorah, Admah and Zeboim, as far as Lasha.”
	Note that none of these areas are in Africa.  They are the areas that the Lord promised to give to Abraham when He called him to leave Ur of the Chaldeans for a promised land (see Genesis 15:18-21). 
	Professor Charles Ryrie, in his Study Bible, makes the following comments regarding this subject:
“Whether Canaan was personally involved with his father, Ham’s sin we do not know (he might have seen Noah’s condition first and then told his father). But Ham is punished for his dishonour to his father by having a son who will bring dishonour to him. The curse is not on the Hamites, but on the Canaanites, the inhabitants of Palestine who were first subjected by Joshua and later by Solomon (see 1 Kings 9:20-21). The Canaanites long ago became extinct:; the curse, therefore, cannot be applied to anyone today.”

The Eerdman’s Bible Dictionary explains:
“…This curse, which applies more to the descendants of Canaan, does not imply the slavery of a particular race (as some have held); rather, it suggests the inferior position of the Canaanites before the conquest relative to the important role played by their neighbors, the Egyptians and the inhabitants of Mesopotamia.”

Conclusion
	Back to our questions: Is Africa cursed? The answer is a resounding NO, because Ham was blessed by the Lord and by the Biblical law of succession, a double portion of that blessing would go to his first son, who is Cush, the Ethiopian, or African. " -- Tokunboh Adeyemo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144632-here-s-why-the-life-of-muhammad-and-jesus-matters-contrary</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 08:55:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Robert Spencer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144632-here-s-why-the-life-of-muhammad-and-jesus-matters-contrary]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here’s why the life of Muhammad [and Jesus] matters: Contrary to what many secularists would have us believe, religions are not entirely determined (or distorted) by the faithful over time. The lives and words of the founders remain central, no matter how long ago they lived. The idea that believers shape religion is derived, instead, from the fashionable 1960s philosophy of deconstructionism, which teaches that written words have no meaning other than that given to them by the reader. Equally important, it follows that if the reader alone finds meaning, there can be no truth (and certainly no religious truth); one person’s meaning is equal to another’s. Ultimately, according to deconstructionism, we all create our own set of “truths,” none better, or worse than any other.
	Yet for the religious man or woman on the streets of Chicago, Rome, Jerusalem, Damascus, Calcutta, and Bangkok, the words of Jesus, Moses, Muhammad, Krishna, and Buddha mean something far greater than any individual’s rendering of them. And even to the less-than-devout reader, the words of these great religious leaders are clearly not equal in their meaning." -- Robert Spencer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147862-there-are-only-two-kinds-of-madness-one-should-guard</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 08:06:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Andre Brink, &quot;A Dry White Season&quot; pg. 304]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147862-there-are-only-two-kinds-of-madness-one-should-guard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are only two kinds of madness one should guard against... One is the belief that we can do everything. The other is the belief that we can do nothing." -- Andre Brink, &quot;A Dry White Season&quot; pg. 304]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160196-how-dare-i-presume-to-say-he-is-my-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 18:52:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Andre  P. Brink]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160196-how-dare-i-presume-to-say-he-is-my-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How dare I presume to say: He is my friend, or even, more cautiously, I think I know him? At the very most we are like two strangers meeting in the white wintry veld and sitting down together for a while to smoke a pipe before proceeding on their separate ways. No more.

Alone. Alone to the very end. I… every one of us. But to have been granted the grace of meeting and touching so fleetingly: is that not the most awesome and wonderful thing one can hope for in this world?" -- Andre  P. Brink]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160193-i-had-never-been-so-close-to-death-before-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 18:55:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Andre Brink]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160193-i-had-never-been-so-close-to-death-before-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had never been so close to death before.
	For a long time, as I lay there trying to clear my mind, I couldn't think coherently at all, conscious only of a terrible, blind bitterness. Why had they singled me out? Didn't they understand? Had everything I'd gone through on their behalf been utterly in vain? Did it really count for nothing? What had happened to logic, meaning and sense? 
	But I feel much calmer now. It helps to discipline oneself like this, writing it down to see it set out on paper, to try and weigh it and find some significance in it. 
	Prof Bruwer: There are only two kinds of madness one should guard against, Ben. One is the belief that we can do everything. The other is the belief that we can do nothing.
	I wanted to help. Right. I meant it very sincerely. But I wanted to do it on my terms. And I am white, and they are black. I thought it was still possible to reach beyond our whiteness and blackness. I thought that to reach out and touch hands across the gulf would be sufficient in itself. But I grasped so little, really: as if good intentions from my side could solve it all. It was presumptuous of me. In an ordinary world, in a natural one, I might have succeeded. But not in this deranged, divided age. I can do all I can for Gordon or scores of others who have come to me; I can imagine myself in their shoes, I can project myself into their suffering. But I cannot, ever, live their lives for them. So what else could come of it but failure?
	Whether I like it or not, whether I feel like cursing my own condition or not -- and that would only serve to confirm my impotence -- I am white.  This is the small, final, terrifying truth of my broken world. I am white. And because I am white I am born into a state of privilege.  Even if I fight the system that has reduced us to this I remain white, and favored by the very circumstances I abhor. Even if I'm hated, and ostracized, and persecuted, and in the end destroyed, nothing can make me black. And so those who are cannot but remain suspicious of me. In their eyes my very efforts to identify myself with Gordon, whit all the Gordons, would be obscene. Every gesture I make, every act I commit in my efforts to help them makes it more difficult for them to define their real needs and discover for themselves their integrity and affirm their own dignity. How else could we hope to arrive beyond predator and prey, helper and helped, white and black, and find redemption?
	On the other hand: what can I do but what I have done? I cannot choose not to intervene: that would be a denial and a mockery not only of everything I believe in, but of the hope that compassion may survive among men. By not acting as I did I would deny the very possibility of that gulf to be bridged. 
	If I act, I cannot but lose. But if I do not act, it is a different kind of defeat, equally decisive and maybe worse. Because then I will not even have a conscience left.
	The end seems ineluctable: failure, defeat, loss. The only choice I have left is whether I am prepared to salvage a little honour, a little decency, a little humanity -- or nothing. It seems as if a sacrifice is impossible to avoid, whatever way one looks at it. But at least one has the choice between a wholly futile sacrifice and one that might, in the long run, open up a possibility, however negligible or dubious, of something better, less sordid and more noble, for our children…
	They live on. We, the fathers, have lost." -- Andre Brink]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192326-if-you-want-to-keep-people-subjugated-the-last-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 06:52:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Desmond Tutu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192326-if-you-want-to-keep-people-subjugated-the-last-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to keep people subjugated, the last thing you place in their hands is a Bible. There's nothing more radical, nothing more revolutionary, nothing more subversive against injustice and oppression than the Bible." -- Desmond Tutu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215113-both-adults-have-always-worked-observes-cox-writing-with-business</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 12:31:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Michael Medved]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215113-both-adults-have-always-worked-observes-cox-writing-with-business]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Both adults have always worked,&quot; observes Cox, writing with business journalist Richard Alm. &quot;Running a household entails a daunting list of chores: cooking, gardening, child care, shopping, washing and ironing, financial management, ferrying family members to ballet lessons and soccer practice... the idea that people at home don't work isn't just insulting to women, who do most of the housework. It also misses how specialization contributes to higher and higher living standards. At one time, both adults worked exclusively at home. The man constructed buildings, tilled the land, raised livestock. The woman prepared meals, preserved food, looked after the children. Living standards rarely raised above the subsistence level.&quot; But as men went to work outside the home- &quot;gaining specialized skills and earning income that allowed the family to buy what it didn't have the time, energy or ability to make at home&quot;-- living standards rose. 
------ Michael Medved quoting Cox and Alm, &quot;10 Big Lies about America&quot; page 224" -- Michael Medved]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13750-if-only-it-were-all-so-simple-if-only-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2009 13:39:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13750-if-only-it-were-all-so-simple-if-only-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If only it were all so simple! If only there were evil people somewhere insidiously committing evil deeds, and it were necessary only to separate them from the rest of us and destroy them. But the line dividing good and evil cuts through the heart of every human being. And who is willing to destroy a piece of his own heart?" -- Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74996-simply-to-endure-is-to-triumph</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 19:19:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Patricia McCormick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74996-simply-to-endure-is-to-triumph]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Simply to endure is to triumph." -- Patricia McCormick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13211-the-christian-ideal-has-not-been-tried-and-found-wanting</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 10:06:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13211-the-christian-ideal-has-not-been-tried-and-found-wanting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Christian ideal has not been tried and found wanting. It has been found difficult; and left untried." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16293-that-men-do-not-learn-very-much-from-the-lessons</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2009 12:04:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16293-that-men-do-not-learn-very-much-from-the-lessons]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That men do not learn very much from the lessons of history is the most important of all the lessons that history has to teach." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221095-the-far-sighted-perfect-love-that-seeks-perfection-of-it-s-object</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 06:32:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Mrs. Charles E. Cowman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221095-the-far-sighted-perfect-love-that-seeks-perfection-of-it-s-object]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The far-sighted, perfect love that seeks perfection of it's object does not weakly shrink from present, transient, suffering. Our Father's love is too true to be weak. Because He loves His children, He chastises them that they may be partakes of His holiness. With this glorious end in view, He spares not for their crying. Made perfect through sufferings, as the Elder Brother [Jesus] was, the sons of God are trained up to obedience and brought to glory through much tribulation. -- Streams in the Dessert, p. 10" -- Mrs. Charles E. Cowman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263255-marriage-which-has-been-the-bourne-of-so-many-narratives</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 10:47:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by George Elliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263255-marriage-which-has-been-the-bourne-of-so-many-narratives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Marriage, which has been the bourne of so many narratives, is still a great beginning, as it was to Adam and Eve, who kept their honey-moon in Eden, but had their first little one among the thorns and thistles of the wilderness.  It is still the beginning of the home epic - the gradual conquest or irremediable loss of that complete union which make the advancing years a climax, and age the harvest of sweet memories in common." -- George Elliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152989-few-things-hold-the-perception-more-thoroughly-captive-than-anxiety</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 10:49:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152989-few-things-hold-the-perception-more-thoroughly-captive-than-anxiety]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Few things hold the perception more thoroughly captive than anxiety about what we have got to say" -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257610-the-wit-of-a-family-is-usually-best-received-among</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 10:53:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257610-the-wit-of-a-family-is-usually-best-received-among]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The wit of a family is usually best received among strangers." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138248-the-problem-with-socialism-is-that-you-eventually-run-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 12:31:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Margaret Thatcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138248-the-problem-with-socialism-is-that-you-eventually-run-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem with socialism is that you eventually run out of other people's money." -- Margaret Thatcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203762-marble-i-perceive-covers-a-multitude-of-sins</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 12:31:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203762-marble-i-perceive-covers-a-multitude-of-sins]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Marble, I perceive, covers a multitude of sins." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/500574-we-humans-can-work-hard-for-each-other-and-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 17:24:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ebookwormy add a quote by David Wilkerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/500574-we-humans-can-work-hard-for-each-other-and-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We humans can work hard for each other, and we should and we must work. But it is God, and only God, who heals.&quot; The Cross and the Switchblade, pg 90." -- David Wilkerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
