<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1005750-katie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1005750-katie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 15:38:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21627-the-best-thing-for-being-sad-replied-merlin-beginning-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 15:38:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by T.H. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21627-the-best-thing-for-being-sad-replied-merlin-beginning-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best thing for being sad,&quot; replied Merlin, beginning to puff and blow, &quot;is to learn something. That's the only thing that never fails. You may grow old and trembling in your anatomies, you may lie awake at night listening to the disorder of your veins, you may miss your only love, you may see the world about you devastated by evil lunatics, or know your honour trampled in the sewers of baser minds. There is only one thing for it then — to learn. Learn why the world wags and what wags it. That is the only thing which the mind can never exhaust, never alienate, never be tortured by, never fear or distrust, and never dream of regretting. Learning is the only thing for you. Look what a lot of things there are to learn." -- T.H. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 13:01:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know you're in love when you can't fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47648-but-if-you-love-and-must-needs-have-desires-let</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 13:17:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47648-but-if-you-love-and-must-needs-have-desires-let]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But if you love and must needs have desires, let these be your desires:
To melt and be like a running brook that sings its melody to the night.
To know the pain of too much tenderness.
To be wounded by your own understanding of love;
And to bleed willingly and joyfully.
To wake at dawn with a winged heart and give thanks for another day of loving;
To rest at noon hour and meditate love's ecstasy;
To return home at eventide with gratitude;
And then to sleep with a prayer for the beloved in your heart and a song of praise on your lips." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 13:33:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love never dies a natural death. It dies because we don't know how to replenish its source. It dies of blindness and errors and betrayals. It dies of illness and wounds; it dies of weariness, of witherings, of tarnishings." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
