<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1005710-jaime]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1005710-jaime" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2008 08:00:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2008 08:00:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jaime add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38318-true-discipleship-is-for-volunteers-only-only-volunteers-will-trust</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 18:07:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jaime add a quote by Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38318-true-discipleship-is-for-volunteers-only-only-volunteers-will-trust]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["True discipleship is for volunteers only.  Only volunteers will trust the Guide sufficiently to follow Him in the dangerous ascent which only He can lead." -- Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38319-we-can-tell-much-by-what-we-have-already-willing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 18:07:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jaime add a quote by Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38319-we-can-tell-much-by-what-we-have-already-willing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can tell much by what we have already willing discarded along the pathway of discipleship.  It is the only pathway where littering is permissible, even encouraged.  In the early stages, the debris left behind includes the grosser sins of commission.  Later debris differs; things begin to be discarded which have caused the misuse or underuse of our time and talent." -- Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38320-if-we-are-serious-about-our-discipleship-jesus-will-eventually</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 18:08:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jaime add a quote by Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38320-if-we-are-serious-about-our-discipleship-jesus-will-eventually]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we are serious about our discipleship, Jesus will eventually request each of us to do those very things which are most difficult for us to do." -- Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38322-give-me-all-of-you-i-don-t-want-so-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 18:10:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jaime add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38322-give-me-all-of-you-i-don-t-want-so-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Give me all of you!!! I don’t want so much of your time, so much of your talents and money, and so much of your work. I want YOU!!! ALL OF YOU!! I have not come to torment or frustrate the natural man or woman, but to KILL IT! No half measures will do. I don’t want to only prune a branch here and a branch there; rather I want the whole tree out! Hand it over to me, the whole outfit, all of your desires, all of your wants and wishes and dreams. Turn them ALL over to me, give yourself to me and I will make of you a new self---in my image. Give me yourself and in exchange I will give you Myself. My will, shall become your will. My heart, shall become your heart." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
