<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1006484-stephanie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1006484-stephanie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 19:59:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79275-our-life-is-like-a-land-journey-too-even-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 19:59:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Lloyd C. Douglas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79275-our-life-is-like-a-land-journey-too-even-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our life is like a land journey, too even and easy and dull over long distances across the plains, too hard and painful up the steep grades; but, on the summits of the mountain, you have a magnificent view--and feel exalted--and your eyes are full of happy tears--and you want to sing--and wish you had wings! And then--you can't stay there, but must continue your journey--you begin climbing down the other side, so busy with your footholds that your summit experience is forgotten." -- Lloyd C. Douglas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33459-no-dear-but-speaking-of-father-reminded-me-how-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 22:53:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33459-no-dear-but-speaking-of-father-reminded-me-how-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No, dear, but speaking of Father reminded me how much I miss him, how much I owe him, and how faithfully I should watch and work to keep his little daughters safe and good for him.

Yet you told him to go, Mother, and didn’t cry when he went, and never complain now, or seem as if you needed any help, said Jo, wondering.

I gave my best to the country I love, and kept my tears till he was gone. Why should I complain, when we both have merely done our duty and will surely be the happier for it in the end? If I don’t seem to need help, it is because I have a better friend, even than Father, to comfort and sustain me. My child, the troubles and temptations of your life are beginning and may be many, but you can overcome and outlive them all if you learn to feel the strength and tenderness of your Heavenly Father as you do that of your earthly one. The more you love and trust Him, and the less you will depend on human power and wisdom. His love and care never tire or change, can never be taken from you, but my become the source of lifelong peace, happiness, and strength. Believe this heartily, and go to God with all your little cares, and hopes, and sins, and sorrows, as freely and confidingly as you come to your mother." -- Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193161-your-father-jo-he-never-loses-patience---never-doubts-or-complains---but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 22:56:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193161-your-father-jo-he-never-loses-patience---never-doubts-or-complains---but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your father, Jo.  He never loses patience,--never doubts or complains,--but always hopes, and works and waits so cheerfully, that one is ashamed to do otherwise before him.  He helped and comforted me, and showed me that I must try to practise all the virtues I would have my little girls possess, for I was their example.  It was easier for your sakes than for my own; a startled or surprised look from one of you, when I spoke sharply, rebuked me more than any words could have done; and the love, respect, and confidence of my children was the sweetest reward I could receive for my efforts to be the woman I would have them copy." -- Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2177-i-am-enough-of-an-artist-to-draw-freely-upon</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 13:04:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2177-i-am-enough-of-an-artist-to-draw-freely-upon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am enough of an artist to draw freely upon my imagination. Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8727-life-isn-t-about-finding-yourself-life-is-about-creating-yourself</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 13:05:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8727-life-isn-t-about-finding-yourself-life-is-about-creating-yourself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life isn't about finding yourself. Life is about creating yourself." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
