<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1006959-roque-strew]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1006959-roque-strew" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 10:29:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/623671-non-deve-fermarsi-l-uomo-in-una-sola-cosa-perch-allora</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 10:29:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roque add a quote by JWvG]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/623671-non-deve-fermarsi-l-uomo-in-una-sola-cosa-perch-allora]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Non deve fermarsi l’uomo in una sola cosa, perchè allora divien matto: bisogna aver mille cose, una confusione nella testa." -- JWvG]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111445-i-was-born-for-the-storm-and-a-calm-does</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 10:29:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roque add a quote by Andrew Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111445-i-was-born-for-the-storm-and-a-calm-does]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was born for the storm, and a calm does not suit me." -- Andrew Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/623672-j-aimais-les-peintures-idiotes-dessus-de-portes-d-cors-toiles-de</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 10:29:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roque add a quote by Arthur Rimbaud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/623672-j-aimais-les-peintures-idiotes-dessus-de-portes-d-cors-toiles-de]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["J'aimais les peintures idiotes, dessus de portes, décors, toiles de saltimbanques, enseignes, enluminures populaires ; la littérature démodée, latin d'église, livres érotiques sans orthographe, romans de nos aïeules, contes de fées, petits livres de l'enfance, opéras vieux, refrains niais, rythmes naïfs." -- Arthur Rimbaud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51971-questions-are-not-happenstance-thoughts-nor-are-questions-common-problems</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 10:18:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roque add a quote by Martin Heidegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51971-questions-are-not-happenstance-thoughts-nor-are-questions-common-problems]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Questions are not happenstance thoughts nor are questions common problems of today which one picks up from hearsay and booklearning and decks out with a gesture of profundity questions grow out of confrontation with the subject matter and the subject matter is there only where eyes are, it is in this manner that questions will be posed and all the more considering that questions that have today fallen out of fashion in the great industry of problems. One stands up for nothing more than the normal running of the industry. Philosophy interprets its corruption as the resurrection of metaphysics." -- Martin Heidegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51972-our-spirits-have-their-own-private-way-of-understanding-each</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 00:04:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roque add a quote by Luigi Pirandello]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51972-our-spirits-have-their-own-private-way-of-understanding-each]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our spirits have their own private way of understanding each other, of becoming intimate, while our external persons are still trapped in the commerce of ordinary words, in the slavery of social rules. Souls have their own needs and their own ambitions, which the body ignores when it sees that it's impossible to satisfy them or achieve them." -- Luigi Pirandello]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73992-the-law-of-causality-i-believe-like-much-that-passes</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 00:34:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roque add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73992-the-law-of-causality-i-believe-like-much-that-passes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The law of causality, I believe, like much that passes muster among philosophers, is a relic of a bygone age, surviving, like the monarchy, only because it is erroneously supposed to do no harm." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/623681-i-am-deeply-sensitive-to-the-spell-of-nationalism-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 15:36:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roque add a quote by Ernest Gellner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/623681-i-am-deeply-sensitive-to-the-spell-of-nationalism-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am deeply sensitive to the spell of nationalism. I can play about thirty Bohemian folk songs ... on my mouth-organ. My oldest friend, who is Czech and a patriot, cannot bear to hear me play them because he says I do it in such a schmalzy way, 'crying into the mouth organ'. I do not think I could have written the book on nationalism which I did write, were I not capable of crying, with the help of a little alcohol, over folk songs, which happen to be my favourite form of music." -- Ernest Gellner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166926-bring-together-things-that-have-not-yet-been-brought-together</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 15:36:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roque add a quote by Robert Bresson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166926-bring-together-things-that-have-not-yet-been-brought-together]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bring together things that have not yet been brought together and did not seem predisposed to be so." -- Robert Bresson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229548-i-have-just-now-come-from-a-party-where-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 14:21:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roque add a quote by Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229548-i-have-just-now-come-from-a-party-where-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have just now come from a party where I was its life and soul; witticisms streamed from my lips, everyone laughed and admired me, but I went away — yes, the dash should be as long as the radius of the earth's orbit ——————————— and wanted to shoot myself." -- Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69425-the-final-belief-is-to-believe-in-a-fiction-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 10:41:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roque add a quote by Wallace Stevens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69425-the-final-belief-is-to-believe-in-a-fiction-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The final belief is to believe in a fiction, which you know to be a fiction, there being nothing else. The exquisite truth is to know that it is a fiction and that you believe in it willingly." -- Wallace Stevens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/695348-for-in-the-immediate-world-everything-is-to-be-discerned</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 00:18:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roque add a quote by James Agee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/695348-for-in-the-immediate-world-everything-is-to-be-discerned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For in the immediate world, everything is to be discerned, for him who can discern it, and central and simply, without either dissection into science, or digestion into art, but with the whole of consciousness, seeking to perceive it as it stands: so that the aspect of a street in sunlight can roar in the heart of itself as a symphony, perhaps as no symphony can: and all of consciousness is shifted from the imagined, the revisive, to the effort to perceive simply the cruel radiation of what is." -- James Agee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/701197-i-ve-never-been-certain-whether-the-moral-of-the-icarus</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 00:23:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roque add a quote by Stanley Kubrick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/701197-i-ve-never-been-certain-whether-the-moral-of-the-icarus]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’ve never been certain whether the moral of the Icarus story should only be, as is generally accepted, ‘don’t try to fly too high,’ or whether it might also be thought of as ‘forget the wax and feathers, and do a better job on the wings." -- Stanley Kubrick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/641877-mais-la-connaissance-du-pass-rendu-vivant-et-pr-sent-o</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 02:54:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roque add a quote by Jacqueline de Romilly]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/641877-mais-la-connaissance-du-pass-rendu-vivant-et-pr-sent-o]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mais la connaissance du passé rendu vivant et présent, où la trouve-t-on ? Eh bien, avant tout, dans la littérature ! Et là est à mes yeux la merveille. On la trouve dans les textes français et étrangers, modernes et anciens. Aussi cela me paraît-il une erreur très grave que de représenter l’enseignement de la littérature comme une espèce d’élégance superflue et gratuite. En fait, c’est grâce à la littérature que se forme presque toute notre idée de la vie ; le détour par les textes conduit directement à la formation de l’homme. Ils nous apportent les analyses et les idées, mais aussi les images, les personnages, les mythes, et les rêves qui se sont succédé dans l’esprit des hommes ; ils nous ont un jour émus parce qu’ils étaient exprimés ou décrits avec force ; et c’est de cette expérience que se nourrit la nôtre." -- Jacqueline de Romilly]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/765377-vielleicht-sind-gewisse-meiner-neulich-ausgesprochenen-bedenken-sehr-bertrieben-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 05:16:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roque add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/765377-vielleicht-sind-gewisse-meiner-neulich-ausgesprochenen-bedenken-sehr-bertrieben-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Vielleicht sind gewisse meiner neulich ausgesprochenen Bedenken sehr übertrieben; so viel, wie ich mich kenne, scheint mir sicher, daß, wenn man mir meine Teufel austriebe, auch meinen Engeln ein kleinen, ein ganz kleiner (sagen wir) Schrecken geschähe, - und - fühlen Sie - gerade darauf darf ich es auf keinen Preis ankommen lassen." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/786166-soyez-r-gl-dans-votre-vie-et-ordinaire-comme-un-bourgeois</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 12:08:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roque add a quote by Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/786166-soyez-r-gl-dans-votre-vie-et-ordinaire-comme-un-bourgeois]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Soyez réglé dans votre vie et ordinaire comme un bourgeois, afin d'être violent et original dans vos œuvres." -- Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
