<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1006886-heather-p]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1006886-heather-p" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 17:09:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22614-warning-if-you-dare-to-read-this-story-you-become</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 17:09:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by James Patterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22614-warning-if-you-dare-to-read-this-story-you-become]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["WARNING
If you dare to read this story, you become part of the Experiment" -- James Patterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 10:22:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that's what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that is holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life.  

A true soul mate is probably the most important person you'll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake.  But to live with a soul mate forever?  Nah. Too painful.  Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then leave.  

A soul mates purpose is to shake you up, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light can get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you have to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132529-death-is-nothing-at-all-i-have-only-slipped-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 16:36:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Henry Scott Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132529-death-is-nothing-at-all-i-have-only-slipped-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death is nothing at all,
I have only slipped into the next room
I am I and you are you
Whatever we were to each other, that we are still.
Call me by my old familiar name,
Speak to me in the easy way which you always used
Put no difference in your tone,
Wear no forced air of solemnity or sorrow
Laugh as we always laughed at the little jokes we enjoyed together.
Play, smile, think of me, pray for me.
Let my name be ever the household world that it always was,
Let it be spoken without effect, without the trace of shadow on it.
Life means all that it ever meant.
It it the same as it ever was, there is unbroken continuity.
Why should I be out of mind because I am out of sight?
I am waiting for you, for an interval, somewhere very near,
Just around the corner.
All is well. " -- Henry Scott Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
