<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1007139-joanna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1007139-joanna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 10:07:13 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202841-there-are-some-things-that-it-is-better-to-begin</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 10:07:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202841-there-are-some-things-that-it-is-better-to-begin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are some things that it is better to begin than to refuse, even though the end may be dark." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334877-i-know-said-pippin-it-was-a-wrench-to-let</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 10:09:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334877-i-know-said-pippin-it-was-a-wrench-to-let]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know,' said Pippin.  'It was a wrench to let it go; but what else could I do?'
'Nothing else,' answered Aragon.  'One who cannot cast away a treasure at need is in fetters.  You did rightly." -- J.R.R. Tolkein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28949-journey-s-end-in-western-lands-beneath-the-sun-the-flowers</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 10:09:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28949-journey-s-end-in-western-lands-beneath-the-sun-the-flowers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Journey’s end

In western lands beneath the Sun
The flowers may rise in Spring,
The trees may bud, the waters run,
The merry finches sing.
Or there maybe 'tis cloudless night,
And swaying branches bear
The Elven-stars as jewels white
Amid their branching hair.

Though here at journey's end I lie
In darkness buried deep,
Beyond all towers strong and high,
Beyond all mountains steep,
Above all shadows rides the Sun
And Stars for ever dwell:
I will not say the Day is done,
Nor bid the Stars farewell.J." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334882-this-was-my-only-and-my-constant-comfort-when-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 10:11:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334882-this-was-my-only-and-my-constant-comfort-when-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This was my only and my constant comfort.  When I think of it, the picture always rises in my mind, of a summer evening, the boys at play in the churchyard, and I sitting on my bed, reading as if for life." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26497-there-are-a-few-people-out-there-with-whom-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 10:12:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Lauren F. Winner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26497-there-are-a-few-people-out-there-with-whom-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are a few people out there with whom you fit just so, and, amazingly, you keep fitting just so even after you have growth spurts or lose weight or stop wearing high heels. You keep fitting after you have children or change religions or stop dyeing your hair or quit your job at Goldman Sachs and take up farming. Somehow, God is gracious enough to give us a few of those people, people you can stretch into, people who don't go away, and whom you wouldn't want to go away, even if they offered." -- Lauren F. Winner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334883-americans-admire-success-englishmen-admire-heroic-failure</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 10:13:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Anne Fadiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334883-americans-admire-success-englishmen-admire-heroic-failure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Americans admire success.  Englishmen admire heroic failure" -- Anne Fadiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55062-when-ada-disappeared-into-the-trees-it-was-like-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 10:15:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Charles Frazier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55062-when-ada-disappeared-into-the-trees-it-was-like-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When Ada disappeared into the trees, it was like a part of the richness of the world had gone with her.  He had been alone in the world and empty for so long.  But she filled him full, and so he believed everything that had been taken out of him might have been for a purpose.  To clear space for something better. -Cold Mountain" -- Charles Frazier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334886-now-he-reduced-his-progress-to-the-rhythm-of-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 10:22:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334886-now-he-reduced-his-progress-to-the-rhythm-of-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now he reduced his progress to the rhythm of his boots -- he walked across the land until he came to the sea.  Everything that impeded him had to be outweighed, even if only by a fraction, by all that drove him on.  In one pan of the scales, his wound, thirst, the blister, tiredness, the heat, the aching in his feet and legs, the Stukas, the distance, the Channel; in the other, I'll wait for you, and the memory of when she had said it, which he had come to treat like a sacred site.  Also, the fear of capture.  His most sensual memories -- their few minutes in the library, the kiss in Whitehall -- was bleached colorless through overuse.  He knew by heart certain passages from her letters, he had revisited their tussle with the vase by the fountain, he remembered the warmth from her arm at the dinner when the twins went missing.  These memories sustained him, but not so easily.  Too often they reminded him of where he was when he last summoned them.  They lay on the far side of a great divide in time, as significant as B.C. and A.D.  Before prison, before war, before the sight of a corpse became a banality.

But these heresies died when he read her last letter.  He touched his breast pocket.  It was a kind of genuflection.  Still there.  Here was something new on the scales.  That he could be cleared had all the simplicity of love.  Merely tasting the possibility reminded him of how much had narrowed and died.  His taste for life, no less, all the old ambitions and pleasures.  The prospect was of rebirth, a triumphant return." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62283-but-when-a-young-lady-is-to-be-a-heroine</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 10:23:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62283-but-when-a-young-lady-is-to-be-a-heroine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But when a young lady is to be a heroine, the perverseness of forty surrounding families cannot prevent her. Something must and will happen to throw a hero in her way." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2579-do-not-read-as-children-do-to-amuse-yourself-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 10:25:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2579-do-not-read-as-children-do-to-amuse-yourself-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not read, as children do, to amuse yourself, or like the ambitious, for the purpose of instruction. No, read in order to live." -- Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124054-they-took-to-silence-they-touched-each-other-without-comment</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 10:27:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by A.S. Byatt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124054-they-took-to-silence-they-touched-each-other-without-comment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They took to silence. They touched each other without comment and without progression. A hand on a hand, a clothed arm, resting on an arm. An ankle overlapping an ankle, as they sat on a beach, and not removed. One night they fell asleep, side by side... He slept curled against her back, a dark comma against her pale elegant phrase." -- A.S. Byatt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334891-how-she-might-have-felt-had-there-been-no-captain</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 10:29:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334891-how-she-might-have-felt-had-there-been-no-captain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How she might have felt had there been no Captain Wentworth in the case, was not worth enquiry; for there was a Captain Wentworth: and be the conclusion of the present suspense good or bad, her affection would be his forever.  Their union, she believed, could not divide her more from other men, than their final separation." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334893-dude-if-kentucky-is-going-to-remind-you-of-paris</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 10:31:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334893-dude-if-kentucky-is-going-to-remind-you-of-paris]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dude, if Kentucky is going to remind you of Paris, we're in a hell of a pickle." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338135-perhaps-he-could-still-weave-together-the-broken-threads-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2011 11:26:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Juliet Marillier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338135-perhaps-he-could-still-weave-together-the-broken-threads-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps he could still weave together the broken threads of his life.  And yet, I wanted him here now.  I needed him here.  In the darkness, if I sat very still, I could almost feel his presence by me, quite near, but not too near.  Didn't I promise to keep you safe, he would say softly.  I have never broken a promise.  Don't look so worried, Jenny.  And yet, he would be careful.  Careful not to move too close.  Careful not to frighten me.  Waiting still.  I am your shelter.  Don't be afraid." -- Juliet Marillier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258313-i-wonder-how-the-book-got-to-guernsey-perhaps-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 17:15:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Mary Ann Shaffer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258313-i-wonder-how-the-book-got-to-guernsey-perhaps-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wonder how the book got to Guernsey? Perhaps there is some secret sort of homing instinct in books that brings them to their perfect readers." -- Mary Ann Shaffer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121811-most-true-is-it-that-beauty-is-in-the-eye</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 19:55:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121811-most-true-is-it-that-beauty-is-in-the-eye]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most true is it that 'beauty is in the eye of the gazer.' My master’s colourless, olive face, square, massive brow, broad and jetty eyebrows, deep eyes, strong features, firm, grim mouth, — all energy, decision, will, — were not beautiful, according to rule; but they were more than beautiful to me; they were full of an interest, an influence that quite mastered me, — that took my feelings from my own power and fettered them in his. I had not intended to love him; the reader knows I had wrought hard to extirpate from my soul the germs of love there detected; and now, at the first renewed view of him, they spontaneously arrived, green and strong! He made me love him without looking at me." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122352-good-night-my--he-stopped-bit-his-lip-and-abruptly-left</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 19:56:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122352-good-night-my--he-stopped-bit-his-lip-and-abruptly-left]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good-night, my-&quot; He stopped, bit his lip, and abruptly left me." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139908-i-know-i-must-conceal-my-sentiments-i-must-smother</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 19:56:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139908-i-know-i-must-conceal-my-sentiments-i-must-smother]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know I must conceal my sentiments: I must smother hope; I must remember that he cannot care much for me. For when I say that I am of his kind, I do not mean that I have his force to influence, and his spell to attract: I mean only that I have certain tastes and feelings in common with him.I must, then, repeat continually that we are forever sundered: - and yet, while I breathe and think, I must love him." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/351911-perhaps-i-will-be-a-great-man-i-mean-perhaps-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 09:02:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Lorraine Hansberry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/351911-perhaps-i-will-be-a-great-man-i-mean-perhaps-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps I will be a great man...I mean perhaps I will hold on to the substance of truth and find my way always with the right course" -- Lorraine Hansberry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35597-never-be-afraid-to-sit-awhile-and-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 09:04:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Lorraine Hansberry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35597-never-be-afraid-to-sit-awhile-and-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never be afraid to sit awhile and think." -- Lorraine Hansberry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44330-beneatha-love-him-there-is-nothing-left-to-love-mama</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 09:13:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Lorraine Hansberry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44330-beneatha-love-him-there-is-nothing-left-to-love-mama]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beneatha: Love him? There is nothing left to love.

Mama: There is always something left to love. And if you ain't learned that, you ain't learned nothing. (Looking at her) Have you cried for that boy today? I don't mean for yourself and for the family 'cause we lost the money. I mean for him: what he been through and what it done to him. Child, when do you think is the time to love somebody the most? When they done good and made things easy for everybody? Well then, you ain't through learning - because that ain't the time at all. It's when he's at his lowest and can't believe in hisself 'cause the world done whipped him so! when you starts measuring somebody, measure him right, child, measure him right. Make sure you done taken into account what hills and valleys he come through before he got to wherever he is." -- Lorraine Hansberry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/356393-telling-stories-never-fails-to-produce-good-in-the-universe</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 08:22:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Mary Pipher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/356393-telling-stories-never-fails-to-produce-good-in-the-universe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Telling stories never fails to produce good in the universe." -- Mary Pipher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274541-to-be-a-devout-reader-was-to-be-an-acolyte</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 15:38:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Tanya Egan Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274541-to-be-a-devout-reader-was-to-be-an-acolyte]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be a devout reader was to be an acolyte of solace." -- Tanya Egan Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181726-he-would-have-told-her---he-would-have-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 12:13:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Juliet Marillier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181726-he-would-have-told-her---he-would-have-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He would have told her - he would have said, it matters not if you are here or there, for I see you before me every moment.  I see you in the light of the water, in the swaying of the young trees in the spring wind.  I see you in the shadows of the great oaks, I hear your voice in the cry of the owl at night.  You are the blood in my veins, and the beating of my heart.  You are my first waking thought, and my last sigh before sleeping.  You are - you are bone of my bone, and breath of my breath." -- Juliet Marillier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267255-perhaps-this-is-what-the-stories-meant-when-they-called</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 12:13:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Juliet Marillier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267255-perhaps-this-is-what-the-stories-meant-when-they-called]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps this is what the stories meant when they called somebody heartsick. Your heart and your stomach and your whole insides felt hollow and empty and aching." -- Juliet Marillier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271435-you-know-not-yet-the-sort-of-love-that-strikes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 12:13:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Juliet Marillier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271435-you-know-not-yet-the-sort-of-love-that-strikes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know not, yet, the sort of love that strikes like a lightning bolt; that clutches hold of you by the heart, as irrevocably as death; that becomes the lodestar by which you steer the rest of your life. I would not wish such a love on anyone, man or woman, for it can make your life a paradise, or it can destroy you utterly." -- Juliet Marillier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/342747-wake-the-sleeper-must-and-confront-his-fears-or-risk</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 12:14:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Juliet Marillier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/342747-wake-the-sleeper-must-and-confront-his-fears-or-risk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wake the sleeper must, and confront his fears, or risk being lost in the dark places of the mind forever." -- Juliet Marillier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241950-i-wish--i-wish-i-could-dry-these-tears-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 12:15:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Juliet Marillier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241950-i-wish--i-wish-i-could-dry-these-tears-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish- I wish I could dry these tears, I wish I could make this better for you. But I don't know how." -- Juliet Marillier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241543-i-like-the-truth-even-when-it-does-trouble-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 12:15:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Juliet Marillier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241543-i-like-the-truth-even-when-it-does-trouble-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like the truth, even when it does trouble me." -- Juliet Marillier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271437-this-is-a-long-goodbye-yet-not-time-enough-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 12:15:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Juliet Marillier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271437-this-is-a-long-goodbye-yet-not-time-enough-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is a long goodbye, yet not time enough. I have no aptitude for this. I cannot learn this. I would hold on, and hold on, until my hands clutch at emptiness." -- Juliet Marillier]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
