<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1007576-laurence-peters]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1007576-laurence-peters" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 18:31:27 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414001-all-i-ever-wanted-was-to-reach-out-and-touch</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 18:31:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurence add a quote by Tahereh Mafi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414001-all-i-ever-wanted-was-to-reach-out-and-touch]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All I ever wanted was to reach out and touch another human being not just with my hands but with my heart." -- Tahereh Mafi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209775-this-is-the-most-enormous-extension-of-vision-of-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 18:35:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurence add a quote by Loren Eiseley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209775-this-is-the-most-enormous-extension-of-vision-of-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is the most enormous extension of vision of which life is capable: the projection of itself into other lives. This is the lonely, magnificent power of humanity. It is . . . the supreme epitome of the reaching out." -- Loren Eiseley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92341-when-it-comes-to-leaders-we-have-if-anything-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 13:16:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurence add a quote by Barbara W. Tuchman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92341-when-it-comes-to-leaders-we-have-if-anything-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When it comes to leaders we have, if anything, a superabundance—hundreds of Pied Pipers…ready and anxious to lead the population. They are scurrying around, collecting consensus, gathering as wide an acceptance as possible. But what they are not doing, very notably, is standing still and saying, ' This is what I believe. This I will do and that I will not do. This is my code of behavior and that is outside it. This is excellent and that is trash.' There is an abdication of moral leadership in the sense of a general unwillingness to state standards….Of all the ills that our poor…society is heir to, the focal one, it seems to me, from which so much of our uneasiness and confusion derive, is the absence of standards. We are too unsure of ourselves to assert them, to stick by them, if necessary in the case of persons who occupy positions of authority, to impose them. We seem to be afflicted by a widespread and eroding reluctance to take any stand on any values, moral, behavioral or esthetic." -- Barbara W. Tuchman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
