<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/100823-john]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/100823-john" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 10:27:52 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24729-there-are-it-seems-two-muses-the-muse-of-inspiration</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 10:27:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24729-there-are-it-seems-two-muses-the-muse-of-inspiration]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are, it seems, two muses: the Muse of Inspiration, who gives us inarticulate visions and desires, and the Muse of Realization, who returns again and again to say &quot;It is yet more difficult than you thought.&quot; This is the muse of form. It may be then that form serves us best when it works as an obstruction, to baffle us and deflect our intended course. It may be that when we no longer know what to do, we have come to our real work and when we no longer know which way to go, we have begun our real journey. The mind that is not baffled is not employed. The impeded stream is the one that sings." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2071-one-of-the-most-important-resources-that-a-garden-makes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 10:35:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2071-one-of-the-most-important-resources-that-a-garden-makes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the most important resources that a garden makes available for use, is the gardener's own body. A garden gives the body the dignity of working in its own support. It is a way of rejoining the human race." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11690-i-imagine-the-dead-waking-dazed-into-a-shadowless-light</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 10:37:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11690-i-imagine-the-dead-waking-dazed-into-a-shadowless-light]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I imagine the dead waking, dazed, into a shadowless light in which they know themselves altogether for the first time. It is a light that is merciless until they can accept its mercy; by it they are at once condemned and redeemed. It is Hell until it is Heaven. Seeing themselves in that light, if they are willing, they see how far they have failed the only justice of loving one another; it punishes them by their own judgment. And yet, in suffering that light's awful clarity, in seeing themselves in it, they see its forgiveness and its beauty, and are consoled. In it they are loved completely, even as they have been, and so are changed into what they could not have been but what, if they could have imagined it, they would have wished to be." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109867-love-the-quick-profit-the-annual-raise-vacation-with-pay</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 10:39:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109867-love-the-quick-profit-the-annual-raise-vacation-with-pay]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love the quick profit, the annual raise,
vacation with pay. Want more
of everything ready-made. Be afraid
to know your neighbors and to die.

And you will have a window in your head.
Not even your future will be a mystery
any more. Your mind will be punched in a card
and shut away in a little drawer.

When they want you to buy something
they will call you. When they want you
to die for profit they will let you know.
So, friends, every day do something
that won’t compute. Love the Lord.
Love the world. Work for nothing.
Take all that you have and be poor.
Love someone who does not deserve it.

Denounce the government and embrace
the flag. Hope to live in that free
republic for which it stands.
Give your approval to all you cannot
understand. Praise ignorance, for what man
has not encountered he has not destroyed.

Ask the questions that have no answers.
Invest in the millenium. Plant sequoias.
Say that your main crop is the forest
that you did not plant,
that you will not live to harvest.

Say that the leaves are harvested
when they have rotted into the mold.
Call that profit. Prophesy such returns.
Put your faith in the two inches of humus
that will build under the trees
every thousand years.

Listen to carrion — put your ear
close, and hear the faint chattering
of the songs that are to come.
Expect the end of the world. Laugh.
Laughter is immeasurable. Be joyful
though you have considered all the facts.
So long as women do not go cheap
for power, please women more than men.

Ask yourself: Will this satisfy
a woman satisfied to bear a child?
Will this disturb the sleep
of a woman near to giving birth?

Go with your love to the fields.
Lie down in the shade. Rest your head
in her lap. Swear allegiance
to what is nighest your thoughts.

As soon as the generals and the politicos
can predict the motions of your mind,
lose it. Leave it as a sign
to mark the false trail, the way
you didn’t go.

Be like the fox
who makes more tracks than necessary,
some in the wrong direction.
Practice resurrection." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112012-especially-among-christians-in-positions-of-wealth-and-power-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 10:42:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112012-especially-among-christians-in-positions-of-wealth-and-power-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Especially among Christians in positions of wealth and power, the idea of reading the Gospels and keeping Jesus' commandments as stated therein has been replaced by a curious process of logic. According to this process, people first declare themselves to be followers of Christ, and then they assume that whatever they say or do merits the adjective &quot;Christian&quot;." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70125-never-be-afraid-to-trust-an-unknown-future-to-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 07:13:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Corrie ten Boom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70125-never-be-afraid-to-trust-an-unknown-future-to-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never be afraid to trust an unknown future to a known God." -- Corrie ten Boom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34052-we-are-unusual-and-tragic-and-alive</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 07:13:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by dave eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34052-we-are-unusual-and-tragic-and-alive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are unusual and tragic and alive." -- dave eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
