<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1008439-tammy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1008439-tammy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 08:29:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65375-life-is-worth-living-as-long-as-there-s-a-laugh</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 08:29:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65375-life-is-worth-living-as-long-as-there-s-a-laugh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is worth living as long as there's a laugh in it." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1141503-his-eyes-were-a-warm-brown-gentle-but-intense-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 13:26:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Janette Rallison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1141503-his-eyes-were-a-warm-brown-gentle-but-intense-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His eyes were a warm brown, gentle but intense. &quot;You know...I never gave you a good-bye kiss.&quot;
It was hard to breathe. &quot;Oh. That's right.&quot;
&quot;I was supposed to do that so you wouldn't be lying.&quot; 
...He leaned toward me gradually, as though giving me time to change my mind. I shut my eyes and let his lips come down on mine. 
Hudson wasn't in a hurry to say good-bye. The kiss was slow, caressing. All the bumps of the road and the sway of the carriage seemed to fade away, replaced by the beating of my heart. I didn't remember putting my free hand around his neck, but it was there somehow, twining through his hair. His arm moved from the back of the seat to my shoulders. I liked the feel of his arm around me. I felt enveloped, cared for. When he lifted his head from mine, my mind was spinning. 
I blinked at him. &quot;Well, you certainly have a way with good-byes." -- Janette Rallison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1141507-seemingly-on-a-whim-he-put-his-hands-on-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 13:32:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Janette Rallison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1141507-seemingly-on-a-whim-he-put-his-hands-on-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Seemingly on a whim, he put his hands on my shoulders, leaned forward, and kissed me too. The pressure of his lips on mine made my heart skid helplessly inside my chest. I shut my eyes and kissed him back...

I stepped away from him taking a deep breath to clear my mind. &quot;Okay, just because I might at some point have your baby, it doesn't mean you can kiss me whenever you want.&quot; 

He smiled, self-satisfied...&quot;Here's another thing you need to learn about women, Stets. They might pretend to like  the bad-boy Robin Hood types, but they can't resist hick-town boys." -- Janette Rallison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1141513-i-didn-t-think-he-would-agree-but-his-gaze-rested</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 13:35:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Janette Rallison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1141513-i-didn-t-think-he-would-agree-but-his-gaze-rested]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I didn't think he would agree, but his gaze rested on me and his expression softened. &quot;Yeah. Some things are worth the risk.&quot; 

It may have been the gentle tone of his voice, or the way his eyes held mine, but I felt he meant me, that he was saying I was worth the risk. And the sentence warmed me in a way I hadn't expected. 

&quot;You're into me,&quot; I said. &quot;I can tell.&quot;

He smiled and didn't deny it." -- Janette Rallison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1141524-you-re-not-a-jerk-you-re-someone-who-has-learned-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 13:44:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Janette Rallison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1141524-you-re-not-a-jerk-you-re-someone-who-has-learned-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're not a jerk. You're someone who has learned a lot over the last year. That's not a bad thing, is it? You don't have to be that other person. You can keep what you've learned.&quot;

He squeezed my hand. &quot;I'm keeping you. I know that much.&quot; He leaned toward me and brushed a strand of hair away from my face. &quot;Speaking of two-timing, I'll have to show you some of the messages you and I sent each other. They were down-right flirty.&quot; 

That made me smile." -- Janette Rallison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1141527-morals-are-meant-to-be-shared-he-held-me-away</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 13:47:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Janette Rallison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1141527-morals-are-meant-to-be-shared-he-held-me-away]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Morals are meant to be shared.&quot; He held me away for another moment, reading, then grinned and handed me the book. &quot;I like this one.&quot; 

...&quot;It's better to love people than wealth. I love Dad, Mom, Kendall, Sandra, Nick, baby Stetson, and especially Hudson. I wouldn't trade them for a mountain of gold.&quot; 

&quot;I love the word 'especially,'&quot; he said. &quot;And I love the person who wrote it.&quot; Then he bent over to kiss me." -- Janette Rallison]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
