<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1009999-fiona-zedde]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1009999-fiona-zedde" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2008 22:29:56 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36861-i-prefer-to-regard-a-dessert-as-i-would-imagine</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2008 22:29:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fiona add a quote by Graham Kerr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36861-i-prefer-to-regard-a-dessert-as-i-would-imagine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I prefer to regard a dessert as I would imagine the perfect woman: subtle, a little bittersweet, not blowsy and extrovert. Delicately made up, not highly rouged. Holding back, not exposing everything and, of course, with a flavor that lasts. " -- Graham Kerr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374135-the-first-time-someone-else-touched-me-with-the-intent</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 23:59:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fiona add a quote by Fiona Zedde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374135-the-first-time-someone-else-touched-me-with-the-intent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first time someone else touched me with the intent to pleasure, I fell in love.  Not with that person, but with the act itself.  Such intimacy and accord.  Even with the awkwardness of first time lovers there was a grace and purity, carnal and beautiful that I knew from that moment on I could never live without." -- Fiona Zedde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374138-just-because-i-ve-been-gone-from-this-country-for-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 00:05:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fiona add a quote by Fiona Zedde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374138-just-because-i-ve-been-gone-from-this-country-for-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just because I’ve been gone from this country for most of my life doesn’t mean I understand it any less.  When I was fifteen I left Jamaica.  I knew that I was a lesbian then and, because of what I looked like, I was an out lesbian.  It was hard for me.  It was hard for the thirteen years I was in England, for various reasons, and it’s going to be difficult here as well.  I don’t anticipate anything being easy.  But I’d rather suffer the chance of someone accosting me for being a dyke than suffer the emotional violence I’d do to myself if I wasn’t honest about who I am." -- Fiona Zedde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374139-across-from-her-hunter-devoured-her-meal-even-more-completely</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 00:07:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fiona add a quote by Fiona Zedde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374139-across-from-her-hunter-devoured-her-meal-even-more-completely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Across from her, Hunter devoured her meal even more completely than she had.  Sinclair watched her sink sharp teeth into the chicken bone, heard it snap, then the soft grunt of satisfaction.  She made soft sucking sounds then emptied her mouth of the tiny ground up remains on a corner of her dish.  Hunter ate with rabbit-like intensity, biting and sucking and spitting in an even rhythm until all that was left on the plate was a small brown and beige pile of ground bones.  She finally looked up and caught Sinclair staring." -- Fiona Zedde]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
