<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1010492-amy-s]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1010492-amy-s" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 19:03:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4660-there-is-something-about-words-in-expert-hands-manipulated-deftly</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 19:03:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Diane Setterfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4660-there-is-something-about-words-in-expert-hands-manipulated-deftly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is something about words. In expert hands, manipulated deftly, they take you prisoner. Wind themselves around your limbs like spider silk, and when you are so enthralled you cannot move, they pierce your skin, enter your blood, numb your thoughts.  Inside you they work their magic." -- Diane Setterfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429357-you-may-tell-a-tale-that-takes-up-residence-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 11:46:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429357-you-may-tell-a-tale-that-takes-up-residence-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may tell a tale that takes up residence in someone's soul, becomes their blood and self and purpose. That tale will move them and drive them and who knows that they might do because of it, because of your words. That is your role, your gift." -- Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21268-find-out-who-you-are-and-do-it-on-purpose</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2012 17:18:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Dolly Parton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21268-find-out-who-you-are-and-do-it-on-purpose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Find out who you are and do it on purpose." -- Dolly Parton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251569-i-have-learned-that-if-you-must-leave-a-place</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2012 18:24:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Beryl Markham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251569-i-have-learned-that-if-you-must-leave-a-place]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have learned that if you must leave a place that you have lived in and loved and where all your yesteryears are buried deep, leave it any way except a slow way, leave it the fastest way you can.  Never turn back and never believe that an hour you remember is a better hour because it is dead.  Passed years seem safe ones, vanquished ones, while the future lives in a cloud, formidable from a distance." -- Beryl Markham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79558-prayer-of-an-anonymous-abbess-lord-thou-knowest-better-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 14:32:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Margot Benary-Isbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79558-prayer-of-an-anonymous-abbess-lord-thou-knowest-better-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Prayer of an Anonymous Abbess:

Lord, thou knowest better than myself that I am growing older and will soon be old. Keep me from becoming too talkative, and especially from the unfortunate habit of thinking that I must say something on every subject and at every opportunity.

Release me from the idea that I must straighten out other peoples' affairs. With my immense treasure of experience and wisdom, it seems a pity not to let everybody partake of it. But thou knowest, Lord, that in the end I will need a few friends.

Keep me from the recital of endless details; give me wings to get to the point.

Grant me the patience to listen to the complaints of others; help me to endure them with charity. But seal my lips on my own aches and pains -- they increase with the increasing years and my inclination to recount them is also increasing.

I will not ask thee for improved memory, only for a little more humility and less self-assurance when my own memory doesn't agree with that of others. Teach me the glorious lesson that occasionally I may be wrong.

Keep me reasonably gentle. I do not have the ambition to become a saint -- it is so hard to live with some of them -- but a harsh old person is one of the devil's masterpieces.

Make me sympathetic without being sentimental, helpful but not bossy. Let me discover merits where I had not expected them, and talents in people whom I had not thought to possess any. And, Lord, give me the grace to tell them so.

Amen" -- Margot Benary-Isbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205230-don-t-fret-we-ll-just-have-to-find-something-else-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 19:57:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Clare B. Dunkle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205230-don-t-fret-we-ll-just-have-to-find-something-else-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't fret. We'll just have to find something else you're good at besides killing people." -- Clare B. Dunkle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263493-i-am-no-bird-and-no-net-ensnares-me-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 12:06:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263493-i-am-no-bird-and-no-net-ensnares-me-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am no bird; and no net ensnares me: I am a free human being with an independent will." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251760-that-man-makes-me-feel-like-i-have-my-bonnet</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 18:11:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251760-that-man-makes-me-feel-like-i-have-my-bonnet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That man makes me feel like I have my bonnet on backwards." -- Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371653-first-lord-no-tattoos-may-neither-chinese-symbol-for-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 19:55:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371653-first-lord-no-tattoos-may-neither-chinese-symbol-for-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First, Lord: No tattoos. May neither Chinese symbol for truth nor Winnie-the-Pooh holding the FSU logo stain her tender haunches.

May she be Beautiful but not Damaged, for it’s the Damage that draws the creepy soccer coach’s eye, not the Beauty.

When the Crystal Meth is offered, May she remember the parents who cut her grapes in half And stick with Beer.

Guide her, protect her

When crossing the street, stepping onto boats, swimming in the ocean, swimming in pools, walking near pools, standing on the subway platform, crossing 86th Street, stepping off of boats, using mall restrooms, getting on and off escalators, driving on country roads while arguing, leaning on large windows, walking in parking lots, riding Ferris wheels, roller-coasters, log flumes, or anything called “Hell Drop,” “Tower of Torture,” or “The Death Spiral Rock ‘N Zero G Roll featuring Aerosmith,” and standing on any kind of balcony ever, anywhere, at any age.

Lead her away from Acting but not all the way to Finance. Something where she can make her own hours but still feel intellectually fulfilled and get outside sometimes And not have to wear high heels.

What would that be, Lord? Architecture? Midwifery? Golf course design? I’m asking You, because if I knew, I’d be doing it, Youdammit.

May she play the Drums to the fiery rhythm of her Own Heart with the sinewy strength of her Own Arms, so she need Not Lie With Drummers.

Grant her a Rough Patch from twelve to seventeen. Let her draw horses and be interested in Barbies for much too long, For childhood is short – a Tiger Flower blooming Magenta for one day – And adulthood is long and dry-humping in cars will wait.

O Lord, break the Internet forever, That she may be spared the misspelled invective of her peers And the online marketing campaign for Rape Hostel V: Girls Just Wanna Get Stabbed.

And when she one day turns on me and calls me a Bitch in front of Hollister, Give me the strength, Lord, to yank her directly into a cab in front of her friends, For I will not have that Shit. I will not have it.

And should she choose to be a Mother one day, be my eyes, Lord, that I may see her, lying on a blanket on the floor at 4:50 A.M., all-at-once exhausted, bored, and in love with the little creature whose poop is leaking up its back.

“My mother did this for me once,” she will realize as she cleans feces off her baby’s neck. “My mother did this for me.” And the delayed gratitude will wash over her as it does each generation and she will make a Mental Note to call me. And she will forget. But I’ll know, because I peeped it with Your God eyes." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317-most-people-are-other-people-their-thoughts-are-someone-else-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 05:47:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317-most-people-are-other-people-their-thoughts-are-someone-else-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most people are other people. Their thoughts are someone else's opinions, their lives a mimicry, their passions a quotation." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43086-christmas-can-be-celebrated-in-the-school-room-with-pine</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 05:48:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Ronald Reagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43086-christmas-can-be-celebrated-in-the-school-room-with-pine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Christmas can be celebrated in the school room with pine trees, tinsel and reindeers, but there must be no mention of the man whose birthday is being celebrated. One wonders how a teacher would answer if a student asked why it was called Christmas." -- Ronald Reagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
