<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1010795-ptreick]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1010795-ptreick" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 09:29:40 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237736-don-t-fuck-with-an-english-major-they-keep-lots-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 09:29:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ptreick add a quote by P.C. Cast]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237736-don-t-fuck-with-an-english-major-they-keep-lots-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't fuck with an English major. They keep lots of useless crap trapped in their heads. Once in a while they let some of it out and it bites you square on the ass." -- P.C. Cast]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465988-sometimes-you-read-a-book-and-it-fills-you-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 21:55:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ptreick add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465988-sometimes-you-read-a-book-and-it-fills-you-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, you read a book and it fills you with this weird evangelical zeal, and you become convinced that the shattered world will never be put back together unless and until all living humans read the book." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287750-i-am-reduced-to-a-thing-that-wants-virginia-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 09:47:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ptreick add a quote by Vita Sackville-West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287750-i-am-reduced-to-a-thing-that-wants-virginia-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am reduced to a thing that wants Virginia. I composed a beautiful letter to you in the sleepless nightmare hours of the night, and it has all gone: I just miss you, in a quite simple desperate human way. You, with all your un-dumb letters, would never write so elementary a phrase as that; perhaps you wouldn’t even feel it. And yet I believe you’ll be sensible of a little gap. But you’d clothe it in so exquisite a phrase that it would lose a little of its reality. Whereas with me it is quite stark: I miss you even more than I could have believed; and I was prepared to miss you a good deal. So this letter is just really a squeal of pain. It is incredible how essential to me you have become. I suppose you are accustomed to people saying these things. Damn you, spoilt creature; I shan’t make you love me any the more by giving myself away like this —But oh my dear, I can’t be clever and stand-offish with you: I love you too much for that. Too truly. You have no idea how stand-offish I can be with people I don’t love. I have brought it to a fine art. But you have broken down my defences. And I don’t really resent it." -- Vita Sackville-West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497161-the-kind-of-life-i-want-is-to-be-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 09:52:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ptreick add a quote by Sara Zarr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497161-the-kind-of-life-i-want-is-to-be-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The kind of life I want is  to be a person who would get a personal note every day." -- Sara Zarr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17605-her-reputation-for-reading-a-great-deal-hung-about-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 22:27:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ptreick add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17605-her-reputation-for-reading-a-great-deal-hung-about-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her reputation for reading a great deal hung about her like the cloudy envelope of a goddess in an epic." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
