<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1010431-brett]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1010431-brett" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 23:58:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38720-may-the-footprints-we-leave-behind-show-that-we-ve-walked</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 23:58:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brett add a quote by American Indian Philosophy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38720-may-the-footprints-we-leave-behind-show-that-we-ve-walked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May the footprints we leave behind show that we've walked in kindness toward the earth and every living thing." -- American Indian Philosophy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 13:09:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brett add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I went to the woods because I wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and see if I could not learn what it had to teach, and not, when I came to die, discover that I had not lived. I did not wish to live what was not life, living is so dear; nor did I wish to practise resignation, unless it was quite necessary. I wanted to live deep and suck out all the marrow of life, to live so sturdily and Spartan-like as to put to rout all that was not life, to cut a broad swath and shave close, to drive life into a corner, and reduce it to its lowest terms." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11895-one-final-paragraph-of-advice-do-not-burn-yourselves-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 23:59:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brett add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11895-one-final-paragraph-of-advice-do-not-burn-yourselves-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One final paragraph of advice: do not burn yourselves out. Be as I am - a reluctant enthusiast....a part-time crusader, a half-hearted fanatic. Save the other half of yourselves and your lives for pleasure and adventure. It is not enough to fight for the land; it is even more important to enjoy it. While you can. While it’s still here. So get out there and hunt and fish and mess around with your friends, ramble out yonder and explore the forests, climb the mountains, bag the peaks, run the rivers, breathe deep of that yet sweet and lucid air, sit quietly for a while and contemplate the precious stillness, the lovely, mysterious, and awesome space. Enjoy yourselves, keep your brain in your head and your head firmly attached to the body, the body active and alive, and I promise you this much; I promise you this one sweet victory over our enemies, over those desk-bound men and women with their hearts in a safe deposit box, and their eyes hypnotized by desk calculators. I promise you this; You will outlive the bastards." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38723-peace-is-not-the-absence-of-conflict-but-the-ability</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 00:00:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brett add a quote by Dorothy Thomas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38723-peace-is-not-the-absence-of-conflict-but-the-ability]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Peace is not the absence of conflict, but the ability to cope with it." -- Dorothy Thomas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32945-when-one-tugs-at-a-single-thing-in-nature-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 16:23:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brett add a quote by John Muir]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32945-when-one-tugs-at-a-single-thing-in-nature-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When one tugs at a single thing in nature, he finds it attached to the rest of the world." -- John Muir]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1071-never-doubt-that-a-small-group-of-thoughtful-committed-citizens</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 00:01:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brett add a quote by Margaret Mead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1071-never-doubt-that-a-small-group-of-thoughtful-committed-citizens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never doubt that a small group of thoughtful, committed, citizens can change the world. Indeed, it is the only thing that ever has." -- Margaret Mead]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
