<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1011501-charles]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1011501-charles" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 10:43:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54224-delight-is-to-him----a-far-far-upward-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 10:43:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54224-delight-is-to-him----a-far-far-upward-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Delight is to him -- a far, far upward, and inward delight -- who against the proud gods and commodores of this earth, ever stands forth his own inexorable self." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54231-but-all-the-things-that-god-would-have-us-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 11:00:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54231-but-all-the-things-that-god-would-have-us-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But all the things that God would have us do are hard for us to do -- remember that -- and hence, he oftener commands us than endeavors to persuade.  And if we obey God, we must disobey ourselves; and it is in this disobeying ourselves, wherein the hardness of obeying God consists." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54235-it-s-the-great-mystery-of-human-life-that-old-grief</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 11:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54235-it-s-the-great-mystery-of-human-life-that-old-grief]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's the great mystery of human life that old grief passes gradually into quiet tender joy." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54239-remember-particularly-that-you-cannot-be-a-judge-of-anyone</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 11:14:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54239-remember-particularly-that-you-cannot-be-a-judge-of-anyone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember particularly that you cannot be a judge of anyone. For no one can judge a criminal until he recognizes that he is just such a criminal as the man standing before him, and that he perhaps is more than all men to blame for that crime. When he understands that, he will be able to be a judge. Though that sounds absurd, it is true.  If I had been righteous myself, perhaps there would have been no criminal standing before me. If you can take upon yourself the crime of the criminal your heart is judging, take it at once, suffer for him yourself, and let him go without reproach. And even if the law itself makes you his judge, act in the same spirit so far as possible, for he will go away and condemn himself more bitterly than you have done. If, after your kiss, he goes away untouched, mocking at you, do not let that be a stumbling-block to you. It shows his time has not yet come, but it will come in due course. And if it come not, no matter; if not he, then another in his place will understand and suffer, and judge and condemn himself, and the truth will be fulfilled. Believe that, believe it without doubt; for in that lies all the hope and faith of the saints." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54240-if-you-sin-yourself-and-grieve-even-unto-death-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 11:17:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54240-if-you-sin-yourself-and-grieve-even-unto-death-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you sin yourself and grieve even unto death for your sins or for your sudden sin, then rejoice for others, rejoice for the righteous man, rejoice that if you have sinned, he is righteous and has not sinned." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54241-if-the-evil-doing-of-men-moves-you-to-indignation-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 11:19:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54241-if-the-evil-doing-of-men-moves-you-to-indignation-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the evil-doing of men moves you to indignation and overwhelming distress, even to a desire for vengeance on the evil-doers, shun above all things that feeling. Go at once and seek suffering for yourself, as though you were yourself guilty of that wrong. Accept that suffering and bear it and your heart will find comfort, and you will understand that you too are guilty, for you might have been a light to the evil-doers, even as the one man sinless, and you were not a light to them. If you had been a light, you would have lightened the path for others too, and the evil-doer might perhaps have been saved by your light from his sin. And even though your light was shining, yet you see men were not saved by it, hold firm and doubt not the power of the heavenly light. Believe that if they were not saved, they will be saved hereafter. And if they are not saved hereafter, then their sons will be saved, for your light will not die even when you are dead. The righteous man departs, but his light remains." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54245-you-must-know-that-there-is-nothing-higher-and-stronger</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 11:29:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54245-you-must-know-that-there-is-nothing-higher-and-stronger]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must know that there is nothing higher and stronger and more wholesome and good for life in the future than some good memory, especially a memory of childhood, of home. People talk to you a great deal about your education, but some good, sacred memory, preserved from childhood, is perhaps the best education. If a man carries many such memories with him into life, he is safe to the end of his days, and if one has only one good memory left in one's heart, even that may sometime be the means of saving us. Perhaps we may even grow wicked later on, may be unable to refrain from a bad action, may laugh at men's tears and at those people who say as Kolya did just now, 'I want to suffer for all men,' and may even jeer spitefully at such people. But however bad we may become -- which God forbid -- [. . .] if we do become so will not dare to laugh inwardly at having been kind and good at this moment! What's more, perhaps, that one memory may keep him from great evil and he will reflect and say, 'Yes, I was good and brave and honest then!' Let him laugh to himself, that's no matter, a man often laughs at what's good and kind. That's only from thoughtlessness. But I assure you, boys, that as he laughs he will say at once in his heart, 'No, I do wrong to laugh, for that's not a thing to laugh at." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54251-he-did-not-know-that-the-new-life-would-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 11:35:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54251-he-did-not-know-that-the-new-life-would-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He did not know that the new life would not be given him for nothing, that he would have to pay dearly for it, that it would cost him great striving, great suffering.                                        
     But that is the beginning of a new story -- the story of the gradual renewal of a man, the story of his gradual regeneration, of his passing from one world into another, of his initiation into a new unknown life. That might be the subject of a new story, but our present story is ended." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54265-each-person-possesses-and-inviolability-founded-on-justice-that-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 12:19:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by John Rawls]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54265-each-person-possesses-and-inviolability-founded-on-justice-that-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each person possesses and inviolability founded on justice that even the welfare of society as a whole cannot override.  For this reason, justice denies that the loss of freedom for some is made right by a greater good shared by others.  It does not allow that the sacrifices imposed on a few are outweighed by the larger sum of advantages enjoyed by many.  Therefore  in a just society the liberties of equal citizenship are taken as settled; the rights secured by justice are not subject to political bargaining or to the calculus of social interests.  The only thing that permits us to acquiesce in an erroneous theory is the lack of a better one; analogously, an injustice is tolerable only when it is necessary to avoid an even greater injustice.  Being first virtues of human activities, truth and justice are uncompromising." -- John Rawls]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54270-theft-is-punished-by-your-law-o-lord-and-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 12:28:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by St. Augustine of Hippo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54270-theft-is-punished-by-your-law-o-lord-and-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Theft is punished by Your law, O Lord, and by the law written in men's hearts, which iniquity itself cannot blot out. For what thief will suffer a thief? Even a rich thief will not suffer him who is driven to it by want. Yet had I a desire to commit robbery, and did so, compelled neither by hunger, nor poverty through a distaste for well-doing, and a lustiness of iniquity. For I pilfered that of which I had already sufficient, and much better. Nor did I desire to enjoy what I pilfered, but the theft and sin itself. There was a pear-tree close to our vineyard, heavily laden with fruit, which was tempting neither for its colour nor its flavour. To shake and rob this some of us wanton young fellows went, late one night (having, according to our disgraceful habit, prolonged our games in the streets until then), and carried away great loads, not to eat ourselves, but to fling to the very swine, having only eaten some of them; and to do this pleased us all the more because it was not permitted.Behold my heart, O my God; behold my heart, which You had pity upon when in the bottomless pit. Behold, now, let my heart tell You what it was seeking there, that I should be gratuitously wanton, having no inducement to evil but the evil itself. It was foul, and I loved it. I loved to perish. I loved my own error— not that for which I erred, but the error itself. Base soul, falling from Your firmament to utter destruction— not seeking anything through the shame but the shame itself!" -- St. Augustine of Hippo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58652-let-no-one-bewail-his-poverty-for-the-universal-kingdom</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 12:47:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by St. John Chrysostom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58652-let-no-one-bewail-his-poverty-for-the-universal-kingdom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let no one bewail his poverty,
For the universal Kingdom has been revealed.
Let no one weep for his iniquities,
For pardon has shown forth from the grave.
Let no one fear death,
For the Saviour's death has set us free.
He that was held prisoner of it has annihilated it.

By descending into Hell, He made Hell captive.
He embittered it when it tasted of His flesh.
And Isaiah, foretelling this, did cry:
Hell, said he, was embittered
When it encountered Thee in the lower regions.

It was embittered, for it was abolished.
It was embittered, for it was mocked.
It was embittered, for it was slain.
It was embittered, for it was overthrown.
It was embittered, for it was fettered in chains.
It took a body, and met God face to face.
It took earth, and encountered Heaven.
It took that which was seen, and fell upon the unseen.

O Death, where is thy sting?
O Hell, where is thy victory? " -- St. John Chrysostom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13211-the-christian-ideal-has-not-been-tried-and-found-wanting</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 12:51:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13211-the-christian-ideal-has-not-been-tried-and-found-wanting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Christian ideal has not been tried and found wanting. It has been found difficult; and left untried." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246-the-unexamined-life-is-not-worth-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 12:52:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Socrates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246-the-unexamined-life-is-not-worth-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The unexamined life is not worth living." -- Socrates]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9939-the-price-good-men-pay-for-indifference-to-public-affairs</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 12:53:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Plato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9939-the-price-good-men-pay-for-indifference-to-public-affairs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The price good men pay for indifference to public affairs is to be ruled by evil men." -- Plato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21401-anybody-can-become-angry-that-is-easy-but-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 12:55:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Aristotle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21401-anybody-can-become-angry-that-is-easy-but-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anybody can become angry — that is easy, but to be angry with the right person and to the right degree and at the right time and for the right purpose, and in the right way — that is not within everybody's power and is not easy." -- Aristotle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14828-we-are-what-we-repeatedly-do-excellence-then-is-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 12:56:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by William Durant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14828-we-are-what-we-repeatedly-do-excellence-then-is-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence, then, is not an act, but a habit." -- William Durant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9177-he-asked-croesus-who-told-you-to-attack-my-land</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 12:58:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Herodotus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9177-he-asked-croesus-who-told-you-to-attack-my-land]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He asked, 'Croesus, who told you to attack my land and meet me as an enemy instead of a friend?'

The King replied, 'It was caused by your good fate and my bad fate. It was the fault of the Greek gods, who with their arrogance, encouraged me to march onto your lands. &lt;b&gt;Nobody is mad enough to choose war whilst there is peace. During times of peace, the sons bury their fathers, but in war it is the fathers who send their sons to the grave&lt;/b&gt;." -- Herodotus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39192-the-nation-that-will-insist-on-drawing-a-broad-line</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 13:00:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Thucydides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39192-the-nation-that-will-insist-on-drawing-a-broad-line]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The nation that will insist on drawing a broad line of demarcation between the fighting man and the thinking man is liable to find its fighting done by fools and its thinking done by cowards." -- Thucydides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76811-in-practice-we-always-base-our-preparations-against-an-enemy</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 13:04:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Thucydides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76811-in-practice-we-always-base-our-preparations-against-an-enemy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In practice we always base our preparations against an enemy on the assumption that his plans are good; indeed, it is right to rest our hopes not on a belief in his blunders, but on the soundness of our provisions.  Nor ought we to believe that there is much difference between man and man, but to think that the superiority lies with him who is reared in the severest school." -- Thucydides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27409-the-awful-thing-is-that-beauty-is-mysterious-as-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 14:28:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27409-the-awful-thing-is-that-beauty-is-mysterious-as-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The awful thing is that beauty is mysterious as well as terrible. God and the devil are fighting there and the battlefield is the heart of man." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22132-the-greatness-comes-not-when-things-go-always-good-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2008 14:14:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Richard Nixon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22132-the-greatness-comes-not-when-things-go-always-good-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greatness comes not when things go always good for you. But the greatness comes when you're really tested, when you take some knocks, some disappointments, when sadness comes. Because only if you've been in the deepest valley can you ever know how magnificent it is to be on the highest mountain." -- Richard Nixon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59866-power-is-the-ultimate-aphrodisiac</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2008 14:31:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Henry Kissinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59866-power-is-the-ultimate-aphrodisiac]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Power is the ultimate aphrodisiac." -- Henry Kissinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8215-political-language-is-designed-to-make-lies-sound-truthful-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 11:12:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8215-political-language-is-designed-to-make-lies-sound-truthful-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Political language is designed to make lies sound truthful and murder respectable, and to give an appearance of solidity to pure wind. " -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13502-people-sleep-peaceably-in-their-beds-at-night-only-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 11:15:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13502-people-sleep-peaceably-in-their-beds-at-night-only-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People sleep peaceably in their beds at night only because rough men stand ready to do violence on their behalf." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16068-a-scrupulous-writer-in-every-sentence-that-he-writes-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 11:16:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16068-a-scrupulous-writer-in-every-sentence-that-he-writes-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A scrupulous writer, in every sentence that he writes, will ask himself at least four questions, thus: 1. What am I trying to say? 2. What words will express it? 3. What image or idiom will make it clearer? 4. Is this image fresh enough to have an effect?" -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1404-if-you-don-t-have-time-to-read-you-don-t-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 11:18:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1404-if-you-don-t-have-time-to-read-you-don-t-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you don't have time to read, you don't have the time (or the tools) to write. Simple as that." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8080-the-road-to-hell-is-paved-with-adverbs</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 11:18:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8080-the-road-to-hell-is-paved-with-adverbs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The road to hell is paved with adverbs." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8830-fiction-is-the-truth-inside-the-lie</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 11:19:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8830-fiction-is-the-truth-inside-the-lie]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fiction is the truth inside the lie." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6606-running-a-close-second-as-a-writing-lesson-was-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 11:19:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6606-running-a-close-second-as-a-writing-lesson-was-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Running a close second [as a writing lesson] was the realization that stopping a piece of work just because it's hard, either emotionally or imaginatively, is a bad idea. Sometimes you have to go on when you don't feel like it, and sometimes you're doing good work when it feels like all you're managing is to shovel shit from a sitting position." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17240-i-recognize-terror-as-the-finest-emotion-and-so-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 11:20:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17240-i-recognize-terror-as-the-finest-emotion-and-so-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I recognize terror as the finest emotion and so I will try to terrorize the reader. But if I find that I cannot terrify, I will try to horrify, and if I find that I cannot horrify, I'll go for the gross-out. I'm not proud. " -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
