<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1011183-robert]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1011183-robert" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 06:20:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54-don-t-walk-behind-me-i-may-not-lead-don-t-walk</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 06:20:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54-don-t-walk-behind-me-i-may-not-lead-don-t-walk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't walk behind me; I may not lead. Don't walk in front of me; I may not follow. Just walk beside me and be my friend." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/819427-the-revelation-of-sonmi-451-to-be-is-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 05:18:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/819427-the-revelation-of-sonmi-451-to-be-is-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Revelation of Sonmi 451 To be is to be perceived, and so to know thyself is only possible through the eyes of the other. The nature of our immortal lives is in the consequences of our words and deeds, that go on and are pushing themselves throughout all time. 

- Our lives are not our own. From womb to tomb, we are bound to others, past and present, and by each crime and every kindness, we birth our future." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16250-and-when-we-speak-we-are-afraid-our-words-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 04:41:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16250-and-when-we-speak-we-are-afraid-our-words-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["and when we speak we are afraid
our words will not be heard
nor welcomed
but when we are silent
we are still afraid
So it is better to speak
remembering
we were never meant to survive" -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2-i-must-not-fear-fear-is-the-mind-killer-fear-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 04:44:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Frank Herbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2-i-must-not-fear-fear-is-the-mind-killer-fear-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I must not fear. Fear is the mind-killer. Fear is the little-death that brings total obliteration. I will face my fear. I will permit it to pass over me and through me. And when it has gone past I will turn the inner eye to see its path. Where the fear has gone there will be nothing. Only I will remain." -- Frank Herbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48237-in-order-to-rise-from-its-own-ashes-a-phoenix</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 04:45:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Octavia Butler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48237-in-order-to-rise-from-its-own-ashes-a-phoenix]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In order to rise
From its own ashes
A phoenix
First
Must
Burn." -- Octavia Butler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 05:01:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 05:01:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that no matter what happens, or how bad it seems today, life does go on, and it will be better tomorrow. I've learned that you can tell a lot about a person by the way he/she handles these three things: a rainy day, lost luggage, and tangled Christmas tree lights. I've learned that regardless of your relationship with your parents, you'll miss them when they're gone from your life. I've learned that making a &quot;living&quot; is not the same thing as making a &quot;life.&quot; I've learned that life sometimes gives you a second chance. I've learned that you shouldn't go through life with a catcher's mitt on both hands; you need to be able to throw something back. I've learned that whenever I decide something with an open heart, I usually make the right decision. I've learned that even when I have pains, I don't have to be one. I've learned that every day you should reach out and touch someone. People love a warm hug, or just a friendly pat on the back. I've learned that I still have a lot to learn. I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
