<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1011694-sarah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1011694-sarah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 16:42:34 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/624-if-i-read-a-book-and-it-makes-my-whole</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 16:42:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Emily Dickinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/624-if-i-read-a-book-and-it-makes-my-whole]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I read a book and it makes my whole body so cold no fire can warm me, I know that is poetry. If I feel physically as if the top of my head were taken off, I know that is poetry. These are the only ways I know it. Is there any other way?" -- Emily Dickinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1894-this-is-not-a-novel-to-be-tossed-aside-lightly</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 15:10:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Dorothy Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1894-this-is-not-a-novel-to-be-tossed-aside-lightly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is not a novel to be tossed aside lightly. It should be thrown with great force." -- Dorothy Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27801-my-gripe-is-not-with-lovers-of-the-truth-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 15:46:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Diane Setterfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27801-my-gripe-is-not-with-lovers-of-the-truth-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My gripe is not with lovers of the truth but with truth herself.  What succor, what consolation is there in truth, compared to a story?  What good is truth, at midnight, in the dark, when the wind is roaring like a bear in the chimney?  When the lightning strikes shadows on the bedroom wall and the rain taps at the window with its long fingernails?  No.  When fear and cold make a statue of you in your bed, don't expect hard-boned and fleshless truth to come running to your aid.  What you need are the plump comforts of a story.  The soothing, rocking safety of a lie." -- Diane Setterfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70664-there-are-all-kinds-of-silences-and-each-of-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 15:01:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Beryl Markham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70664-there-are-all-kinds-of-silences-and-each-of-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are all kinds of silences and each of them means a different thing. There is the silence that comes with morning in a forest, and this is different from the silence of a sleeping city. There is silence after a rainstorm, and before a rainstorm, and these are not the same. There is the silence of emptiness, the silence of fear, the silence of doubt. There is a certain silence that can emanate from a lifeless object as from a chair lately used, or from a piano with old dust upon its keys, or from anything that has answered to the need of a man, for pleasure or for work. This kind of silence can speak. Its voice may be melancholy, but it is not always so; for the chair may have been left by a laughing child or the last notes of the piano may have been raucous and gay. Whatever the mood or the circumstance, the essence of its quality may linger in the silence that follows. It is a soundless echo." -- Beryl Markham]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
