<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1011265-amber]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1011265-amber" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 12:34:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16398-nothing-is-more-practical-than-finding-god-that-is-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 12:34:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber  add a quote by Pedro Arrupe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16398-nothing-is-more-practical-than-finding-god-that-is-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing is more practical than finding God, 
That is, than falling in a love in a quite absolute, final way. 
What you are in love with, what seizes your imagination will affect everything. 
It will decide what will get you out of bed in the mornings, 
What you will do with your evenings, 
How you spend your weekends, 
What you read, 
Who you know, 
What breaks your heart, 
And what amazes you with joy and gratitude. 
Fall in love, stay in love, and it will decide everything." -- Pedro Arrupe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 12:35:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber  add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We accept the love we think we deserve." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/779-love-doesn-t-just-sit-there-like-a-stone-it-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 12:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber  add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/779-love-doesn-t-just-sit-there-like-a-stone-it-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love doesn't just sit there, like a stone, it has to be made, like bread; remade all the time, made new." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/753-i-like-not-only-to-be-loved-but-also-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 12:38:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber  add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/753-i-like-not-only-to-be-loved-but-also-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like not only to be loved, but also to be told that I am loved. I am not sure that you are of the same mind. But the realm of silence is large enough beyond the grave. This is the world of light and speech, and I shall take leave to tell you that you are very dear." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8238-he-dug-so-deeply-into-her-sentiments-that-in-search</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 15:35:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber  add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8238-he-dug-so-deeply-into-her-sentiments-that-in-search]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He dug so deeply into her sentiments that in search of interest he found love, because by trying to make her love him he ended up falling in love with her. Petra Cotes, for her part, loved him more and more as she felt his love increasing, and that was how in the ripeness of autumn she began to believe once more in the youthful superstition that poverty was the servitude of love. Both looked back then on the wild revelry, the gaudy wealth, and the unbridled fornication as an annoyance and they lamented that it had cost them so much of their lives to find the paradise of shared solitude. Madly in love after so many years of sterile complicity, they enjoyed the miracle of living each other as much at the table as in bed, and they grew to be so happy that even when they were two worn-out people they kept on blooming like little children and playing together like dogs." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
