<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1012284-daniel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1012284-daniel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 11:34:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36995-do-you-believe-that-what-you-believe-is-really-real</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 11:34:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Del Tackett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36995-do-you-believe-that-what-you-believe-is-really-real]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you believe that what you believe is really real?" -- Del Tackett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 20:14:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37377-the-busybody-banned-as-sexist-demeaning-to-older-women-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 17:52:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Denise Duhamel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37377-the-busybody-banned-as-sexist-demeaning-to-older-women-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The busybody (banned as sexist, demeaning to older women) who lives next door called my daughter a tomboy (banned as sexist) when she climbed the jungle (banned; replaced with &quot;rain forest&quot;) gym. Then she had the nerve to call her an egghead and a bookworm (both banned as offensive; replaced with &quot;intellectual&quot;) because she read fairy (banned because suggests homosexuality; replace with &quot;elf&quot;) tales.

I'm tired of the Language Police turning a deaf ear (banned as handicapism) to my complaints. I'm no Pollyanna (banned as sexist) and will not accept any lame (banned as offensive; replace with &quot;walks with a cane&quot;) excuses at this time.

If Alanis Morrissette can play God (banned) in &lt;i&gt;Dogma&lt;/i&gt; (banned as ethnocentric; replace with &quot;Doctrine&quot; or &quot;Belief&quot;), why can't my daughter play stickball (banned as regional or ethnic bias) on boy's night out (banned as sexist)? Why can't she build a snowman (banned, replace with &quot;snow person&quot;) without that fanatic (banned as ethnocentric; replace with &quot;believer,&quot; &quot;follower,&quot; or &quot;adherent&quot;) next door telling her she's going to hell (banned; replaced with &quot;heck&quot; or &quot;darn&quot;)?

Do you really think this is what the Founding Fathers (banned as sexist; replace with &quot;the Founders&quot; or &quot;the Framers&quot;) had in mind? That we can't even enjoy our Devil (banned)-ed ham sandwiches in peace? I say put a stop to this cult (banned as ethnocentric) of PC old wives' tales (banned as sexist; replace with &quot;folk wisdom&quot;) and extremist (banned as ethnocentric; replace with &quot;believer,&quot; &quot;follower,&quot; or &quot;adherent&quot;) conservative duffers (banned as demeaning to older men).

As an heiress (banned as sexist; replace with &quot;heir&quot;) to the first amendment, I feel that only a heretic (use with caution when comparing religions) would try to stop American vernacular from flourishing in all its inspirational (banned as patronizing when referring to a person with disabilities) splendor." -- Denise Duhamel]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
