<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1013083-laura-walker]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1013083-laura-walker" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 15:21:34 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1392-when-we-honestly-ask-ourselves-which-person-in-our-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 15:21:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Henri Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1392-when-we-honestly-ask-ourselves-which-person-in-our-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we honestly ask ourselves which person in our lives mean the most to us, we often find that it is those who, instead of giving advice, solutions, or cures, have chosen rather to share our pain and touch our wounds with a warm and tender hand. The friend who can be silent with us in a moment of despair or confusion, who can stay with us in an hour of grief and bereavement, who can tolerate not knowing, not curing, not healing and face with us the reality of our powerlessness, that is a friend who cares." -- Henri Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8215-political-language-is-designed-to-make-lies-sound-truthful-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 15:35:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8215-political-language-is-designed-to-make-lies-sound-truthful-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Political language is designed to make lies sound truthful and murder respectable, and to give an appearance of solidity to pure wind. " -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22664-slavery-is-such-an-atrocious-debasement-of-human-nature-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 15:37:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22664-slavery-is-such-an-atrocious-debasement-of-human-nature-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Slavery is such an atrocious debasement of human nature, that its very extirpation, if not performed with solicitous care, may sometimes open a source of serious evils. The unhappy man who has been treated as a brute animal, too frequently sinks beneath the common standard of the human species. The galling chains, that bind his body, do also fetter his intellectual faculties, and impair the social affections of his heart… To instruct, to advise, to qualify those, who have been restored to freedom, for the exercise and enjoyment of civil liberty… and to procure for their children an education calculated for their future situation in life; these are the great outlines of the annexed plan, which we have adopted.

[&lt;i&gt;For the Pennsylvania Society for Promoting the Abolition of Slavery, 1789&lt;/i&gt;]" -- Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6403-they-who-can-give-up-essential-liberty-to-obtain-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 15:37:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6403-they-who-can-give-up-essential-liberty-to-obtain-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They who can give up essential liberty to obtain a little temporary safety deserve neither liberty nor safety." -- Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
