<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1013458-stacy-martin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1013458-stacy-martin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 14:23:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1203984-let-go-of-the-battle-breathe-quietly-and-let-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 14:23:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Jack Kornfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1203984-let-go-of-the-battle-breathe-quietly-and-let-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let go of the battle. Breathe quietly and let it be. Let your body relax and your heart soften. Open to whatever you experience without fighting." -- Jack Kornfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1024020-and-it-killed-me-because-i-could-never-forget-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 14:25:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by A.L. Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1024020-and-it-killed-me-because-i-could-never-forget-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And it killed me because i could never forget him. Couldn't because he'd permanently etched himself to me, left a part of himself forever within me. For so many year I'd loved him, but when he'd gone this time, he'd taken a part of me captive too, a piece that could never be retrieved because it would always belong to him." -- A.L. Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66625-when-i-get-lonely-these-days-i-think-so-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 14:27:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66625-when-i-get-lonely-these-days-i-think-so-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I get lonely these days, I think: So BE lonely, Liz. Learn your way around loneliness. Make a map of it. Sit with it, for once in your life. Welcome to the human experience. But never again use another person's body or emotions as a scratching post for your own unfulfilled yearnings." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331352-instructions-for-freedom-1-life-s-metaphors-are-god-s-instructions-2</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 14:29:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331352-instructions-for-freedom-1-life-s-metaphors-are-god-s-instructions-2]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Instructions for freedom&quot;:
1. Life's metaphors are God's instructions.
2. You have just climbed up and above the roof, there is nothing between you and the Infinite; now, let go.
3. The day is ending, it's time for something that was beautiful to turn into something else that is beautiful. Now, let go.
4. Your wish for resolution was a prayer. You are being here is God's response, let go and watch the stars came out, in the inside and in the outside.
5. With all your heart ask for Grace and let go. 
6. With all your heart forgive him, forgive yourself and let him go.
7. Let your intention be freedom from useless suffering then, let go.
8. Watch the heat of day pass into the cold night, let go.
9. When the Karma of a relationship is done, only Love remains. It's safe, let go.
10. When the past has past from you at last, let go.. then, climb down and begin the rest of your life with great joy." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456196-i-m-not-laughing-i-was-actually-crying-and-please-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 14:31:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert in Eat, Pray, Love.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456196-i-m-not-laughing-i-was-actually-crying-and-please-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’m not laughing.” I was actually crying. “And please don’t laugh at me now, but I think the reason it’s so hard for me to get over this guy is because I seriously believed David was my soul mate. ”He probably was. Your problem is you don’t understand what that word means. People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that’s what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that’s holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life. A true soul mate is probably the most important person you’ll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake. But to live with a soul mate forever? Nah. Too painful. Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then they leave. And thank God for it. Your problem is, you just can’t let this one go. It’s over, Groceries. David’s purpose was to shake you up, drive you out of your marriage that you needed to leave, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light could get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you had to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master and beat it. That was his job, and he did great, but now it’s over. Problem is, you can’t accept that his relationship had a real short shelf life. You’re like a dog at the dump, baby – you’re just lickin’ at the empty tin can, trying to get more nutrition out of it. And if you’re not careful, that can’s gonna get stuck on your snout forever and make your life miserable. So drop it.“But I love him.”
“So love him.” “But I miss him.” “So miss him. Send him some love and light every time you think about him, then drop it. You’re just afraid to let go of the last bits of David because then you’ll be really alone, and Liz Gilbert is scared to death of what will happen if she’s really alone. But here’s what you gotta understand, Groceries. If you clear out all that space in your mind that you’re using right now to obsess about this guy, you’ll have a vacuum there, an open spot – a doorway. And guess what the universe will do with the doorway? It will rush in – God will rush in – and fill you with more love than you ever dreamed. So stop using David to block that door. Let it go." -- Elizabeth Gilbert in Eat, Pray, Love.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268923-but-at-some-point-you-have-to-make-peace-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 14:35:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268923-but-at-some-point-you-have-to-make-peace-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But at some point you have to make peace with what you were given and if God wanted me to be a shy girl with think, dark hair, He would have made me that way, but He didn't.  Useful, then, might be to accept how I was made and embody myself fully therein." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268211-liz-you-must-be-very-polite-with-yourself-when-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 14:36:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268211-liz-you-must-be-very-polite-with-yourself-when-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Liz, you must be very polite with yourself when you are learning something new." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/615063-listen-to-me-someday-you-re-gonna-look-back-on-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 14:36:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/615063-listen-to-me-someday-you-re-gonna-look-back-on-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen to me. Someday you're gonna look back on this moment of your life as such a sweet time of grieving. You'll see that you were in mourning and your heart was broken, but your life was changing." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317192-you-take-whatever-works-from-wherever-you-can-find-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 14:37:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317192-you-take-whatever-works-from-wherever-you-can-find-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You take whatever works from wherever you can find it, and you keep moving toward the light." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460359-big-deal-so-you-fell-in-love-with-someone-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:21:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460359-big-deal-so-you-fell-in-love-with-someone-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Big deal. So you fell in love with someone. Don’t you see what happened? This guy touched a place in your heart deeper than you thought you were capable of reaching, I mean you got zapped, kiddo. But that love you felt, that’s just the beginning. You just got a taste of love. That’s just limited little rinky-dink mortal love. Wait till you see how much more deeply you can love than that. Heck, Groceries—you have the capacity to someday love the whole world. It’s your destiny. Don’t laugh." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215313-in-venice-in-the-middle-ages-there-was-once-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:23:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215313-in-venice-in-the-middle-ages-there-was-once-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In Venice in the Middle Ages there was once a profession for a man called a codega--a fellow you hired to walk in front of you at night with a lit lantern, showing you the way, scaring off thieves and demons, bringing you confidence and protection through the dark streets. " -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/552902-and-love-is-always-complicated-but-still-humans-most-try</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:25:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/552902-and-love-is-always-complicated-but-still-humans-most-try]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And love is always complicated. But still humans most try to love each other, darling. We must get out hearts broken sometimes. This is a good sign, having a broken heart. It means we have tried for something." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460340-even-in-the-worst-tragedies-and-crisis-there-s-no-reason</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:27:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460340-even-in-the-worst-tragedies-and-crisis-there-s-no-reason]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even in the worst tragedies and crisis, there’s no reason to add to everyone’s misery by looking miserable yourself." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460349-when-the-past-has-passed-from-you-at-last-let</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:28:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460349-when-the-past-has-passed-from-you-at-last-let]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the past has passed from you at last, let go. Then climb down and begin the rest of your life. With great joy." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/536473-whenever-i-get-lonely-these-days-i-think-so-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:29:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/536473-whenever-i-get-lonely-these-days-i-think-so-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever I get lonely these days I think: So be lonely, Liz. Learn your way around loneliness. Make a map of it. Sit with it, for once in your life. Welcome to the human experience. But never again use another person's body or emotions as scratching post for your own unfulfilled yearnings." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/671990-every-try-to-take-a-toy-away-from-a-toddler</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:36:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/671990-every-try-to-take-a-toy-away-from-a-toddler]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every try to take a toy away from a toddler? They don't like that, do they? They start kicking and screaming. Best way to take a toy away from a toddler is distract the kid, give him something else to play with. Instead of trying to forcefully take thoughts out of your mind, give your mind something better to play with." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980832-in-the-end-i-ve-come-to-believe-in-something-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:42:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980832-in-the-end-i-ve-come-to-believe-in-something-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the end, I’ve come to believe in something I call the ‘physics of the quest’, a force in nature governed by the laws of gravity. The rules of quest physics goes something like this: If you’re brave enough to leave behind everything familiar and comforting and set out on a truth seeking journey either internally or externally, and if you are truly willing to regard everything that happens to you on that journey as a clue and if you accept everyone you meet along the way as a teacher and if you are prepared most of all to face and forgive some of the most difficult realities about yourself, then the truth will not be witheld from you" -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182896-i-no-longer-believed-in-the-idea-of-soul-mates</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:43:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Lisa Kleypas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182896-i-no-longer-believed-in-the-idea-of-soul-mates]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I no longer believed in the idea of soul mates, or love at first sight.  But I was beginning to believe that a very few times in your life, if you were lucky, you might meet someone who was exactly right for you.  Not because he was perfect, or because you were, but because your combined flaws were arranged in a way that allowed two separate beings to hinge together." -- Lisa Kleypas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227010-to-be-fully-seen-by-somebody-then-and-be-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:46:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227010-to-be-fully-seen-by-somebody-then-and-be-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be fully seen by somebody, then, and be loved anyhow - this is a human offering that can border on miraculous." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/319244-how-would-your-life-be-different-if-you-walked-away-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:49:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Steve Maraboli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/319244-how-would-your-life-be-different-if-you-walked-away-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How would your life be different if…You walked away from gossip and verbal defamation? Let today be the day…You speak only the good you know of other people and encourage others to do the same." -- Steve Maraboli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104126-there-is-greatness-in-doing-something-you-hate-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:50:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Shmuley Boteach]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104126-there-is-greatness-in-doing-something-you-hate-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is greatness in doing something you hate for the sake of someone you love." -- Shmuley Boteach]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177007-there-are-three-things-all-wise-men-fear-the-sea</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:52:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177007-there-are-three-things-all-wise-men-fear-the-sea]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are three things all wise men fear: the sea in storm, a night with no moon, and the anger of a gentle man." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350254-it-had-flaws-but-what-does-that-matter-when-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:53:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350254-it-had-flaws-but-what-does-that-matter-when-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It had flaws, but what does that matter when it comes to matters of the heart? We love what we love. Reason does not enter into it. In many ways, unwise love is the truest love. Anyone can love a thing &lt;i&gt;because&lt;/i&gt;. That's as easy as putting a penny in your pocket. But to love something &lt;i&gt;despite&lt;/i&gt;. To know the flaws and love them too. That is rare and pure and perfect." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161323-my-parents-danced-together-her-head-on-his-chest-both</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:54:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161323-my-parents-danced-together-her-head-on-his-chest-both]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My parents danced together, her head on his chest. Both had their eyes closed. They seemed so perfectly content. If you can find someone like that, someone who you can hold and close your eyes to the world with, then you're lucky. Even if it only lasts for a minute or a day. The image of them gently swaying to the music is how I picture love in my mind even after all these years." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/354460-i-ve-waited-a-long-time-to-show-these-flowers-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:54:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/354460-i-ve-waited-a-long-time-to-show-these-flowers-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've waited a long time to show these flowers how pretty you are." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381682-i-have-an-apple-that-thinks-its-a-pear-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:55:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381682-i-have-an-apple-that-thinks-its-a-pear-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have an apple that thinks its a pear. And a bun that thinks it’s a cat. And a lettuce that thinks its a lettuce.&quot;
&quot;It’s a clever lettuce, then.&quot;
&quot;Hardly,&quot; she said with a delicate snort. &quot;Why would anything clever think it’s a lettuce?&quot;
&quot;Even if it is a lettuce?&quot; I asked.
&quot;Especially then,&quot; she said. &quot;Bad enough to be a lettuce. How awful to think you are a lettuce too." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278876-i-have-known-her-longer-my-smile-said-true-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:57:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278876-i-have-known-her-longer-my-smile-said-true-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have known her longer, my smile said.  True, you have been inside the circle of her arms, tasted her mouth, felt the warmth of her, and that is something I have never had.  But there is a part of her that is only for me.  You cannot touch it, no matter how hard you might try.  And after she has left you I will still be here, making her laugh.  My light shining in her.  I will still be here long after she has forgotten your name." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381331-all-the-truth-in-the-world-is-held-in-stories</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:58:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381331-all-the-truth-in-the-world-is-held-in-stories]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All the truth in the world is held in stories." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/342954-you-lack-the-requisite-spine-and-testicular-fortitude-to-study</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:58:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/342954-you-lack-the-requisite-spine-and-testicular-fortitude-to-study]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You lack the requisite spine and testicular fortitude to study under me." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157144-its-like-he-knows-he-s-better-than-you-but-doesn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:59:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157144-its-like-he-knows-he-s-better-than-you-but-doesn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Its like he knows he's better than you, but doesn't look down on you for it because he knows it's not your fault." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
