<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1014043-noriko-nakada]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1014043-noriko-nakada" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 06:32:47 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341090-her-father-had-taught-her-about-hands-about-a-dog-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 06:32:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Noriko add a quote by Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341090-her-father-had-taught-her-about-hands-about-a-dog-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her father had taught her about hands. About a dog's paws. Whenever her father was alone with a dog in a house he would lean over and smell the skin at the base of its paw. This, he would say, as if coming away from a brandy snifter, is the greatest smell in the world! A bouquet! Great rumours of travel! She would pretend disgust, but the dog's paw was a wonder: the smell of it never suggested dirt. It's a cathedral! her father had said, so-and-so's garden, that field of grasses, a walk through cyclamen--a concentration of hints of all the paths the animal had taken during the day." -- Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360751-truth-disappears-with-history-and-gossip-tells-us-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 06:35:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Noriko add a quote by Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360751-truth-disappears-with-history-and-gossip-tells-us-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Truth disappears with history and gossip tells us in the end nothing of personal relationships. There are stories of elopements, unrequited love, family feuds, and exhausting vendettas, which everyone was drawn into, had to be involved with. But nothing is said of the closeness between two people: how they grew in the shade of each other's presence. No one speaks of that exchange of gift and character - the way a person took on and recognized in himself he smile of a lover. Individuals are seen only in the context of these swirling social tides. It was almost impossible for a couple to do anything without rumour leaving their shoulders like a flock of messenger pigeons.

Where is the intimate and truthful in all this? Teenager and Uncle. Husband and lover. A lost father in his solace. And why do I want to know of this privacy? After the cups of tea, coffee, public conversations...I want to sit down with someone and talk with utter directness, want to talk to all the lost history like that deserving lover." -- Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/505363-as-the-lights-fade-to-a-distant-glow-i-look</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 08:40:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Noriko add a quote by Noriko Nakada]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/505363-as-the-lights-fade-to-a-distant-glow-i-look]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As the lights fade to a distant glow, I look back toward the city and imagine, somewhere in all of those lives, a little girl who is a lot like me. Maybe she rides in a car thinking about someone living far away from these lights and people. Even though our lives are separated by so much I wonder if she imagines the world through eyes like mine." -- Noriko Nakada]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
