<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/101412-whitney]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/101412-whitney" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 08:20:17 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121051-everything-had-changed-suddenly--the-tone-the-moral-climate-you-didn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 08:20:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by Boris Pasternak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121051-everything-had-changed-suddenly--the-tone-the-moral-climate-you-didn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything had changed suddenly--the tone, the moral climate; you didn't know what to think, whom to listen to. As if all your life you had been led by the hand like a small child and suddenly you were on your own, you had to learn to walk by yourself. There was no one around, neither family nor people whose judgment you respected. At such a time you felt the need of committing yourself to something absolute--life or truth or beauty--of being ruled by it in place of the man-made rules that had been discarded. You needed to surrender to some such ultimate purpose more fully, more unreservedly than you had ever done in the old familiar, peaceful days, in the old life that was now abolished and gone for good." -- Boris Pasternak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9417-we-sleep-to-time-s-hurdy-gurdy-we-wake-if-ever-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 08:22:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9417-we-sleep-to-time-s-hurdy-gurdy-we-wake-if-ever-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We sleep to time's hurdy-gurdy; we wake, if ever we wake, to the silence of God. And then, when we wake to the deep shores of time uncreated, then when the dazzling dark breaks over the far slopes of time, then it's time to toss things, like our reason, and our will; then it's time to break our necks for home.
There are no events but thoughts and the heart's hard turning, the heart's slow learning where to love and whom. The rest is merely gossip, and tales for other times." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
