<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/101408-heather-steele]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/101408-heather-steele" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 05:16:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 05:16:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that everything happens for a reason. People change so that you can learn to let go, things go wrong so that you appreciate them when they're right, you believe lies so you eventually learn to trust no one but yourself, and sometimes good things fall apart so better things can fall together." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 05:21:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13959-do-you-know-how-long-a-year-takes-when-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 06:30:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13959-do-you-know-how-long-a-year-takes-when-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you know how long a year takes when it's going away?' Dunbar repeated to Clevinger. 'This long.' He snapped his fingers. 'A second ago you were stepping into college with your lungs full of fresh air. Today you're an old man.'

'Old?' asked Clevinger with surprise. 'What are you talking about?'

'Old.'

'I'm not old.'

'You're inches away from death every time you go on a mission. How much older can you be at your age? A half minute before that you were stepping into high school, and an unhooked brassiere was as close as you ever hoped to get to Paradise. Only a fifth of a second before that you were a small kid with a ten-week summer vacation that lasted a hundred thousand years and still ended too soon. Zip! They go rocketing by so fast. How the hell else are you ever going to slow down?' Dunbar was almost angry when he finished.

'Well, maybe it is true,' Clevinger conceded unwillingly in a subdued tone. 'Maybe a long life does have to be filled with many unpleasant conditions if it's to seem long. But in that event, who wants one?'

'I do,' Dunbar told him.

'Why?' Clevinger asked.

'What else is there?" -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16831-we-all-die-the-goal-isn-t-to-live-forever-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 06:35:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16831-we-all-die-the-goal-isn-t-to-live-forever-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all die. The goal isn't to live forever, the goal is to create something that will." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16072-the-unreal-is-more-powerful-than-the-real-because-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 06:36:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16072-the-unreal-is-more-powerful-than-the-real-because-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The unreal is more powerful than the real. Because nothing is as perfect as you can imagine it. Because its only intangible ideas, concepts, beliefs, fantasies that last. Stone crumbles. Wood rots. People, well, they die. But things as fragile as a thought, a dream, a legend, they can go on and on. If you can change the way people think. The way they see themselves. The way they see the world. You can change the way people live their lives. That's the only lasting thing you can create." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40805-in-a-world-where-billions-believe-their-deity-conceived-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 06:40:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40805-in-a-world-where-billions-believe-their-deity-conceived-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a world where billions believe their deity conceived a mortal child with a virgin human, it's stunning how little imagination most people display." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17967-i-want-out-of-the-labels-i-don-t-want-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 06:40:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17967-i-want-out-of-the-labels-i-don-t-want-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want out of the labels. I don't want my whole life crammed into a single word. A story. I want to find something else, unknowable, some place to be that's not on the map. A real adventure.' 
A spinx. A mystery. A blank. Unknown. Undefined." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33324-without-access-to-true-chaos-we-ll-never-have-true-peace</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 06:46:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33324-without-access-to-true-chaos-we-ll-never-have-true-peace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without access to true chaos, we'll never have true peace. Unless everything can get worse, it won't get any better." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66252-the-most-unfair-thing-about-life-is-the-way-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 06:49:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by george carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66252-the-most-unfair-thing-about-life-is-the-way-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most unfair thing about life is the way it ends. I mean, life is tough. It takes up a lot of your time. What do you get at the end of it? A Death! What’s that, a bonus? I think the life cycle is all backwards. You should die first, get it out of the way. Then you live in an old age home. You get kicked out when you’re too young, you get a gold watch, you go to work. You work forty years until you’re young enough to enjoy your retirement. You do drugs, alcohol, you party, you get ready for high school. You go to grade school, you become a kid, you play, you have no responsibilities, you become a little baby, you go back into the womb, you spend your last nine months floating …and you finish off as an orgasm." -- george carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52852-here-s-all-you-have-to-know-about-men-and-women</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 06:59:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52852-here-s-all-you-have-to-know-about-men-and-women]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's all you have to know about men and women: women are crazy, men are stupid. And the main reason women are crazy is that men are stupid." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3550-life-is-an-awful-ugly-place-to-not-have-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 08:59:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3550-life-is-an-awful-ugly-place-to-not-have-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is an awful, ugly place to not have a best friend." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37490-no-relationship-is-perfect-ever-there-are-always-some-ways</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 09:00:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37490-no-relationship-is-perfect-ever-there-are-always-some-ways]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No relationship is perfect, ever. There are always some ways you have to bend, to compromise, to give something up in order to gain something greater...The love we have for each other is bigger than these small differences. And that's the key. It's like a big pie chart, and the love in a relationship has to be the biggest piece. Love can make up for a lot." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53396-what-is-family-they-were-the-people-who-claimed-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 09:02:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53396-what-is-family-they-were-the-people-who-claimed-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is family? They were the people who claimed you. In good, in bad, in parts or in whole, they were the ones who showed up, who stayed in there, regardless. It wasn't just about blood relations or shared chromosomes, but something wider, bigger. We had many families over time. Our family of origin, the family we created, and the groups you moved through while all of this was happening: friends, lovers, sometimes even strangers. None of them perfect, and we couldn't expect them to be. You can't make any one person your world. The trick was to take what each could give you and build your world from it." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73187-music-is-a-total-constant-that-s-why-we-have-such</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 09:02:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73187-music-is-a-total-constant-that-s-why-we-have-such]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Music is a total constant. That's why we have such a strong visceral connection to it, you know? Because a song can take you back instantly to a moment, or a place, or even a person. No matter what else has changed in your or the world, that one song says the same, just like that moment." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45379-family-isn-t-something-that-s-supposed-to-be-static-or-set</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 09:02:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45379-family-isn-t-something-that-s-supposed-to-be-static-or-set]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Family isn’t something that’s supposed to be static, or set. People marry in, divorce out. They’re born, they die. It’s always evolving, turning into something else." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66508-it-s-a-lot-easier-to-be-lost-than-found-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 09:03:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66508-it-s-a-lot-easier-to-be-lost-than-found-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's a lot easier to be lost than found. It's the reason we're always searching and rarely discovered--so many locks not enough keys." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68741-i-wondered-which-was-harder-in-the-end-the-act</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 09:03:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68741-i-wondered-which-was-harder-in-the-end-the-act]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wondered which was harder, in the end. The act of telling, or who you told it to. Or maybe if, when you finally got it out, the story was really all that mattered." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93329-so-you-re-always-honest-i-said-aren-t-you-no-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 09:06:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93329-so-you-re-always-honest-i-said-aren-t-you-no-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So you're always honest,&quot; I said.
&quot;Aren't you?&quot;
&quot;No,&quot; I told him. &quot;I'm not.&quot;
&quot;Well, that's good to know, I guess.&quot;
&quot;I'm not saying I'm a liar,&quot; I told him. He raised his eyebrows. &quot;That's not how I meant it, anyways.&quot;
&quot;How'd you mean it, then?&quot;
&quot;I just...I don't always say what I feel.&quot;
&quot;Why not?&quot;
&quot;Because the truth sometimes hurts,&quot; I said.
&quot;Yeah,&quot; he said. &quot;So do lies, though." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/91548-my-point-is-there-are-a-lot-of-people-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 09:10:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/91548-my-point-is-there-are-a-lot-of-people-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My point is, there are a lot of people in the world. No one ever sees everything the same way you do; it just doesn't happen. So when you find one person who gets a couple of things, especially if they're important ones... you might as well hold on to them. You know?" -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17901-anyone-who-imagines-that-bliss-is-normal-is-going-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 14:16:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Jenkin Lloyd Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17901-anyone-who-imagines-that-bliss-is-normal-is-going-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who imagines that bliss is normal is going to waste a lot of time running around shouting that he has been robbed. The fact is that most putts don’t drop, most beef is tough, most children grow up to be just like people, most successful marriages require a high degree of mutual toleration, and most jobs are more often dull than otherwise. Life is just like an old time rail journey ... delays, sidetracks, smoke, dust, cinders, and jolts, interspersed only occasionally by beautiful vistas and thrilling bursts of speed. The trick is to thank the Lord for letting you have the ride." -- Jenkin Lloyd Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43274-we-have-become-a-sloppy-bunch-of-people-we-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 22:24:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Greg Behrendt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43274-we-have-become-a-sloppy-bunch-of-people-we-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have become a sloppy bunch of people. We say things we don't mean. We make promises we don't keep. &quot;I'll call you.&quot; &quot;Let's get together.&quot; We know we won't. On the Human Interaction Stock Exchange, our words have lost almost all their value. And the spiral continues, as we now don't even expect people to keep their word; in fact we might even be embarrassed to point out to the dirty liar that they never did what they said they'd do. So if a guy you're dating doesn't call when he says he's doing to, why should that be such a big deal? Because you should be dating a man who's at least as good as his word." -- Greg Behrendt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1420-i-wanted-a-perfect-ending-now-i-ve-learned-the-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 20:36:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Gilda Radner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1420-i-wanted-a-perfect-ending-now-i-ve-learned-the-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted a perfect ending. Now I've learned, the hard way, that some poems don't rhyme, and some stories don't have a clear beginning, middle, and end. Life is about not knowing, having to change, taking the moment and making the best of it, without knowing what's going to happen next.
Delicious Ambiguity." -- Gilda Radner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9444-none-of-us-really-changes-over-time-we-only-become</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 20:37:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Anne Rice]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9444-none-of-us-really-changes-over-time-we-only-become]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["None of us really changes over time. We only become more fully what we are." -- Anne Rice]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20112-when-adults-say-teenagers-think-they-are-invincible-with-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 20:39:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20112-when-adults-say-teenagers-think-they-are-invincible-with-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When adults say, &quot;Teenagers think they are invincible&quot; with that sly, stupid smile on their faces, they don't know how right they are. We need never be hopeless, because we can never be irreparably broken. We think that we are invincible because we are. We cannot be born, and we cannot die. Like all energy, we can only change shapes and sizes and manifestations. They forget that when they get old. They get scared of losing and failing. But that part of us greater than the sum of our parts cannot begin and cannot end, and so it cannot fail." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39953-there-s-always-going-to-be-bad-stuff-out-there-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 20:40:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39953-there-s-always-going-to-be-bad-stuff-out-there-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's always going to be bad stuff out there. But here's the amazing thing -- light trumps darkness, every time. You stick a candle into the dark, but you can't stick the dark into the light." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 23:32:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 23:32:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 23:33:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 23:33:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19884-be-yourself-everyone-else-is-already-taken</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 23:33:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19884-be-yourself-everyone-else-is-already-taken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be yourself; everyone else is already taken." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
