<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1014181-bobby]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1014181-bobby" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2010 09:54:24 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293729-when-a-book-is-read-an-irrevocable-thing-happens</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2010 09:54:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bobby add a quote by Mike Carey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293729-when-a-book-is-read-an-irrevocable-thing-happens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a book is read an irrevocable thing happens — a murder, followed by an imposture. The story in the mind murders the story on the page, and takes its place." -- Mike Carey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/457580-design-is-not-limited-to-fancy-new-gadgets-our-family</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 07:06:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bobby add a quote by Steve Jobs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/457580-design-is-not-limited-to-fancy-new-gadgets-our-family]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Design is not limited to fancy new gadgets. Our family just bought a new washing machine and dryer. We didn’t have a very good one so we spent a little time looking at them. It turns out that the Americans make washers and dryers all wrong. The Europeans make them much better – but they take twice as long to do clothes! It turns out that they wash them with about a quarter as much water and your clothes end up with a lot less detergent on them. Most important, they don’t trash your clothes. They use a lot less soap, a lot less water, but they come out much cleaner, much softer, and they last a lot longer. We spent some time in our family talking about what’s the trade-off we want to make. We ended up talking a lot about design, but also about the values of our family. Did we care most about getting our wash done in an hour versus an hour and a half? Or did we care most about our clothes feeling really soft and lasting longer? Did we care about using a quarter of the water? We spent about two weeks talking about this every night at the dinner table. We’d get around to that old washer-dryer discussion. And the talk was about design. We ended up opting for these Miele appliances, made in Germany. They’re too expensive, but that’s just because nobody buys them in this country. They are really wonderfully made and one of the few products we’ve bought over the last few years that we’re all really happy about. These guys really thought the process through. They did such a great job designing these washers and dryers. I got more thrill out of them than I have out of any piece of high tech in years." -- Steve Jobs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328058-which-meant-i-d-get-depressed-and-that-was-the-big</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 16:22:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bobby add a quote by Ned Vizzini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328058-which-meant-i-d-get-depressed-and-that-was-the-big]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...which meant I'd get depressed, and that was the big one because I knew what that did to me: it made it so I wouldn't get out of bed, which led to the ultimate thing-- homelessness.  If you can't get out of bed for long enough, people come and take your bed away." -- Ned Vizzini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508982-i-wasn-t-gifted-mom-was-wrong-i-was-just-smart</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 16:26:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bobby add a quote by Ned Vizzini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508982-i-wasn-t-gifted-mom-was-wrong-i-was-just-smart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wasn’t gifted. Mom was wrong. I was just smart and I worked hard. I had fooled myself into thinking that was something important to the rest of the world. Other people were complicit in this ruse. Nobody had told me I was common." -- Ned Vizzini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508984-i-can-t-function-here-anymore-i-mean-in-life-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 16:28:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bobby add a quote by Ned Vizzini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508984-i-can-t-function-here-anymore-i-mean-in-life-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can’t function here anymore. I mean in life: I can’t function in this life. I’m no better off than when I was in bed last night, with one difference: when I was in my own bed—or my mom’s—I could do something about it; now that I’m here I can’t do anything. I can’t ride my bike to the Brooklyn Bridge; I can’t take a whole bunch of pills and go for the good sleep; the only thing I can do is crush my head in the toilet seat, and I still don’t even know if that would work. They take away your options and all you can do is live, and it’s just like Humble said: I’m not afraid of dying; I’m afraid of living. I was afraid before, but I’m afraid even more now that I’m a public joke. The teachers are going to hear from the students. They’ll think I’m trying to make an excuse for bad work." -- Ned Vizzini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322320-people-are-screwed-up-in-this-world-i-d-rather-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 16:33:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bobby add a quote by Ned Vizzini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322320-people-are-screwed-up-in-this-world-i-d-rather-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People are screwed up in this world. I'd rather be with someone screwed up and open about it than somebody perfect and ready to explode." -- Ned Vizzini]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
