<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1015795-joseph-sales]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1015795-joseph-sales" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 08:09:05 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309293-justice-is-the-first-virtue-of-social-institutions-as-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 08:09:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by John Rawls]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309293-justice-is-the-first-virtue-of-social-institutions-as-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Justice is the first virtue of social institutions, as truth is of systems of thought.  A theory however elegant and economical must be rejected or revised if it is untrue; likewise laws and institutions no matter how efficient and well-arranged must be reformed or abolished if they are unjust.  Each person possesses an inviolability founded on justice that even the welfare of society as a whole cannot override.  For this reason justice denies that the loss of freedom for some is made right by a greater good shared by others.  It does not allow that the sacrifices imposed on a few are outweighed by the larger sum of advantages enjoyed by many.  Therefore in a just society the liberties of equal citizenship are taken as settled; the rights secured by justice are not subject to political bargaining or to the calculus of social interests." -- John Rawls]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152999-a-man-lives-not-only-his-personal-life-as-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 15:57:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by Thomas Mann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152999-a-man-lives-not-only-his-personal-life-as-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man lives not only his personal life, as an individual, but also, consciously or unconsciously, the life of his epoch and his contemporaries. He may regard the general, impersonal foundations of his existence as definitely settled and taken for granted, and be as far from assuming a critical attitude towards them as our good Hans Castorp really was; yet it is quite conceivable that he may none the less be vaguely conscious of the deficiencies of his epoch and find them prejudicial to his own moral well-being. All sorts of personal aims, hopes, ends, prospects, hover before the eyes of the individual, and out of these he derives the impulse to ambition and achievement. Now, if the life about him, if his own time seems, however outwardly stimulating, to be at bottom empty of such food for his aspirations; if he privately recognises it to be hopeless, viewless, helpless, opposing only a hollow silence to all the questions man puts, consciously or unconsciously, yet somehow puts, as to the final, absolute, and abstract meaning in all his efforts and activities; then, in such a case, a certain laming of the personality is bound to occur, the more inevitably the more upright the character in question; a sort of palsy, as it were, which may extend from his spiritual and moral over into his physical and organic part. In an age that affords no satisfying answer to the eternal question of 'Why?' 'To what end?' a man who is capable of achievement over and above the expected modicum must be equipped either with a moral remoteness and single-mindedness which is rare indeed and of heroic mould, or else with an exceptionally robust vitality. Hans Castorp had neither one nor the other of these; and thus he must be considered mediocre, though in an entirely honourable sense." -- Thomas Mann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181711-he-thought-what-a-fine-thing-it-was-that-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 15:58:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by Thomas Mann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181711-he-thought-what-a-fine-thing-it-was-that-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He thought what a fine thing it was that people made music all over the world, even in the strangest settings – probably even on polar expeditions." -- Thomas Mann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182260-we-do-not-fear-being-called-meticulous-inclining-as-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 15:59:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by Thomas Mann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182260-we-do-not-fear-being-called-meticulous-inclining-as-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We do not fear being called meticulous, inclining as we do to the view that only the exhaustive can be truly interesting." -- Thomas Mann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119668-what-you-call-passion-is-not-a-spiritual-force-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 16:01:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119668-what-you-call-passion-is-not-a-spiritual-force-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What you call passion is not a spiritual force, but friction between the soul and the outside world. Where passion dominates, that does not signify the presence of greater desire and ambition, but rather the misdirection of these qualities toward and isolated and false goal, with a consequent tension and sultriness in the atmosphere. Those who direct the maximum force of their desires toward the center, toward true being, toward perfection, seem quieter than the passionate souls because the flame of their fervor cannot always be seen. In argument, for example, they will not shout or wave their arms. But, I assure you, they are nevertheless, burning with subdued fires." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119681-a-game-master-or-teacher-who-was-primarily-concerned-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 16:02:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119681-a-game-master-or-teacher-who-was-primarily-concerned-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A game master or teacher who was primarily concerned with being close enough to the &quot;innermost meaning&quot; would be a very bad teacher. To be candid, I myself, for example, have never in my life said a word to my pupils about the &quot;meaning&quot; of music; if there is one it does not need my explanations. On the other hand I have always made a great point of having my pupils count their eighths and sixteenths nicely. Whatever you become, teacher, scholar, or musician, have respect for the &quot;meaning&quot; but do not imagine that it can be taught." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7810-let-us-be-grateful-to-the-people-who-make-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2011 20:40:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7810-let-us-be-grateful-to-the-people-who-make-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let us be grateful to the people who make us happy; they are the charming gardeners who make our souls blossom." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
