<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1015612-kristy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1015612-kristy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 15:59:59 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78085-if-we-face-the-fact-for-it-is-a-fact</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 15:59:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78085-if-we-face-the-fact-for-it-is-a-fact]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we face the fact, for it is a fact,  that there is no arm to cling to, but that we go alone and that our relation is to the world of reality and not only to the world of men and women..." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1791-a-book-must-be-the-axe-for-the-frozen-sea</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 16:01:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1791-a-book-must-be-the-axe-for-the-frozen-sea]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book must be the axe for the frozen sea within us." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21847-there-is-nothing-i-would-not-do-for-those-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 16:03:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21847-there-is-nothing-i-would-not-do-for-those-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing I would not do for those who are really my friends. I have no notion of loving people by halves, it is not my nature." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78153-i-really-would-like-to-stop-working-forever-never-work-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 20:08:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Allen Ginsberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78153-i-really-would-like-to-stop-working-forever-never-work-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I really would like to stop working forever–never work again, never do anything like the kind of work I’m doing now–and do nothing but write poetry and have leisure to spend the day outdoors and go to museums and see friends. And I’d like to keep living with someone — maybe even a man — and explore relationships that way. And cultivate my perceptions, cultivate the visionary thing in me. Just a literary and quiet city-hermit existence." -- Allen Ginsberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23163-often-on-a-wet-day-i-begin-counting-up-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 14:10:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23163-often-on-a-wet-day-i-begin-counting-up-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Often on a wet day I begin counting up; what I've read and what I haven't read." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22133-but-then-anyone-who-s-worth-anything-reads-just-what-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 14:10:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22133-but-then-anyone-who-s-worth-anything-reads-just-what-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But then anyone who's worth anything reads just what he likes, as the mood takes him, and with extravagant enthusiasm." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156889-i-read-the-fuck-out-of-every-book-i-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 18:05:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156889-i-read-the-fuck-out-of-every-book-i-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read the fuck out of every book I can get my hands on." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261132-owing-to-the-flood-of-shallow-books-which-really-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 10:13:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261132-owing-to-the-flood-of-shallow-books-which-really-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Owing to the flood of shallow books which really are exhausted in one reading, the modern mind tends to think every book is the same, finished in one reading.  But it is not so.  And gradually the modern mind will realize it again.  The real joy of a book lies in reading it over and over again, and always finding something different, coming upon another meaning, another level of meaning.  It is, as usual, a question of values: we are so overwhelmed with quantities of books, that we hardly realize any more that a book can be valuable, valuable like a jewel, or a lovely picture, into which you can look deeper and deeper and get a more profound experience very time.  It is far, far better to read one book six times, at intervals, than to read six several books." -- D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22123-reading-makes-immigrants-of-us-all-it-takes-us-away</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 22:02:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Hazel Rochman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22123-reading-makes-immigrants-of-us-all-it-takes-us-away]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reading makes immigrants of us all. It takes us away from home, but more important, it finds homes for us everywhere. ." -- Hazel Rochman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78158-i-can-never-read-all-the-books-i-want-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 15:59:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78158-i-can-never-read-all-the-books-i-want-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can never read all the books I want; I can never be all the people I want and live all the lives I want. I can never train myself in all the skills I want. And why do I want? I want to live and feel all the shades, tones and variations of mental and physical experience possible in life. And I am horribly limited." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12019-when-we-re-incomplete-we-re-always-searching-for-somebody-to-complete</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 19:36:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12019-when-we-re-incomplete-we-re-always-searching-for-somebody-to-complete]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we're incomplete, we're always searching for somebody to complete us. When, after a few years or a few months of a relationship, we find that we're still unfulfilled, we blame our partners and take up with somebody more promising. This can go on and on--series polygamy--until we admit that while a partner can add sweet dimensions to our lives, we, each of us, are responsible for our own fulfillment. Nobody else can provide it for us, and to believe otherwise is to delude ourselves dangerously and to program for eventual failure every relationship we enter." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117986-it-seems-to-me-if-you-add-music-and-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 19:39:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117986-it-seems-to-me-if-you-add-music-and-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seems to me if you add music (and books, probably, and films, and plays, and anything that makes you feel) at the center of your being, then you can't afford to sort out your love life, start to think of it as the finished product. You've got to pick at it, keep it alive and in turmoil, you've got to pick at it and unravel it until it all comes apart and you're compelled to start all over again. Maybe we live life at too high a pitch, those of us who absorb emotional things all day, and as a consequence we can never feel merely content: we have to be unhappy, or ecstatically, head-over-heels happy, and those states are difficult to achieve within a stable, solid relationship." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2011 17:47:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Kent M. Keith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Paradoxical Commandments

People are illogical, unreasonable, and self-centered.
Love them anyway.

If you do good, people will accuse you of selfish ulterior motives.
Do good anyway.

If you are successful, you will win false friends and true enemies.
Succeed anyway.

The good you do today will be forgotten tomorrow.
Do good anyway.

Honesty and frankness make you vulnerable.
Be honest and frank anyway.

The biggest men and women with the biggest ideas can be shot down by the smallest men and women with the smallest minds.
Think big anyway.

People favor underdogs but follow only top dogs.
Fight for a few underdogs anyway.

What you spend years building may be destroyed overnight.
Build anyway.

People really need help but may attack you if you do help them.
Help people anyway.

Give the world the best you have and you'll get kicked in the teeth.
Give the world the best you have anyway." -- Kent M. Keith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191324-i-am-too-intelligent-too-demanding-and-too-resourceful-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2012 05:30:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191324-i-am-too-intelligent-too-demanding-and-too-resourceful-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am too intelligent, too demanding, and too resourceful for anyone to be able to take charge of me entirely. No one knows me or loves me completely. I have only myself" -- Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
