<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1015287-molly]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1015287-molly" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 22:58:46 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40131-consider-a-move-the-steady-time-of-being-unknown-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 22:58:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Michael Ryan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40131-consider-a-move-the-steady-time-of-being-unknown-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Consider A Move

The steady time of being unknown,
in solitude, without friends,
is not a steadiness that sustains.
I hear your voice waver on the phone:

&lt;i&gt;Haven't talked to anyone for days.
I drive around. I sit in parking lots.&lt;/i&gt;
The voice zeroes through my ear, and waits.
What should I say? There are ways

to meet people you will want to love?
I know of none. You come out stronger
having gone through this? I no longer
believe that, if I once did. Consider a move,

a change, a job, a new place to live,
someplace you'd like to be. &lt;i&gt;That's not it&lt;/i&gt;,
you say. Now time turns back. We almost touch.
Then what is? I ask. What is?" -- Michael Ryan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37438-you-ll-have-to-learn-to-forgive-he-said-for-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 16:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Patrick McCabe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37438-you-ll-have-to-learn-to-forgive-he-said-for-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You'll have to learn to forgive,&quot; he said. &quot;For if you don't, you know what will happen?&quot;
&quot;What, Doctor?&quot; I croaked, for my outburst had exhausted me.
&quot;It will destroy you,&quot; he said as he handed me the tea.
A tear came into my eye when he said it for I knew it was true and I would have loved to be able to do it (not because of its destroying me but because it was right, and deep down I knew that) but I couldn't and the more I thought of it the more the blood came coursing to my head so that whenever I'd write I'd find myself clutching the pencil so tight I broke the lead how many times I don't know, hundreds." -- Patrick McCabe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82835-i-feel-like-an-inadequate-machine-a-machine-that-breaks</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 16:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by May Sarton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82835-i-feel-like-an-inadequate-machine-a-machine-that-breaks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I feel like an inadequate machine, a machine that breaks down at crucial moments, grinds to a dreadful hault, 'won't go,' or, even worse, explodes in some innocent person's face." -- May Sarton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223136-i-m-perfect-at-feelings-so-i-have-no-problem-telling</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 16:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Brenda Shaughnessy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223136-i-m-perfect-at-feelings-so-i-have-no-problem-telling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm Perfect at Feelings, 
so I have no problem telling you 
why you cried over the third lost 
metal or the mousetrap. I knew 
that orgasms weren't your fault
 and that feeling of keeping solid 
in yourself but wanting an ecstatic 
black hole was just bad beauty.
  
Certain loves were perfect 
in the daytime and had every
 right to express carnally behind 
the copy machine and there are
 no hard feelings for the boozy
 sodomy and sorry XX daisy chain, 
whenever it felt right for you.  

And when the moment of soft
 levitation with erasing hands
 made you feel dirty, like 
the main person to think up love 
in the first place, I knew that. 
It's okay, you're an innocent 
with the brilliance of an animal

stuffing yourself sick on a kill. 
Don't, don't feel like the runt alien
 on my ship: I get you. I know 
the dimensions of your wishing
 and losing and don't think you 
a glutton with petty beefs. But 
even I, who know your triggers,  

your emblematic sacs of sad fury, 
I understand why the farthest fat trees
 sliver down with your disappointment
 and why the big sense of the world, 
wrong before you, shrugs but 
somewhere grasps your spinning, 
stunning, alone. But you have me." -- Brenda Shaughnessy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374439-adam-wet-his-dry-lips-and-tried-to-ask-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 16:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374439-adam-wet-his-dry-lips-and-tried-to-ask-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Adam wet his dry lips and tried to ask and failed and tried again. &quot;Why do they have to do it?&quot; he said. &quot;Why is it?&quot;

Cyrus was deeply moved and he spoke as he had never spoken before. &quot;I don't know,&quot; he said. &quot;I've studied and maybe learned how things are, but I&quot;m not even close to why they are. And you must not expect to find that people understand what they do. So many things are done instinctively, the way a bee makes honey or a fox dips his paws into a stream to fool dogs. A fox can't say why he does it, and what bee remembers winter or expects it to come again? When I knew you had to go I thought to leave the future open so you could dig out your own findings, and then it seemed better if I could protect you with the little I know. You'll go in soon now--you've come to the age.&quot;

&quot;I don't want to,&quot; said Adam quickly.

&quot;You'll go in soon,&quot; his father went on, not hearing. &quot;And I want to tell you so you won't be surprised. They'll first strip off your clothes, but they'll go deeper than that. They'll shuck off any little dignity you have--you'll lose what you think of as your decent right to live and be let alone to live. They'll make you live and eat and sleep and shit close to other men. And when they dress you up again you'll not be able to tell yourself from the others. You can't even wear a scrap or pin a note on your breast to say, 'This is me--separate from the rest.'&quot;

&quot;I don't want to do it,&quot; said Adam.

&quot;After a while,&quot; said Cyrus, &quot;you'll think no thought the others do not think. You'll know no word the others can't say. And you'll do things because the others do them. You'll feel the danger in any difference whatever-- a danger to the whole crowd of like-thinking, like-acting men.&quot;

&quot;What if I don't?&quot; Adam demanded.

&quot;Yes,&quot; said Cyrus, &quot;sometimes that happens. Once in a while there is a man who won't do what is demanded of him, and do you know what happens? The whole machine devotes itself coldly to the destruction of his difference. They'll beat your spirit and  your nerves, your body and your mind, with iron rods until the dangerous difference goes out of you. And if you can't finally give in, they'll vomit you up and leave you stinking outside--neither part of themselves nor yet free. It's better to fall in with them. They only do it to protect themselves [...]" -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37439-i-suppose-i-ve-never-set-out-to-write-a-novel</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 16:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Alice McDermott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37439-i-suppose-i-ve-never-set-out-to-write-a-novel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I suppose I've never set out to write a novel in which nothing happens . . . only to write a novel about the lives of certain characters. That nothing 'happens' in their lives is beside the point to me; I'm still interested in how they live, and think, and speak, and make some sense of their own experience. Incident (in novels and in life) is momentary, and temporary, but the memory of an incident, the story told about it, the meaning it takes on or loses over time, is lifelong and fluid, and that's what interests me and what I hope will prove interesting to readers. We're deluged with stories of things that have happened, events, circumstances, actions, etc. We need some stories that reveal how we think and feel and hope and dream. " -- Alice McDermott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15417-when-a-child-first-catches-adults-out----when-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 16:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15417-when-a-child-first-catches-adults-out----when-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a child first catches adults out -- when it first walks into his grave little head that adults do not always have divine intelligence, that their judgments are not always wise, their thinking true, their sentences just -- his world falls into panic desolation. The gods are fallen and all safety gone. And there is one sure thing about the fall of gods: they do not fall a little; they crash and shatter or sink deeply into green muck. It is a tedious job to build them up again; they never quite shine. And the child's world is never quite whole again. It is an aching kind of growing." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37377-the-busybody-banned-as-sexist-demeaning-to-older-women-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 16:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Denise Duhamel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37377-the-busybody-banned-as-sexist-demeaning-to-older-women-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The busybody (banned as sexist, demeaning to older women) who lives next door called my daughter a tomboy (banned as sexist) when she climbed the jungle (banned; replaced with &quot;rain forest&quot;) gym. Then she had the nerve to call her an egghead and a bookworm (both banned as offensive; replaced with &quot;intellectual&quot;) because she read fairy (banned because suggests homosexuality; replace with &quot;elf&quot;) tales.

I'm tired of the Language Police turning a deaf ear (banned as handicapism) to my complaints. I'm no Pollyanna (banned as sexist) and will not accept any lame (banned as offensive; replace with &quot;walks with a cane&quot;) excuses at this time.

If Alanis Morrissette can play God (banned) in &lt;i&gt;Dogma&lt;/i&gt; (banned as ethnocentric; replace with &quot;Doctrine&quot; or &quot;Belief&quot;), why can't my daughter play stickball (banned as regional or ethnic bias) on boy's night out (banned as sexist)? Why can't she build a snowman (banned, replace with &quot;snow person&quot;) without that fanatic (banned as ethnocentric; replace with &quot;believer,&quot; &quot;follower,&quot; or &quot;adherent&quot;) next door telling her she's going to hell (banned; replaced with &quot;heck&quot; or &quot;darn&quot;)?

Do you really think this is what the Founding Fathers (banned as sexist; replace with &quot;the Founders&quot; or &quot;the Framers&quot;) had in mind? That we can't even enjoy our Devil (banned)-ed ham sandwiches in peace? I say put a stop to this cult (banned as ethnocentric) of PC old wives' tales (banned as sexist; replace with &quot;folk wisdom&quot;) and extremist (banned as ethnocentric; replace with &quot;believer,&quot; &quot;follower,&quot; or &quot;adherent&quot;) conservative duffers (banned as demeaning to older men).

As an heiress (banned as sexist; replace with &quot;heir&quot;) to the first amendment, I feel that only a heretic (use with caution when comparing religions) would try to stop American vernacular from flourishing in all its inspirational (banned as patronizing when referring to a person with disabilities) splendor." -- Denise Duhamel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108134-people-like-you-to-be-something-preferably-what-they-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 16:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108134-people-like-you-to-be-something-preferably-what-they-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People like you to be something, preferably what they are." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37440-writing-about-sex-is-not-as-personally-revealing-as-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 16:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Doreen Baingana]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37440-writing-about-sex-is-not-as-personally-revealing-as-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing about sex is not as personally revealing as one might think, because like anything else you write about, the words are not the deed. I have not done those words, I have done and felt private things for which words such as &quot;sex&quot; and &quot;lust&quot; are only poor apologies." -- Doreen Baingana]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186663-it-s-a-hard-thing-to-leave-any-deeply-routine-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 16:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186663-it-s-a-hard-thing-to-leave-any-deeply-routine-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s a hard thing to leave any deeply routine life, even if you hate it." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37442-memories-are-killing-so-you-must-not-think-of-certain</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 16:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Samuel Beckett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37442-memories-are-killing-so-you-must-not-think-of-certain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Memories are killing. So you must not think of certain things, of those that are dear to you, or rather you must think of them, for if you don’t there is the danger of finding them, in your mind, little by little." -- Samuel Beckett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37443-there-are-a-hundred-things-she-has-tried-to-chase</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 16:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37443-there-are-a-hundred-things-she-has-tried-to-chase]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are a hundred things she has tried to chase away the things she won't remember and that she can't even let herself think about because that's when the birds scream and the worms crawl and somewhere in her mind it's always raining a slow and endless drizzle.

You will hear that she has left the country, that there was a gift she wanted you to have, but it is lost before it reaches you. Late one night the telephone will sign, and a voice that might be hers will say something that you cannot interpret before the connection crackles and is broken.

Several years later, from a taxi, you will see someone in a doorway who looks like her, but she will be gone by the time you persuade the driver to stop. You will never see her again. 

Whenever it rains you will think of her.  " -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4261-there-is-enough-treachery-hatred-violence-absurdity-in-the-average</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 16:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by charles bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4261-there-is-enough-treachery-hatred-violence-absurdity-in-the-average]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["there is enough treachery, hatred violence absurdity in the average
human being to supply any given army on any given day and the best at murder are those who preach against it
and the best at hate are those who preach love and the best at war finally are those who preach peace" -- charles bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37444-there-are-indeed-many-wonders-and-with-regard-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 16:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Pindar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37444-there-are-indeed-many-wonders-and-with-regard-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are indeed many wonders, and with regard to the stories people tell one another, it may be that such tales go beyond the true account and, embellished with iridescent lies, beguile them." -- Pindar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256372-when-we-strike-a-balance-between-the-challenge-of-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 16:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Ariel Gore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256372-when-we-strike-a-balance-between-the-challenge-of-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we strike a balance between the challenge of an activity and our skill at performing it, when the rhythm of the work itself feels in sync with our pulse, when we know that what we're doing matters, we can get totally absorbed in our task. That is happiness.

The life coach Martha Beck asks new potential clients, &quot;Is there anything you do regularly that makes you forget what time it is?&quot; 

That forgetting -- that pure absorption -- is what the psychologist Mihaly Csikzentmihalyi calls &quot;flow&quot; or optimal experience. In an interview with Wired magazine, he described flow as &quot;being completely involved in an activity for its own sake. The ego falls away. Time flies. Every action, movement and thought follows inevitably from the previous one, like playing jazz. Your whole being is involved, and you're using your skills to the utmost.&quot;

In a typical day that teeters between anxiety and boredom, flow experiences are those flashes of intense living -- bright against the dull. These optimal experiences can happen when we're engaged in work paid and unpaid, in sports, in music, in art. 

The researchers Maria Allison and Margaret Duncan have studied the role of flow in women's lives and looked at factors that contributed to what they call &quot;antiflow.&quot; Antiflow was associated with repetitive household tasks, repetitive tasks at work, unchallenging tasks, and work we see as meaningless. But there's an element of chaos when it comes to flow. Even if we're doing meaningful and challenging work, that sense of total absoprtion can elude us. We might get completely and beautifully lost in something today, and, try as we might to re-create the same conditions tomorrow, our task might jsut feel like, well, work. 

In A Life of One's Own, Marion Milner described her effort to re-create teh conditions of her own recorded moments of happiness, saying, &quot;Often when I felt certain that I had discovered the little mental act which produced the change I walked on air, exulting that I had found the key to my garden of delight and could slip through the door whenever I wished. But most often when I came again the place seemed different, the door overgrown with thorns and my key stuck in the lock. It was as if the first time I had said 'abracadabra' the door had opened, but the next time I must use a different word. (123-124)." -- Ariel Gore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192467-i-often-carry-things-to-read-so-that-i-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 23:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192467-i-often-carry-things-to-read-so-that-i-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I often carry things to read
so that I will not have to look at
the people." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37445-every-room-i-ve-lived-in-since-i-was-given-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 23:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Jonathan Lethem]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37445-every-room-i-ve-lived-in-since-i-was-given-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every room I've lived in since I was given my own room at eleven was lined with, and usually overfull of, books. My employment in bookstores was always continuous with my private hours: shelving and alphabetizing, building shelves, and browsing-- in my collection and others-- in order to understand a small amount about the widest possible number of books. Such numbers of books are constantly acquired that constant culling is necessary; if I slouch in this discipline, the books erupt. I've also bricked myself in with music--vinyl records, then compact discs. My homes have been improbably information-dense, like capsules for survival of a nuclear war, or models of the interior of my own skull. That comparison--room as brain-- is one I've often reached for in describing the rooms of others, but it began with the suspicion that I'd externalized my own brain, for anyone who cared to look." -- Jonathan Lethem]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/307083-love-opens-the-doors-into-everything-as-far-as-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 23:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by May Sarton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/307083-love-opens-the-doors-into-everything-as-far-as-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love opens the doors into everything, as far as I can see, including and perhaps most of all, the door into one's own secret, and often terrible and frightening, real self." -- May Sarton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37446-do-not-be-concerned-with-the-faults-of-other-persons</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 23:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Zen Master Dogen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37446-do-not-be-concerned-with-the-faults-of-other-persons]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not be concerned with the faults of other persons. Do not see others' faults with a hateful mind. There is an old saying that if you stop seeing others' faults, then naturally seniors and venerated and juniors are revered. Do not imitate others' faults; just cultivate virtue. Buddha prohibited unwholesome actions, but did not tell us to hate those who practice unwholesome actions." -- Zen Master Dogen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132381-i-loved-them-all-the-way-one-loves-at-any</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 23:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by May Sarton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132381-i-loved-them-all-the-way-one-loves-at-any]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I loved them all the way one loves at any age -- if it's real at all -- obsessively, painfully, with wild exultation, with guilt, with conflict; I wrote poems to and about them, I put them into novels (disguised of course); I brooded upon why they were as they were, so often maddening don't you know? I wrote them ridiculous letters. I lived with their faces. I knew their every gesture by heart. I stalked them like wild animals. I studied them as if they were maps of the world -- and in a way I suppose they were." -- May Sarton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18881-i-m-a-kind-of-paranoiac-in-reverse-i-suspect-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 23:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18881-i-m-a-kind-of-paranoiac-in-reverse-i-suspect-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm a kind of paranoiac in reverse. I suspect people of plotting to make me happy." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/337806-the-proper-basis-for-marriage-is-mutual-misunderstanding-the-happiness</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 23:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/337806-the-proper-basis-for-marriage-is-mutual-misunderstanding-the-happiness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The proper basis for marriage is mutual misunderstanding. The happiness of a married man depends on the people he has not married. One should always be in love - that's the reason one should never marry." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37698-the-small-wad-of-burning-paper-drew-down-to-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 23:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37698-the-small-wad-of-burning-paper-drew-down-to-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The small wad of burning paper drew down to a wisp of flame and then died out leaving a faint pattern for just a moment in the incandescence like the shape of a flower, a molten rose. Then all was dark again." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460794-dipping-into-the-archive-is-always-an-interesting-if-sometimes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 23:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Moyra Davey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460794-dipping-into-the-archive-is-always-an-interesting-if-sometimes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dipping into the archive is always an interesting, if sometimes unsettling, proposition. It often begins with anxiety, with the fear that the thing you want won't surface. But ultimately the process is a little like tapping into the unconscious, and can bring with it the ambivalent gratification of rediscovering forgotten selves.

Rather than making new pictures why can't I just recycle some of these old ones? Claim &quot;found&quot; photographs from among my boxes? And have this gesture signify &quot;resistance to further production/consumption&quot;? (96)" -- Moyra Davey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37700-he-thought-each-memory-recalled-must-do-some-violence-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 23:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37700-he-thought-each-memory-recalled-must-do-some-violence-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He thought each memory recalled must do some violence to its origins. As in a party game. Say the words and pass it on. So be sparing. What you alter in the remembering has yet a reality, known or not." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460796-i-am-developing-new-coping-mechanisms-for-lost-words-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 23:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Moyra Davey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460796-i-am-developing-new-coping-mechanisms-for-lost-words-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am developing new coping mechanisms for lost words and lost negatives, as here for instance: compensate by describing the episode instead. When something is lost, redirect energy, follow the derivé, the chance and flow of what life tosses us, and make something new instead. 

Remember that I'm often struck by certain passages of descriptive writing, writing that is not about driving home a point but about providing detail, background, setting the scene (it's tempting to call this the stadium of writing). It has a &quot;something from nothing&quot; quality: a pleasurable experience has been had, and no one has paid a price. Remember that writing does not have to be torture (107)." -- Moyra Davey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41336-such-a-captive-maiden-having-plenty-of-time-to-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 23:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41336-such-a-captive-maiden-having-plenty-of-time-to-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Such a captive maiden, having plenty of time to think, soon realizes that her tower, its height and architecture, are like her ego only incidental: that what really keeps her where she is is magic, anonymous and malignant, visited on her from outside and for no reason at all. Having no apparatus except gut fear and female cunning to examine this formless magic, to understand how it works, how to measure its field strength, count its lines of force, she may fall back on superstition, or take up a useful hobby like embroidery, or go mad, or marry a disk jockey. If the tower is everywhere and the knight of deliverance no proof against its magic, what else?" -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11119-whenever-you-feel-like-criticizing-any-one-just-remember-that-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 23:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11119-whenever-you-feel-like-criticizing-any-one-just-remember-that-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever you feel like criticizing any one...just remember that all the people in this world haven't had the advantages that you've had." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18163-catch-me-as-if-i-have-surely-been-out-committing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 23:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Molly add a quote by Ana Castillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18163-catch-me-as-if-i-have-surely-been-out-committing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Catch me, as if I have surely been out committing a violation against you, my sin of insisting on existing without you. " -- Ana Castillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
