<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1015254-maria-rocio]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1015254-maria-rocio" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 18:18:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13208-you-fight-your-superficiality-your-shallowness-so-as-to-try</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 18:18:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria Rocio add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13208-you-fight-your-superficiality-your-shallowness-so-as-to-try]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You fight your superficiality, your shallowness, so as to try to come at people without unreal expectations, without an overload of bias or hope or arrogance, as untanklike as you can be, sans cannon and machine guns and steel plating half a foot thick; you come at them unmenacingly on your own ten toes instead of tearing up the turf with your caterpillar treads, take them on with an open mind, as equals, man to man, as we used to say, and yet you never fail to get them wrong.  You might as well have the brain of a tank.  You get them wrong before you meet them, while you're anticipating meeting them; you get them wrong while you're with them; and then you go home to tell somebody else about the meeting and you get them all wrong again.  Since the same generally goes for them with you, the whole thing is really a dazzling illusion. ...  The fact remains that getting people right is not what living is all about anyway.  It's getting them wrong that is living, getting them wrong and wrong and wrong and then, on careful reconsideration, getting them wrong again.  That's how we know we're alive:  we're wrong.  Maybe the best thing would be to forget being right or wrong about people and just go along for the ride.  But if you can do that -- well, lucky you." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18719-the-truth-will-set-you-free-but-not-until-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 18:31:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria Rocio add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18719-the-truth-will-set-you-free-but-not-until-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth will set you free. But not until it is finished with you." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2638-both-destiny-s-kisses-and-its-dope-slaps-illustrate-an-individual-person-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 18:31:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria Rocio add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2638-both-destiny-s-kisses-and-its-dope-slaps-illustrate-an-individual-person-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Both destiny's kisses and its dope-slaps illustrate an individual person's basic personal powerlessness over the really meaningful events in his life: i.e. almost nothing important that ever happens to you happens because you engineer it.  Destiny has no beeper; destiny always leans trenchcoated out of an alley with some sort of Psst that you usually can't even hear because you're in such a rush to or from something important you've tried to engineer." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23624-i-read-i-say-i-study-and-read-i-bet</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 18:31:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria Rocio add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23624-i-read-i-say-i-study-and-read-i-bet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read,&quot; I say. &quot;I study and read. I bet I've read everything you read. Don't think I haven't. I consume libraries. I wear out spines and ROM-drives. I do things like get in a taxi and say, &quot;The library, and step on it.&quot; My instincts concerning syntax and mechanics are better than your own, I can tell, with all due respect. But it transcends the mechanics. I'm not a machine. I feel and believe. I have opinions. Some of them are interesting. I could, if you'd let me, talk and talk." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28675-i-have-filled-3-mead-notebooks-trying-to-figure-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 18:31:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria Rocio add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28675-i-have-filled-3-mead-notebooks-trying-to-figure-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have filled 3 Mead notebooks trying to figure out whether it was Them or Just Me." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3526-there-are-no-choices-without-personal-freedom-buckeroo-it-s-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 18:32:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria Rocio add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3526-there-are-no-choices-without-personal-freedom-buckeroo-it-s-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are no choices without personal freedom, Buckeroo. It's not us who are dead inside. These things you find so weak and contemptible in us---these are just the hazards of being free." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 18:32:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria Rocio add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are bored and disgusted by politics and don't bother to vote, you are in effect voting for the entrenched Establishments of the two major parties, who please rest assured are not dumb, and who are keenly aware that it is in their interests to keep you disgusted and bored and cynical and to give you every possible reason to stay at home doing one-hitters and watching MTV on primary day.  By all means stay home if you want, but don't bullshit yourself that you're not voting.  In reality, there is &lt;i&gt;no such thing as not voting:&lt;/i&gt; you either vote by voting, or you vote by staying home and tacitly doubling the value of some Diehard's vote." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29426-mr-robinson-was-a-polished-sort-of-person-he-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 18:51:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria Rocio add a quote by Susanna Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29426-mr-robinson-was-a-polished-sort-of-person-he-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mr. Robinson was a polished sort of person.  He was so clean and healthy and pleased about everything that he positively shone - which is only to be expected in a fairy or an angel, but is somewhat disconcerting in an attorney." -- Susanna Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 09:21:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria Rocio add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 09:21:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria Rocio add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16261-life-is-a-disease-sexually-transmitted-and-invariably-fatal</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 10:12:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria Rocio add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16261-life-is-a-disease-sexually-transmitted-and-invariably-fatal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is a disease: sexually transmitted, and invariably fatal." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5251-sometimes-you-wake-up-sometimes-the-fall-kills-you-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 10:12:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria Rocio add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5251-sometimes-you-wake-up-sometimes-the-fall-kills-you-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes you wake up. Sometimes the fall kills you. And sometimes, when you fall, you fly." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109113-in-mexico-i-first-encountered-the-attitude-that-was-missing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 12:20:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria Rocio add a quote by Pete Hamill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109113-in-mexico-i-first-encountered-the-attitude-that-was-missing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In Mexico, I first encountered the attitude that was missing from the optimistic sense of living in the United States: a tragic sense of life. Such a sense doesn’t force us into a somber cone of depression and futility; it urges the opposite. The tragic sense opens a human being to the exuberant joys of the present. To laughter, carnal ity, the comical varieties of love, to music and art, to the small human glories of the day." -- Pete Hamill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27182-today-you-are-thirteen-weeks-old-and-already-controversial-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 12:26:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria Rocio add a quote by Suzanne Finnamore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27182-today-you-are-thirteen-weeks-old-and-already-controversial-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today you are thirteen weeks old and already controversial.  You should know that the mention of the name Pablo is alarming to a very few, highly insignificant people.  From this palsied paction there is occasionally the slightest pause, and then, 'Oh, really.  Pablo.'  Then with a small, self-depreciating chuckle, they might tilt their heads playfully and say something like 'Aren't you afraid people will think he's Mexican?'
... I find it amusing when they balk at Pablo, as though we were naming you Jesus H. Christ and jamming our nails into your hands.  They seem to feel your name is up for general discussion, like naming a local bridge or a stray cat.
Hmmm.  Mr. Whiskers?  I don't like Mr. Whiskers.  I like the name Blackie.'
Aren't you afraid people will think he's black?" -- Suzanne Finnamore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113602-you-must-learn-to-live-as-i-do---in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 08:17:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria Rocio add a quote by Susanna Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113602-you-must-learn-to-live-as-i-do---in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["you must learn to live as I do - in the face of constant criticism, opposition and censure. That, sir, is the English way." -- Susanna Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/773622-everything-was-in-confusion-in-the-oblonskys-house</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2013 07:52:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria Rocio add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/773622-everything-was-in-confusion-in-the-oblonskys-house]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything was in confusion in the Oblonskys' house." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
