<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1015045-nola]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1015045-nola" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 18:10:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110028-if-you-are-interested-in-something-you-will-focus-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 18:10:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nola add a quote by Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110028-if-you-are-interested-in-something-you-will-focus-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are interested in something, you will focus on it, and if you focus attention on anything, it is likely that you will become interested in it. Many of the things we find interesting are not so by nature, but because we took the trouble of paying attention to them." -- Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116368-we-live-less-than-the-time-it-takes-to-blink</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2008 09:37:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nola add a quote by Chaim Potok]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116368-we-live-less-than-the-time-it-takes-to-blink]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We live less than the time it takes to blink an eye, if we measure our lives against eternity...a blink of an eye in itself is nothing. But the eye that blinks, that is something. A span of life is nothing. But the man who lives that span, he is something. He can fill that tiny span with meaning, so its quality is immeasurable though its quantity may be insignificant...A man must fill his life with meaning, meaning is not automatically given to life." -- Chaim Potok]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116482-eight-hours-work-eight-hours-sleep-and-eight-hours-recreation</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2008 18:43:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nola add a quote by Susa Young Gates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116482-eight-hours-work-eight-hours-sleep-and-eight-hours-recreation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eight hours work, eight hours sleep, and eight hours recreation - Brigham Young" -- Susa Young Gates]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116487-books-are-better-than-television-the-internet-or-the-computer</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2008 18:55:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nola add a quote by Oliver DeMille]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116487-books-are-better-than-television-the-internet-or-the-computer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are better than television, the internet, or the computer for &lt;i&gt;educating and maintaining freedom.&lt;/i&gt;
Books matter because they state ideas and then attempt to thoroughly prove them. They have an advantage &lt;i&gt;precisely because they slow down the process,&lt;/i&gt; allowing the reader to internalize, respond, react and transform. The ideas in books matter because time is taken to establish truth, and because the reader must take the time to consider each idea and either accept it or, if he rejects it, to think through sound reasons for doing so. A nation of people who write and read is a nation with the attention span to earn an education and free society if they choose." -- Oliver DeMille]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105539-a-man-may-possess-a-profound-knowledge-of-history-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:29:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nola add a quote by David O. McKay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105539-a-man-may-possess-a-profound-knowledge-of-history-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man may possess a profound knowledge of history and mathematics; he may be an authority in psychology, biology, or astronomy; he may know all the discovered truths pertaining to geology and natural science; but if he has not with this knowledge that nobility of soul which prompts him to deal justly with his fellow men, to practice virtue and holiness in his personal life, he is not truly an educated man.

Character is the aim of true education; and science, history, and literature are but means used to accomplish the desired end. Character is not the result of chance work but of continuous right thinking and right acting." -- David O. McKay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 16:31:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nola add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is our choices, Harry, that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442413-think-of-the-most-fussy-science-teacher-you-ever-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 18:47:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nola add a quote by Sam Kean]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442413-think-of-the-most-fussy-science-teacher-you-ever-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Think of the most fussy science teacher you ever had. The one who docked your grade if the sixth decimal place in your answer was rounded incorrectly; who tucked in his periodic table T-shirt, corrected every student who said &quot;weight&quot; when he or she meant &quot;mass&quot;, and made everyone, including himself, wear goggles even while mixing sugar water. Now try to imagine someone whom your teacher would hate for being anal-retentive. That is the kind of person who works for a bureau of standards and measurement." -- Sam Kean]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83529-i-couldn-t-possibly-have-sex-with-someone-with-such-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 18:19:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nola add a quote by Russell Brand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83529-i-couldn-t-possibly-have-sex-with-someone-with-such-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I couldn't possibly have sex with someone with such a slender grasp on grammar!" -- Russell Brand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79715-in-writing-you-must-kill-all-your-darlings</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 14:03:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nola add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79715-in-writing-you-must-kill-all-your-darlings]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In writing, you must kill all your darlings." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
