<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1016856-jesica]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1016856-jesica" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:17:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298-a-day-without-sunshine-is-like-you-know-night</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:17:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298-a-day-without-sunshine-is-like-you-know-night]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A day without sunshine is like, you know, night." -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2177-i-am-enough-of-an-artist-to-draw-freely-upon</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:18:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2177-i-am-enough-of-an-artist-to-draw-freely-upon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am enough of an artist to draw freely upon my imagination. Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1928-if-you-re-looking-for-sympathy-you-ll-find-it-between-shit</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:24:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1928-if-you-re-looking-for-sympathy-you-ll-find-it-between-shit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're looking for sympathy you'll find it between shit and syphilis in the dictionary." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29269-we-were-not-a-hugging-people-in-terms-of-emotional</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:25:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29269-we-were-not-a-hugging-people-in-terms-of-emotional]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We were not a hugging people. In terms of emotional comfort it was our belief that no amount of physical contact could match the healing powers of a well made cocktail." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23968-shit-is-the-tofu-of-cursing-and-can-be-molded</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:33:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23968-shit-is-the-tofu-of-cursing-and-can-be-molded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Shit is the tofu of cursing and can be molded to whichever condition the speaker desires. Hot as shit. Windy as shit. I myself was confounded as shit..." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33500-actually-orcas-aren-t-quite-as-complex-as-scientists-imagine-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:35:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Christopher Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33500-actually-orcas-aren-t-quite-as-complex-as-scientists-imagine-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Actually, orcas aren't quite as complex as scientists imagine.  Most killer whales are just four tons of doofus dressed up like a police car." -- Christopher Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9629-her-mind-blackens-the-blackness-is-not-a-thought-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:36:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9629-her-mind-blackens-the-blackness-is-not-a-thought-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[her] mind blackens. The blackness is not a thought, but if it could be pressed into a thought, if a chemical from a dropper could be dripped onto it causing its color and essence to become visible, it would take the shape of this sentence: Why does no one want me?" -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:39:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Insanity is doing the same thing, over and over again, but expecting different results." -- Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5979-anyone-who-thinks-sitting-in-church-can-make-you-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:40:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Garrison Keillor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5979-anyone-who-thinks-sitting-in-church-can-make-you-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who thinks sitting in church can make you a Christian must also think that sitting in a garage can make you a car." -- Garrison Keillor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5544-the-trouble-with-being-in-the-rat-race-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:43:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Lily Tomlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5544-the-trouble-with-being-in-the-rat-race-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble with being in the rat race is that even if you win, you're still a rat." -- Lily Tomlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12450-writing-is-easy-you-only-need-to-stare-at-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:47:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Gene Fowler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12450-writing-is-easy-you-only-need-to-stare-at-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing is easy. You only need to stare at a blank piece of paper until drops of blood form on your forehead." -- Gene Fowler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3564-there-s-some-heinous-fuckery-goin-on-mon</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:58:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Christopher Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3564-there-s-some-heinous-fuckery-goin-on-mon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's some heinous fuckery goin' on mon." -- Christopher Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11121-one-of-the-greatest-myths-in-the-world--</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:59:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11121-one-of-the-greatest-myths-in-the-world--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the greatest myths in the world - &amp; the phrase 'greatest myths' is just a fancy way of saying 'big fat lies' -- is that troublesome things get less &amp; less troublesome if you do them more &amp; more. People say this myth when they are teaching children to ride bicycles, for instance, as though falling off a bicycle &amp; skinning your knee is less troublesome the fourteenth time you do it than it is the first time. The truth is that troublesome things tend to remain troublesome no matter how many times you do them, &amp; that you should avoid doing them unless they are absolutely urgent." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13163-but-there-are-times-in-this-harum-scarum-world-when-figuring</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 13:00:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13163-but-there-are-times-in-this-harum-scarum-world-when-figuring]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But there are times in this harum-scarum world when figuring out the right thing to do is quite simple, but doing the right thing is simply impossible...." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32552-assumptions-are-dangerous-things-to-make-and-like-all-dangerous</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 13:03:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32552-assumptions-are-dangerous-things-to-make-and-like-all-dangerous]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Assumptions are dangerous things to make, and like all dangerous things to make -- bombs, for instance, or strawberry shortcake -- if you make even the tiniest mistake you can find yourself in terrible trouble. Making assumptions simply means believing things are a certain way with little or no evidence that shows you are correct, and you can see at once how this can lead to terrible trouble. For instance, one morning you might wake up and make the assumption that your bed was in the same place that it always was, even though you would have no real evidence that this was so. But when you got out of your bed, you might discover that it had floated out to sea, and now you would be in terrible trouble all because of the incorrect assumption that you'd made. You can see that it is better not to make too many assumptions, particularly in the morning." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34449-strange-as-it-may-seem-i-still-hope-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 13:03:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34449-strange-as-it-may-seem-i-still-hope-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Strange as it may seem, I still hope for the best, even though the best, like an interesting piece of mail, so rarely arrives, and even when it does it can be lost so easily." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33480-miracles-are-like-meatballs-because-nobody-can-exactly-agree-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 13:04:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33480-miracles-are-like-meatballs-because-nobody-can-exactly-agree-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Miracles are like meatballs, because nobody can exactly agree on what they are made of, where they come from, or how often they should appear." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 13:06:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4388-ford-you-re-turning-into-a-penguin-stop-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 13:17:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4388-ford-you-re-turning-into-a-penguin-stop-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ford... you're turning into a penguin. Stop it." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31932-a-learning-experience-is-one-of-those-things-that-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 13:18:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31932-a-learning-experience-is-one-of-those-things-that-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A learning experience is one of those things that says, 'You know that thing you just did? Don't do that." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28433-would-it-save-you-a-lot-of-time-if-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 13:21:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28433-would-it-save-you-a-lot-of-time-if-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Would it save you a lot of time if I just gave up and went mad now?" -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19308-capital-letters-were-always-the-best-way-of-dealing-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 13:22:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19308-capital-letters-were-always-the-best-way-of-dealing-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Capital Letters Were Always The Best Way Of Dealing With Things You Didn't Have A Good Answer To." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31144-i-think-fish-is-nice-but-then-i-think-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 13:25:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31144-i-think-fish-is-nice-but-then-i-think-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think fish is nice, but then I think that rain is wet, so who am I to judge?" -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36812-why-is-always-the-most-difficult-question-to-answer-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 13:27:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36812-why-is-always-the-most-difficult-question-to-answer-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why?' is always the most difficult question to answer. You know where you are when someone asks you 'What's the time?' or 'When was the battle of 1066?'   or 'How do these seatbelts work that go tight when you slam the brakes on, Daddy?' The answers are easy and are, respectively, 'Seven-thirty in the evening,' 'Ten-fifteen in the morning,' and 'Don't ask stupid questions." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51320-he-took-a-sip-of-my-father-s-weak-coffee-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 13:49:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51320-he-took-a-sip-of-my-father-s-weak-coffee-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He took a sip of my father’s weak coffee and spit it back into the mug. &quot;This shit’s like making love in a canoe.&quot;
&quot;Excuse me?&quot;
&quot;It’s fucking near water." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63949-kools-and-newports-were-for-black-people-and-lower-class-whites</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 13:50:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63949-kools-and-newports-were-for-black-people-and-lower-class-whites]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kools and Newports were for black people and lower-class whites. Camels were for procrastinators, those who wrote bad poetry, and those who put off writing bad poetry. Merits were for sex addicts, Salems were for alcoholics, and Mores were for people who considered themselves to be outrageous but really weren't." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1420-i-wanted-a-perfect-ending-now-i-ve-learned-the-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 13:52:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Gilda Radner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1420-i-wanted-a-perfect-ending-now-i-ve-learned-the-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted a perfect ending. Now I've learned, the hard way, that some poems don't rhyme, and some stories don't have a clear beginning, middle, and end. Life is about not knowing, having to change, taking the moment and making the best of it, without knowing what's going to happen next.
Delicious Ambiguity." -- Gilda Radner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6597-poets-have-been-mysteriously-silent-on-the-subject-of-cheese</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 13:53:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6597-poets-have-been-mysteriously-silent-on-the-subject-of-cheese]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Poets have been mysteriously silent on the subject of cheese." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/988-sometimes-our-light-goes-out-but-is-blown-again-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 13:55:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Albert Schweitzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/988-sometimes-our-light-goes-out-but-is-blown-again-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes our light goes out, but is blown again into instant flame by an encounter with another human being." -- Albert Schweitzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34999-everyone-should-be-able-to-do-one-card-trick-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 18:50:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jesica add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34999-everyone-should-be-able-to-do-one-card-trick-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone should be able to do one card trick, tell two jokes, and recite three poems, in case they are ever trapped in an elevator." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
