<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1017136-anthony-paul]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1017136-anthony-paul" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 17:18:22 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/973350-indeed-the-very-first-acknowledgment-as-far-as-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 17:18:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Susan Sontag]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/973350-indeed-the-very-first-acknowledgment-as-far-as-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Indeed, the very first acknowledgment (as far as I am aware) of the attraction of mutilated bodies occurs in a founding description of mental conflict. It is a passage in The Republic, Book IV, where Plato’s Socrates describes how our reason may be overwhelmed by an unworthy desire, which drives the self to become angry with a part of its nature." -- Susan Sontag]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/973561-just-six-weeks-to-wait-then-we-ll-go-out-we-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 20:43:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/973561-just-six-weeks-to-wait-then-we-ll-go-out-we-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just six weeks to wait; then we’ll go out, we’ll go for walks together again, we’ll think and feel together; together we will keep silence, too, between long, long private discussions; for then we will tell each other what letters cannot say. Will we have any moments of peaceable, trusting joy, Michel? I almost feel I am no longer capable of this without you, but will I be so with you? [. . .] Your friend who will never abandon you and who forbids you to think of such a thing." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/976884-when-consulted-on-one-of-the-earliest-texts-by-alain</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 22:21:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/976884-when-consulted-on-one-of-the-earliest-texts-by-alain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When consulted on one of the earliest texts by Alain Badiou, an article on Althusser, Derrida’s reply was both frank and open-minded: I’ve just read Badiou’s text. Like you yourself and Barthes, I find it at least irritating in its tone, the author’s pomposity, the ‘marks’ he hands out to everyone as if it were prize-giving or the Last Judgment. I still think that it’s important. [. . .] I don’t think there’s any doubt of this, and am all the more prepared to grant it this importance because I am far from feeling ‘philosophically’ ready to follow him in his arguments or his conclusions.5" -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/977193-admitting-that-his-distance-probably-contained-a-sort-of-crypto-communist</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 06:27:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/977193-admitting-that-his-distance-probably-contained-a-sort-of-crypto-communist]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Admitting that his distance probably contained ‘a sort of crypto-Communist legacy’, Derrida spoke in more detail about his attitude to the student movement in his interview with Maurizio Ferraris: I did not say no to ‘68’, I took part in the demonstrations, I organized the first general assembly at the École Normale. Still, rightly or wrongly, my heart was not ‘on the barricades’. What really bothered me was not so much the apparent spontaneity, which I do not believe in, but the spontaneist political eloquence, the call for transparency, for communication without relay or delay, the liberation from every sort of apparatus, party or union. [. . .] Spontaneism, like workerism, pauperism, struck me as something to be wary of. I wouldn’t say my conscience is clear on this matter and that it’s as simple as that. These days [. . .], I would be more cautious about formulating this critique of spontaneism." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/977196-to-the-paris-apartment-which-for-him-was-synonymous-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 06:30:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/977196-to-the-paris-apartment-which-for-him-was-synonymous-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To the Paris apartment, which for him was synonymous with promiscuity, he preferred a house with a garden, in countryside which was not really countryside." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/977208-the-plane-that-had-taken-off-from-baltimore-was-caught</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 06:39:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/977208-the-plane-that-had-taken-off-from-baltimore-was-caught]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The plane that had taken off from Baltimore was caught in bad weather, which meant the Derridas missed their connection at Boston. Derrida found this delay and the whole chaotic journey a real trial. On the flight the following day, he spent the whole time tense and hunched up, clenching his fists tightly. And when Marguerite coaxed him to relax, he replied, furiously: ‘Don’t you realize that I’m keeping the plane in the air by the sole force of my will?’ He was traumatized for a long time, and for several years he refused to get back into a plane." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/977308-the-time-for-argument-was-over-foucault-wanted-to-crush</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 08:34:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/977308-the-time-for-argument-was-over-foucault-wanted-to-crush]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The time for argument was over: Foucault wanted to crush an enemy, even though he claimed he loathed this kind of attack, in one of his last interviews.*" -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/977311-in-derrida-s-words-anti-oedipus-was-a-very-bad-book-confused</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 08:36:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/977311-in-derrida-s-words-anti-oedipus-was-a-very-bad-book-confused]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In Derrida’s words, Anti-Oedipus was a ‘very bad book (confused, full of contorted disclaimers, etc.) but an important symptomatic event, to judge from the demand to which it is clearly meant to supply and the way it has been welcomed by a very broad and dubious sector of opinion’.29" -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/977321-between-derrida-and-women-who-had-been-so-often-ignored</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 08:41:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/977321-between-derrida-and-women-who-had-been-so-often-ignored]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Between Derrida and women (who had been so often ignored by the Western philosophical tradition), an alliance was soon to be formed. A personal factor probably played a part in this process." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/977329-the-review-l-arc-meanwhile-wished-to-devote-a-complete-issue</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 08:51:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/977329-the-review-l-arc-meanwhile-wished-to-devote-a-complete-issue]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The review L’Arc, meanwhile, wished to devote a complete issue to Derrida. Catherine Clément submitted a list of contributors in which there were more writers than philosophers in the traditional sense: Hélène Cixous, François Laruelle, Claude Ollier, Roger Laporte, Edmond Jabès, and so on." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978430-marked-as-it-was-by-the-zeitgeist-glas-can-also</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 10:56:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978430-marked-as-it-was-by-the-zeitgeist-glas-can-also]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Marked as it was by the Zeitgeist, Glas can also be read as a reply to Deleuze and Guattari’s Anti-Oedipus, which had so irritated Derrida." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978496-even-though-spivak-s-translation-met-with-some-criticism-and-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 12:10:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978496-even-though-spivak-s-translation-met-with-some-criticism-and-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even though Spivak’s translation met with some criticism and had to be revised several times, Of Grammatology achieved astronomical sales of nearly 100,000 copies." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978509-jean-his-younger-son-remembers-a-father-who-was-almost</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 12:24:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978509-jean-his-younger-son-remembers-a-father-who-was-almost]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jean, his younger son, remembers a father who was almost always working:" -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978511-what-was-difficult-to-deal-with-was-his-permanent-anxiety</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 12:26:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978511-what-was-difficult-to-deal-with-was-his-permanent-anxiety]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What was difficult to deal with was his permanent anxiety: when we were little, he was afraid we’d go and play outside or wander a bit too far away; later on, motorbikes and drugs were real nightmares for him. When he was angry, this was always due to anxiety, especially if we came home later than we’d said we would." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978532-i-m-going-to-swim-as-much-as-possible-i-m-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 12:39:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978532-i-m-going-to-swim-as-much-as-possible-i-m-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’m going to swim as much as possible. I’m in poor shape physically. I’ve put on weight (as always when I’m tired) and I feel as heavy as a bag of lead." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978588-by-l-vy-s-own-admission-they-were-not-interested-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 13:20:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978588-by-l-vy-s-own-admission-they-were-not-interested-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By Lévy’s own admission, they were not interested in the Haby Reform. They had come to the Estates General spoiling for a fight. ‘Most of those people had continually taken sides against me for two years,’ he relates. ‘I considered them to be my enemies. I said to myself that there were two different ways of defending philosophy. This was the theme of many of my interventions of that time. So I was at war with the university system. And the university system paid me back by being at total war with me.’15" -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978594-b--h-l-vy-i-am-amazed-to-see-that-when-somebody</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 13:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978594-b--h-l-vy-i-am-amazed-to-see-that-when-somebody]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["B.-H. Lévy: I am amazed to see that when somebody (I’ve been given leave to speak, so I will) starts to explain something here, to put on trial the institution of philosophy, to put on trial those men who for years have benefited from this system and who react only when they feel threatened, that person is told to shut up. [. . .] I’m amazed that, when I myself am given leave to speak, a certain number of men come over to grab the mike from me and trigger an incident. As far as I’m concerned, that’s what I wanted to say: I’ve been amazed ever since yesterday to hear people putting the media on trial: do you think it was the philosophy professors who were the first to denounce the Gulag? It was television and the media. Do you think that it’s in his capacity as a philosophy professor that, a year ago, when Brezhnev came to Paris, Glucksmann opened his ‘opinion column’ to three dissidents from the East and caused a scandal? That was the media. It wasn’t the Estates General of philosophy. I’m amazed that today, as 76,000 Vietnamese are castaway by the Malaysian government, nobody even mentions the fact. I’m amazed that, the day before Corsican militants are scheduled to appear in the State security court, including a philosophy teacher, Mondoloni ." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978638-when-he-read-the-text-for-the-first-time-alan</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 14:11:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978638-when-he-read-the-text-for-the-first-time-alan]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When he read the text for the first time, Alan Bass, who was far from being a novice, had the impression that it would be as complicated as trying to translate Joyce into French. Derrida acknowledged that the ‘Envois’ were very encrypted and agreed to provide Bass with explanations, comments, and suggestions whenever required. ‘Most of this work was done by letter,’ Alan Bass recalls. He would send me my pages back with many annotations. But we had at least one long session together in a railway station buffet, while he was between trains. There were many details that would have escaped my notice if he hadn’t drawn my attention to them. For example, in the sentence ‘Est-ce taire un nom?’ [‘Is this to keep silence about a name?’], you also have to read ‘Esther’, which is one of the forenames of his mother, but also a biblical name that plays a very active part in the book. In spite of all my efforts, many of these effects disappeared in the translation.15 Hans-Joachim Metzger, the German translator of The Post Card, would find the work equally demanding. ‘On reading your questions,’ Derrida wrote to him, ‘I see yet again that you have read the text better than I have. That’s why a translator is absolutely unbearable, and the better he is, the scarier he is: the super-ego in person." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978640-but-for-some-readers-especially-derrida-s-closest-friends-the-allusions</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 14:12:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978640-but-for-some-readers-especially-derrida-s-closest-friends-the-allusions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But for some readers, especially Derrida’s closest friends, the allusions to reality at the centre of the ‘Envois’ seemed barely tolerable. Pierre remembers how he recoiled from the work. ‘When The Post Card was published, I sensed how much private life, how many disguised confidences, even how much exhibitionism there was in the book. I had no desire to be confronted with it, at any case in this form, and this no doubt played its part in the fact that I read relatively few of my father’s books.’18" -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978651-but-in-november-the-problem-of-nanterre-raised-its-head</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 14:19:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978651-but-in-november-the-problem-of-nanterre-raised-its-head]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But, in November, the problem of Nanterre raised its head again, now more urgently. One Saturday morning, after an hour’s journey under a heavy downpour, Ricoeur found only one student waiting for him in the room where he was to give his agrégation class. He was furious, and went straight up to the office to ask to take early retirement." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980436-next-to-a-corpus-of-which-the-critic-has-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 21:37:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980436-next-to-a-corpus-of-which-the-critic-has-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Next to a corpus of which the critic ‘has not retained intact a single fragment’,5 he reintroduces the body, including his own penis." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980516-your-favourite-quality-in-a-woman-thought-your-favourite-virtue</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 22:27:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980516-your-favourite-quality-in-a-woman-thought-your-favourite-virtue]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your favourite quality in a woman?: Thought. Your favourite virtue?: Faithfulness." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980520-he-had-a-kind-of-urgent-drive-to-be-forever</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 22:32:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980520-he-had-a-kind-of-urgent-drive-to-be-forever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He had a kind of urgent drive to be forever producing something, to get involved in more and more projects, to leave traces. To the people who, like Claire Nancy, rebuked him sometimes for publishing too much, he replied: ‘I can’t help it. It’s my way of fighting against death." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980525-derrida-had-an-irresistible-desire-to-seduce-and-if-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 22:37:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980525-derrida-had-an-irresistible-desire-to-seduce-and-if-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Derrida had an irresistible desire to seduce. And if he almost never spoke of his relationship to women, this was because his obsession with secrecy was greater in this area than in any other. But many people knew that ‘the feminine’ was, for him, always in the plural. If Derrida vaunted faithfulness in his reply to the Proust questionnaire, this was because every relationship was for him a unique, irreplaceable event; so he felt capable of faithfulness to many people." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980526-as-marguerite-derrida-puts-it-i-ve-always-thought-that-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 22:38:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980526-as-marguerite-derrida-puts-it-i-ve-always-thought-that-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As Marguerite Derrida puts it: ‘I’ve always thought that it was mainly through his capacity for listening that Jacques could seduce women." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980528-in-spite-of-ups-and-downs-the-union-between-jacques</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 22:40:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980528-in-spite-of-ups-and-downs-the-union-between-jacques]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In spite of ups and downs, the union between Jacques and Marguerite remained essential and indestructible. Nothing could undermine it over the forty-eight years of their life together. According to Avital Ronell, ‘Marguerite never considered anyone to be a rival. She always had something nice to say about the women who were close or too close to Jacques, which does not mean that she did not suffer because of them." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980529-ultimately-the-only-thing-that-sometimes-annoyed-marguerite-was-jacques-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 22:42:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980529-ultimately-the-only-thing-that-sometimes-annoyed-marguerite-was-jacques-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ultimately, the only thing that sometimes annoyed Marguerite was Jacques’s jealous temperament. ‘He wasn’t happy when he couldn’t reach me straightaway." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980533-i-now-have-at-home-i-can-freely-admit-three</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 22:46:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980533-i-now-have-at-home-i-can-freely-admit-three]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I now have at home, I can freely admit, three computers and two of then also have a zip drive, an extra hard disk [. . .] and when I write a long text that’s hanging around without being printed out, I never leave the house without making copies of the text in question [. . .]. There are at least ten copies that I leave in different places, because there are also risks of fire, of burglary. And here, in my briefcase, I have my essential current work. This is the neurosis that develops with technology.26" -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980537-avital-ronell-a-committed-vegetarian-relates-that-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 22:49:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980537-avital-ronell-a-committed-vegetarian-relates-that-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Avital Ronell – a committed vegetarian – relates that one day, at a dinner with Chantal and René Major, she let one dish go by without taking a helping, which caused a certain embarrassment. When she said she had perfectly decent philosophical reasons for not eating meat, Derrida turned to ask her what they were. So Avital told him what it meant to her to incorporate the body of the other. Shortly afterwards, Derrida, who was extraordinarily receptive to this kind of thing, started to speak of carnophallogocentrism rather than phallogocentrism. Later on, with me and in front of me, he said he was a vegetarian. But one day, someone told me he had eaten a steak tartare, as carnivorous a kind of food as you can get. For me, it was as if he had betrayed me. When I spoke to him about it, he initially said I was behaving like a cop. Then he said, neatly: ‘I’m a vegetarian who sometimes eats meat." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980538-after-dinners-in-ris-orangis-derrida-would-gladly-offer-to-drive</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 22:50:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Benoît Peeters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980538-after-dinners-in-ris-orangis-derrida-would-gladly-offer-to-drive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After dinners in Ris-Orangis, Derrida would gladly offer to drive home any guests without transport. He enjoyed driving, and always went into Paris by car. He’d learned when still very young, on the job, with his father’s car. But since he had never studied the highway code, he had his own ideas about it, which could sometimes lead to spectacular results. He considered, for example, that most ‘no entry’ signs did not actually apply to him, and that big roads should automatically have priority over smaller ones. At the wheel, he rapidly lost his cool. In traffic jams, he could almost get hysterical. And, to crown it all, whenever he stopped for even a short time he would start taking notes. In a letter to Éric Clémens, he indicated in a PS: ‘Excuse the handwriting, I’m writing in the car (what a life!), but I’ve stopped, not even at a red light. I’ve just thought of the title for a book: Written at a Red Light . . .’33 But while he was not a reassuring figure at the wheel, he never had an accident." -- Benoît Peeters]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
