<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1017840-jan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1017840-jan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 17:42:59 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/426350-who-ever-loved-that-loved-not-at-first-sight-wrote</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 17:42:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by Arthur Phillips]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/426350-who-ever-loved-that-loved-not-at-first-sight-wrote]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who ever loved that loved not at first sight?&quot; wrote Marlowe, the man Shakespeare feared for many years was the better writer, the man who with those words issued a license to misery to millions of underexperienced teenagers and thousands of overeducated middle-aged jackasses." -- Arthur Phillips]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/824667-when-i-run-the-world-librarians-will-be-exempt-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 21:19:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by Karen Joy Fowler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/824667-when-i-run-the-world-librarians-will-be-exempt-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I run the world, librarians will be exempt from tragedy. Even their smaller sorrows will last only for as long as you can take out a book." -- Karen Joy Fowler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/897261-how-angry-am-i-you-don-t-want-to-know-nobody</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 22:23:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by Claire Messud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/897261-how-angry-am-i-you-don-t-want-to-know-nobody]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How angry am I? You don't want to know. Nobody wants to know about that.

I'm a good girl, I'm a nice girl, I'm a straight-A, strait-laced, good daughter, good career girl, and I never stole anybody's boyfriend and I never ran out on a girlfriend, and I put up with my parents' shit and my brother's shit, and I'm not a girl anyhow, I'm over forty fucking years old, and I'm good at my job and I'm great with kids and I held my mother's hand when she died, after four years of holding her hand while she was dying, and I speak to my father every day on the telephone -- every day, mind you, and what kind of weather do you have on your side of the river, because here it's pretty gray and a bit muggy too? It was supposed to say &quot;Great Artist&quot; on my tombstone, but if I died right now it would say &quot;such a good teacher/daughter/friend&quot; instead; and what I really want to shout, and want in big letters on that grave, too, is FUCK YOU ALL." -- Claire Messud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/997733-my-youth-was-the-most-stubborn-peremptory-part-of-myself</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 18:31:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by Susan Choi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/997733-my-youth-was-the-most-stubborn-peremptory-part-of-myself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My youth was the most stubborn, peremptory part of myself. In my most relaxed moments, it governed my being. It pricked up its ears at the banter of eighteen-year-olds on the street. It frankly examined their bodies. It did not know its place: that my youth governed me with such ease didn't mean I was young. It meant I was divided as if housing a stowaway soul, rife with itches and yens which demanded a stern vigilance. I didn't live thoughtlessly in my flesh anymore. My body had not, in its flesh, fundamentally changed quite so much as it now could intuit the change that would only be dodged by an untimely death, and to know both those bodies at once, the youthful, and the old, was to me the quintessence of being middle-aged. Now I saw all my selves, even those that did not yet exist, and the task was remembering which I presented to others." -- Susan Choi]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
