<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1017155-andy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1017155-andy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 18:11:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37722-beware-the-irrational-however-seductive-shun-the-transcendent-and-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 18:11:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andy add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37722-beware-the-irrational-however-seductive-shun-the-transcendent-and-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beware the irrational, however seductive. Shun the 'transcendent' and all who invite you to subordinate or annihilate yourself. Distrust compassion; prefer dignity for yourself and others. Don't be afraid to be thought arrogant or selfish. Picture all experts as if they were mammals. Never be a spectator of unfairness or stupidity. Seek out argument and disputation for their own sake; the grave will supply plenty of time for silence. Suspect your own motives, and all excuses. Do not live for others any more than you would expect others to live for you." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40227-if-a-drought-strikes-them-animals-perish--man-builds-irrigation-canals</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 18:25:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andy add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40227-if-a-drought-strikes-them-animals-perish--man-builds-irrigation-canals]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a drought strikes them, animals perish--man builds irrigation canals; if a flood strikes them, animals perish--man builds dams; if a carnivorous pack attacks them, animals perish--man writes the Constitution of the United States." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45103-said-during-a-debate-when-his-opponent-ridiculously-asserted-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 19:37:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andy add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45103-said-during-a-debate-when-his-opponent-ridiculously-asserted-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[&lt;i&gt;Said during a debate when his opponent ridiculously asserted that atheism and belief in evolution leads to Nazism&lt;/i&gt;:]

Atheism by itself is of course not a moral position or a political one of any kind, it simply is the refusal to believe in a supernatural dimension. For you to say of Naziism, that it was the implementation of the work of [author:Charles Darwin|12793] is a filthy slander, undeserving of you, and an insult to this audience.  [author:Darwin|12793]’s thought was not taught in Germany; [author:Darwinism|12793] was derided in Germany along with every other form of unbelief that all the great modern atheists, [author:Darwin|12793], [author:Einstein|9810] and [author:Freud|10017] were alike despised by the National Socialist regime.

Now, just to take the most notorious of the 20th century totalitarianisms, the most finished example, the most perfected one, the most ruthless and refined one, that of National Socialism, the one that fortunately allowed the escape of all these great atheists, thinkers and many others, to the United States, a country of separation of church and state, that gave them welcome, if it’s an atheistic regime, then how come that in the first chapter of Mein Kampf, that [author:Hitler|30691] says that he’s doing God’s work and executing God’s will in destroying the Jewish people?  How come the fuhrer oath that every officer of the Party and the Army had to take, making [author:Hitler|30691] into a minor god, begins “I swear in the name of almighty God, my loyalty to the Fuhrer?” How come that on the belt buckle of every Nazi soldier it says Gott mit uns, God on our side? How come that the first treaty made by the Nationalist Socialist dictatorship, the very first is with the Vatican? It’s exchanging political control of Germany for Catholic control of German education. How come that the church has celebrated the birthday of the Fuhrer every year, on that day until democracy put an end to this filthy, quasi-religious, superstitious, barbarous, reactionary system. Again, this is not a difference of emphasis between us to suggest that there’s something fascistic about me and about my beliefs is something I won't hear said and you shouldn't believe." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
