<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1017158-samantha]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1017158-samantha" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 13:29:41 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 13:29:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the only people for me are the mad ones, the ones who are mad to live, mad to talk, mad to be saved, desirous of everything at the same time, the ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn like fabulous yellow roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320907-the-whole-universe-was-crazy-and-cock-eyed-and-extremely-strange</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 13:31:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320907-the-whole-universe-was-crazy-and-cock-eyed-and-extremely-strange]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The whole universe was crazy and cock-eyed and extremely strange." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320909-another-hour-it-would-come-streaming-through-the-golden-gate</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 13:37:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320909-another-hour-it-would-come-streaming-through-the-golden-gate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Another hour it would come streaming through the Golden Gate to shroud the romantic city in white, and a young man would hold his girl by the hand and climb slowly up a long white sidewalk with a bottle of Tokay in his pocket. That was Frisco; and beautiful women standing in white doorways, waiting for their men; and Coit Tower, and the Embarcadero, and Market Street, and the eleven teeming hills.
I spun around till I was dizzy; I thought I'd fall down as in a dream, clear off the precipice. Oh where is the girl I love? I thought, and looked everywhere, as I had looked everywhere in the little world below. And before me was the great raw bulge and bulk of my American continent; somewhere far across, gloomy, crazy New York was throwing up its cloud of dust and brown steam. There is something brown and holy about the East; and California is white like washlines and emptyheaded -- at least that's what I thought then." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320911-her-little-shoulders-drove-me-mad-i-hugged-her-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 13:41:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320911-her-little-shoulders-drove-me-mad-i-hugged-her-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her little shoulders drove me mad; I hugged her and hugged her. And she loved it.
'I love love,' she said, closing her eyes. I promised her beautiful love. I gloated over her. Our stories were told; we subsided into silence and sweet anticipatory thoughts. It was as simple as that. You could have all your Peaches and Bettys and Marylous and Ritas and Camilles and Inezes in this world; this was my girl and my kind of girlsoul, and I told her that." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320912-i-d-sleep-and-forget-it-i-had-my-own-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 13:41:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320912-i-d-sleep-and-forget-it-i-had-my-own-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd sleep and forget it; I had my own life, my own sad and ragged life forever." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320914-we-stood-under-a-roadlamp-thumbing-when-suddenly-cars-full</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 13:45:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320914-we-stood-under-a-roadlamp-thumbing-when-suddenly-cars-full]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We stood under a roadlamp, thumbing, when suddenly cars full of young kids roared by with streamers flying. 'Yaah! Yaah! we won! we won!' they all shouted. Then they yoohooed us and got great glee out of seeing a guy and a girl on the road. Dozens of such cars passed, full of young faces and 'throaty young voices,' as the saying goes. I hated every one of them. Who did they think they were, yaahing at somebody on the road just because they were little high-school punks and their parents carved the roast beef on Sunday afternoons? Who did they think they were, making fun of a girl reduced to poor circumstances with a man who wanted to belove?" -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320915-ah-it-was-a-fine-night-a-warm-night-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 13:46:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320915-ah-it-was-a-fine-night-a-warm-night-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ah, it was a fine night, a warm night, a wine-drinking night, a moony night, and a night to hug your girl and talk and spit and be heavengoing. This we did." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320916-the-cowboy-music-twanged-in-the-roadhouse-and-carried-across</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 13:46:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320916-the-cowboy-music-twanged-in-the-roadhouse-and-carried-across]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The cowboy music twanged in the roadhouse and carried across the fields, all sadness. It was all right with me. I kissed my baby and we put out the lights." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322044-if-he-does-go-the-change-will-be-doleful-suppose</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 15:08:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322044-if-he-does-go-the-change-will-be-doleful-suppose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If he does go, the change will be doleful. Suppose he should be absent spring, summer, and autumn: how joyless sunshine and fine days will seem!" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322587-i-look-through-the-window-at-the-huge-valley-lit</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2010 10:44:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Rigoberto Gonzalez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322587-i-look-through-the-window-at-the-huge-valley-lit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I look through the window at the huge valley lit up with different colors. The town is cradled by the dark mountains. From afar it looks as if nothing can get in or out, but judging by the stillness of the view it's as if the citizens have made peace with it and have settled without worry into their insular but protected haven each evening. There are people in the world, I imagine, who are born and die in the same town, maybe even in the same house, or bed. Creatures without migration: have they not lived a life because they have not moved? What of the migratory los González, moving from one place to another and marking every stopping place with angst? What kind of alternative is that? For once my father and I are thinking thinking the same way, sharing a similar yearning for our starting points to have been different, for our final destination to be anything other than the tearful, resentful arrival it is likely to be." -- Rigoberto Gonzalez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191225-nothing-contributes-so-much-to-tranquilize-the-mind-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 14:47:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Mary Wollstonecraft Shelley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191225-nothing-contributes-so-much-to-tranquilize-the-mind-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing contributes so much to tranquilize the mind as a steady purpose a point on which the soul may fix its intellectual eye." -- Mary Wollstonecraft Shelley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61024-i-also-became-a-poet-and-for-one-year-lived</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 14:58:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Mary Wollstonecraft Shelley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61024-i-also-became-a-poet-and-for-one-year-lived]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I also became a poet, and for one year lived in a Paradise of my own creation; I imagined that I also might obtain a niche in the temple where the names of Homer and Shakespeare are consecrated." -- Mary Wollstonecraft Shelley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81414-a-human-being-in-perfection-ought-always-to-preserve-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2011 12:34:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Mary Wollstonecraft Shelley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81414-a-human-being-in-perfection-ought-always-to-preserve-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A human being in perfection ought always to preserve a calm and peaceful mind and never to allow passion or a transitory desire to disturb his tranquility. I do not think that the pursuit of knowledge is an exception to this rule. If the study to which you apply yourself has a tendency to weaken your affections and to destroy your taste for those simple pleasures in which no alloy can possibly mix, then that study is certainly unlawful, that is to say, not befitting the human mind. If this rule were always observed; if no man allowed any pursuit whatsoever to interfere with the tranquillity of his domestic affections, Greece had not been enslaved, Caesar would have spared his country, America would have been discovered more gradually, and the empires of Mexico and Peru had not been destroyed." -- Mary Wollstonecraft Shelley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/330768-alas-why-does-man-boast-of-sensibilities-superior-to-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 18:43:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Mary Shelley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/330768-alas-why-does-man-boast-of-sensibilities-superior-to-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alas! Why does man boast of sensibilities superior to those apparent in the brute; it only renders them more necessary beings. If our impulses were confined to hunger, thirst, and desire, we might be nearly free; but now we are moved by every wind that blows and a chance word or scene that that word may convey to us." -- Mary Shelley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393539-laws-aren-t-ghosts-in-this-country-they-walk-around-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 20:11:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by John Updike]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393539-laws-aren-t-ghosts-in-this-country-they-walk-around-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Laws aren't ghosts in this country, they walk around with the smell of earth on them." -- John Updike]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154951-everybody-who-tells-you-how-to-act-has-whiskey-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 20:12:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by John Updike]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154951-everybody-who-tells-you-how-to-act-has-whiskey-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody who tells you how to act has whiskey on their breath." -- John Updike]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313859-the-fullness-ends-when-we-give-nature-her-ransom-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 20:13:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by John Updike]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313859-the-fullness-ends-when-we-give-nature-her-ransom-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fullness ends when we give Nature her ransom, when we make children for her. Then she is through with us, and we become, first inside, and then outside, junk. Flower stalks." -- John Updike]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401544-he-demonstrated-that-there-was-no-such-thing-as-free</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 14:47:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401544-he-demonstrated-that-there-was-no-such-thing-as-free]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He demonstrated that there was no such thing as free will, since men's creative impulses were determined, as all else, by the economic structure of the epoch in which they lived." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401550-an-open-car-drove-by-fleeing-into-the-country-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 14:53:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401550-an-open-car-drove-by-fleeing-into-the-country-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An open car drove by, fleeing into the country. The car was overfilled with people bound for a picnic. There was a jumble of bright sweaters, and scarfs fluttering in the wind; a jumble of voices shrieking without purpose over the roar of the motor, and overstressed hiccoughs of laughter; a girl sat sidewise, her legs flung over the side of the car; she wore a man's straw hat slipping down to her nose and she yanked savagely at the strings of a ukelele, ejecting raucous sounds, yelling 'Hey!' These people were enjoying a day of their existence; they were shrieking to the sky their release from the work and the burdens of the days behind them; they had worked and carried the burdens in order to reach a goal -- and this was the goal." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401552-i-take-the-only-desire-one-can-really-permit-oneself</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 14:54:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401552-i-take-the-only-desire-one-can-really-permit-oneself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I take the only desire one can really permit oneself. Freedom, Alvah, freedom. . .To ask nothing. To expect nothing. To depend on nothing." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401554-now-take-a-human-body-why-wouldn-t-you-like-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 14:59:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401554-now-take-a-human-body-why-wouldn-t-you-like-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now take a human body. Why wouldn't you like to see a human body with a curling tail with a crest of ostrich feathers at the end? And with ears shaped like acanthus leaves? It would be ornamental, you know, instead of the stark, bare ugliness we have now. Well, why don't you like the idea? Because it would be useless and pointless. Because the beauty of the human body is that it hasn't a single muscle which doesn't serve its purpose, you want to choke it with trimmings, you want to sacrifice its purpose to its envelope -- not knowing even why you want that kind of an envelope? You want it to look like a hybrid beast produced by crossing the bastards of ten different species until you get a creature without guts, without heart or brain, a creature all pelt, tail, claws and feathers? Why? You must tell me, because I've never been able to understand it." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105839-the-cards-are-stacked-quite-properly-i-imagine-against-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 19:24:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105839-the-cards-are-stacked-quite-properly-i-imagine-against-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The cards are stacked (quite properly, I imagine) against all professional aesthetes, and no doubt we all deserve the dark, wordy, academic deaths we all sooner or later die." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105841-and-the-old-horror-of-being-a-professional-writer-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 19:26:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105841-and-the-old-horror-of-being-a-professional-writer-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the old horror of being a professional writer, and the usual stench of words that goes with it, is begining to drive me out of my seat. (Buddy)" -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132372-you-re-lucky-if-you-get-time-to-sneeze-in-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 19:28:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132372-you-re-lucky-if-you-get-time-to-sneeze-in-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're lucky if you get time to sneeze in this goddam phenomenal world." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84940-but-it-s-the-truth-even-if-it-didn-t-happen</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 13:11:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Ken Kesey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84940-but-it-s-the-truth-even-if-it-didn-t-happen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But it's the truth even if it didn't happen." -- Ken Kesey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/745-perhaps-all-the-dragons-in-our-lives-are-princesses-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 19:47:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/745-perhaps-all-the-dragons-in-our-lives-are-princesses-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps all the dragons in our lives are princesses who are only waiting to see us act, just once, with beauty and courage. Perhaps everything that frightens us is, in its deepest essence, something helpless that wants our love." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487180-and-i-wonder-if-beethoven-held-his-breath-the-first</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 20:22:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[samantha add a quote by Andrea Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487180-and-i-wonder-if-beethoven-held-his-breath-the-first]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["and I wonder if Beethoven held his breath
the first time his fingers touched the keys
the same way a soldier holds his breath
the first time his finger clicks the trigger.
We all have different reasons for forgetting to breathe." -- Andrea Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
