<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1018760-sissy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1018760-sissy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 11:20:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19375-humanity-has-advanced-when-it-has-advanced-not-because-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 11:20:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sissy add a quote by tom robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19375-humanity-has-advanced-when-it-has-advanced-not-because-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humanity has advanced, when it has advanced, not because it has been sober, responsible, and cautious, but because it has been playful, rebellious, and immature." -- tom robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12019-when-we-re-incomplete-we-re-always-searching-for-somebody-to-complete</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 11:21:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sissy add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12019-when-we-re-incomplete-we-re-always-searching-for-somebody-to-complete]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we're incomplete, we're always searching for somebody to complete us. When, after a few years or a few months of a relationship, we find that we're still unfulfilled, we blame our partners and take up with somebody more promising. This can go on and on--series polygamy--until we admit that while a partner can add sweet dimensions to our lives, we, each of us, are responsible for our own fulfillment. Nobody else can provide it for us, and to believe otherwise is to delude ourselves dangerously and to program for eventual failure every relationship we enter." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12878-just-because-you-re-naked-doesn-t-mean-you-re-sexy-just-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 11:24:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sissy add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12878-just-because-you-re-naked-doesn-t-mean-you-re-sexy-just-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just because you're naked doesn't mean you're sexy. Just because you're cynical doesn't mean you're cool." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12409-there-are-only-two-mantras-yum-and-yuck-mine-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 11:24:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sissy add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12409-there-are-only-two-mantras-yum-and-yuck-mine-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are only two mantras, yum and yuck, mine is yum." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7514-now-tequila-may-be-the-favored-beverage-of-outlaws-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 11:26:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sissy add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7514-now-tequila-may-be-the-favored-beverage-of-outlaws-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now tequila may be the favored beverage of outlaws but that doesn't mean it gives them preferential treatment. In fact, tequila probably has betrayed as many outlaws as has the central nervous system and dissatisfied wives. Tequila, scorpion honey, harsh dew of the doglands, essence of Aztec, crema de cacti; tequila, oily and thermal like the sun in solution; tequila, liquid geometry of passion; Tequila, the buzzard god who copulates in midair with the ascending souls of dying virgins; tequila, firebug in the house of good taste; O tequila, savage water of sorcery, what confusion and mischief your sly, rebellious drops do generate!" -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18-3-there-are-bears-and-there-are-small-dogs-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 11:27:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sissy add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18-3-there-are-bears-and-there-are-small-dogs-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["3. There are bears and there are small dogs. Be strong like bear! If they take out your teeth, sit on the dogs. Bears always forget they can just sit on the dogs. Sit on the dogs." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37807-i-see-colors-like-you-hear-jet-planes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 11:29:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sissy add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37807-i-see-colors-like-you-hear-jet-planes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I see colors like you hear jet planes." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3418-i-wanted-so-many-times-while-driving-to-flip-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 11:29:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sissy add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3418-i-wanted-so-many-times-while-driving-to-flip-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted so many times while driving to flip, to skid and flip and fall from the car and have something happen.  I wanted to land on my head and lose half of it, or land on my legs and lose one or both.  I wanted something to happen so my choices would be fewer, so my map would have a route straight through, in red.  I wanted limitations, boundaries, to ease the burden; because the agony, Jack, when we were up there in the dark, was in the silence!  All I ever wanted was to know what to do.  In these last months I've had no clue, I've been paralyzed by the quiet, and for a moment something spoke to me, and we came here, or came to Africa, and intermittently there were answers, intermittently there was a chorus and they sang to us and pointing, and were watching and approving, but just as often there was silence, and we stood blinking under the sun, or under the black sky, and we had to think of what to do next." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
