<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1020055-julie-mitchell]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1020055-julie-mitchell" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 14:13:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10046-there-did-not-have-to-be-a-moral-she-need</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 14:13:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10046-there-did-not-have-to-be-a-moral-she-need]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There did not have to be a moral. She need only show separate minds, as alive as her own, struggling with the idea that other minds were equally alive. It wasn't only wickedness and scheming that made people unhappy, it was confusion and misunderstanding, above all, it was the failure to grasp the simple truth that other people are as real as you. And only in a story could you enter these different minds and show how they had an equal value. That was the only moral a story need have." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4735-fate-is-like-a-strange-unpopular-restaurant-filled-with-odd</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 09:55:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4735-fate-is-like-a-strange-unpopular-restaurant-filled-with-odd]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fate is like a strange, unpopular restaurant filled with odd little waiters who bring you things you never asked for and don't always like." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278402-one-of-the-remarkable-things-about-love-is-that-despite</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 19:04:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278402-one-of-the-remarkable-things-about-love-is-that-despite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the remarkable things about love is that, despite very irritating people writing poems and songs about how pleasant it is, it really is quite pleasant." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108850-having-an-aura-of-menace-is-like-having-a-pet</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 19:05:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108850-having-an-aura-of-menace-is-like-having-a-pet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Having an aura of menace is like having a pet weasel, because you rarely meet someone who has one, and when you do, it makes you want to hide under the coffee table." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135255-having-a-personal-philosophy-is-like-having-a-pet-marmoset</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 19:06:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135255-having-a-personal-philosophy-is-like-having-a-pet-marmoset]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Having a personal philosophy is like having a pet marmoset, because it may be very attractive when you acquire it, but there may be situations when it will not come in handy at all." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59558-a-man-of-my-acquaintance-once-wrote-a-poem-called</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 19:07:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59558-a-man-of-my-acquaintance-once-wrote-a-poem-called]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man of my acquaintance once wrote a poem called &quot;The Road Less Traveled&quot;, describing a journey he took through the woods along a path most travelers never used. The poet found that the road less traveled was peaceful but quite lonely, and he was probably a bit nervous as he went along, because if anything happened on the road less traveled, the other travelers would be on the road more frequently traveled and so couldn't hear him as he cried for help. Sure enough, that poet is dead." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/627230-there-s-lots-of-people-will-help-you-with-alcohol-business</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 20:57:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/627230-there-s-lots-of-people-will-help-you-with-alcohol-business]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There’s lots of people will help you with alcohol business, but there’s no one out there arranging little meetings where you can stand up and say, ‘My name is Sam Vimes and I’m a really suspicious bastard." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10087-if-cats-looked-like-frogs-we-d-realize-what-nasty-cruel</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 21:12:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10087-if-cats-looked-like-frogs-we-d-realize-what-nasty-cruel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If cats looked like frogs we'd realize what nasty, cruel little bastards they are.  Style.  That's what people remember." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11285-god-does-not-play-dice-with-the-universe-he-plays</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 21:13:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11285-god-does-not-play-dice-with-the-universe-he-plays]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God does not play dice with the universe; He plays an ineffable game of His own devising, which might be compared, from the perspective of any of the other players [i.e. everybody], to being involved in an obscure and complex variant of poker in a pitch-dark room, with blank cards, for infinite stakes, with a Dealer who won't tell you the rules, and who &lt;i&gt;smiles all the time&lt;/i&gt;." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13375-and-what-would-humans-be-without-love-rare-said-death</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 21:13:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13375-and-what-would-humans-be-without-love-rare-said-death]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And what would humans be without love?&quot;
RARE, said Death." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66591-all-right-said-susan-i-m-not-stupid-you-re-saying-humans</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 21:15:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66591-all-right-said-susan-i-m-not-stupid-you-re-saying-humans]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All right,&quot; said Susan. &quot;I'm not stupid. You're saying humans need... &lt;i&gt;fantasies&lt;/i&gt; to make life bearable.&quot;

REALLY? AS IF IT WAS SOME KIND OF PINK PILL? NO. HUMANS NEED FANTASY TO BE HUMAN. TO BE THE PLACE WHERE THE FALLING ANGEL MEETS THE RISING APE.

&quot;Tooth fairies? Hogfathers? Little—&quot;

YES. AS PRACTICE. YOU HAVE TO START OUT LEARNING TO BELIEVE THE &lt;i&gt;LITTLE&lt;/i&gt; LIES.

&quot;So we can believe the big ones?&quot;

YES. JUSTICE. MERCY. DUTY. THAT SORT OF THING.

&quot;They're not the same at all!&quot;

YOU THINK SO? THEN TAKE THE UNIVERSE AND GRIND IT DOWN TO THE FINEST POWDER AND SIEVE IT THROUGH THE FINEST SIEVE AND THEN &lt;i&gt;SHOW&lt;/i&gt; ME ONE ATOM OF JUSTICE, ONE MOLECULE OF MERCY. AND YET—Death waved a hand. AND YET YOU ACT AS IF THERE IS SOME IDEAL ORDER IN THE WORLD, AS IF THERE IS SOME...SOME &lt;i&gt;RIGHTNESS&lt;/i&gt; IN THE UNIVERSE BY WHICH IT MAY BE JUDGED.

&quot;Yes, but people have &lt;i&gt;got&lt;/i&gt; to believe that, or what's the &lt;i&gt;point&lt;/i&gt;—&quot;

MY POINT EXACTLY." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104638-she-wondered-whether-there-would-ever-come-an-hour-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2013 21:55:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104638-she-wondered-whether-there-would-ever-come-an-hour-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She wondered whether there would ever come an hour in her life when she didn't think of him -- didn't speak to him in her head, didn't relive every moment they'd been together, didn't long for his voice and his hands and his love. She had never dreamed of what it would feel like to love someone so much; of all the things that had astonished her in her adventures, that was what astonished her the most. She thought the tenderness it left in her heart was like a bruise that would never go away, but she would cherish it forever." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328188-i-will-love-you-with-no-regard-to-the-actions</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 20:59:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328188-i-will-love-you-with-no-regard-to-the-actions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will love you with no regard to the actions of our enemies or the jealousies of actors. I will love you with no regard to the outrage of certain parents or the boredom of certain friends. I will love you no matter what is served in the world’s cafeterias or what game is played at each and every recess. I will love you no matter how many fire drills we are all forced to endure, and no matter what is drawn upon the blackboard in blurry, boring chalk. I will love you no matter how many mistakes I make when trying to reduce fractions, and no matter how difficult it is to memorize the periodic table.
I will love you no matter what your locker combination was, or how you decided to spend your time during study hall. I will love you no matter how your soccer team performed in the tournament or how many stains I received on my cheerleading uniform. I will love you if I never see you again, and I will love you if I see you every Tuesday. I will love you if you cut your hair and I will love you if you cut the hair of others. I will love you if you abandon your baticeering, and I will love you if you if you retire from the theater to take up some other, less dangerous occupation. I will love you if you drop your raincoat on the floor instead of hanging it up and I will love you if you betray your father. I will love you even if you announce that the poetry of Edgar Guest is the best in the world and even if you announce that the work of Zilpha Keatley Snyder is unbearably tedious. I will love you if you abandon the theremin and take up the harmonica and I will love you if you donate your marmosets to the zoo and your tree frogs to M. I will love you as a starfish loves a coral reef and as a kudzu loves trees, even if the oceans turn to sawdust and the trees fall in the forest without anyone around to hear them. I will love you as the pesto loves the fettuccini and as the horseradish loves the miyagi, as the tempura loves the ikura and the pepperoni loves the pizza.
I will love you as the manatee loves the head of lettuce and as the dark spot loves the leopard, as the leech loves the ankle of a wader and as a corpse loves the beak of the vulture. I will love you as the doctor loves his sickest patient and a lake loves its thirstiest swimmer. I will love you as the beard loves the chin, and the crumbs love the beard, and the damp napkin loves the crumbs, and the precious document loves the dampness in the napkin, and the squinting eye of the reader loves the smudged print of the document, and the tears of sadness love the squinting eye as it misreads what is written. I will love you as the iceberg loves the ship, and the passengers love the lifeboat, and the lifeboat loves the teeth of the sperm whale, and the sperm whale loves the flavor of naval uniforms. i will love you as a child loves to overhear the conversations of its parents, and the parents love the sound of their own arguing voices, and as the pen loves to write down the words these voices utter in a notebook for safekeeping. I will love you as a shingle loves falling off a house on a windy day and striking a grumpy person across the chin, and as an oven loves malfunctioning in the middle of roasting a turkey.
I will love you as an airplane loves to fall from a clear blue sky and as an escalator loves to entangle expensive scarves in its mechanisms. I will love you as a wet paper towel loves to be crumpled into a ball and thrown at a bathroom ceiling and as an eraser loves to leave dust in the hairdos of people who talk too much. I will love you as a cufflink loves to drop from its shirt and explore the party for itself and as a pair of white gloves loves to slip delicately into the punchbowl. I will love you as the taxi loves the muddy splash of a puddle and as a library loves the patient tick of a clock." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491534-it-s-a-metaphor-see-you-put-the-killing-thing-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 18:54:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491534-it-s-a-metaphor-see-you-put-the-killing-thing-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's a metaphor, see: You put the killing thing right between your teeth, but you don't give it the power to do its killing." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485702-some-people-don-t-understand-the-promises-they-re-making-when-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 21:11:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485702-some-people-don-t-understand-the-promises-they-re-making-when-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people don't understand the promises they're making when they make them,&quot; I said.

&quot;Right, of course. But you keep the promise anyway. That's what love is. Love is keeping the promise anyway." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494769-it-is-always-tedious-when-someone-tells-you-that-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 21:42:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494769-it-is-always-tedious-when-someone-tells-you-that-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is always tedious when someone tells you that if you don't stop crying, they will give you something to cry about, because if you are crying then you already have something to cry about, and so there is no reason for them to give you anything additional to cry about, thank you very much." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/947803-the-song-is-called-the-itsy-bitsy-spider-and-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 21:42:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/947803-the-song-is-called-the-itsy-bitsy-spider-and-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The song is called “The Itsy Bitsy Spider,” and it is one of the saddest songs ever composed. It tells the story of a small spider who is trying to climb up a water spout, but every time its climb is half over, there is a great burst of water, either due to rain or somebody turning the spout on, and at the end of the song, the spider has decided to try one more time, and will likely be washed away once again." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11776-last-night-i-dreamt-i-went-to-manderley-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2014 21:46:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Daphne Du Maurier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11776-last-night-i-dreamt-i-went-to-manderley-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Last night I dreamt I went to Manderley again." -- Daphne Du Maurier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/537031-sometimes-you-read-a-book-and-it-fills-you-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 20:26:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by John Green The Fault in Our Stars]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/537031-sometimes-you-read-a-book-and-it-fills-you-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, you read a book and it fills you with this weird evangelical zeal, and you become convinced that the shattered world will never be put back together unless and until all living humans read the book. And then there are book which you can't tell people about, books so special and rare and yours that advertising your affection feels like a betrayal." -- John Green The Fault in Our Stars]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
