<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1020227-rob]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1020227-rob" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 22:50:19 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19927-a-genuine-work-of-art-must-mean-many-things-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 22:50:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by George MacDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19927-a-genuine-work-of-art-must-mean-many-things-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A genuine work of art must mean many things; the truer its art, the more things it will mean.  If my drawing, on the other hand, is so far from being a work of art that it needs THIS IS A HORSE written under it, what can it matter that neither you nor your child should know what it means?  It is there not so much to convey a meaning as to wake a meaning.  If it do not even wake an interest, throw it aside.  A meaning may be there, but it is not for you.  If, again, you do not know a horse when you see it, the name written under it will not serve you much.  At all events, the business of the painter is not to teach zoology." -- George MacDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37632-i-am-the-twentieth-century-i-am-the-ragtime-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 23:19:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37632-i-am-the-twentieth-century-i-am-the-ragtime-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the twentieth century. I am the ragtime and the tango; sans-serif, clean geometry. I am the virgin's-hair whip and the cunningly detailed shackles of decadent passion. I am every lonely railway station in every capital of Europe. I am the Street, the fanciless buildings of government. the cafe-dansant, the clockwork figure, the jazz saxophone, the tourist-lady's hairpiece, the fairy's rubber breasts, the travelling clock which always tells the wrong time and chimes in different keys. I am the dead palm tree, the Negro's dancing pumps, the dried fountain after tourist season. I am all the appurtenances of night." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47925-literary-fiction-and-poetry-are-real-marginalized-right-now-there-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 13:21:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47925-literary-fiction-and-poetry-are-real-marginalized-right-now-there-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Literary fiction and poetry are real marginalized right now. There's a fallacy that some of my friends sometimes fall into, the ol' &quot;The audience is stupid. The audience only wants to go this deep. Poor us, we're marginalized because of TV, the great hypnotic blah, blah.&quot; You can sit around and have these pity parties for yourself. Of course this is bullshit. If an art form is marginalized it's because it's not speaking to people. One possible reason is that the people it's speaking to have become too stupid to appreciate it. That seems a little easy to me." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62733-for-every-reader-who-dies-today-a-viewer-is-born</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 13:23:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62733-for-every-reader-who-dies-today-a-viewer-is-born]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For every reader who dies today, a viewer is born, and we seem to be witnessing . . . the final tipping balance." -- Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62735-you-are-fiercely-heterosexual-and-well-formed-and-it-s-no-one-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 13:25:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Mark Leyner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62735-you-are-fiercely-heterosexual-and-well-formed-and-it-s-no-one-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are fiercely heterosexual and well-formed, and it's no one's business that you've shrunk your parents and keep them in a terranium, but you have a gatling gun for a mouth, and if that's a diary you're producing from your cleavage, I'm leaving." -- Mark Leyner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62736-i-hurried-away-to-the-white-hall-of-phantasy-heedless</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 13:26:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by George MacDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62736-i-hurried-away-to-the-white-hall-of-phantasy-heedless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hurried away to the white hall of Phantasy heedless of the innumerable forms of beauty that crowded my way: these might cross my eyes, but the unseen filled my brain." -- George MacDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98274-fiction-is-one-of-the-few-experiences-where-loneliness-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2010 12:56:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98274-fiction-is-one-of-the-few-experiences-where-loneliness-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fiction is one of the few experiences where loneliness can be both confronted and relieved. Drugs, movies where stuff blows up, loud parties -- all these chase away loneliness by making me forget my name's Dave and I live in a one-by-one box of bone no other party can penetrate or know. Fiction, poetry, music, really deep serious sex, and, in various ways, religion -- these are the places (for me) where loneliness is countenanced, stared down, transfigured, treated." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/579618-things-happen-when-people-are-not-where-they-belong-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 06:39:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Richard Ford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/579618-things-happen-when-people-are-not-where-they-belong-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things happen when people are not where they belong, and the world moves forward and back by that principle." -- Richard Ford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607432-conversations-with-adults-other-than-a-person-s-parents-had-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 16:31:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Richard Ford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607432-conversations-with-adults-other-than-a-person-s-parents-had-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Conversations with adults other than a person's parents had more of an outcome." -- Richard Ford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607438-no-matter-the-evidence-of-your-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 16:35:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Richard Ford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607438-no-matter-the-evidence-of-your-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[". . . no matter the evidence of your life, or who you believe you are, or what you're willing to take credit for or draw your vital strength and pride from--anything at all can follow anything at all." -- Richard Ford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607445-what-i-know-is-you-have-chance-in-life--of-surviving</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 16:40:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Richard Ford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607445-what-i-know-is-you-have-chance-in-life--of-surviving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I know is, you have chance in life--of surviving it--if you tolerate loss well; manage not to be a cynic through it all; to subordinate,  as Ruskin implied, to keep proportion, to connect the unequal things into a whole that preserves the good, even if admittedly good is often not simple to find." -- Richard Ford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1275422-we-all-have-histories-of-one-kind-or-another-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 10:31:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Richard Ford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1275422-we-all-have-histories-of-one-kind-or-another-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all have histories of one kind or another. Some of us have careers that do fine or that do lousy. Something got us to where we are, and nobody’s history could’ve brought another Tom, Dick or Harry to the same place. And to me that fact limits the final usefulness of these stories. To the extent that it’s incompletely understood or undisclosed, or just plain fabricated, I suppose it’s true that history can make mystery. And I am always vitally interested in life’s mysteries, which are never in too great a supply, and which I should say are something very different from the dreaminess I just mentioned. Dreaminess is, among other things, a state of suspended recognition, and a response to too much useless and complicated factuality. Its symptoms can be a long-term interest in the weather, or a sustained soaring feeling, or a bout of the stares that you sometimes can not even know about except in retrospect, when the time may seem fogged. When you are young and you suffer it, it is not so bad and in some ways it’s normal and even pleasurable. But when you get to my age, dreaminess is not so pleasurable, at least as a steady diet, and one should avoid it if you’re lucky enough to know it exists, which many people aren’t." -- Richard Ford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1280857-what-s-friendship-s-realest-measure-i-ll-tell-you-the-amount-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 18:44:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Richard Ford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1280857-what-s-friendship-s-realest-measure-i-ll-tell-you-the-amount-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What’s friendship’s realest measure? I’ll tell you. The amount of precious time you’ll squander on someone else’s calamities and fuck-ups." -- Richard Ford]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
