<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1021268-erin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1021268-erin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 10:58:18 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181244-off-we-skip-like-the-most-heartless-things-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 10:58:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by J. M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181244-off-we-skip-like-the-most-heartless-things-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Off we skip like the most heartless things in the world, which is what children are, but so attractive; and we have an entirely selfish time, and then when we have need of special attention we nobly return for it, confident that we shall be rewarded instead of smacked." -- J. M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215903-and-the-child-francie-nolan-was-of-all-the-rommelys</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 23:35:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Betty Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215903-and-the-child-francie-nolan-was-of-all-the-rommelys]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the child, Francie Nolan, was of all the Rommelys and all the Nolans. She had the violent weaknesses and passion for beauty of the shanty Nolans. She was a mosaic of her grandmother Rommely's mysticism, her tale-telling, her great belief in everything and her compassion for the weak ones. She had a lot of her grandfather Rommely's cruel will. She had some of her Aunt Evy's talent for mimicking, some of Ruthie Nolan's possessiveness. She had Aunt Sissy's love for life and her love for children. She had Johnny's sentimentality without his good looks. She had all of Katie's soft ways and only half of the invisible steel of Katie. She was made up of all these good and these bad things. 
She was made up of more, too. She was the books she read in the library. She was the flower in the brown bowl. Part of her life was made from the tree growing rankly in the yard. She was the bitter quarrels she had with her brother whom she loved dearly. She was Kitie's secret, desparing weeping. She was the shame of her father staggering home drunk. 
She was all of these things and of something more that did not come from the Rommelys nor the Nolans, the reading, the observing, the living from day to day. It was something that had been born into her and her only- the something different from anyone else in the two families. It was what God or whatever is His equivalent puts into each soul that is given life- the one different thing such as that which makes no two fingerprints on the face of the earth alike." -- Betty Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/589093-in-theory-momentos-serve-to-bring-back-the-moment-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 14:02:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/589093-in-theory-momentos-serve-to-bring-back-the-moment-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In theory momentos serve to bring back the moment. In fact they serve only to make clear how inadequately I appreciated the moment when it was here. How inadequately I appreciated the moment when it was here is something else I could never afford to see." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/612087-i-do-not-know-many-people-who-think-they-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 14:13:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/612087-i-do-not-know-many-people-who-think-they-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not know many people who think they have succeeded as parents. Those who do tend to cite the markers that indicate (their own) status in the world: the Stanford degree....Those of us less inclined to compliment ourselves on our parenting skills, in other words most of us, recite rosaries of our failures, our neglects, our derelictions and delinquencies." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/527790-chucking-her-under-her-chin-he-said-what-are-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 00:51:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/527790-chucking-her-under-her-chin-he-said-what-are-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chucking her under her chin, he said, &quot;What are you doing here, honey? You're not even old enough to know how bad life gets.&quot;

And it was then Cecilia gave orally what was to be her only form of suicide note, and a useless one at that, because she was going to live: &quot;Obviously, Doctor,&quot; she said, &quot;you've never been a thirteen-year-old girl." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214319-next-year-he-did-not-come-for-her-she-waited</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 00:27:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214319-next-year-he-did-not-come-for-her-she-waited]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Next year he did not come for her. She waited in a new frock because the old one simply would not meet, but he never came.
&quot;Perhaps he is ill,&quot; Michael said.
&quot;You know he is never ill.&quot;
Michael came close to her and whispered, with a shiver, &quot;Perhaps there is no such person, Wendy!&quot; and then Wendy would have cried if Michael had not been crying." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216838-all-children-except-one-grow-up-they-soon-know-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 21:09:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216838-all-children-except-one-grow-up-they-soon-know-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All children, except one, grow up. They soon know that they will grow up, and the way Wendy knew was this. One day when she was two years old she was playing in a garden, and she plucked another flower and ran with it to her mother. I suppose she must have looked rather delightful, for Mrs Darling put her hand to her heart and cried, ‘Oh, why can’t you remain like this for ever!’ This was all that passed between them on the subject, but henceforth Wendy knew that she must grow up. You always know after you are two. Two is the beginning of the end." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15669-in-time-they-could-not-even-fly-after-their-hats</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 21:12:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15669-in-time-they-could-not-even-fly-after-their-hats]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In time they could not even fly after their hats. Want of practice, they called it; but what it really meant was that they no longer believed." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57427-all-the-boys-were-grown-up-and-done-for-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 21:12:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57427-all-the-boys-were-grown-up-and-done-for-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All the boys were grown up and done for by this time; so it is scarcely worth while saying anything more about them. You may see the twins and Nibs and Curly any day going to an office, each carrying a little bag and an umbrella. Michael is an engine driver. Slightly married a lady of title, and so he became a lord. You see that judge in a wig coming out at the iron door? That used to be Tootles. The bearded man who doesn't know any story to tell his children was once John." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484518-years-rolled-on-again-and-wendy-had-a-daughter-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 21:14:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484518-years-rolled-on-again-and-wendy-had-a-daughter-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Years rolled on again, and Wendy had a daughter. This ought not to be written in ink but in a golden splash." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/975208-as-you-look-at-wendy-you-may-see-her-hair</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 21:18:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/975208-as-you-look-at-wendy-you-may-see-her-hair]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As you look at Wendy you may see her hair becoming white, and her figure little again, for all this happened long ago. Jane is now a common grown-up, with a daughter called Margaret; and every spring-cleaning time, except when he forgets,Peter comes for Margaret and takes her to Neverland, where she tells him stories about himself, to which he listens eagerly. When Margaret grows up she will have a daughter, who is to be Peter's mother in turn; and so it will go on, so long as children are gay and innocent and heartless." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/600442-the-fear-is-for-what-is-still-to-be-lost</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 21:31:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/600442-the-fear-is-for-what-is-still-to-be-lost]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fear is for what is still to be lost." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/513059-when-i-began-writing-these-pages-i-believed-their-subject</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 21:31:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/513059-when-i-began-writing-these-pages-i-believed-their-subject]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I began writing these pages I believed their subject to be children, the ones we have and the ones we wish we had, the ways in which we depend on our children to depend on us, the ways in which we encourage them to remain children, the ways in which they remain more unknown to us than they do to their more casual acquaintances; the ways in which we remain equally opaque to them." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1015965-we-still-counted-happiness-and-health-and-love-and-luck</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 21:46:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1015965-we-still-counted-happiness-and-health-and-love-and-luck]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We still counted happiness and health and love and luck and beautiful children as &quot;ordinary blessings." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/513062-adoption-i-was-to-learn-although-not-immediately-is-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 11:55:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/513062-adoption-i-was-to-learn-although-not-immediately-is-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Adoption, I was to learn although not immediately, is hard to get right.
As a concept, even what was then its most widely approved narrative carried bad news: if someone &quot;chose&quot; you, what does that tell you?
Doesn't it tell you that you were available to be &quot;chosen&quot;?
Doesn't it tell you, in the end, that there are only two people in the world?
The ones who &quot;chose&quot; you?
And the other who didn't?
Are we beginning to see how the word &quot;abandonment&quot; might enter the picture? Might we not make efforts to avoid such abandonment? Might not such efforts be characterized as &quot;frantic&quot;? Do we want to ask ourselves what follows? Do we need to ask ourselves what words come next to mind? Isn't one of those words &quot;fear&quot;? Isn't another of those words &quot;anxiety&quot;?" -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1150409-one-question-would-you-have-called-buying-pastel-linen-dresses</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 12:00:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1150409-one-question-would-you-have-called-buying-pastel-linen-dresses]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One question: would you have called buying pastel linen dresses for Saigon a mark of 'privilege'? Or would you have called it more a mark of bone stupidity?" -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1150411-once-she-was-born-i-was-never-not-afraid</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 12:01:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1150411-once-she-was-born-i-was-never-not-afraid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once she was born, I was never not afraid." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162092-it-s-come-at-last-she-thought-the-time-when-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 11:01:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Betty Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162092-it-s-come-at-last-she-thought-the-time-when-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's come at last,&quot; she thought, &quot;the time when you can no longer stand between your children and heartache.  When there wasn't enough food in the house you pretended that you weren't hungry so they could have more.  In the cold of a winter's night you got up and put your blanket on their bed so they wouldn't be cold.  You'd kill anyone who tried to harm them - I tried my best to kill that man in the hallway.  Then one sunny day, they walk out in all innocence and they walk right into the grief that you'd give your life to spare them from." -- Betty Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
