<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1021858-michael]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1021858-michael" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 10:22:17 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147877-i-hoisted-the-lid-off-the-spode-vegetable-dish-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 10:22:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Alan Bradley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147877-i-hoisted-the-lid-off-the-spode-vegetable-dish-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hoisted the lid off the Spode vegetable dish and, from the depths of its hand-painted butterflies and raspberries, spooned out a generous helping of peas. Using my knife as a ruler and my fork as a prod, I marshaled the peas so that they formed meticulous rows and columns across my plate: rank upon rank of little green spheres, spaced with a precision that would have delighted the heart of the most exacting Swiss watchmaker. Then, beginning at the bottom left, I speared the first pea with my fork and ate it." -- Alan Bradley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147879-it-is-not-unknown-for-fathers-with-a-brace-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 10:25:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Alan Bradley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147879-it-is-not-unknown-for-fathers-with-a-brace-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not unknown for fathers with a brace of daughters to reel off their names in order of birth when summoning the youngest, and I had long ago become accustomed to being called 'Ophelia Daphne Flavia, damn it." -- Alan Bradley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147881-whenever-i-m-out-of-doors-and-find-myself-wanting-to-have-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 10:26:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Alan Bradley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147881-whenever-i-m-out-of-doors-and-find-myself-wanting-to-have-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever I'm out-of-doors and find myself wanting to have a first-rate think, I fling myself down on my back, throw my arms and legs out so that I look like an asterisk, and gaze at the sky. " -- Alan Bradley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179525-the-rain-made-for-an-odd-effect-forty-floors-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 08:34:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Jonathan Dee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179525-the-rain-made-for-an-odd-effect-forty-floors-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The rain made for an odd effect forty floors up, because you didn't get to see it hit anything on the way down, it was just a kind of static in the gray air." -- Jonathan Dee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179534-she-had-written-darcy-the-letter-and-posted-it-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 08:48:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Thomas Mullen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179534-she-had-written-darcy-the-letter-and-posted-it-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had written Darcy the letter and posted it from her husband's tenth-story office while he was away in some strumpet's bed. And then she'd transformed herself into a bird, and then an anvil, and then a corpse." -- Thomas Mullen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257082-he-was-telling-me-that-our-country-s-blood-soaked-and-atrocity-littered</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2010 19:00:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Wes  Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257082-he-was-telling-me-that-our-country-s-blood-soaked-and-atrocity-littered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...he was telling me that our [country's] blood-soaked and atrocity-littered past was important but that the future didn't have to be its slave." -- Wes  Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296326-and-so-now-having-been-born-i-m-going-to-rewind</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 06:21:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296326-and-so-now-having-been-born-i-m-going-to-rewind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And so now, having been born, I'm going to rewind the film, so that my pink blanket flies off, my crib scoots across the floor as my umbilical cord reattaches, and I cry out as I'm sucked back between my mother's legs. She gets really fat again. Then back some more as a spoon stops swinging and a thermometer goes back into its velvet case. Sputnik chases its rocket trail back to the launching pad and polio stalks the land. There's a quick shot of my father as a twenty-year-old clarinetist, playing an Artie Shaw number into the phone, and then he's in church, age eight, being scandalized by the price of candles; and next my grandfather is untaping his first U.S. dollar bill over a cash register in 1931. Then we're out of America completely; we're in the middle of the ocean, the sound track sounding funny in reverse. A steamship appears, and up on a deck a lifeboat is curiously rocking; but then the boat docks, stern first, and we're up on dry land again, where the film unspools, back at the beginning..." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296328-my-grandfather-s-short-employ-at-the-ford-motor-company-marked</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 06:26:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296328-my-grandfather-s-short-employ-at-the-ford-motor-company-marked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My grandfather's short employ at the Ford Motor Company marked the only time any Stephanides has ever worked in the automotive industry. Instead of cars, we could become manufacturers of hamburger platters and Greek salads, industrialists of spanakopita and grilled cheese sandwiches, technocrats of rice pudding and banana cream pie. Our assembly line was the grill; our heavy machinery, the soda fountain." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 06:26:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Emotions, in my experience, aren't covered by single words. I don't believe in &quot;sadness,&quot; &quot;joy,&quot; or &quot;regret.&quot; Maybe the best proof that the language is patriarchal is that it oversimplifies feeling. I'd like to have at my disposal complicated hybrid emotions, Germanic train-car constructions like, say, &quot;the happiness that attends disaster.&quot; Or: &quot;the disappointment of sleeping with one's fantasy.&quot; I'd like to show how &quot;intimations of mortality brought on by aging family members&quot; connects with &quot;the hatred of mirrors that begins in middle age.&quot; I'd like to have a word for &quot;the sadness inspired by failing restaurants&quot; as well as for &quot;the excitement of getting a room with a minibar.&quot; I've never had the right words to describe my life, and now that I've entered my story, I need them more than ever. " -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296329-grief-is-what-tells-you-who-you-are-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 06:29:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Gail Caldwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296329-grief-is-what-tells-you-who-you-are-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Grief is what tells you who you are alone." -- Gail Caldwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296331-the-rest-of-the-family-tree-had-a-root-system</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 06:35:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Gail Caldwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296331-the-rest-of-the-family-tree-had-a-root-system]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The rest of the family tree had a root system soggy with alcohol... One aunt had fallen asleep with her face in the mashed potatoes at Thanksgiving dinner; another's fondness for Coors was so unwavering that I can still remember the musky smell of the beer and the coldness of the cans. Most of the men drank the way all Texas men drank, or so I believed, which meant that they were tough guys who could hold their liquor until they couldn't anymore--a capacity that often led to some cloudy version of doom, be it financial ruin or suicide or the lesser betrayal of simple estrangement. Both social drinkers, my parents had eluded these tragic endings; in the postwar Texas of suburbs and cocktails, their drinking was routine but undramatic." -- Gail Caldwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/326021-i-ve-come-to-see-our-central-nervous-system-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 11:56:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Darin Strauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/326021-i-ve-come-to-see-our-central-nervous-system-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've come to see our central nervous system as a kind of vintage switchboard, all thick foam wires and old-fashioned plugs. The circuitry isn't properly equipped; after a surplus of emotional information the system overloads, the circuit breaks, the board runs dark. That's what shock is." -- Darin Strauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154364-in-the-immemorial-style-of-young-men-under-pressure-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 18:42:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154364-in-the-immemorial-style-of-young-men-under-pressure-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the immemorial style of young men under pressure, they decided to lie down for a while and waste time." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392454-best-to-let-the-broken-glass-be-broken-glass-let</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 14:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Colson Whitehead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392454-best-to-let-the-broken-glass-be-broken-glass-let]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Best to let the broken glass be broken glass, let it splinter into smaller pieces and dust and scatter. Let the cracks between things widen until they are no longer cracks but the new places for things. That was where they were now. The world wasn't ending: it had ended and now they were in the new place. They could not recognize it because they had never seen it before." -- Colson Whitehead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411419-she-writes-only-in-pencil-as-if-the-words-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 06:01:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Dawn Tripp]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411419-she-writes-only-in-pencil-as-if-the-words-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She writes only in pencil, as if the words might need to be revoked--borrowed words, for the most part, plucked out of other mouths..." -- Dawn Tripp]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434003-there-are-so-many-people-we-could-become-and-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 13:49:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Dan Chaon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434003-there-are-so-many-people-we-could-become-and-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are so many people we could become, and we leave such a trail of bodies through our teens and twenties that it's hard to tell which one is us. How many versions do we abandon over the years?" -- Dan Chaon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/458598-anger-and-fatigue-well-up-all-over-the-country-fall</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2011 14:22:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Marzena Sowa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/458598-anger-and-fatigue-well-up-all-over-the-country-fall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anger and fatigue well up all over the country. Fall has arrives, with its biting winds, its long rainy evenings. The gloom matches our overall mood. It mirrors the minds of the adults. And we children absorb everything, we drink everything in without anyone noticing, until the moment we get squeezed. We're baby sponges, you can't just wring us out, you have to be careful what you soak us in. Even washed, rinsed, dried a hundred times over, traces still remain in us." -- Marzena Sowa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460463-she-was-a-large-disordered-woman-like-a-child-s-drawing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2011 17:07:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460463-she-was-a-large-disordered-woman-like-a-child-s-drawing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was a large, disordered woman, like a child's drawing that didn't stay within the lines." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497622-the-light-the-sky-the-water-they-were-all-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2012 11:28:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Adam Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497622-the-light-the-sky-the-water-they-were-all-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The light, the sky, the water, they were all things you looked *through* during the day. At night, they were things you looked *into*. You looked *into* the stars, you looked *into* dark rollers and the surprising platinum flash of their caps." -- Adam Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497625-where-we-are-from-s-tories-are-factual-if-a-farmer</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2012 11:31:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Adam Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497625-where-we-are-from-s-tories-are-factual-if-a-farmer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where we are from... [s]tories are factual. If a farmer is declared a music virtuoso by the state, everyone had better start calling him maestro. And secretly, he'd be wise to start practicing the piano. For us, the story is more important than the person. If a man and his story are in conflict, it is the man who must change." -- Adam Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498704-the-next-day-she-was-silent-for-breakfast-she-murdered</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 13:00:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Adam Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498704-the-next-day-she-was-silent-for-breakfast-she-murdered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The next day, she was silent. For breakfast, she murdered an onion and served it raw." -- Adam Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62239-books-are-the-perfect-entertainment-no-commercials-no-batteries-hours</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2012 08:40:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62239-books-are-the-perfect-entertainment-no-commercials-no-batteries-hours]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are the perfect entertainment: no commercials, no batteries, hours of enjoyment for each dollar spent. What I wonder is why everybody doesn't carry a book around for those inevitable dead spots in life." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/591482-technically-just-like-with-the-rings-of-a-tree</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 19:06:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Herman Koch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/591482-technically-just-like-with-the-rings-of-a-tree]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["... technically, just like with the rings of a tree or Carbon-14, it had to be possible to measure the passage of time by the melting of vanilla ice cream." -- Herman Koch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/688812-reading-isn-t-the-opposite-of-doing-it-s-the-opposite-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 08:28:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Will Schwalbe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/688812-reading-isn-t-the-opposite-of-doing-it-s-the-opposite-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reading isn't the opposite of doing, it's the opposite of dying." -- Will Schwalbe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/696894-mom-had-always-taught-all-of-us-to-examine-decisions</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 17:32:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Will Schwalbe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/696894-mom-had-always-taught-all-of-us-to-examine-decisions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mom had always taught all of us to examine decisions by reversibility--that is, to hedge our bets. When you couldn't decide between two things, she suggested you choose the one that allowed you to change course if necessary. Not the road less traveled but the road with the exit ramp." -- Will Schwalbe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/705352-one-of-the-many-things-i-love-about-bound-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 17:35:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Will Schwalbe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/705352-one-of-the-many-things-i-love-about-bound-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the many things I love about bound books is their sheer physicality. Electronic books live out of sight and out of mind. But printed books have body, presence. Sure, sometimes they'll elude you by hiding in improbable places... But at other times they'll confront you, and you'll literally stumble over some tomes you hadn't thought about in weeks or years. I often seek electronic books, but they never come after me. They may make me feel, but I can't feel them. They are all soul with no flesh, no texture, and no weight. They can get in your head but can't whack you upside it." -- Will Schwalbe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/666672-i-often-forget-that-other-people-s-stories-aren-t-simply-introductions</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 17:36:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Will Schwalbe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/666672-i-often-forget-that-other-people-s-stories-aren-t-simply-introductions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I often forget that other people's stories aren't simply introductions to my own more engaging, more dramatic, more relevant, and better-told tales, but rather ends in themselves, tales I can learn from or repeat or dissect or savor." -- Will Schwalbe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/705353-when-you-re-with-someone-who-is-dying-you-may-need</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 17:40:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Will Schwalbe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/705353-when-you-re-with-someone-who-is-dying-you-may-need]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...when you're with someone who is dying, you may need to celebrate the past, live the present, and mourn the future all at the same time." -- Will Schwalbe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/653725-we-re-all-in-the-end-of-your-life-book-club-whether-we-acknowledge-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 17:43:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Will Schwalbe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/653725-we-re-all-in-the-end-of-your-life-book-club-whether-we-acknowledge-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're all in the end-of-your-life book-club, whether we acknowledge it or not; each book we read may well be the last, each conversation the final one." -- Will Schwalbe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/658470-we-all-owe-everyone-for-everything-that-happens-in-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 17:43:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Will Schwalbe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/658470-we-all-owe-everyone-for-everything-that-happens-in-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all owe everyone for everything that happens in our lives.  But it's not owing like a debt to one person--it's really that we owe everyone for everything.  Our whole lives can change in an instant--so each person that keeps that from happening, no matter how small a role they play, is also responsible for all of it.  Just by giving friendship and love, you keep the people around you from giving up--and each expression of friendship or love may be the one that makes all the difference." -- Will Schwalbe]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
