<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1021233-guy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1021233-guy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 22:42:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38085-petruchio-come-come-you-wasp-i-faith-you-are-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 22:42:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Guy add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38085-petruchio-come-come-you-wasp-i-faith-you-are-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Petruchio: Come, come, you wasp; i' faith, you are too angry.
Katherine: If I be waspish, best beware my sting.
Petruchio: My remedy is then, to pluck it out.
Katherine: Ay, if the fool could find where it lies.
Petruchio: Who knows not where a wasp does wear his sting? In his tail.
Katherine: In his tongue.
Petruchio: Whose tongue?
Katherine: Yours, if you talk of tails: and so farewell.
Petruchio: What, with my tongue in your tail? Nay, come again, Good Kate; I am a gentleman." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38088-no-matter-what-terror-the-earth-could-produce---winds</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 22:44:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Guy add a quote by Lorrie Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38088-no-matter-what-terror-the-earth-could-produce---winds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No matter what terror the earth could produce - winds, seas - a person could produce the same, lived with the same, lived with all that mixed-up nature swirling inside, every bit. There was nothing as complex in the world - no flower or stone - as a single hello from a human being." -- Lorrie Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38089-i-love-a-lot-of-people-understand-none-of-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 22:46:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Guy add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38089-i-love-a-lot-of-people-understand-none-of-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love a lot of people, understand none of them..." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11193-love-after-love-the-time-will-come-when-with-elation</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 22:47:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Guy add a quote by Derek Walcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11193-love-after-love-the-time-will-come-when-with-elation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love After Love

The time will come 
when, with elation 
you will greet yourself arriving 
at your own door, in your own mirror 
and each will smile at the other's welcome, 

and say, sit here. Eat. 
You will love again the stranger who was your self.
Give wine. Give bread. Give back your heart 
to itself, to the stranger who has loved you 

all your life, whom you ignored 
for another, who knows you by heart. 
Take down the love letters from the bookshelf, 

the photographs, the desperate notes, 
peel your own image from the mirror. 
Sit. Feast on your life." -- Derek Walcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38091-artists-talk-a-lot-about-freedom-so-recalling-the-expression</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 22:49:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Guy add a quote by John Cage]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38091-artists-talk-a-lot-about-freedom-so-recalling-the-expression]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Artists talk a lot about freedom. So, recalling the expression &quot;free as a bird,&quot; Morton Feldman went to a park one day and spent some time watching our feathered friends. When he came back, he said, &quot;You know? They're not free: they're fighting over bits of food." -- John Cage]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38103-after-all-these-years-i-see-that-i-was-mistaken</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 00:31:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Guy add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38103-after-all-these-years-i-see-that-i-was-mistaken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After all these years, I see that I was mistaken about Eve in the beginning; it is better to live outside the Garden with her than inside it without her." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38104-how-can-it-be-described-how-can-any-of-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 00:33:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Guy add a quote by Lorrie Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38104-how-can-it-be-described-how-can-any-of-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How can it be described? How can any of it be described? The trip and the story of the trip are two different things. The narrator is the one who has stayed home, but then, afterward, presses her mouth upon the traveler’s mouth, in order to make the mouth work, to make the mouth say, say, say. One cannot go to a place and speak of it; one cannot both see and say, not really. One can go, and upon returning make a lot of hand motions and indications with the arms. The mouth itself, working at the speed of light, at the eye’s instructions, is necessarily struck still; so fast, so much to report, it hangs open and dumb as a gutted bell. All that unsayable life! That’s where the narrator comes in. The narrator comes with her kisses and mimicry and tidying up. The narrator comes and makes a slow, fake song of the mouth’s eager devastation." -- Lorrie Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
