<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1022881-aksana]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1022881-aksana" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 19:16:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36027-it-is-in-vain-to-say-human-beings-ought-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 19:16:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aksana add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36027-it-is-in-vain-to-say-human-beings-ought-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is in vain to say human beings ought to be satisfied with tranquillity: they must have action; and they will make it if they cannot find it. Millions are condemned to a stiller doom than mine, and millions are in silent revolt against their lot. Nobody knows how many rebellions besides political rebellions ferment in the masses of life which people earth. Women are supposed to be very calm generally: but women feel just as men feel; they need exercise for their faculties, and a field for their efforts, as much as their brothers do; they suffer from too rigid a restraint, to absolute a stagnation, precisely as men would suffer; and it is narrow-minded in their more privileged fellow-creatures to say that they ought to confine themselves to making puddings and knitting stockings, to playing on the piano and embroidering bags. It is thoughtless to condemn them, or laugh at them, if they seek to do more or learn more than custom has pronounced necessary for their sex." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150402-it-is-hard-work-to-control-the-workings-of-inclination</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 20:48:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aksana add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150402-it-is-hard-work-to-control-the-workings-of-inclination]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is hard work to control the workings of inclination and turn the bent of nature; but that it may be done, I know from experience.  God has given us, in a measure, the power to make our own fate: and when our energies seem to demand a sustenance they cannot get--when our will strains after a path we may not follow--we need neither starve from inanition, not stand still in despair: we have but to seek another nourishment for the mind, as strong as the forbidden fruit it longed to taste--and perhaps purer; and to hew out for the adventurous foot a road as direct and broad as the one Fortune has blocked up against us, if rougher than it." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184216-life-is-so-often-unfair-and-painful-and-love-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2009 21:29:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aksana add a quote by Jenna Blum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184216-life-is-so-often-unfair-and-painful-and-love-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is so often unfair and painful and love is hard to find and you have to take it whenever and wherever you can get it, no matter how brief it is or how it ends." -- Jenna Blum]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
