<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1023808-jennifer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1023808-jennifer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 22:15:20 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/750963-there-is-a-moment-between-sleeping-and-waking-where-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 22:15:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Will Wiles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/750963-there-is-a-moment-between-sleeping-and-waking-where-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a moment between sleeping and waking where one is free. Consciousness has returned, but awareness has yet to rip away the thin screen between the waker and his surroundings, his reality. You float free of context, in no place – not sleeping, not fully awake, not at the mercy of the unknowns of the subconscious, and not yet exposed to the dull knowns of care and routine. It is at this point, between two worlds, that I think I am happiest." -- Will Wiles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/459853-there-will-come-a-time-when-all-of-us-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 22:15:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/459853-there-will-come-a-time-when-all-of-us-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There will come a time when all of us are dead.  All of us.  There will come a time when there are no human beings remaining to remember that anyone ever existed or that our species ever did anything.  There will be no one left to remember Aristotle or Cleopatra, let alone you.  Everything that we did and built and wrote and thought and discovered will be forgotten and all of this will have been for naught.  Maybe that time is coming soon and maybe it is millions of years away, but even if we survive the collapse of our sun, we will not survive forever.  There was time before organisms experienced consciousness, and there will be time after.  And if the inevitability of human oblivion worries you, I encourage you to ignore it.  God knows that’s what everyone else does." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371692-there-is-no-ideal-world-for-you-to-wait-around</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 23:57:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Isaac Marion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371692-there-is-no-ideal-world-for-you-to-wait-around]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no ideal world for you to wait around for. The world is always just what it is now, and it's up to you how you respond to it." -- Isaac Marion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386227-i-want-to-change-my-punctuation-i-long-for-exclamation</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 23:57:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Isaac Marion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386227-i-want-to-change-my-punctuation-i-long-for-exclamation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to change my punctuation. I long for exclamation marks, but I'm drowning in ellipses." -- Isaac Marion]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
