<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1023355-beth]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1023355-beth" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 11:17:32 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19951-a-person-doesn-t-ask-permission-to-fall-in-love-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 11:17:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Ann Rinaldi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19951-a-person-doesn-t-ask-permission-to-fall-in-love-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A person doesn't ask permission to fall in love; not even of themselves." -- Ann Rinaldi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137349-i-also-talk-a-lot-in-deeper-reading-about-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 07:25:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Kelly Gallagher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137349-i-also-talk-a-lot-in-deeper-reading-about-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I also talk a lot in Deeper Reading about the importance that confusion plays. When my students come to me, they think confusion is bad. They are wrong. Confusion is the place where learning occurs." -- Kelly Gallagher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89170-what-it-love-you-ask-dear-child-love-is-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 07:25:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Ann Rinaldi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89170-what-it-love-you-ask-dear-child-love-is-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What it love, you ask. Dear child, love is like the light and there are two kinds, the bursting fireworks of the moment and the solid, fixed stars that sometimes become obscured in the heavens, but are always there, year after year, for a lifetime. You must experience the first in order to appreciate the second." -- Ann Rinaldi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4111-margery-i-blurted-out-in-a-passion-of-frustration-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 13:35:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Laurie R. King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4111-margery-i-blurted-out-in-a-passion-of-frustration-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Margery,&quot; I blurted out in a passion of frustration. &quot;I don't know what to make of you!&quot;

Nor I you, Mary. Frankly, I cannot begin to comprehend the motives of a person who dedicates a large portion of her life to the contemplation of a God in whom she only marginally believes.&quot;

I felt stunned, as if she had struck me in the diaphragm. She looked down at me, trying to measure the effect of her words.

Mary, you believe in the power that the idea of God has on the human mind. You believe in the way human beings talk about the unknowable, reach for the unattainable, pattern their imperfect lives and offer their paltry best up to the beingless being that created the universe and powers its continuation. What you balk as it believing the evidence of your eyes, that God can reach out and touch a single human life in a concrete way.&quot; She smiled a sad, sad smile. &quot;You mustn't be so cold, Mary. If you are, all you will see is a cold God, cold friends, cold love. God is not cold-never cold. God sears with heat, not ice, the heat of a thousand suns, heat that inflames but does not consume. You need warmth, Mary-you, Mary, need it. You fear it, you flirt with it, you imagine that you can stand in its rays and retain your cold intellectual attitude towards it. You imagine that you can love with your brain. Mary, oh my dear Mary, you sit in the hall and listen to me like some wild beast staring at a campfire, unable to leave, fearful of losing your freedom if you come any closer. It won't consume you; I won't capture you. Love does not do either. It only brings life. Please, Mary, don't let yourself be tied up by the bonds of cold academia.&quot;

Her words, the power of her conviction, broke over me like a great wave, inundating me, robbing me of breath, and, as they receded in the room, they pulled hard at me to folllow. I struggled to keep my footing against the wash of Margery's vision, and only when it began to lose its strength, dissipated against the silence in the room, was I seized by a sudden terror at the nearness of my escape." -- Laurie R. King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17350-sorry-hamlet-said-rubbing-his-temples-i-don-t-know-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 14:03:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Jasper Fforde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17350-sorry-hamlet-said-rubbing-his-temples-i-don-t-know-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sorry,&quot; [Hamlet] said, rubbing his temples. &quot;I don't know what came over me. All of a sudden I had this overwhelming desire to talk for a very long time without actually doing anything." -- Jasper Fforde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189071-religion-isn-t-the-cause-of-wars-it-s-the-excuse</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 14:05:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Jasper Fforde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189071-religion-isn-t-the-cause-of-wars-it-s-the-excuse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Religion isn't the cause of wars, it's the excuse." -- Jasper Fforde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58314-it-s-simple-if-you-go-to-see-saturday-night-fever</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 14:06:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Jasper Fforde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58314-it-s-simple-if-you-go-to-see-saturday-night-fever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's simple. If you go to see 'Saturday Night Fever' expecting it to be good, it's a corker. However, if you go expecting it to be a crock of shit, it's that, too. Thus 'Saturday Night Fever' can exist in two mutually opposing states at the very same time, yet only by the weight of our expectations. From this principle we can deduce that any opposing states can be governed by human expectation - even, as in the case of retro-deficit-engineering, the present use of a future technology.&quot; 

&quot;I think I understand that. Does it work with any John Travolta movie?&quot; 

&quot;Only the artistically ambiguous ones such as 'Pulp Fiction' or 'Face/Off.' 'Battlefield Earth' doesn't work, because it's a stinker no matter how much you think you're going to like it, and 'Get Shorty' doesn't work either, because you'd be hard-pressed not to enjoy it, irrespective of any preconceived notions." -- Jasper Fforde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14876-prejudices-it-is-well-known-are-most-difficult-to-eradicate</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 06:43:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14876-prejudices-it-is-well-known-are-most-difficult-to-eradicate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Prejudices, it is well known, are most difficult to eradicate from the heart whose soil has never been loosened or fertilised by education: they grow there, firm as weeds among stones." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117583-who-is-more-humble-the-scientist-who-looks-at-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 07:29:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117583-who-is-more-humble-the-scientist-who-looks-at-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who is more humble?  The scientist who looks at the universe with an open mind and accepts whatever the universe has to teach us, or somebody who says everything in this book must be considered the literal truth and never mind the fallibility of all the human beings involved?" -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406772-guys-always-think-tears-are-a-sign-of-weakness-they-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 12:11:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Donna Barr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406772-guys-always-think-tears-are-a-sign-of-weakness-they-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Guys always think tears are a sign of weakness.  They’re a sign of FRUSTRATION. She’s only crying so she won’t cut your throat in your sleep.  So make nice and be grateful." -- Donna Barr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62015-why-can-t-we-get-all-the-people-together-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 16:18:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62015-why-can-t-we-get-all-the-people-together-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why can't we get all the people together in the world that we really like and then just stay together?  I guess that wouldn't work.  Someone would leave.  Someone always leaves.  Then we would have to say good-bye.  I hate good-byes.  I know what I need.  I need more hellos." -- Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229349-well-i-can-understand-how-you-feel-you-worked-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 16:23:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229349-well-i-can-understand-how-you-feel-you-worked-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, I can understand how you feel. You worked hard, studying for the spelling bee, and I suppose you feel you let everyone down, and you made a fool of yourself and everything. But did you notice something, Charlie Brown?&quot; 
&quot;What's that?&quot;
&quot;The world didn't come to an end." -- Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229360-linus-what-s-wrong-charlie-brown-charlie-brown-i-just-got</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 16:24:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229360-linus-what-s-wrong-charlie-brown-charlie-brown-i-just-got]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Linus: What's wrong, Charlie Brown? 
Charlie Brown: I just got terrible news. The teacher says we're going on a field trip to an art museum; and I have to get an A on my report or I'll fail the whole course. Why do we have to have all this pressure about grades, Linus? 
Linus: Well, I think that the purpose of going to school is to get good grades so then you can go on to high school; and the purpose is to study hard so you can get good grades so you can go to college; and the purpose of going to college is so you can get good grades so you can go on to graduate school; and the purpose of that is to work hard and get good grades so we can get a job and be successful so that we can get married and have kids so we can send them to grammar school to get good grades so they can go to high school to get good grades so they can go to college and work hard... 
Charlie Brown: Good grief!" -- Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99044-i-was-fifteen-when-i-first-met-sherlock-holmes-fifteen</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 21:08:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Laurie R. King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99044-i-was-fifteen-when-i-first-met-sherlock-holmes-fifteen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was fifteen when I first met Sherlock Holmes, fifteen years old with my nose in a book as I walked the Sussex Downs, and nearly stepped on him. In my defense I must say it was an engrossing book, and it was very rare to come across another person in that particular part of the world in that war year of 1915." -- Laurie R. King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445645-ma-alesh-no-matter-never-mind-what-can-you-do-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 21:10:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Laurie R. King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445645-ma-alesh-no-matter-never-mind-what-can-you-do-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ma'alesh; no matter; never mind; what can you do but accept things as they are? Ma'alesh, your pot overturned in the fire; ma'alesh, your prize mare died; ma'alesh, you lost all your possessions and half your family. The word was the everyday essence of Islam - which itself, after all, means &quot;submission." -- Laurie R. King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25106-do-one-thing-every-day-that-scares-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 16:11:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25106-do-one-thing-every-day-that-scares-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do one thing every day that scares you." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2627-the-trouble-with-having-an-open-mind-of-course-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 11:36:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2627-the-trouble-with-having-an-open-mind-of-course-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble with having an open mind, of course, is that people will insist on coming along and trying to put things in it." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57741-dumbledore-watched-her-fly-away-and-as-her-silvery-glow</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 09:18:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57741-dumbledore-watched-her-fly-away-and-as-her-silvery-glow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dumbledore watched her fly away, and as her silvery glow faded he turned back to Snape, and his eyes were full of tears.
&quot;After all this time?&quot;
&quot;Always,&quot; said Snape." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
