<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1023151-jennifer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1023151-jennifer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 13:20:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004-we-are-cups-constantly-and-quietly-being-filled-the-trick</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 13:20:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004-we-are-cups-constantly-and-quietly-being-filled-the-trick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are cups, constantly and quietly being filled. The trick is, knowing how to tip ourselves over and let the beautiful stuff out." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 13:21:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41667-whether-i-shall-turn-out-to-be-the-hero-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 13:21:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41667-whether-i-shall-turn-out-to-be-the-hero-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whether I shall turn out to be the hero of my own life, or whether that station will be held by anybody else, these pages must show." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43770-i-dream-of-land-cut-only-where-streams-glistened-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 13:24:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Nancy E. Turner ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43770-i-dream-of-land-cut-only-where-streams-glistened-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I dream of land, cut only where streams glistened with birdsong wander through quiet hills burnt hard by the scrape of wind, and of a porch from which a single road leads only homeward.  " -- Nancy E. Turner ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43773-not-i-nor-anyone-else-can-travel-that-road-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 13:25:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43773-not-i-nor-anyone-else-can-travel-that-road-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not I, nor anyone else can travel that road for you.
You must travel it by yourself.
It is not far.  It is within reach.
Perhaps you have been on it since you were born, and did not know.  
Perhaps it is everywhere - on water and land." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43774-who-am-i-i-am-not-a-disease-nor-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 13:26:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Erica Orloff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43774-who-am-i-i-am-not-a-disease-nor-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who Am I? I am not a disease, nor my weight, nor even my family. I am not my job, or my things, or the house I live in. I am not the words used to describe me (quiet or boring or something else I haven't thought of), the books I read, or the clothes I wear. I am not what you see, on the outside or what I say or even the things I do. It's all illusory. I am, instead, this essence inside. I am the strength that gives me breath each day. I am the love I feel within. I am a light in the dark. I am a little piece of this universe. I am human. I am silence. I am hope burning. I am kindness. I am laughter. I am all of these things. I am." -- Erica Orloff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 13:32:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to write the book that wants to be written. And if the book will be too difficult for grown-ups, then you write it for children." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 13:32:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finish each day and be done with it. You have done what you could.  Some blunders and absurdities no doubt crept in; forget them as soon as you can. Tomorrow is a new day.  You shall begin it serenely and with too high a spirit to be encumbered with your old nonsense." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 13:32:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11193-love-after-love-the-time-will-come-when-with-elation</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 13:34:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Derek Walcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11193-love-after-love-the-time-will-come-when-with-elation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love After Love

The time will come 
when, with elation 
you will greet yourself arriving 
at your own door, in your own mirror 
and each will smile at the other's welcome, 

and say, sit here. Eat. 
You will love again the stranger who was your self.
Give wine. Give bread. Give back your heart 
to itself, to the stranger who has loved you 

all your life, whom you ignored 
for another, who knows you by heart. 
Take down the love letters from the bookshelf, 

the photographs, the desperate notes, 
peel your own image from the mirror. 
Sit. Feast on your life." -- Derek Walcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 06:52:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opposite of love is not hate, it's indifference. The opposite of art is not ugliness, it's indifference. The opposite of faith is not heresy, it's indifference. And the opposite of life is not death, it's indifference." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 06:53:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that is gold does not glitter,
Not all those who wander are lost;
The old that is strong does not wither,
Deep roots are not reached by the frost.

From the ashes a fire shall be woken,
A light from the shadows shall spring;
Renewed shall be blade that was broken,
The crownless again shall be king." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 06:53:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be yourself in a world that is constantly trying to make you something else is the greatest accomplishment." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17062-i-do-not-want-people-to-be-very-agreeable-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 06:54:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17062-i-do-not-want-people-to-be-very-agreeable-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not want people to be very agreeable, as it saves me the trouble of liking them a great deal." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2279-being-deeply-loved-by-someone-gives-you-strength-while-loving</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 06:54:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Lao Tzu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2279-being-deeply-loved-by-someone-gives-you-strength-while-loving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being deeply loved by someone gives you strength, while loving someone deeply gives you courage." -- Lao Tzu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 06:55:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the world were merely seductive, that would be easy. If it were merely challenging, that would be no problem. But I arise in the morning torn between a desire to improve the world and a desire to enjoy the world. This makes it hard to plan the day." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 06:55:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is our choices, Harry, that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2008 14:28:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be patient toward all that is unsolved in your heart and try to love the questions themselves, like locked rooms and like books that are now written in a very foreign tongue. Do not now seek the answers, which cannot be given you because you would not be able to live them. And the point is, to live everything. Live the questions now. Perhaps you will then gradually, without noticing it, live along some distant day into the answer." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126353-in-life-a-person-can-take-one-of-two-attitudes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 17:58:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126353-in-life-a-person-can-take-one-of-two-attitudes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In life, a person can take one of two attitudes: to build or to plant.  The builders might take years over their tasks, but one day, they finish what they're doing.  Then they find that they're hemmed in by their own walls.  Life loses its meaning when the building stops.  

Then there are those who plant.  They endure storms and all the vicissitudes of the seasons, and they rarely rest.  But unlike a building, a garden never stops growing.  And while it requires the gardener's constant attention, it also allows life for the gardener to be a great adventure. 

Gardeners always recognize each other, because they know that in the history of each plant lies the growth of the whole World." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126354-you-are-always-someones-favorite-unfolding-story</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 18:07:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Ann Patchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126354-you-are-always-someones-favorite-unfolding-story]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are always someones favorite unfolding story" -- Ann Patchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430-life-is-too-short-or-too-long-for-me-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 18:10:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430-life-is-too-short-or-too-long-for-me-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is too short, or too long, for me to allow myself the luxury of living it so badly." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3583-passion-makes-a-person-stop-eating-sleeping-working-feeling-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 18:10:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3583-passion-makes-a-person-stop-eating-sleeping-working-feeling-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Passion makes a person stop eating, sleeping, working, feeling at peace. A lot of people are frightened because, when it appears, it demolishes all the old things it finds in its path. 

No one wants their life thrown into chaos. That is why a lot of people keep that threat under control, and are somehow capable of sustaining a house or a structure that is already rotten. They are the engineers of the superseded. 

Other people think exactly the opposite: they surrender themselves without a second thought, hoping to find in passion the solutions to all their problems. They make the other person responsible for their happiness and blame them for their possible unhappiness. They are either euphoric because something marvelous has happened or depressed because something unexpected has just ruined everything. 

Keeping passion at bay or surrendering blindly to it - which of these two attitudes is the least destructive? 

I don't know." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22925-we-can-never-judge-the-lives-of-others-because-each</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 18:11:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22925-we-can-never-judge-the-lives-of-others-because-each]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can never judge the lives of others, because each person knows only their own pain and renunciation. It's one thing to feel that you are on the right path, but it's another to think that yours is the only path." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18171-when-i-had-nothing-to-lose-i-had-everything-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 18:11:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18171-when-i-had-nothing-to-lose-i-had-everything-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I had nothing to lose, I had everything. When I stopped being who I am, I found myself." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15209-this-is-what-we-call-love-when-you-are-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 18:11:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15209-this-is-what-we-call-love-when-you-are-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what we call love. When you are loved, you can do anything in creation. When you are loved, there's no need at all to understand what's happening, because everything happens within you." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46264-we-are-travelers-on-a-cosmic-journey-stardust-swirling-and-dancing-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 18:14:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46264-we-are-travelers-on-a-cosmic-journey-stardust-swirling-and-dancing-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are travelers on a cosmic journey,stardust,swirling and dancing in the eddies and whirlpools of infinity. Life is eternal. We have stopped for a moment to encounter each other, to meet, to love, to share.This is a precious moment. It is a little parenthesis in eternity." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20765-i-started-my-life-with-a-single-absolute-that-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 18:15:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20765-i-started-my-life-with-a-single-absolute-that-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I started my life with a single absolute: that the world was mine to shape in the image of my highest values and never to be given up to a lesser standard, no matter how long or hard the struggle." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13799-to-say-i-love-you-one-must-know-first-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 18:16:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13799-to-say-i-love-you-one-must-know-first-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To say &quot;I love you&quot; one must know first how to say the &quot;I&quot;." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23520-why-do-they-always-teach-us-that-it-s-easy-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 18:16:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23520-why-do-they-always-teach-us-that-it-s-easy-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why do they always teach us that it's easy and evil to do what we want and that we need discipline to restrain ourselves? It's the hardest thing in the world--to do what we want. And it takes the greatest kind of courage. I mean, what we really want." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16072-the-unreal-is-more-powerful-than-the-real-because-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2009 20:39:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16072-the-unreal-is-more-powerful-than-the-real-because-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The unreal is more powerful than the real. Because nothing is as perfect as you can imagine it. Because its only intangible ideas, concepts, beliefs, fantasies that last. Stone crumbles. Wood rots. People, well, they die. But things as fragile as a thought, a dream, a legend, they can go on and on. If you can change the way people think. The way they see themselves. The way they see the world. You can change the way people live their lives. That's the only lasting thing you can create." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
