<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1023712-jim]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1023712-jim" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 08:50:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2203-it-is-what-you-read-when-you-don-t-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 08:50:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2203-it-is-what-you-read-when-you-don-t-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is what you read when you don't have to that determines what you will be when you can't help it." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 08:50:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened." -- Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 08:50:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 08:50:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3092-jazz-isn-t-dead-it-just-smells-funny</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 09:25:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3092-jazz-isn-t-dead-it-just-smells-funny]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jazz isn't dead. It just smells funny." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19049-music-is-your-own-experience-your-thoughts-your-wisdom-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 09:25:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Charlie Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19049-music-is-your-own-experience-your-thoughts-your-wisdom-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Music is your own experience, your thoughts, your wisdom. If you don't live it, it won't come out of your horn. They teach you that music has boundaries. But, man, there's no boundary line to art." -- Charlie Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39214-i-will-say-too-that-lovemaking-if-sincere-is-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 09:25:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39214-i-will-say-too-that-lovemaking-if-sincere-is-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will say, too, that lovemaking, if sincere, is one of the best ideas Satan put in the apple she gave to the serpent to give to Eve. The best idea in that apple, though, is making jazz." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71826-and-what-gift-of-america-to-the-rest-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 09:26:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71826-and-what-gift-of-america-to-the-rest-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And what gift of America to the rest of the world is actually most appreciated by the rest of the world? It is African American jazz and its offshoots. What is my definition of jazz? &quot;Safe sex of the highest order." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20870-the-first-rule-is-to-keep-an-untroubled-spirit-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2009 13:47:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20870-the-first-rule-is-to-keep-an-untroubled-spirit-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first rule is to keep an untroubled spirit. The second is to look things in the face and know them for what they are." -- Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84250-anti-intellectualism-has-been-a-constant-thread-winding-its-way-through</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 18:16:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Isaac Asimov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84250-anti-intellectualism-has-been-a-constant-thread-winding-its-way-through]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anti-intellectualism has been a constant thread winding its way through our political and cultural life, nurtured by the false notion that democracy means that &lt;i&gt;'my ignorance is just as good as your knowledge.'&lt;/i&gt;" -- Isaac Asimov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265375-don-t-tell-me-the-sky-s-the-limit-when-there-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 08:15:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Paul Brandt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265375-don-t-tell-me-the-sky-s-the-limit-when-there-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't tell me the sky's the limit when there are footprints on the moon." -- Paul Brandt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42142-there-are-no-ordinary-people-you-have-never-talked-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 07:21:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42142-there-are-no-ordinary-people-you-have-never-talked-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are no ordinary people. You have never talked to a mere mortal. Nations, cultures, arts, civilizations - these are mortal, and their life is to ours as the life of a gnat. But it is immortals whom we joke with, work with, marry, snub and exploit - immortal horrors or everlasting splendors. This does not mean that we are to be perpetually solemn. We must play. But our merriment must be of that kind (and it is, in fact, the merriest kind) which exists between people who have, from the outset, taken each other seriously - no flippancy, no superiority, no presumption." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13641-imagine-yourself-as-a-living-house-god-comes-in-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 07:30:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13641-imagine-yourself-as-a-living-house-god-comes-in-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine yourself as a living house. God comes in to rebuild that house. At first, perhaps, you can understand what He is doing. He is getting the drains right and stopping the leaks in the roof and so on; you knew that those jobs needed doing and so you are not surprised. But presently He starts knocking the house about in a way that hurts abominably and does not seem to make any sense. What on earth is He up to? The explanation is that He is building quite a different house from the one you thought of - throwing out a new wing here, putting on an extra floor there, running up towers, making courtyards. You thought you were being made into a decent little cottage: but He is building a palace. He intends to come and live in it Himself." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47924-some-day-you-will-be-old-enough-to-start-reading</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2013 07:53:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47924-some-day-you-will-be-old-enough-to-start-reading]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some day you will be old enough to start reading fairy tales again." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14451-music-expresses-that-which-cannot-be-put-into-words-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 07:29:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Victor hugo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14451-music-expresses-that-which-cannot-be-put-into-words-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Music expresses that which cannot be put into words and that which cannot remain silent" -- Victor hugo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230027-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 18:55:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230027-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look again at that dot. That's here. That's home. That's us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every &quot;superstar,&quot; every &quot;supreme leader,&quot; every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there-on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam.

The Earth is a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena.  Think of the endless cruelties visited by the inhabitants of one corner of this pixel on the scarcely distinguishable inhabitants of some other corner, how frequent their misunderstandings, how eager they are to kill one another, how fervent their hatreds.  Think of the rivers of blood spilled by all those generals and emperors so that, in glory and triumph, they could become the momentary masters of a fraction of a dot.

Our posturings, our imagined self-importance, the delusion that we have some privileged position in the Universe, are challenged by this point of pale light. Our planet is a lonely speck in the great enveloping cosmic dark. In our obscurity, in all this vastness, there is no hint that help will come from elsewhere to save us from ourselves.

The Earth is the only world known so far to harbor life. There is nowhere else, at least in the near future, to which our species could migrate. Visit, yes. Settle, not yet.  Like it or not, for the moment the Earth is where we make our stand.

It has been said that astronomy is a humbling and character-building experience. There is perhaps no better demonstration of the folly of human conceits than this distant image of our tiny world. To me, it underscores our responsibility to deal more kindly with one another, and to preserve and cherish the pale blue dot, the only home we've ever known." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
