<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1023264-slay-belle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1023264-slay-belle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 07:16:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39983-from-30-feet-away-she-looked-like-a-lot-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 07:16:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Slay add a quote by Raymond Chandler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39983-from-30-feet-away-she-looked-like-a-lot-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From 30 feet away she looked like a lot of class. From 10 feet away she looked like something made up to be seen from 30 feet away." -- Raymond Chandler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39985-in-everything-that-can-be-called-art-there-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 07:21:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Slay add a quote by Raymond Chandler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39985-in-everything-that-can-be-called-art-there-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In everything that can be called art there is a quality of redemption. It may be pure tragedy, if it is high tragedy, and it may be pity and irony, and it may be the raucous laughter of the strong man. But down these mean streets a man must go who is not himself mean, who is neither tarnished nor afraid.

The detective in this kind of story must be such a man. He is the hero; he is everything. He must be a complete man and a common man and yet an unusual man. He must be, to use a rather weathered phrase, a man of honor -- by instinct, by inevitability, without thought of it, and certainly without saying it. He must be the best man in his world and a good enough man for any world. I do not care much about his private life; he is neither a eunuch nor a satyr; I think he might seduce a duchess and I am quite sure he would not spoil a virgin; if he is a man of honor in one thing, he is that in all things.

He is a relatively poor man, or he would not be a detective at all. He is a common man or he could not go among common people. He has a sense of character, or he would not know his job. He will take no man's money dishonestly and no man's insolence without due and dispassionate revenge. He is a lonely man and his pride is that you will treat  him as a proud man or be very sorry you ever saw him. He talks as the man of his age talks -- that is, with rude wit, a lively sense of the grotesque, a disgust for sham, and a contempt for pettiness.

The story is the man's adventure in search of a hidden truth, and it would be no adventure if it did not happen to a man fit for adventure. He has a range of awareness that startles you, but it belongs to him by right, because it belongs to the world he lives in. If there  were enough like him, the world would be a very safe place to live in, without becoming too dull to be worth living in.  " -- Raymond Chandler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 07:22:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Slay add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things need not have happened to be true. Tales and dreams are the shadow-truths that will endure when mere facts are dust and ashes, and forgot." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21491-stories-may-well-be-lies-but-they-are-good-lies</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 07:23:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Slay add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21491-stories-may-well-be-lies-but-they-are-good-lies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories may well be lies, but they are good lies that say true things, and which can sometimes pay the rent." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12414-nothing-which-we-are-to-perceive-in-this-world-equals</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 08:09:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Slay add a quote by e.e. cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12414-nothing-which-we-are-to-perceive-in-this-world-equals]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["nothing which we are to perceive in this world equals 
the power of your intense fragility:whose texture 
compels me with the colour of its countries, 
rendering death and forever with each breathing 

(i do not know what it is about you that closes 
and opens;only something in me understands 
the voice of your eyes is deeper than all roses) 
nobody,not even the rain, has such small hands

-excerpt of #35 from &quot;100 Selected Poems" -- e.e. cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2008 11:47:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Slay add a quote by Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a soul, Doctor. You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; a soul. You &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a body, temporarily." -- Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23652-my-name-is-mary-katherine-blackwood-i-am-eighteen-years</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 19:42:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Slay add a quote by Shirley Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23652-my-name-is-mary-katherine-blackwood-i-am-eighteen-years]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My name is Mary Katherine Blackwood. I am eighteen years old, and I live with my sister Constance. I have often thought that with any luck at all, I could have been born a werewolf, because the two middle fingers on both my hands are the same length, but I have had to be content with what I had. I dislike washing myself, and dogs, and noise. I like my sister Constance, and Richard Plantagenet, and Amanita phalloides, the death-cup mushroom. Everyone else in our family is dead." -- Shirley Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050-dwight-stay-smart-stay-cool-it-s-time-to-prove-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 07:11:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Slay add a quote by Frank Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050-dwight-stay-smart-stay-cool-it-s-time-to-prove-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["DWIGHT:

Stay smart. Stay cool. It's time to prove to you're friends that you're worth a damn. 
Sometimes that means dying. 
Sometimes it means killing a whole lot of people." -- Frank Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181130-i-came-ready-to-fight-genghis-khan-and-i-walk</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 10:37:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Slay add a quote by Richard Kadrey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181130-i-came-ready-to-fight-genghis-khan-and-i-walk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I came ready to fight Genghis Khan and I walk in on a shut-in playing the biggest Dungeons and Dragons game in history." -- Richard Kadrey]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
