<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1024683-kathleen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1024683-kathleen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 15:16:31 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12845-never-confuse-movement-with-action</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 15:16:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12845-never-confuse-movement-with-action]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never confuse movement with action." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6687-road-to-hell-paved-in-unbought-stuffed-dogs-not-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 19:34:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6687-road-to-hell-paved-in-unbought-stuffed-dogs-not-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Road to hell paved in unbought stuffed dogs. Not my fault." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41668-let-other-pens-dwell-on-guilt-and-misery</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 19:34:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41668-let-other-pens-dwell-on-guilt-and-misery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let other pens dwell on guilt and misery." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56217-times-are-bad-children-no-longer-obey-their-parents-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 19:37:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Cicero. M Tullius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56217-times-are-bad-children-no-longer-obey-their-parents-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Times are bad.  Children no longer obey their parents, and everyone is writing a book." -- Cicero. M Tullius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56218-facilis-descensus-averni-noctes-atque-dies-patet-atri-ianua-ditis</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 19:41:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Virgil]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56218-facilis-descensus-averni-noctes-atque-dies-patet-atri-ianua-ditis]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Facilis descensus Averni:
noctes atque dies patet atri ianua Ditis;
sed revocare gradium superasque evadere ad auras.
hoc opus, hic labor est." -- Virgil]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9431-the-only-true-wisdom-is-in-knowing-you-know-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2008 12:19:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Socrates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9431-the-only-true-wisdom-is-in-knowing-you-know-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only true wisdom is in knowing you know nothing." -- Socrates]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56220-mointeach---treoraich-m-each-dhan-aite-sam-bi-na-h-eoin</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 19:45:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Rody Gorman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56220-mointeach---treoraich-m-each-dhan-aite-sam-bi-na-h-eoin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mointeach - treoraich m'each
Dhan aite sam bi na h-eoin a' ceileireadh" -- Rody Gorman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56223-and-oh-man-quo-he-am-i-no-a-bonny</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 19:46:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Robert Louis Stevenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56223-and-oh-man-quo-he-am-i-no-a-bonny]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And 'Oh man!' quo he, 'am I no a bonny fighter?" -- Robert Louis Stevenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22798-the-trouble-is-that-we-have-a-bad-habit-encouraged</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 19:59:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Ursula K. LeGuin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22798-the-trouble-is-that-we-have-a-bad-habit-encouraged]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble is that we have a bad habit, encouraged by pendants and sophisticates, of considering happiness as something rather stupid. Only pain is intellectual, only evil interesting. This is the treason of the artist: a refusal to admit the banality of evil and the terrible boredom of pain." -- Ursula K. LeGuin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25747-the-beet-is-the-most-intense-of-vegetables-the-radish</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 18:24:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25747-the-beet-is-the-most-intense-of-vegetables-the-radish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The beet is the most intense of vegetables. The radish, admittedly, is more feverish, but the fire of the radish is a cold fire, the fire of discontent not of passion. Tomatoes are lusty enough, yet there runs through tomatoes an undercurrent of frivolity. Beets are deadly serious.

Slavic peoples get their physical characteristics from potatoes, their smoldering inquietude from radishes, their seriousness from beets.

The beet is the melancholy vegetable, the one most willing to suffer. You can't squeeze blood out of a turnip...

The beet is the murderer returned to the scene of the crime. The beet is what happens when the cherry finishes with the carrot. The beet is the ancient ancestor of the autumn moon, bearded, buried, all but fossilized; the dark green sails of the grounded moon-boat stitched with veins of primordial plasma; the kite string that once connected the moon to the Earth now a muddy whisker drilling desperately for rubies.

The beet was Rasputin's favorite vegetable. You could see it in his eyes." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192264-yahweh-you-ve-been-unhappy-because-you-ve-desired-things-that-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 16:23:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Mike Carey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192264-yahweh-you-ve-been-unhappy-because-you-ve-desired-things-that-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;b&gt;Yahweh:&lt;/b&gt; You've been unhappy because you've desired things that cannot be.

&lt;b&gt;Lucifer:&lt;/b&gt; That's what desire IS. The need for what we can't have. The need for what's readily available is called greed." -- Mike Carey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198154-they-used-to-call-the-devil-the-father-of-lies</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 16:27:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Mike Carey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198154-they-used-to-call-the-devil-the-father-of-lies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They used to call the devil the father of lies. But for someone whose sin is meant to be pride, you'd think that lying would leave something of a sour taste. So my theory is that when the devil wants to get something out of you, he doesn't lie at all. He tells you the exact, literal truth. And he lets you find your own way to hell." -- Mike Carey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/210973-that-s-what-i-ve-never-been-able-to-get-about-religion</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 16:27:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Mike Carey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/210973-that-s-what-i-ve-never-been-able-to-get-about-religion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's what I've never been able to get about religion: that charmless combination  of altruism and insanity.  Give me a cynical, self-interested bastard any day of the week; at least you can play chicken with him and know he'll stick to the rules." -- Mike Carey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230027-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 12:20:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230027-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look again at that dot. That's here. That's home. That's us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every &quot;superstar,&quot; every &quot;supreme leader,&quot; every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there-on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam.

The Earth is a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena.  Think of the endless cruelties visited by the inhabitants of one corner of this pixel on the scarcely distinguishable inhabitants of some other corner, how frequent their misunderstandings, how eager they are to kill one another, how fervent their hatreds.  Think of the rivers of blood spilled by all those generals and emperors so that, in glory and triumph, they could become the momentary masters of a fraction of a dot.

Our posturings, our imagined self-importance, the delusion that we have some privileged position in the Universe, are challenged by this point of pale light. Our planet is a lonely speck in the great enveloping cosmic dark. In our obscurity, in all this vastness, there is no hint that help will come from elsewhere to save us from ourselves.

The Earth is the only world known so far to harbor life. There is nowhere else, at least in the near future, to which our species could migrate. Visit, yes. Settle, not yet.  Like it or not, for the moment the Earth is where we make our stand.

It has been said that astronomy is a humbling and character-building experience. There is perhaps no better demonstration of the folly of human conceits than this distant image of our tiny world. To me, it underscores our responsibility to deal more kindly with one another, and to preserve and cherish the pale blue dot, the only home we've ever known." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65002-when-you-re-lost-in-those-woods-it-sometimes-takes-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 17:54:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65002-when-you-re-lost-in-those-woods-it-sometimes-takes-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you're lost in those woods, it sometimes takes you a while to realize that you are lost. For the longest time, you can convince yourself that you've just wandered off the path, that you'll find your way back to the trailhead any moment now. Then night falls again and again, and you still have no idea where you are, and it's time to admit that you have bewildered yourself so far off the path that you don't even know from which direction the sun rises anymore." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33460-let-there-be-spaces-in-your-togetherness-and-let-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 19:18:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33460-let-there-be-spaces-in-your-togetherness-and-let-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let there be spaces in your togetherness, And let the winds of the heavens dance between you. Love one another but make not a bond of love: Let it rather be a moving sea between the shores of your souls. Fill each other's cup but drink not from one cup. Give one another of your bread but eat not from the same loaf. Sing and dance together and be joyous, but let each one of you be alone, Even as the strings of a lute are alone though they quiver with the same music. Give your hearts, but not into each other's keeping. For only the hand of Life can contain your hearts. And stand together, yet not too near together: For the pillars of the temple stand apart, And the oak tree and the cypress grow not in each other's shadow." -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150553-there-are-some-people-you-like-immediately-some-whom-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 15:17:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150553-there-are-some-people-you-like-immediately-some-whom-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are some people you like immediately, some whom you think you might learn to like in the fullness of time, and some that you simply want to push away from you with a sharp stick." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115468-the-prophets-accept-all-agony-and-trust-it-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 19:49:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Jelalludin Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115468-the-prophets-accept-all-agony-and-trust-it-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Prophets accept all agony and trust it
For the water has never feared the fire." -- Jelalludin Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2827-if-you-free-yourself-from-the-conventional-reaction-to-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 16:14:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by John McPhee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2827-if-you-free-yourself-from-the-conventional-reaction-to-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you free yourself from the conventional reaction to a quantity like a million years, you free yourself a bit from the boundaries of human time. And then in a way you do not live at all, but in another way you live forever." -- John McPhee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35532-if-by-some-fiat-i-had-to-restrict-all-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 16:14:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by John McPhee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35532-if-by-some-fiat-i-had-to-restrict-all-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If by some fiat I had to restrict all this writing to one sentence, this is the one I would choose: The summit of Mt. Everest is marine limestone. 
" -- John McPhee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129185-beauty-is-terror-whatever-we-call-beautiful-we-quiver-before</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2014 11:51:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129185-beauty-is-terror-whatever-we-call-beautiful-we-quiver-before]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beauty is terror. Whatever we call beautiful, we quiver before it." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242820-it-s-a-very-greek-idea-and-a-very-profound-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2014 11:51:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242820-it-s-a-very-greek-idea-and-a-very-profound-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's a very Greek idea, and a very profound one. Beauty is terror. Whatever we call beautiful, we quiver before it. And what could be more terrifying and beautiful, to souls like the Greeks or our own, than to lose control completely? To throw off the chains of being for an instant, to shatter the accident of our mortal selves? Euripides speaks of the Maenads: head thrown I back, throat to the stars, &quot;more like deer than human being.&quot; To be absolutely free! One is quite capable, of course, of working out these destructive passions in more vulgar and less efficient ways. But how glorious to release them in a single burst! To sing, to scream, to dance barefoot in the woods in the dead of night, with no more awareness of mortality than an animal! These are powerful mysteries. The bellowing of bulls. Springs of honey bubbling from the ground. If we are strong enough in our souls we can rip away the veil and look that naked, terrible beauty right in the face; let God consume us, devour us, unstring our bones. Then spit us out reborn." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65014-could-it-be-because-it-reminds-us-that-we-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2014 11:52:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65014-could-it-be-because-it-reminds-us-that-we-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Could it be because it reminds us that we are alive, of our mortality, of our individual souls- which, after all, we are too afraid to surrender but yet make us feel more miserable than any other thing? But isn't it also pain that often makes us most aware of self? It is a terrible thing to learn as a child that one is a being separate from the world, that no one and no thing hurts along with one's burned tongues and skinned knees, that one's aches and pains are all one’s own. Even more terrible, as we grow old, to learn that no person, no matter how beloved, can ever truly understand us. Our own selves make us most unhappy, and that's why we're so anxious to lose them, don't you think?" -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139342-for-if-the-modern-mind-is-whimsical-and-discursive-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2014 11:52:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139342-for-if-the-modern-mind-is-whimsical-and-discursive-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For if the modern mind is whimsical and discursive, the classical mind is narrow, unhesitating, relentless. It is not a quality of intelligence that one encounters frequently these days. But though I can digress with the best of them, I am nothing in my soul if not obsessive.  " -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
