<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/102619-tshiung-han-see]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/102619-tshiung-han-see" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 20:08:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230027-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 20:08:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tshiung Han add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230027-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look again at that dot. That's here. That's home. That's us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every &quot;superstar,&quot; every &quot;supreme leader,&quot; every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there-on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam.

The Earth is a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena.  Think of the endless cruelties visited by the inhabitants of one corner of this pixel on the scarcely distinguishable inhabitants of some other corner, how frequent their misunderstandings, how eager they are to kill one another, how fervent their hatreds.  Think of the rivers of blood spilled by all those generals and emperors so that, in glory and triumph, they could become the momentary masters of a fraction of a dot.

Our posturings, our imagined self-importance, the delusion that we have some privileged position in the Universe, are challenged by this point of pale light. Our planet is a lonely speck in the great enveloping cosmic dark. In our obscurity, in all this vastness, there is no hint that help will come from elsewhere to save us from ourselves.

The Earth is the only world known so far to harbor life. There is nowhere else, at least in the near future, to which our species could migrate. Visit, yes. Settle, not yet.  Like it or not, for the moment the Earth is where we make our stand.

It has been said that astronomy is a humbling and character-building experience. There is perhaps no better demonstration of the folly of human conceits than this distant image of our tiny world. To me, it underscores our responsibility to deal more kindly with one another, and to preserve and cherish the pale blue dot, the only home we've ever known." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 00:13:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tshiung Han add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opposite of love is not hate, it's indifference. The opposite of art is not ugliness, it's indifference. The opposite of faith is not heresy, it's indifference. And the opposite of life is not death, it's indifference." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5890-be-steady-and-well-ordered-in-your-life-so-that-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 02:05:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tshiung Han add a quote by Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5890-be-steady-and-well-ordered-in-your-life-so-that-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be steady and well-ordered in your life so that you can be fierce and original in your work." -- Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/752558-the-faster-we-walk-the-more-ground-we-lose</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 02:11:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tshiung Han add a quote by Iain Sinclair]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/752558-the-faster-we-walk-the-more-ground-we-lose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The faster we walk, the more ground we lose." -- Iain Sinclair]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178306-life-has-no-meaning-each-of-us-has-meaning-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 05:41:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tshiung Han add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178306-life-has-no-meaning-each-of-us-has-meaning-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life has no meaning. Each of us has meaning and we bring it to life. It is a waste to be asking the question when you are the answer." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70385-the-purpose-of-business-is-to-create-and-keep-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 23:10:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tshiung Han add a quote by Peter Drucker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70385-the-purpose-of-business-is-to-create-and-keep-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The purpose of business is to create and keep a customer." -- Peter Drucker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/558205-we-are-all-so-afraid-we-are-all-so-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 00:00:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tshiung Han add a quote by Ford Madox Ford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/558205-we-are-all-so-afraid-we-are-all-so-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all so afraid, we are all so alone, we all so need from the outside the assurance of our own worthiness to exist. So, for a time, if such a passion come to fruition, the man will get what he wants. He will get the moral support, the encouragement, the relief from the sense of loneliness, the assurance of his own worth. But these things pass away; inevitably they pass away as the shadows pass across sundials. It is sad, but it is so. The pages of the book will become familiar; the beautiful corner of the road will have been turned too many times. Well, this is the saddest story." -- Ford Madox Ford]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
