<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1026782-kisholi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1026782-kisholi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 00:48:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39964-i-personally-believe-we-developed-language-because-of-our-deep</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 00:48:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Jane Wagner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39964-i-personally-believe-we-developed-language-because-of-our-deep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I personally believe we developed language because of our deep inner need to complain." -- Jane Wagner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16568-it-would-seem-that-you-have-no-useful-skill-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 00:54:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16568-it-would-seem-that-you-have-no-useful-skill-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It would seem that you have no useful skill or talent whatsoever,&quot; he said. &quot;Have you thought of going into teaching?" -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10981-when-we-don-t-know-who-to-hate-we-hate-ourselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 01:51:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10981-when-we-don-t-know-who-to-hate-we-hate-ourselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we don't know who to hate, we hate ourselves." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32161-anne-i-don-t-want-to-live-now</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 02:14:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Anne Sexton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32161-anne-i-don-t-want-to-live-now]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anne, I don't want to live. . . . Now listen, life is lovely, but I Can't Live It. I can't even explain. I know how silly it sounds . . . but if you knew how it Felt. To be alive, yes, alive, but not be able to live it. Ay that's the rub. I am like a stone that lives . . . locked outside of all that's real. . . . Anne, do you know of such things, can you hear???? I wish, or think I wish, that I were dying of something for then I could be brave, but to be not dying, and yet . . . and yet to [be] behind a wall, watching everyone fit in where I can't, to talk behind a gray foggy wall, to live but to not reach or to reach wrong . . . to do it all wrong . . . believe me, (can you?) . . . what's wrong. I want to belong. I'm like a jew who ends up in the wrong country. I'm not a part. I'm not a member. I'm frozen." -- Anne Sexton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45521-i-admire-addicts-in-a-world-where-everybody-is-waiting</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 19:17:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45521-i-admire-addicts-in-a-world-where-everybody-is-waiting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I admire addicts. In a world where everybody is waiting for some blind, random disaster or some sudden disease, the addict has the comfort of knowing what will most likely wait for him down the road. He's taken some control over his ultimate fate, and his addiction keeps the cause of his death from being a total surprise." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42723-love-is-so-short-forgetting-is-so-long</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 03:38:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42723-love-is-so-short-forgetting-is-so-long]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is so short, forgetting is so long." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55206-the-universe-contains-any-amount-of-horrible-ways-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 03:52:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55206-the-universe-contains-any-amount-of-horrible-ways-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The universe contains any amount of horrible ways to be woken up, such as the noise of the mob breaking down the front door, the scream of fire engines, or the realization that today is the Monday which on Friday night was a comfortably long way off. 

A dog's wet nose is not strictly speaking the worst of the bunch, but it has it's own peculiar dreadfulness which connoisseurs of the ghastly and dog owners everywhere have come to know and dread. It's like having a small piece of defrosting liver pressed lovingly against you." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31992-a-bone-to-the-dog-is-not-charity-charity-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 08:11:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Jack London]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31992-a-bone-to-the-dog-is-not-charity-charity-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A bone to the dog is not charity. Charity is the bone shared with the dog, when you are just as hungry as the dog." -- Jack London]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2008 02:36:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Emotions, in my experience, aren't covered by single words. I don't believe in &quot;sadness,&quot; &quot;joy,&quot; or &quot;regret.&quot; Maybe the best proof that the language is patriarchal is that it oversimplifies feeling. I'd like to have at my disposal complicated hybrid emotions, Germanic train-car constructions like, say, &quot;the happiness that attends disaster.&quot; Or: &quot;the disappointment of sleeping with one's fantasy.&quot; I'd like to show how &quot;intimations of mortality brought on by aging family members&quot; connects with &quot;the hatred of mirrors that begins in middle age.&quot; I'd like to have a word for &quot;the sadness inspired by failing restaurants&quot; as well as for &quot;the excitement of getting a room with a minibar.&quot; I've never had the right words to describe my life, and now that I've entered my story, I need them more than ever. " -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3463-i-don-t-know-why-we-are-here-but-i-m-pretty</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 02:16:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Ludwig Wittgenstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3463-i-don-t-know-why-we-are-here-but-i-m-pretty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know why we are here, but I'm pretty sure that it is not in order to enjoy ourselves." -- Ludwig Wittgenstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13519-reality-continues-to-ruin-my-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2008 05:08:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Bill Watterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13519-reality-continues-to-ruin-my-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reality continues to ruin my life." -- Bill Watterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/645-it-is-sometimes-an-appropriate-response-to-reality-to-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2008 09:34:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Philip K. Dick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/645-it-is-sometimes-an-appropriate-response-to-reality-to-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is sometimes an appropriate response to reality to go insane." -- Philip K. Dick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40552-i-am-a-sick-man-i-am-a-spiteful-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2008 09:44:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40552-i-am-a-sick-man-i-am-a-spiteful-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am a sick man... I am a spiteful man.  I am an unpleasant man.  I think my liver is diseased.  However, I don't know beans about my disease, and I am not sure what is bothering me.  I don't treat it and never have, though I respect medicine and doctors.  Besides, I am extremely superstitious, let's say sufficiently so to respect medicine.  (I am educated enough not to be superstitious, but I am.)  No, I refuse to treat it out of spite.  You probably will not understand that.  Well, but I understand it.  Of course I can't explain to you just whom I am annoying in this case by my spite.  I am perfectly well aware that I cannot &quot;get even&quot; with the doctors by not consulting them.  I know better than anyone that I thereby injure only myself and no one else.  But still, if I don't treat it, its is out of spite.  My liver is bad, well then-- let it get even worse!" -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73730-for-after-all-you-do-grow-up-you-do-outgrow</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2008 09:50:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73730-for-after-all-you-do-grow-up-you-do-outgrow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For, after all, you do grow up, you do outgrow your ideals, which turn to dust and ashes, which are shattered into fragments; and if you have no other life, you just have to build one up out of these fragments. And all the time your soul is craving and longing for something else. And in vain does the dreamer rummage about in his old dreams, raking them over as though they were a heap of cinders, looking in these cinders for some spark, however tiny, to fan it into a flame so as to warm his chilled blood by it and revive in it all that he held so dear before, all that touched his heart, that made his blood course through his veins, that drew tears from his eyes, and that so splendidly deceived him!" -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132270-we-were-outside-the-world-we-didn-t-even-own-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 02:16:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Kim Stanley Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132270-we-were-outside-the-world-we-didn-t-even-own-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We were outside the world, we didn't even own things -- some clothes. . . . This arrangement resembles the prehistoric way to live, and it therefore feels right to us, because our brains recognize it from 3 millions of years practicing it. In essence our brains grew to their current configuration in response to the realities of that life. So as a result people grow powerfully attached to that kind of life, when they get the chance to live it. It allows you to concentrate your attention on the real work, which means everything that is done to stay alive, to make things, or satisfy one's curiosity, or play. That is utopia." -- Kim Stanley Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47856-i-m-not-sure-what-i-am-i-just-know-there-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 02:16:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Jeff Lindsay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47856-i-m-not-sure-what-i-am-i-just-know-there-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not sure what I am.  I just know there's something dark in me.  I hide it.  I certainly don't talk about it, but it's there always, this Dark Passenger.  And when he's driving, I feel alive, half sick with the thrill of complete wrongness.  I don't fight him, I don't want to.  He's all I've got.  Nothing else could love me, not even... especially not me.  Or is that just a lie the Dark Passenger tells me?  Because lately there are these moments when I feel connected to something else... someone.  It's like the mask is slipping and things... people... who never mattered before are suddenly starting to matter.  It scares the hell out of me." -- Jeff Lindsay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1718-the-very-least-you-can-do-in-your-life-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 02:16:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1718-the-very-least-you-can-do-in-your-life-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The very least you can do in your life is figure out what you hope for. And the most you can do is live inside that hope. Not admire it from a distance but live right in it, under its roof." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2491-i-ll-think-of-it-tomorrow-at-tara-i-can-stand</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 02:16:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2491-i-ll-think-of-it-tomorrow-at-tara-i-can-stand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'll think of it tomorrow, at Tara. I can stand it then. Tomorrow, I'll think of some way to get him back. After all, tomorrow is another day." -- Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108473-i-own-a-crevice-stuffed-with-moss-and-a-couch</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 07:19:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by John A. Haines]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108473-i-own-a-crevice-stuffed-with-moss-and-a-couch]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I own a crevice stuffed with moss
and a couch of lemming fur;
I sit and listen to the music
of water dripping on a distant stone.
Or I sing to myself
of stealth and loneliness

No one comes to see me
but I hear outside
the scratching of claws,
the warm, inquisitive breath … 
(from 'The Hermitage')" -- John A. Haines]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9766-in-the-shop-window-you-have-promptly-identified-the-cover</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 07:19:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9766-in-the-shop-window-you-have-promptly-identified-the-cover]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the shop window you have promptly identified the cover with the title you were looking for. Following this visual trail, you have forced your way through the shop past the thick barricade of Books You Haven't Read, which are frowning at you from the tables and shelves, trying to cow you...And thus you pass the outer girdle of ramparts, but then you are attacked by the infantry of Books That If You Had More Than One Life You Would Certainly Also Read But Unfortunately Your Days Are Numbered. With a rapid maneuver you bypass them and move into the phalanxes of the Books You Mean To Read But There Are Others You Must Read First, the Books Too Expensive Now And You'll Wait Till They're Remaindered, the Books ditto When They Come Out in Paperback, Books You Can Borrow From Somebody, Books That Everybody's Read So It's As If You Had Read Them, Too. " -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28069-i-attempted-briefly-to-consecrate-myself-in-the-public-library</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 07:19:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28069-i-attempted-briefly-to-consecrate-myself-in-the-public-library]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I attempted briefly to consecrate myself in the public library, believing every crack in my soul could be chinked with a book." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52994-what-makes-you-think-human-beings-are-sentient-and-aware</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 07:19:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Michael Crichton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52994-what-makes-you-think-human-beings-are-sentient-and-aware]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What makes you think human beings are sentient and aware? There's no evidence for it. Human beings never think for themselves, they find it too uncomfortable. For the most part, members of our species simply repeat what they are told-and become upset if they are exposed to any different view. The characteristic human trait is not awareness but conformity, and the characteristic result is religious warfare. Other animals fight for territory or food; but, uniquely in the animal kingdom, human beings fight for their 'beliefs.' The reason is that beliefs guide behavior which has evolutionary importance among human beings. But at a time when our behavior may well lead us to extinction, I see no reason to assume we have any awareness at all. We are stubborn, self-destructive conformists. Any other view of our species is just a self-congratulatory delusion. Next question." -- Michael Crichton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63513-the-thought-of-suicide-is-a-great-consolation-by-means</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 07:21:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63513-the-thought-of-suicide-is-a-great-consolation-by-means]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The thought of suicide is a great consolation: by means of it one gets through many a dark night." -- Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68202-some-people-turn-sad-awfully-young-no-special-reason-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 02:57:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68202-some-people-turn-sad-awfully-young-no-special-reason-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people turn sad awfully young. No special reason, it seems, but they seem almost to be born that way. They bruise easier, tire faster, cry quicker, remember longer and, as I say, get sadder younger than anyone else in the world. I know, for I'm one of them." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96080-that-is-another-chamber-of-my-heart-that-shows-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 08:16:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96080-that-is-another-chamber-of-my-heart-that-shows-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That is another chamber of my heart that shows no electrical activity - the chamber that used to flicker into life when I saw a film that moved me, or read a book that inspired me, or listened to music that made me want to cry. I closed that chamber myself, for all the usual reasons. And now I seem to have made a pact with some philistine devil: if I don't attempt to re-open it, I will be allowed just enough energy and optimism to get through a working day without wanting to hang myself." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182195-the-name-is-salvatore-as-in-savior</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 16:41:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by L.J. Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182195-the-name-is-salvatore-as-in-savior]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The name is Salvatore. As in savior." -- L.J. Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83952-drummer-beat-and-piper-blow-harper-strike-and-soldier-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 17:04:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Anne McCaffrey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83952-drummer-beat-and-piper-blow-harper-strike-and-soldier-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Drummer, beat, and piper, blow
Harper, strike, and soldier, go
Free the flame and sear the grasses
Til the dawning Red Star passes" -- Anne McCaffrey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83529-i-couldn-t-possibly-have-sex-with-someone-with-such-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 07:08:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Russell Brand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83529-i-couldn-t-possibly-have-sex-with-someone-with-such-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I couldn't possibly have sex with someone with such a slender grasp on grammar!" -- Russell Brand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/462082-maybe-i-m-strange-and-perverse-but-i-ve-always-thought-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 07:09:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Therese Doucet]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/462082-maybe-i-m-strange-and-perverse-but-i-ve-always-thought-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe I’m strange and perverse, but I’ve always thought there was something sexy about a compelling argument." -- Therese Doucet]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278701-books-are-finite-sexual-encounters-are-finite-but-the-desire</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 07:18:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kisholi add a quote by Roberto Bolano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278701-books-are-finite-sexual-encounters-are-finite-but-the-desire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are finite, sexual encounters are finite, but the desire to read and to fuck is infinite; it surpasses our own deaths, our fears, our hopes for peace." -- Roberto Bolano]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
