<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1027627-marit]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1027627-marit" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2010 11:36:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142274-people-are-afraid-of-themselves-of-their-own-reality-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2010 11:36:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Jim Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142274-people-are-afraid-of-themselves-of-their-own-reality-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People are afraid of themselves, of their own reality; their feelings most of all. People talk about how great love is, but that’s bullshit. Love hurts. Feelings are disturbing. People are taught that pain is evil and dangerous. How can they deal with love if they’re afraid to feel? Pain is meant to wake us up. People try to hide their pain. But they’re wrong. Pain is something to carry, like a radio. You feel your strength in the experience of pain. It’s all in how you carry it. That’s what matters. Pain is a feeling. Your feelings are a part of you. Your own reality. If you feel ashamed of them, and hide them, you’re letting society destroy your reality. You should stand up for your right to feel your pain." -- Jim Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4852-so-this-is-my-life-and-i-want-you-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2010 11:37:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4852-so-this-is-my-life-and-i-want-you-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So, this is my life. And I want you to know that I am both happy and sad and I'm still trying to figure out how that could be." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67508-passion-it-lies-in-all-of-us-sleeping-waiting-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2010 11:37:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67508-passion-it-lies-in-all-of-us-sleeping-waiting-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Passion. It lies in all of us. Sleeping... waiting... and though unwanted, unbidden, it will stir... open its jaws and howl. It speaks to us... guides us. Passion rules us all. And we obey. What other choice do we have? Passion is the source of our finest moments. The joy of love... the clarity of hatred... the ecstasy of grief. It hurts sometimes more than we can bear. If we could live without passion, maybe we'd know some kind of peace. But we would be hollow. Empty rooms, shuttered and dank. Without passion, we'd be truly dead." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178598-gale-is-mine-i-am-his-anything-else-is-unthinkable</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2010 11:43:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178598-gale-is-mine-i-am-his-anything-else-is-unthinkable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Gale is mine. I am his. Anything else is unthinkable." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229349-well-i-can-understand-how-you-feel-you-worked-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 08:57:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229349-well-i-can-understand-how-you-feel-you-worked-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, I can understand how you feel. You worked hard, studying for the spelling bee, and I suppose you feel you let everyone down, and you made a fool of yourself and everything. But did you notice something, Charlie Brown?&quot; 
&quot;What's that?&quot;
&quot;The world didn't come to an end." -- Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49790-if-i-stand-here-i-can-see-the-little-red</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 09:00:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49790-if-i-stand-here-i-can-see-the-little-red]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I stand here, I can see the Little Red Haired girl when she comes out of her house... Of course, if she sees me peeking around this tree, she'll think I'm the dumbest person in the world... But if I don't peek around the tree, I'll never see her... Which means I probably AM the dumbest person in the world... which explains why I'm standing in a batch of poison oak." -- Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82437-you-ll-get-over-it-it-s-the-clich-s-that-cause-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 04:46:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82437-you-ll-get-over-it-it-s-the-clich-s-that-cause-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You’ll get over it…” It’s the clichés that cause the trouble. To lose someone you love is to alter your life for ever. You don’t get over it because ‘it” is the person you loved. The pain stops, there are new people, but the gap never closes. How could it? The particularness of someone who mattered enough to grieve over is not made anodyne by death. This hole in my heart is in the shape of you and no-one else can fit it. Why would I want them to?" -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4141-the-buddhists-say-there-are-149-ways-to-god-i-m</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 04:46:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4141-the-buddhists-say-there-are-149-ways-to-god-i-m]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Buddhists say there are 149 ways to God. I'm not looking for God, only for myself, and that is far more complicated. God has had a great deal written about Him; nothing has been written about me. God is bigger, like my mother, easier to find, even in the dark. I could be anywhere, and since I can't describe myself I can't ask for help." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140515-it-has-been-said-time-heals-all-wounds-i-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 13:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Rose Kennedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140515-it-has-been-said-time-heals-all-wounds-i-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It has been said, 'time heals all wounds.' I do not agree. The wounds remain. In time, the mind, protecting its sanity, covers them with scar tissue and the pain lessens. But it is never gone." -- Rose Kennedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14318-there-s-a-fine-line-between-support-and-stalking-and-let-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2010 11:50:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14318-there-s-a-fine-line-between-support-and-stalking-and-let-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There’s a fine line between support and stalking and let’s all stay on the right side of that." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382184-we-were-as-hansel-and-gretel-and-we-ventured-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 15:10:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Patti Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382184-we-were-as-hansel-and-gretel-and-we-ventured-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We were as Hansel and Gretel and we ventured out into the black forest of the world." -- Patti Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25303-it-may-help-to-understand-human-affairs-to-be-clear</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 06:20:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25303-it-may-help-to-understand-human-affairs-to-be-clear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It may help to understand human affairs to be clear that most of the great triumphs and tragedies of history are caused, not by people being fundamentally good or fundamentally bad, but by people being fundamentally people." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68871-an-angel-who-did-not-so-much-fall-as-saunter</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 06:21:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Neil Gaiman &amp; Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68871-an-angel-who-did-not-so-much-fall-as-saunter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An Angel who did not so much Fall as Saunter Vaguely Downwards." -- Neil Gaiman &amp; Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18344-sometimes-i-lie-awake-at-night-and-i-ask-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 12:38:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18344-sometimes-i-lie-awake-at-night-and-i-ask-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I lie awake at night and I ask, &quot;Is life a multiple choice test or is it a true or false test?&quot; ...Then a voice comes to me out of the dark and says, &quot;We hate to tell you this but life is a thousand word essay." -- Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11867-sometimes-i-lie-awake-at-night-and-i-ask-where</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2012 08:38:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Charlie Schultz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11867-sometimes-i-lie-awake-at-night-and-i-ask-where]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I lie awake at night, and I ask, 'Where have I gone wrong'.
Then a voice says to me, 'This is going to take more than one night." -- Charlie Schultz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411561-there-s-nothing-like-unrequited-love-to-take-all-the-flavor</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2012 08:44:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411561-there-s-nothing-like-unrequited-love-to-take-all-the-flavor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's nothing like unrequited love to take all the flavor out of a peanut butter sandwich." -- Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185805-because-nerds-like-us-are-allowed-to-be-unironically-enthusiastic</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2012 08:46:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185805-because-nerds-like-us-are-allowed-to-be-unironically-enthusiastic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…because nerds like us are allowed to be unironically enthusiastic about stuff… Nerds are allowed to love stuff, like jump-up-and-down-in-the-chair-can’t-control-yourself love it. Hank, when people call people nerds, mostly what they’re saying is ‘you like stuff.’ Which is just not a good insult at all. Like, ‘you are too enthusiastic about the miracle of human consciousness’." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/649723-this-was-the-boy-i-loved-a-little-bit-messy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 13:48:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Michelle Hodkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/649723-this-was-the-boy-i-loved-a-little-bit-messy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This was the boy I loved. A little bit messy. A little bit ruined. A beautiful disaster. Just like me." -- Michelle Hodkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20112-when-adults-say-teenagers-think-they-are-invincible-with-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 07:26:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20112-when-adults-say-teenagers-think-they-are-invincible-with-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When adults say, &quot;Teenagers think they are invincible&quot; with that sly, stupid smile on their faces, they don't know how right they are. We need never be hopeless, because we can never be irreparably broken. We think that we are invincible because we are. We cannot be born, and we cannot die. Like all energy, we can only change shapes and sizes and manifestations. They forget that when they get old. They get scared of losing and failing. But that part of us greater than the sum of our parts cannot begin and cannot end, and so it cannot fail." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257367-the-venn-diagram-of-boys-who-don-t-like-smart-girls</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 13:46:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257367-the-venn-diagram-of-boys-who-don-t-like-smart-girls]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The venn diagram of boys who don’t like smart girls and boys you don’t wanna date is a circle." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/400826-such-lonely-lost-things-you-find-on-your-way-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 10:31:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/400826-such-lonely-lost-things-you-find-on-your-way-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Such lonely, lost things you find on your way.  It would be easier, if you were the only one lost.  But lost children always find each other, in the dark, in the cold.  It is as though they are magnetized and can only attract their like.  How I would like to lead you to brave, stalwart friends who would protect you and play games with dice and teach you delightful songs that have no sad endings.  If you would only leave cages locked and turn away from unloved Wyverns, you could stay Heartless." -- Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297930-when-you-don-t-know-everything-that-you-could-know-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2014 12:06:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Scott Lynch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297930-when-you-don-t-know-everything-that-you-could-know-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you don't know everything that you could know, it's a fine time to shut your fucking noisemaker and be polite." -- Scott Lynch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142853-some-day-locke-lamora-he-said-some-day-you-re-going</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 04:44:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Scott Lynch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142853-some-day-locke-lamora-he-said-some-day-you-re-going]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some day, Locke Lamora,” he said, “some day, you’re going to fuck up so magnificently, so ambitiously, so overwhelmingly that the sky will light up and the moons will spin and the gods themselves will shit comets with glee. And I just hope I’m still around to see it.”
“Oh please,” said Locke. “It’ll never happen." -- Scott Lynch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72745-the-reason-that-the-rich-were-so-rich-vimes-reasoned</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 02:02:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marit add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72745-the-reason-that-the-rich-were-so-rich-vimes-reasoned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The reason that the rich were so rich, Vimes reasoned, was because they managed to spend less money.

Take boots, for example. He earned thirty-eight dollars a month plus allowances. A really good pair of leather boots cost fifty dollars. But an affordable pair of boots, which were sort of OK for a season or two and then leaked like hell when the cardboard gave out, cost about ten dollars. Those were the kind of boots Vimes always bought, and wore until the soles were so thin that he could tell where he was in Ankh-Morpork on a foggy night by the feel of the cobbles.

But the thing was that good boots lasted for years and years. A man who could afford fifty dollars had a pair of boots that'd still be keeping his feet dry in ten years' time, while the poor man who could only afford cheap boots would have spent a hundred dollars on boots in the same time and would still have wet feet.

This was the Captain Samuel Vimes 'Boots' theory of socioeconomic unfairness." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
