<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1027995-j-aleksandr-wootton]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1027995-j-aleksandr-wootton" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:43:17 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166132-the-telephone-bell-was-ringing-wildly-but-without-result-since</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:43:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Charles Walter Stansby Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166132-the-telephone-bell-was-ringing-wildly-but-without-result-since]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The telephone bell was ringing wildly, but without result, since there was no-one in the room but the corpse." -- Charles Walter Stansby Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:44:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:44:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:46:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16261-life-is-a-disease-sexually-transmitted-and-invariably-fatal</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:46:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16261-life-is-a-disease-sexually-transmitted-and-invariably-fatal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is a disease: sexually transmitted, and invariably fatal." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:47:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I say is, a town isn't a town without a bookstore. It may call itself a town, but unless it's got a bookstore it knows it's not fooling a soul." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:48:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things need not have happened to be true. Tales and dreams are the shadow-truths that will endure when mere facts are dust and ashes, and forgot." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58240-being-a-writer-is-a-very-peculiar-sort-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:49:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58240-being-a-writer-is-a-very-peculiar-sort-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being a writer is a very peculiar sort of a job: it's always you versus a blank sheet of paper (or a blank screen) and quite often the blank piece of paper wins." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81428-d-on-t-ever-apologize-to-an-author-for-buying-something-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:49:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81428-d-on-t-ever-apologize-to-an-author-for-buying-something-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[D]on't ever apologize to an author for buying something in paperback, or taking it out from a library (that's what they're there for. Use your library). Don't apologize to this author for buying books second hand, or getting them from bookcrossing or borrowing a friend's copy. What's important to me is that people read the books and enjoy them, and that, at some point in there, the book was bought by someone. And that people who like things, tell other people. The most important thing is that people read... " -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65656-this-is-how-you-do-it-you-sit-down-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:50:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65656-this-is-how-you-do-it-you-sit-down-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is how you do it: you sit down at the keyboard and you put one word after another until its done. It's that easy, and that hard." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21491-stories-may-well-be-lies-but-they-are-good-lies</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:50:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21491-stories-may-well-be-lies-but-they-are-good-lies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories may well be lies, but they are good lies that say true things, and which can sometimes pay the rent." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42627-most-people-don-t-realize-how-important-librarians-are-i-ran</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:51:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42627-most-people-don-t-realize-how-important-librarians-are-i-ran]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most people don't realize how important librarians are. I ran across a book recently which suggested that the peace and prosperity of a culture was solely related to how many librarians it contained. Possibly a slight overstatement. But a culture that doesn't value its librarians doesn't value ideas and without ideas, well, where are we?" -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25303-it-may-help-to-understand-human-affairs-to-be-clear</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:53:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25303-it-may-help-to-understand-human-affairs-to-be-clear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It may help to understand human affairs to be clear that most of the great triumphs and tragedies of history are caused, not by people being fundamentally good or fundamentally bad, but by people being fundamentally people." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125898-you-re-always-you-and-that-don-t-change-and-you-re-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:55:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125898-you-re-always-you-and-that-don-t-change-and-you-re-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're always you, and that don't change, and you're always changing, and there's nothing you can do about it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66833-i-know-that-david-tennant-s-hamlet-isn-t-till-july-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:56:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66833-i-know-that-david-tennant-s-hamlet-isn-t-till-july-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know that David Tennant's Hamlet isn't till July. And lots of people are going to be doing Dr Who in Hamlet jokes, so this is just me getting it out of the way early, to avoid the rush...
&quot;To be, or not to be, that is the question. Weeelll.... More of A question really. Not THE question. Because, well, I mean, there are billions and billions of questions out there, and well, when I say billions, I mean, when you add in the answers, not just the questions, weeelll, you're looking at numbers that are positively astronomical and... for that matter the other question is what you lot are doing on this planet in the first place, and er, did anyone try just pushing this little red button?" -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156274-stories-you-read-when-you-re-the-right-age-never-quite</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:57:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156274-stories-you-read-when-you-re-the-right-age-never-quite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories you read when you're the right age never quite leave you. You may forget who wrote them or what the story was called. Sometimes you'll forget precisely what happened, but if a story touches you it will stay with you, haunting the places in your mind that you rarely ever visit." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147382-you-ve-a-good-heart-sometimes-that-s-enough-to-see-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 14:58:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147382-you-ve-a-good-heart-sometimes-that-s-enough-to-see-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've a good heart.  Sometimes that's enough to see you safe wherever you go.  But mostly, it's not." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38853-people-believe-thought-shadow-it-s-what-people-do-they-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 15:00:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38853-people-believe-thought-shadow-it-s-what-people-do-they-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People believe, thought Shadow. It's what people do. They believe, and then they do not take responsibility for their beliefs; they conjure things, and do not trust the conjuration. People populate the darkness; with ghost, with gods, with electrons, with tales. People imagine, and people believe; and it is that rock solid belief, that makes things happen." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71624-there-was-a-girl-and-her-uncle-sold-her-put</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 15:02:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71624-there-was-a-girl-and-her-uncle-sold-her-put]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was a girl, and her uncle sold her. Put like that it seems so simple.

No man, proclaimed Donne, is an island, and he was wrong. If we were not islands, we would be lost, drowned in each other's tragedies. We are insulated (a word that means, literally, remember, made into an island) from the tragedy of others, by our island nature and by the repetitive shape and form of the stories. The shape does not change: there was a human being who was born, lived and then by some means or other, died. There. You may fill in the details from your own experience. As unoriginal as any other tale, as unique as any other life. Lives are snowflakes- forming patterns we have seen before, as like one another as peas in a pod (and have you ever looked at peas in a pod? I mean, really looked at them? There's not a chance you'll mistake one for another, after a minute's close inspection) but still unique.

Without individuals we see only numbers, a thousand dead, a hundred thousand dead, &quot;casualties may rise to a million.&quot; With individual stories, the statistics become people- but even that is a lie, for the people continue to suffer in numbers that themselves are numbing and meaningless. Look, see the child's swollen, swollen belly and the flies that crawl at the corners of his eyes, this skeletal limbs: will it make it easier for you to know his name, his age, his dreams, his fears? To see him from the inside? And if it does, are we not doing a disservice to his sister, who lies in the searing dust beside him, a distorted distended caricature of a human child? And there, if we feel for them, are they now more important to us than a thousand other children touched by the same famine, a thousand other young lives who will soon be food for the flies' own myriad squirming children?

We draw our lines around these moments of pain, remain upon our islands, and they cannot hurt us. They are covered with a smooth, safe, nacreous layer to let them slip, pearllike, from our souls without real pain.

Fiction allows us to slide into these other heads, these other places, and look out through other eyes. And then in the tale we stop before we die, or we die vicariously and unharmed, and in the world beyond the tale we turn the page or close the book, and we resume our lives.

A life that is, like any other, unlike any other.

And the simple truth is this: There was a girl, and her uncle sold her." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57789-some-hats-can-only-be-worn-if-you-re-willing-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 15:04:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57789-some-hats-can-only-be-worn-if-you-re-willing-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some hats can only be worn if you're willing to be jaunty, to set them at an angle and to walk beneath them with a spring in your stride as if you're only a step away from dancing. They demand a lot of you." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28570-i-said-to-my-soul-be-still-and-wait-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 15:06:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28570-i-said-to-my-soul-be-still-and-wait-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I said to my soul, be still and wait without hope, for hope would be hope for the wrong thing; wait without love, for love would be love of the wrong thing; there is yet faith, but the faith and the love are all in the waiting. Wait without thought, for you are not ready for thought: So the darkness shall be the light, and the stillness the dancing." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2835-genuine-poetry-can-communicate-before-it-is-understood</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 15:06:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2835-genuine-poetry-can-communicate-before-it-is-understood]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Genuine poetry can communicate before it is understood." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12452-some-editors-are-failed-writers-but-so-are-most-writers</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 15:07:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12452-some-editors-are-failed-writers-but-so-are-most-writers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some editors are failed writers, but so are most writers." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13681-humankind-cannot-bear-very-much-reality</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 15:07:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by T. S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13681-humankind-cannot-bear-very-much-reality]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humankind cannot bear very much reality." -- T. S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30810-footfalls-echo-in-the-memory-down-the-passage-we-did</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 15:07:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30810-footfalls-echo-in-the-memory-down-the-passage-we-did]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Footfalls echo in the memory, down the passage we did not take, towards the door we never opened, into the rose garden." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1098-words-strain-crack-and-sometimes-break-under-the-burden-under</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 15:08:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by T.S. Eliot.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1098-words-strain-crack-and-sometimes-break-under-the-burden-under]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Words strain, 
Crack and sometimes break, under the burden, 
Under the tension, slip, slide, perish, 
Decay with imprecision, will not stay in place, 
Will not stay still." -- T.S. Eliot.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127797-i-love-reading-another-reader-s-list-of-favorites-even-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 15:08:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127797-i-love-reading-another-reader-s-list-of-favorites-even-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love reading another reader’s list of favorites. Even when I find I do not share their tastes or predilections, I am provoked to compare, contrast, and contradict. It is a most healthy exercise, and one altogether fruitful." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 15:10:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fairy tales are more than true: not because they tell us that dragons exist, but because they tell us that dragons can be beaten." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1031-literature-is-a-luxury-fiction-is-a-necessity</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 15:11:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1031-literature-is-a-luxury-fiction-is-a-necessity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Literature is a luxury; fiction is a necessity." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23382-i-am-not-absentminded-it-is-the-presence-of-mind</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 15:11:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. Aleksandr add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23382-i-am-not-absentminded-it-is-the-presence-of-mind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am not absentminded. It is the presence of mind that makes me unaware of everything else." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
