<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1028212-tat-w]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1028212-tat-w" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 21:10:39 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42697-we-must-become-so-alone-so-utterly-alone-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 21:10:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42697-we-must-become-so-alone-so-utterly-alone-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must become so alone, so utterly alone, that we withdraw into our innermost self. It is a way of bitter suffering. But then our solitude is overcome, we are no longer alone, for we find that our innermost self is the spirit, that it is God, the indivisible. And suddenly we find ourselves in the midst of the world, yet undisturbed by its multiplicity, for our innermost soul we know ourselves to be one with all being." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9726-your-task-is-not-to-seek-for-love-but-merely</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 20:31:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9726-your-task-is-not-to-seek-for-love-but-merely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your task is not to seek for love, but merely to seek and find all the barriers within yourself that you have built against it." -- Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116538-if-you-prefer-smoke-over-fire-then-get-up-now</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 10:57:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Adyashanti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116538-if-you-prefer-smoke-over-fire-then-get-up-now]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you prefer smoke over fire
then get up now and leave.
For I do not intend to perfume
your mind's clothing
with more sooty knowledge.

No, I have something else in mind.
Today I hold a flame in my left hand
and a sword in my right.
There will be no damage control today.

For God is in a mood
to plunder your riches and
fling you nakedly
into such breathtaking poverty
that all that will be left of you
will be a tendency to shine.

So don't just sit around this flame
choking on your mind.
For this is no campfire song
to mindlessly mantra yourself to sleep with.

Jump now into the space
between thoughts
and exit this dream
before I burn the damn place down." -- Adyashanti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378539-enlightenment-is-a-destructive-process-it-has-nothing-to-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 10:58:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Adyashanti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378539-enlightenment-is-a-destructive-process-it-has-nothing-to-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Enlightenment is a destructive process. It
has nothing to do with becoming better or being happier. Enlightenment is the
crumbling away of untruth. It's seeing
through the facade of pretence. It's the
complete eradication of everything we
imagined to be true." -- Adyashanti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/481269-i-believe-that-the-measure-of-my-soul-is-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 20:23:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Joseph Grenny]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/481269-i-believe-that-the-measure-of-my-soul-is-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that the measure of my soul is my capacity to love imperfect people." -- Joseph Grenny]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13719-we-are-what-we-pretend-to-be-so-we-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 20:31:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13719-we-are-what-we-pretend-to-be-so-we-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are what we pretend to be, so we must be careful about what we pretend to be." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18271-there-is-always-some-madness-in-love-but-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 18:08:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18271-there-is-always-some-madness-in-love-but-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is always some madness in love. But there is also always some reason in madness." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164054-unfortunately-as-a-society-we-do-not-teach-our-children</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 10:08:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Jill Bolte Taylor, Ph.D.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164054-unfortunately-as-a-society-we-do-not-teach-our-children]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Unfortunately, as a society, we do not teach our children that they need to &lt;i&gt;tend carefully the garden of their minds&lt;/i&gt;.  Without structure, censorship, or discipline, our thoughts run rampant on automatic.  Because we have not learned how to more carefully manage what goes on inside our brains, we remain vulnerable to not only what other people think about us, but also to advertising and/or political manipulation." -- Jill Bolte Taylor, Ph.D.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126603-when-we-are-being-compassionate-we-consider-another-s-circumstance-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 10:09:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Jill Bolte Taylor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126603-when-we-are-being-compassionate-we-consider-another-s-circumstance-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we are being compassionate, we consider another's circumstance with love rather than judgement... To be compassionate is to move into the right here, right now with an open heart consciousness and a willingness to be supportive." -- Jill Bolte Taylor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/551027-yesterday-i-was-clever-so-i-wanted-to-change-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 19:40:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/551027-yesterday-i-was-clever-so-i-wanted-to-change-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yesterday I was clever, so I wanted to change the world.  Today I am wise, so I am changing myself." -- Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12656-silence-make-the-real-conversations-between-friends-not-the-saying</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 21:04:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Margaret Lee Runbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12656-silence-make-the-real-conversations-between-friends-not-the-saying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Silence make the real conversations between friends. Not the saying, but the never needing to say that counts." -- Margaret Lee Runbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26110-you-wouldn-t-worry-so-much-about-what-others-think-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 16:46:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26110-you-wouldn-t-worry-so-much-about-what-others-think-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You wouldn't worry so much about what others think of you if you realized how seldom they do." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38095-blessed-is-the-man-who-having-nothing-to-say-abstains</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 19:00:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38095-blessed-is-the-man-who-having-nothing-to-say-abstains]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Blessed is the man who, having nothing to say, abstains from giving us wordy evidence of the fact." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21454-by-believing-passionately-in-something-that-still-does-not-exist</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 20:52:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21454-by-believing-passionately-in-something-that-still-does-not-exist]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By believing passionately in something that still does not exist, we create it. The nonexistent is whatever we have not sufficiently desired." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115825-your-children-are-not-your-children-they-are-sons-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2013 10:48:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115825-your-children-are-not-your-children-they-are-sons-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your children are not your children.
They are sons and daughters of Life's longing for itself.  
They come through you but not from you.
And though they are with you yet they belong not to you.

You may give them your love but not your thoughts,
For they have their own thoughts.
You may house their bodies but not their souls,
For thir souls dwell in the house of tomorrow, which you cannot visit, not even in your dreams.
You may strive to be like them, but seek not to make them like you.
For life goes not backward nor tarries with yesterday.
You are the bows from which your children as living arrows are sent forth.
The archer sees the make upon the path of the infinite, and He bends you with His might that His arrows may go swift and far.
Let your bending in the archer's hand be for gladness.
For even as He loves the arrow that flies, so He also loves the bow that is stable." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3750-your-pain-is-the-breaking-of-the-shell-that-encloses</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2013 10:50:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3750-your-pain-is-the-breaking-of-the-shell-that-encloses]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your pain is the breaking of the shell that encloses your understanding... And could you keep your heart in wonder at the daily miracles of your life, your pain would not seem less wondrous than your joy" -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/673573-when-we-are-stricken-and-cannot-bear-our-lives-any</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 19:40:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/673573-when-we-are-stricken-and-cannot-bear-our-lives-any]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we are stricken and cannot bear our lives any longer, then a tree has something to say to us: Be still! Be still! Look at me! Life is not easy, life is not difficult. Those are childish thoughts. . . . Home is neither here nor there. Home is within you, or home is nowhere at all." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73541-give-up-defining-yourself---to-yourself-or-to-others</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 19:50:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73541-give-up-defining-yourself---to-yourself-or-to-others]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Give up defining yourself - to yourself or to others. You won't die. You will come to life. And don't be concerned with how others define you. When they define you, they are limiting themselves, so it's their problem. Whenever you interact with people, don't be there primarily as a function or a role, but as the field of conscious Presence. You can only lose something that you have, but you cannot lose something that you are." -- Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20204-there-is-no-need-to-search-achievement-leads-to-nowhere</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 21:15:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Dan Millman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20204-there-is-no-need-to-search-achievement-leads-to-nowhere]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no need to search; achievement leads to nowhere. It makes no difference at all, so just be happy now! Love is the only reality of the world, because it is all One, you see. And the only laws are paradox, humor and change. There is no problem, never was, and never will be. Release your struggle, let go of your mind, throw away your concerns, and relax into the world. No need to resist life, just do your best. Open your eyes and see that you are far more than you imagine. You are the world, you are the universe; you are yourself and everyone else, too! It's all the marvelous Play of God. Wake up, regain your humor. Don't worry, just be happy. You are already free!" -- Dan Millman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525097-letting-go-means-to-come-to-the-realization-that-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 22:15:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Steve Maraboli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525097-letting-go-means-to-come-to-the-realization-that-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Letting go means to come to the realization that some people are a part of your history, but not a part of your destiny." -- Steve Maraboli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1420-i-wanted-a-perfect-ending-now-i-ve-learned-the-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 22:20:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Gilda Radner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1420-i-wanted-a-perfect-ending-now-i-ve-learned-the-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted a perfect ending. Now I've learned, the hard way, that some poems don't rhyme, and some stories don't have a clear beginning, middle, and end. Life is about not knowing, having to change, taking the moment and making the best of it, without knowing what's going to happen next.
Delicious Ambiguity." -- Gilda Radner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367077-people-can-attach-themselves-to-something--an-idea-another-person-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 19:00:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Deb Caletti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367077-people-can-attach-themselves-to-something--an-idea-another-person-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People can attach themselves to something--an idea, another person, a desire--with an impossibly strong grip, and in the case of restless ghosts, a grip stronger than death. Will is a powerful thing. Will--it's supposed to be a good treat, a more determined and persistent version of determination and persistence. But will and obsession--they sit right next to each other. They pretend to be strangers and all the while meet secretly at midnight.&quot; -" -- Deb Caletti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23089-the-meeting-of-two-personalities-is-like-the-contact-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 14:59:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23089-the-meeting-of-two-personalities-is-like-the-contact-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The meeting of two personalities is like the contact of two chemical substances: if there is any reaction, both are transformed." -- Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236728-we-re-all-seeking-that-special-person-who-is-right-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 15:01:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Galway Kinnell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236728-we-re-all-seeking-that-special-person-who-is-right-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We’re all seeking that special person who is right for us. But if you’ve been through enough relationships, you begin to suspect there’s no right person, just different flavors of wrong. Why is this? Because you yourself are wrong in some way, and you seek out partners who are wrong in some complementary way. But it takes a lot of living to grow fully into your own wrongness. And it isn’t until you finally run up against your deepest demons, your unsolvable problems—the ones that make you truly who you are—that we’re ready to find a lifelong mate. Only then do you finally know what you’re looking for. You’re looking for the wrong person. But not just any wrong person: the right wrong person—someone you lovingly gaze upon and think, “This is the problem I want to have.”

I will find that special person who is wrong for me in just the right way.

Let our scars fall in love." -- Galway Kinnell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23747-i-will-love-you-always-when-this-red-hair-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 15:11:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Laurell K. Hamilton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23747-i-will-love-you-always-when-this-red-hair-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will love you always. When this red hair is white, I will still love you. When the smooth softness of youth is replaced by the delicate softness of age, I will still want to touch your skin. When your face is full of the lines of every smile you have ever smiled, of every surprise I have seen flash through your eyes, when every tear you have ever cried has left its mark upon your face,I will treasure you all the more, because I was there to see it all. I will share your life with you, Meredith, and I will love you until the last breath leaves your body or mine." -- Laurell K. Hamilton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95639-seize-the-moments-of-happiness-love-and-be-loved-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 15:43:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95639-seize-the-moments-of-happiness-love-and-be-loved-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Seize the moments of happiness, love and be loved! That is the only reality in the world, all else is folly. It is the one thing we are interested in here." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71463-1-be-impeccable-with-your-word-speak-with-integrity-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 09:09:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Don Miguel Ruiz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71463-1-be-impeccable-with-your-word-speak-with-integrity-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["1. Be Impeccable With Your Word
Speak with integrity. Say only what you mean. Avoid using the word to speak against yourself or to gossip about others. Use the power of your word in the direction of truth and love. 

2. Don't Take Anything Personally
Nothing others do is because of you. What others say and do is a projection of their own reality, their own dream. When you are immune to the opinions and actions of others, you won't be the victim of needless suffering. 

3. Don't Make Assumptions
Find the courage to ask questions and to express what you really want. Communicate with others as clearly as you can to avoid misunderstandings, sadness and drama. With just this one agreement, you can completely transform your life. 

4. Always Do Your Best
Your best is going to change from moment to moment; it will be different when you are healthy as opposed to sick. Under any circumstance, simply do your best, and you will avoid self-judgment, self-abuse and regret." -- Don Miguel Ruiz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10651-when-i-let-go-of-what-i-am-i-become</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 11:25:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Lao Tzu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10651-when-i-let-go-of-what-i-am-i-become]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I let go of what I am, I become what I might be." -- Lao Tzu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446591-all-that-is-necessary-to-awaken-to-yourself-as-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 21:08:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Adyashanti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446591-all-that-is-necessary-to-awaken-to-yourself-as-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that is necessary to awaken to yourself as the radiant emptiness of spirit is to stop seeking something more or better or different, and to turn your attention inward to the awake silence that you are." -- Adyashanti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50542-the-best-fighter-is-never-angry</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 11:25:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tat add a quote by Lao Tzu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50542-the-best-fighter-is-never-angry]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best fighter is never angry." -- Lao Tzu]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
