<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1028778-dawn-anderson]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1028778-dawn-anderson" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 13:21:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249522-i-do-not-think-god-makes-bad-things-happen-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 13:21:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dawn add a quote by Elizabeth Moon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249522-i-do-not-think-god-makes-bad-things-happen-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not think God makes bad things happen just so that people can grow spiritually. Bad parents do that, my mother said. Bad parents make things hard and painful for their children and then say it was to help them grow. Growing and living are hard enough already; children do not need things to be harder. I think this is true even for normal children. I have watched little children learning to walk; they all struggle and fall down many times. Their faces show that it is not easy. It would be stupid to tie bricks on them to make it harder. If that is true for learning to walk, then I think it is true for other growing and learning as well. 
God is suppose to be the good parent, the Father. So I think God would not make things harder than they are. I do not think I am autistic because God thought my parents needed a challenge or I needed a challenge. I think it is like if I were a baby and a rock fell on me and broke my leg. Whatever caused it was an accident. God did not prevent the accident, but He did not cause it, either.... I think my autism is an accident, but what I do with it is me." -- Elizabeth Moon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219543-sometimes-i-wonder-how-normal-normal-people-are-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 13:21:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dawn add a quote by Elizabeth Moon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219543-sometimes-i-wonder-how-normal-normal-people-are-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I wonder how normal normal people are, and I wonder that most in the grocery store." -- Elizabeth Moon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263895-everything-in-my-life-that-i-value-has-been-gained</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 13:21:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dawn add a quote by Elizabeth Moon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263895-everything-in-my-life-that-i-value-has-been-gained]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything in my life that I value has been gained at the cost of not saying what I really think and saying what they want me to say." -- Elizabeth Moon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
