<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1029105-matt]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1029105-matt" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 17:56:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15891-there-is-something-beautiful-about-a-billion-stars-held-steady</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 17:56:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Donald Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15891-there-is-something-beautiful-about-a-billion-stars-held-steady]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is something beautiful about a billion stars held steady by a God who knows what He is doing. (They hang there, the stars, like notes on a page of music, free-form verse, silent mysteries swirling in the blue like jazz.) And as I lay there, it occurred to me that God is up there somewhere. Of course, I had always known He was, but this time I felt it, I realized it, the way a person realizes they are hungry or thirsty. The knowledge of God seeped out of my brain and into my heart. I imagined Him looking down on this earth, half angry because His beloved mankind had cheated on Him, had committed adultery, and yet hopelessly in love with her, drunk with love for her." -- Donald Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17001-it-is-inbred-in-us-that-we-have-to-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 18:00:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Oswald Chambers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17001-it-is-inbred-in-us-that-we-have-to-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is inbred in us that we have to do exceptional things for God: but we have not. We have to be exceptional in the ordinary things, to be holy in mean streets, among mean people, and this is not learned in five minutes" -- Oswald Chambers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4242-if-we-maintain-the-open-mindedness-of-children-we-challenge-fixed</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 18:47:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Brennan Manning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4242-if-we-maintain-the-open-mindedness-of-children-we-challenge-fixed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we maintain the open-mindedness of children, we challenge fixed ideas and established structures, including our own. We listen to people in other denominations and religions. We don't find demons in those with whom we disagree. We don't cozy up to people who mouth our jargon. If we are open, we rarely resort to either-or: either creation or evolution, liberty or law, sacred or secular, Beethoven or Madonna. We focus on both-and, fully aware that God's truth cannot be imprisoned in a small definition. " -- Brennan Manning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83578-has-your-relationship-with-god-changed-the-way-you-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 16:17:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Francis Chan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83578-has-your-relationship-with-god-changed-the-way-you-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Has your relationship with God changed the way you live your life?" -- Francis Chan]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
