<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1029838-tom]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1029838-tom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 10:22:49 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20790-we-are-sorry-for-the-inconvenience-but-this-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 10:22:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Subcomandante Marcos]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20790-we-are-sorry-for-the-inconvenience-but-this-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are sorry for the inconvenience, but this is a revolution." -- Subcomandante Marcos]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75939-a-specter-is-haunting-europe-the-specter-of-communism-all-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 17:52:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Karl Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75939-a-specter-is-haunting-europe-the-specter-of-communism-all-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A specter is haunting Europe—the specter of Communism. All the powers of old Europe have entered into a holy alliance to exorcise this specter; Pope and Czar, Metternich and Guizot, French radicals and German police spies.

Where is the party in opposition that has not been decried as Communistic by its opponents in power? Where the opposition that has not hurled back the branding reproach of Communism, against the more advanced opposition parties, as well as against its reactionary adversaries?

Two things result from this fact.

I. Communism is already acknowledged by all European powers to be in itself a power.

II. It is high time that Communists should openly, in the face of the whole world, publish their views, their aims, their tendencies, and meet this nursery tale of the Specter of Communism with a Manifesto of the party itself." -- Karl Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67118-a-non-writing-writer-is-a-monster-courting-insanity-letter-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 17:53:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67118-a-non-writing-writer-is-a-monster-courting-insanity-letter-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A non-writing writer is a monster courting insanity.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;Letter to Max Brod&lt;/i&gt;, July 5, 1922]" -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3535-once-there-were-brook-trout-in-the-streams-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 17:55:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3535-once-there-were-brook-trout-in-the-streams-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once there were brook trout in the streams in the mountains. You could see them standing in the amber current where the white edges of their fins wimpled softly in the flow. They smelled of moss in your hand. Polished and muscular and torsional. On their backs were vermiculate patterns that were maps of the world in its becoming. Maps and mazes. Of a thing which could not be put back. Not be made right again. In the deep glens where they lived all things were older than man and they hummed of mystery." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187405-paranoids-are-not-paranoid-because-they-re-paranoid-but-because-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 17:57:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187405-paranoids-are-not-paranoid-because-they-re-paranoid-but-because-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Paranoids are not paranoid because they're paranoid, but because they keep putting themselves, fucking idiots, deliberately into paranoid situations." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38129-literature-was-not-born-the-day-when-a-boy-crying</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 17:59:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38129-literature-was-not-born-the-day-when-a-boy-crying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Literature was not born the day when a boy crying &quot;wolf, wolf&quot; came running out of the Neanderthal valley with a big gray wolf at his heels; literature was born on the day when a boy came crying &quot;wolf, wolf&quot; and there was no wolf behind him." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169865-to-my-mind-a-well-developed-sense-of-humor-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 17:59:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Thomas Ligotti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169865-to-my-mind-a-well-developed-sense-of-humor-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To my mind, a well-developed sense of humor is the surest indication of a person's humanity, no matter how black and bitter that humor may be." -- Thomas Ligotti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249420-i-had-two-dreams-about-him-after-he-died-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2010 21:06:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249420-i-had-two-dreams-about-him-after-he-died-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had two dreams about him after he died.  I dont remember the first one all that well but it was about meetin him in town somewheres and he give me some money and I think I lost it.  But the second one it was like we was both back in older times and I was on horseback goin through the mountains of a night.  Goin through this pass in the mountains.  It was cold and there was snow on the ground and he rode past me and kept on goin.  Never said nothin.  He just rode on past and he had this blanket wrapped around him and he had his head down and when he rode past I seen he was carryin fire in a horn the way people used to do and I could see the horn from the light inside of it.  About the color of the moon.  And in the dream I knew that he was goin on ahead and that he was fixin to make a fire somewhere out there in all that dark and all that cold and I knew that whenever I got there he would be there.  And then I woke up." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275483-the-advice-i-like-to-give-young-artists-or-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 21:23:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Chuck Close]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275483-the-advice-i-like-to-give-young-artists-or-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The advice I like to give young artists, or really anybody who'll listen to me, is not to wait around for inspiration. Inspiration is for amateurs; the rest of us just show up and get to work. If you wait around for the clouds to part and a bolt of lightning to strike you in the brain, you are not going to make an awful lot of work. All the best ideas come out of the process; they come out of the work itself. Things occur to you. If you're sitting around trying to dream up a great art idea, you can sit there a long time before anything happens. But if you just get to work, something will occur to you and something else will occur to you and something else that you reject will push you in another direction. Inspiration is absolutely unnecessary and somehow deceptive. You feel like you need this great idea before you can get down to work, and I find that's almost never the case." -- Chuck Close]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27510-the-hottest-places-in-hell-are-reserved-for-those-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 10:38:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by John F. Kennedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27510-the-hottest-places-in-hell-are-reserved-for-those-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The hottest places in hell are reserved for those who, in times of great moral crisis, maintain their neutrality." -- John F. Kennedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
