<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1029325-heidi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1029325-heidi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 10:34:47 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1143-i-choose-to-believe-that-i-owe-my-very-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 10:34:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heidi add a quote by Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1143-i-choose-to-believe-that-i-owe-my-very-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I choose to believe that I owe my very
life to you--ay--smile, and think it an exaggeration if you will.
I believe it, because it adds a value to that life to think--oh,
Miss Hale!' continued he, lowering his voice to such a tender
intensity of passion that she shivered and trembled before him,
'to think circumstance so wrought, that whenever I exult in
existence henceforward, I may say to myself, &quot;All this gladness
in life, all honest pride in doing my work in the world, all this
keen sense of being, I owe to her!&quot; And it doubles the gladness,
it makes the pride glow, it sharpens the sense of existence till
I hardly know if it is pain or pleasure, to think that I owe it
to one--nay, you must, you shall hear'--said he, stepping
forwards with stern determination--'to one whom I love, as I do
not believe man ever loved woman before.' He held her hand tight
in his. He panted as he listened for what should come. " -- Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1150880-suddenly-it-seemed-imperative-to-plan-his-next-steps-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 20:28:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heidi add a quote by Heidi Ashworth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1150880-suddenly-it-seemed-imperative-to-plan-his-next-steps-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suddenly, it seemed imperative to plan his next steps with a steaming cup of tea at hand and his feet resting on the fender of a cheerful fire. It was far too long before he could make his thoughts a reality, but once he had changed into his dressing gown and bespoken a pot of tea, he thought he just might live." -- Heidi Ashworth]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
