<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/103-alexandra]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/103-alexandra" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 13:44:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 13:44:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexandra add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255486-10-of-life-is-made-up-of-what-happens-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 12:15:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexandra add a quote by Charles R. Swindoll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255486-10-of-life-is-made-up-of-what-happens-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["10% of life is made up of what happens to you.
90% of life is decided by how you react." -- Charles R. Swindoll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372993-but-i-think-the-first-real-change-in-women-s-body</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 13:06:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexandra add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372993-but-i-think-the-first-real-change-in-women-s-body]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I think the first real change in women’s body image came when JLo turned it butt-style. That was the first time that having a large-scale situation in the back was part of mainstream American beauty. Girls wanted butts now. Men were free to admit that they had always enjoyed them. And then, what felt like moments later, boom—Beyoncé brought the leg meat. A back porch and thick muscular legs were now widely admired. And from that day forward, women embraced their diversity and realized that all shapes and sizes are beautiful. Ah ha ha. No. I’m totally messing with you. All Beyonce and JLo have done is add to the laundry list of attributes women must have to qualify as beautiful. Now every girl is expected to have Caucasian blue eyes, full Spanish lips, a classic button nose, hairless Asian skin with a California tan, a Jamaican dance hall ass, long Swedish legs, small Japanese feet, the abs of a lesbian gym owner, the hips of a nine-year-old boy, the arms of Michelle Obama, and doll tits. The person closest to actually achieving this look is Kim Kardashian, who, as we know, was made by Russian scientists to sabotage our athletes." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
