<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1030455-peter-macinnis]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1030455-peter-macinnis" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 21:02:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39918-the-writer-found-that-certain-freshwater-crustaceans-namely-californian-species</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 21:02:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Peter add a quote by Jacques Loeb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39918-the-writer-found-that-certain-freshwater-crustaceans-namely-californian-species]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The writer found that certain freshwater crustaceans, namely Californian species of Daphnia, copepods, and Gammarus when indifferent to light can be made intensely positively heliotropic by adding some acid to the fresh water, especially the weak acid CO2.  When carbonated water (or beer) to the extent of about 5 c.c. or 10 c.c. is slowly and carefully added to 50 c.c. of fresh water containing these Daphnia, the animals will become intensely positive and will collect in a dense cluster on the window side of the dish.  Stronger acids act in the same way but the animals are likely to die quickly. . . Alcohols act in the same way.  In the case of Gammarus the positive heliotropism lasts only a few seconds, while in Daphnia it lasts from 10 to 50 minutes and can be renewed by the further careful addition of some CO2." -- Jacques Loeb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39920-in-the-circle-where-i-was-raised-i-knew-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 21:03:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Peter add a quote by Shirley Hazzard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39920-in-the-circle-where-i-was-raised-i-knew-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the circle where I was raised, I knew of no one knowledgeable in the visual arts, no one who regularly attended musical performances, and only two adults other than my teachers who spoke without embarrassment of poetry and literature — both of these being women.  As far as I can recall, I never heard a man refer to a good or a great book.  I knew no one who had mastered, or even studied, another language from choice.  And our articulate, conscious life proceeded without acknowledgement of the preceding civilisations which had produced it." -- Shirley Hazzard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39923-science-is-part-of-culture-culture-isn-t-only-art-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 21:05:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Peter add a quote by Max Perutz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39923-science-is-part-of-culture-culture-isn-t-only-art-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Science is part of culture.  Culture isn't only art and music and literature, it's also understanding what the world is made of and how it functions.  People should know something about stars, matter and chemistry.  People often say that they don't like chemistry but we deal with chemistry all the time.  People don't know what heat is, they hardly know what water is. I'm always surprised how little people know about anything.  I'm puzzled by it." -- Max Perutz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39925-the-division-of-our-culture-is-making-us-more-obtuse</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 21:07:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Peter add a quote by C.P. Snow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39925-the-division-of-our-culture-is-making-us-more-obtuse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The division of our culture is making us more obtuse than we need be: we can repair communications to some extent: but, as I have said before, we are not going to turn out men and women who understand as much of their world as Piero della Francesca did of his, or Pascal, or Goethe.  With good fortune, however, we can educate a large proportion of our better minds so that they are not ignorant of the imaginative experience, both in the arts and in science, nor ignorant either of the endowments of applied science, of the remediable suffering of most of their fellow humans, and of the responsibilities which, once seen, cannot be denied." -- C.P. Snow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39928-at-one-time-the-state-of-culture-in-czechoslovakia-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 21:08:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Peter add a quote by Vaclav Havel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39928-at-one-time-the-state-of-culture-in-czechoslovakia-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At one time, the state of culture in Czechoslovakia was described, rather poignantly, as a 'Biafra of the spirit'. . . I simply do not believe that we have all lain down and died.  I see far more than graves and tombstones around me.  I see evidence of this in . . . expensive books on astronomy printed in a hundred thousand copies (they would hardly find that many readers in the USA) . . ." -- Vaclav Havel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39931-caroline-sister-of-william-was-trained-by-him-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 21:09:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Peter add a quote by Percy Scholes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39931-caroline-sister-of-william-was-trained-by-him-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Caroline, sister of William, was trained by him as a singer in the Bath days and had considerable success in Handel's oratorios under her brother's conductorship.  (The method of training adopted was for her to sing the violin parts of concertos with a gag in her mouth.)  It was with great reluctance that she dropped music to be trained as an assistant astronomer, yet she made discoveries — eight minor planets, one of them named after her." -- Percy Scholes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39934-author-oersted-3403791-would-never-have-made-his-great-discovery-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 21:11:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Peter add a quote by Lord Kelvin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39934-author-oersted-3403791-would-never-have-made-his-great-discovery-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[author:Oersted|3403791] would never have made his great discovery of the action of galvanic currents on magnets had he stopped in his researches to consider in what manner they could possibly be turned to practical account; and so we would not now be able to boast of the wonders done by the electric telegraphs.  Indeed, no great law in Natural Philosophy has ever been discovered for its practical implications, but the instances are innumerable of investigations apparently quite useless in this narrow sense of the word which have led to the most valuable results." -- Lord Kelvin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220778-a-lot-of-the-people-who-read-a-bestselling-novel</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 13:29:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Peter add a quote by The Economist]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220778-a-lot-of-the-people-who-read-a-bestselling-novel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A lot of the people who read a bestselling novel, for example, do not read much other fiction. By contrast, the audience for an obscure novel is largely composed of people who read a lot. That means the least popular books are judged by people who have the highest standards, while the most popular are judged by people who literally do not know any better. An American who read just one book this year was disproportionately likely to have read ‘The Lost Symbol’, by Dan Brown. He almost certainly liked it." -- The Economist]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
