<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1030422-nicole]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1030422-nicole" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 00:23:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39101-in-a-nervous-and-slender-leaved-mimosa-grove-at-the-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 00:23:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39101-in-a-nervous-and-slender-leaved-mimosa-grove-at-the-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a nervous and slender-leaved mimosa grove at the back of their villa we found a perch on the ruins of a low stone wall.  She trembled and twitched as I kissed the corner of her parted lips and the hot lobe of her ear.  A cluster of stars palely glowed above us between the silhouettes of long thin leaves; that vibrant sky seemed as naked as she was under her light frock.  I saw her face in the sky, strangely distinct, as if it emitted a faint radiance of its own.  Her legs, her lovely live legs, were not too close together, and when my hand located what it sought, a dreamy and eerie expression, half-pleasure, half-pain, came over those childish features.  She sat a little higher than I, and whenever in her solitary ecstasy she was led to kiss me, her head would bend with a sleepy, soft, drooping movement that was almost woeful, and her bare knees caught and compressed my wrist, and slackened again; and her quivering mouth, distorted by the acridity of some mysterious potion, with a sibilant intake of breath came near to my face.  She would try to relieve the pain of love by first roughly rubbing her dry lips against mine; then my darling would draw away with a nervous toss of her hair, and then again come darkly near and let me feed on her open mouth, while with a generosity that was ready to offer her everything, my heart, my throat, my entrails, I gave her to hold in her awkward fist the scepter of my passion." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39102-madness-is-too-glamorous-a-term-to-convey-what-happens</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 00:24:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39102-madness-is-too-glamorous-a-term-to-convey-what-happens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Madness is too glamorous a term to convey what happens to most people who are losing their minds. That word is too exciting, too literary, too interesting in its connotations, to convey the boredom, the slowness, the dreariness, the dampness of depression…depression is pure dullness, tedium straight up. Depression is, especially these days, an overused term to be sure, but never one associated with anything wild, anything about dancing all night with a lampshade on your head and then going home and killing yourself…The word madness allows its users to celebrate the pain of its sufferers, to forget that underneath all the acting-out and quests for fabulousness and fine poetry, there is a person in huge amounts of dull, ugly agony...Remember that when you’re at the point at which you’re doing something as desperate and violent as sticking your head in an oven, it is only because the life that preceded this act felt even worse. Think about living in depression from moment to moment, and know it is not worth any of the great art that comes as its by-product." -- Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19071-the-one-you-love-and-the-one-who-loves-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 17:57:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19071-the-one-you-love-and-the-one-who-loves-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The one you love and the one who loves you are never, ever the same person." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39104-my-understanding-of-the-past-has-been-savagely-undermined</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 00:27:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Penelope Lively]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39104-my-understanding-of-the-past-has-been-savagely-undermined]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My understanding of the past has been savagely undermined." -- Penelope Lively]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39105-a-stone-has-been-cast-into-the-reliable-immutable-pond</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 00:27:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Penelope Lively]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39105-a-stone-has-been-cast-into-the-reliable-immutable-pond]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A stone has been cast into the reliable immutable pond of the past, and as the ripples subside everything appears different. The reflections are quite other; everything has swung and shattered, it is all beyond recovery" -- Penelope Lively]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39106-there-is-an-idea-of-a-patrick-bateman-some-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 00:28:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39106-there-is-an-idea-of-a-patrick-bateman-some-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…there is an idea of a Patrick Bateman, some kind of abstraction, but there is no real me, only an entity, something illusory, and though I can hide my cold gaze and you can shake my hand and feel flesh gripping yours and maybe you can even sense our lifestyles are probably comparable: I simply am not there.  It is hard for me to make sense on any given level.  Myself is fabricated, an aberration.  I am a noncontingent human being.  My personality is sketchy and unformed, my heartlessness goes deep and is persistent.  My conscience, my pity, my hopes disappeared a long time ago (probably at Harvard) if they ever did exist.  There are no more barriers to cross.  All I have in common with the uncontrollable and the insane, the vicious and the evil, all the mayhem I have caused and my utter indifference toward it, I have now surpassed.  I still, though, hold on to one single bleak truth: no one is safe, nothing is redeemed.  Yet I am blameless.  Each model of human behavior must be assumed to have some validity.  Is evil something you are?  Or is it something you do?  My pain is constant and sharp and I do not hope for a better world for anyone.  In fact, I want my pain to be inflicted on others.  I want no one to escape.  But even after admitting this—and I have countless times, in just about every act I’ve committed—and coming face-to-face with these truths, there is no catharsis.  I gain no deeper knowledge about myself, no new understanding can be extracted from my telling.  There has been no reason for me to tell you any of this.  This confession has meant nothing…." -- Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39107-i-had-all-the-characteristics-of-a-human-being-flesh-blood</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 00:29:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39107-i-had-all-the-characteristics-of-a-human-being-flesh-blood]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had all the characteristics of a human being—flesh, blood, skin, hair—but my depersonalization was so intense, had gone so deep, that my normal ability to feel compassion had been eradicated, the victim of a slow, purposeful erasure.  I was simply imitating reality, a rough resemblance of a human being, with only a dim corner of my mind functioning" -- Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39108-the-thing-is-i-am-so-lonely-i-can-hardly</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 00:30:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Talitha Stevenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39108-the-thing-is-i-am-so-lonely-i-can-hardly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The thing is, I am so lonely I can hardly breathe." -- Talitha Stevenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39109-in-reality-they-all-lived-in-a-kind-of-hieroglyphic</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 00:31:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39109-in-reality-they-all-lived-in-a-kind-of-hieroglyphic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In reality they all lived in a kind of hieroglyphic world, where the real thing was never said or done or even thought, but only represented by a set of arbitrary signs." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39112-now-and-then-an-inch-below-the-water-s-surface-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 01:10:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39112-now-and-then-an-inch-below-the-water-s-surface-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now and then, an inch below the water's surface, the muscles of his stomach tightened involuntarily as he recalled another detail. A drop of water on her upper arm. Wet. An embroidered flower, a simple daisy, sewn between the cups of her bra. Her breasts wide apart and small. On her back, a mole half covered by a strap. When she climbed out of the pond a glimpse of the triangular darkness her knickers were supposed to conceal. Wet. He saw it, he made himself see it again. The way her pelvic bones stretched the material clear of the skin, the deep curve of her waist, her startling whiteness. When she reached for her skirt, a carelessly raised foot revealed a patch of soil on each pad of her sweetly diminished toes. Another mole the size of a farthing on her thigh and something purplish on her calf--a strawberry mark, a scar. Not blemishes. Adornments." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20889-there-is-just-this-for-consolation-an-hour-here-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 22:43:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Michael Cunningham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20889-there-is-just-this-for-consolation-an-hour-here-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is just this for consolation: an hour here or there, when our lives seem, against all odds and expectations, to burst open and give us everything we've ever imagined , though everyone but children (and perhaps even they) knows these hours will inevitably be followed by others, far darker and more difficult. Still, we cherish the city, the morning, we hope, more than anything, for more. Heaven only knows why we love it so." -- Michael Cunningham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6453-you-don-t-know-what-goes-on-in-anyone-s-life-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2008 08:57:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Jay Asher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6453-you-don-t-know-what-goes-on-in-anyone-s-life-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t know what goes on in anyone’s life but your own. And when you mess with one part of a person’s life, you’re not messing with just that part. Unfortunately, you can’t be that precise and selective. When you mess with one part of a person’s life, you’re messing with their entire life. Everything. . . affects everything." -- Jay Asher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119501-she-seems-so-cool-so-focused-so-quiet-yet-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 22:55:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119501-she-seems-so-cool-so-focused-so-quiet-yet-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She seems so cool, so focused, so quiet, yet her eyes remain fixed upon the horizon. You think you know all there is to know about her immediately upon meeting her, but everything you think you know is wrong. Passion flows through her like a river of blood. 

She only looked away for a moment, and the mask slipped, and you fell. All your tomorrows start here." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22087-this-much-i-m-certain-of-it-doesn-t-happen-immediately-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 00:50:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22087-this-much-i-m-certain-of-it-doesn-t-happen-immediately-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This much I'm certain of: it doesn't happen immediately. You'll finish [the book] and that will be that, until a moment will come, maybe in a month, maybe a year, maybe even several years. You'll be sick or feeling troubled or deeply in love or quietly uncertain or even content for the first time in your life. It won't matter. Out of the blue, beyond any cause you can trace, you'll suddenly realize things are not how you perceived them to be at all. For some reason, you will no longer be the person you believed you once were. You'll detect slow and subtle shifts going on all around you, more importantly shifts in you. Worse, you'll realize it's always been shifting, like a shimmer of sorts, a vast shimmer, only dark like a room. But you won't understand why or how. You'll have forgotten what granted you this awareness in the first place&lt;br&gt;
...&lt;br&gt;
You might try then, as I did, to find a sky so full of stars it will blind you again. Only no sky can blind you now. Even with all that iridescent magic up there, your eye will no longer linger on the light, it will no longer trace constellations. You'll care only about the darkness and you'll watch it for hours, for days, maybe even for years, trying in vain to believe you're some kind of indispensable, universe-appointed sentinel, as if just by looking you could actually keep it all at bay. It will get so bad you'll be afraid to look away, you'll be afraid to sleep.&lt;br&gt;
Then no matter where you are, in a crowded restaurant or on some desolate street or even in the comforts of your own home, you'll watch yourself dismantle every assurance you ever lived by. You'll stand aside as a great complexity intrudes, tearing apart, piece by piece, all of your carefully conceived denials, whether deliberate or unconscious. And then for better or worse you'll turn, unable to resist, though try to resist you still will, fighting with everything you've got not to face the thing you most dread, what is now, what will be, what has always come before, the creature you truly are, the creature we all are, buried in the nameless black of a name.&lt;br&gt;
And then the nightmares will begin." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120469-boys-are-just-boys-after-all-but-sometimes-girls-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2010 02:13:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120469-boys-are-just-boys-after-all-but-sometimes-girls-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Boys are just boys after all, but sometimes girls really seem to be the turn of a pale wrist, or the sudden jut of a hip, or a clutch of very dark hair falling across a freckled forehead. I'm not saying that's what they really are. I'm just saying sometimes it seems that way, and that those details (a thigh mole, a full face flush, a scar the precise shape and size of a cashew nut) are so many hooks waiting to land you." -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223827-boys-will-be-boys-that-s-what-people-say-no-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 15:39:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Hilary Thayer Hamann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223827-boys-will-be-boys-that-s-what-people-say-no-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;i&gt;Boys will be boys&lt;/i&gt;, that's what people say.  No one ever mentions how girls have to be something other than themselves altogether.  We are to stifle the same feelings that boys are encouraged to display.  We are to use gossip as a means of policing ourselves -- this way those who do succumb to sex but are not damaged by it are damaged instead by peer malice.  Girls demand a covenant because if one gives in, others will be expected to do the same.  We are to remain united in cruelty, ignorance, and aversion.  Or we are to starve the flesh from our bones, penalizing the body for its nature, castigating ourselves for advances we are powerless to prevent.  We are to make false promises then resist the attentions solicited.  Basically we are to become expert liars.  (p. 65)" -- Hilary Thayer Hamann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41926-every-life-is-inexplicable-i-kept-telling-myself-no-matter</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2010 22:44:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Paul Auster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41926-every-life-is-inexplicable-i-kept-telling-myself-no-matter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every life is inexplicable, I kept telling myself. No matter how many facts are told, no matter how many details are given, the essential thing resists telling. To say that so and so was born here and went there, that he did this and did that, that he married this woman and had these children, that he lived, that he died, that he left behind these books or this battle or that bridge – none of that tells us very much." -- Paul Auster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58943-they-belonged-to-that-vast-group-of-human-automata-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 02:34:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58943-they-belonged-to-that-vast-group-of-human-automata-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They belonged to that vast group of human automata who go through life without neglecting to perform a single one of the gestures executed by the surrounding puppets." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34197-she-was-so-evidently-the-victim-of-the-civilization-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 02:34:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34197-she-was-so-evidently-the-victim-of-the-civilization-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was so evidently the victim of the civilization which had produced her, that the links of her bracelet seemed like manacles chaining her to her fate." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58659-i-was-just-a-screw-or-cog-in-the-great</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 02:34:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58659-i-was-just-a-screw-or-cog-in-the-great]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was just a screw or cog in the great machine I called life, and when I dropped out of it I found I was of no use anywhere else." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202812-she-had-been-bored-all-afternoon-by-percy-gryce-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 02:34:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202812-she-had-been-bored-all-afternoon-by-percy-gryce-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had been bored all afternoon by Percy Gryce... but she could not ignore him on the morrow, she must follow up her success, must submit to more boredom, must be ready with fresh compliances and adaptibilities, and all on the bare chance that he might ultimately decide to do her the honour of boring her for life." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23158-of-course-i-loved-books-more-than-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 02:58:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Diane Setterfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23158-of-course-i-loved-books-more-than-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of course I loved books more than people." -- Diane Setterfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188039-men-are-afraid-that-women-will-laugh-at-them-women</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 14:24:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188039-men-are-afraid-that-women-will-laugh-at-them-women]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men are afraid that women will laugh at them. Women are afraid that men will kill them." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7038-kiss-me-and-you-will-see-how-important-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 05:24:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7038-kiss-me-and-you-will-see-how-important-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kiss me, and you will see how important I am." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417301-a-man-is-unlikely-to-be-brought-within-earshot-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 17:13:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Naomi Wolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417301-a-man-is-unlikely-to-be-brought-within-earshot-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man is unlikely to be brought within earshot of women as they judge men's appearance, height, muscle tone, sexual technique, penis size, personal grooming, or taste in clothes--all of which we do. The fact is that women are able to view men just as men view women, as objects for sexual and aesthetic evaluation; we too are effortlessly able to choose the male &quot;ideal&quot; from a lineup and if we could have male beauty as well as everything else, most of us would not say no. But so what? Given all that, women make the choice, by and large, to take men as human beings first." -- Naomi Wolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36597-ignoring-isn-t-the-same-as-ignorance-you-have-to-work</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 19:33:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36597-ignoring-isn-t-the-same-as-ignorance-you-have-to-work]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ignoring isn’t the same as ignorance, you have to work at it." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2029-if-you-knew-what-was-going-to-happen-if-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 19:33:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2029-if-you-knew-what-was-going-to-happen-if-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you knew what was going to happen, if you knew everything that was going to happen next—if you knew in advance the consequences of your own actions—you'd be doomed. You'd be ruined as God. You'd be a stone. You'd never eat or drink or laugh or get out of bed in the morning. You'd never love anyone, ever again. You'd never dare to." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104390-i-don-t-want-to-see-anyone-i-lie-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 19:33:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104390-i-don-t-want-to-see-anyone-i-lie-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't want to see anyone. I lie in the bedroom with the curtains drawn and nothingness washing over me like a sluggish wave. Whatever is happening to me is my own fault. I have done something wrong, something so huge I can't even see it, something that's drowning me. I am inadequate and stupid, without worth. I might as well be dead." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223189-i-was-always-attracted-not-by-some-quantifiable-external-beauty</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 14:30:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223189-i-was-always-attracted-not-by-some-quantifiable-external-beauty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was always attracted not by some quantifiable, external beauty, but by something deep down, something absolute. Just as some people have a secret love for rainstorms, earthquakes, or blackouts, I liked that certain undefinable something directed my way by members of the opposite sex. For want of a better word, call it magnetism. Like it or not, it’s a kind of power that snares people and reels them in." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255376-just-because-you-discover-that-you-may-like-somebody-after</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 14:34:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Steve Kluger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255376-just-because-you-discover-that-you-may-like-somebody-after]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just because you discover that you may like somebody after all, it doesn't necessarily mean there's any attraction." -- Steve Kluger]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
