<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1031122-arminda]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1031122-arminda" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 19:39:40 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2343-i-am-at-the-moment-writing-a-lengthy-indictment-against</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 19:39:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminda add a quote by John Kennedy Toole]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2343-i-am-at-the-moment-writing-a-lengthy-indictment-against]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am at the moment writing a lengthy indictment against our century. When my brain begins to reel from my literary labors, I make an occasional cheese dip." -- John Kennedy Toole]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33307-you-were-sick-but-now-you-re-well-again-and-there-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 19:39:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminda add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33307-you-were-sick-but-now-you-re-well-again-and-there-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You were sick, but now you're well again, and there's work to do." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40296-are-you-ready-for-new-urban-fragrances-yeah-i-guess</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 19:39:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminda add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40296-are-you-ready-for-new-urban-fragrances-yeah-i-guess]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Are You Ready for New Urban Fragrances?

Yeah, I guess I'm ready, but listen:

Perfume is a disguise. Since the middle ages, we have worn masks of fruit and flowers in order to conceal from ourselves the meaty essence of our humanity. We appreciate the sexual attractant of the rose, the ripeness of the orange, more than we honor our own ripe carnality.

Now today we want to perfume our cities, as well; to replace their stinging fumes of disturbed fossils' sleep with the scent of gardens and orchards. Yet, humans are not bees any more than they are blossoms. If we must pull an olfactory hood over our urban environment, let it be of a different nature.

I want to travel on a train that smells like snowflakes.

I want to sip in cafes that smell like comets.

Under the pressure of my step, I want the streets to emit the precise odor of a diamond necklace.

I want the newspapers I read to smell like the violins left in pawnshops by weeping hobos on Christmas Eve.

I want to carry luggage that reeks of the neurons in Einstein's brain.

I want a city's gases to smell like the golden belly hairs of the gods.

And when I gaze at a televised picture of the moon, I want to detect, from a distance of 239,000 miles, the aroma of fresh mozzarella." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
