<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1031188-anita-fortuna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1031188-anita-fortuna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 16:26:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382254-a-certain-king-had-a-beautiful-garden-and-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 16:26:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anita add a quote by Brothers Grimm]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382254-a-certain-king-had-a-beautiful-garden-and-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A certain king had a beautiful garden, and in the garden stood a tree which bore golden apples. These apples were always counted, and about the time when they began to grow ripe it was found that every night one of them was gone. The king became very angry at this, and ordered the gardener to keep watch all night under the tree. The gardener set his eldest son to watch; but about twelve o'clock he fell asleep, and in the morning another of the apples was missing. Then the second son was ordered to watch; and at midnight he too fell asleep, and in the morning another apple was gone. Then the third son offered to keep watch; but the gardener at first would not let him, for fear some harm should come to him: however, at last he consented, and the young man laid himself under the tree to watch. As the clock struck twelve he heard a rustling noise in the air, and a bird came flying that was of pure gold; and as it was snapping at one of the apples with its beak, the gardener's son jumped up and shot an arrow at it. But the arrow did the bird no harm; only it dropped a golden feather from its tail, and then flew away. The golden feather was brought to the king in the morning, and all the council was called together. Everyone agreed that it was worth more than all the wealth of the kingdom: but the king said, 'One feather is of no use to me, I must have the whole bird." -- Brothers Grimm]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/547137-people-i-have-discovered-are-layers-and-layers-of-secrets</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 23:47:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anita add a quote by Veronica Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/547137-people-i-have-discovered-are-layers-and-layers-of-secrets]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People, I have discovered, are layers and layers of secrets. You believe you know them, that you understand them, but their motives are always hidden from you, buried in their own hearts. You will never know them, but sometimes you decide to trust them." -- Veronica Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1169805-the-future-wafts-in-and-out-of-my-world-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 02:00:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anita add a quote by Addison Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1169805-the-future-wafts-in-and-out-of-my-world-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The future wafts in and out of my world like a ghost—like a lumbering beast, begging to be tamed. For so long it sat locked in mystery, surrounding me, fickle as the wind. I see it now for the noose it is, the game that never satisfies, the warrior that always kills." -- Addison Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1203875-shame-is-prides-cloke</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 00:24:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anita add a quote by William Blake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1203875-shame-is-prides-cloke]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Shame is Prides cloke." -- William Blake]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37760-the-apple-tree-never-asks-the-beech-how-he-shall</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 00:29:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anita add a quote by William Blake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37760-the-apple-tree-never-asks-the-beech-how-he-shall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The apple tree never asks the beech how he shall grow, nor the lion, the horse, how he shall take his prey." -- William Blake]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1204054-i-have-only-been-trying-to-please-you-for-peace</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 04:03:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anita add a quote by C S Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1204054-i-have-only-been-trying-to-please-you-for-peace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have only been trying to please you, for peace sake." -- C S Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1204732-of-course-having-allowed-oneself-to-drift-unresisting-unpraying-accepting</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 15:49:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anita add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1204732-of-course-having-allowed-oneself-to-drift-unresisting-unpraying-accepting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of course. Having allowed oneself to drift, unresisting, unpraying, accepting every half-conscious solicitation from our desires, we reached a point where we no longer believed the Faith. Just in the same way, a jealous man, drifting and unresisting, reaches a point at which he believes lies about his best friend: a drunkard reaches a point at which (for the moment) he actually believes that another glass will do him no harm. The beliefs are sincere in the sense that they do occur as psychological events in the man's mind. If that's what you mean by sincerity they are sincere, and so were ours. But errors which are sincere in that sense are not innocent." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1205018-isn-t-that-a-bit-hard-on-their-own-parents-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 21:33:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anita add a quote by C S Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1205018-isn-t-that-a-bit-hard-on-their-own-parents-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't that a bit hard on their own parents?&quot; &quot;No. There are those that steal other people's children. But her motherhood was of a different kind. Those on whom it fell went back to their natural parents loving them more. Few men looked on her without becoming, in a certain fashion, her lovers. But it was the kind of love that made them not less true, but truer, to their own wives." -- C S Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
