<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1031775-noelle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1031775-noelle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 07:42:45 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320282-wildlife-we-are-constantly-told-would-run-loose-across-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 07:42:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Noelle add a quote by Matthew Scully]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320282-wildlife-we-are-constantly-told-would-run-loose-across-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wildlife, we are constantly told, would run loose across our towns and cities were it not for the sport hunters to control their population, as birds would blanket the skies without the culling services of Ducks Unlimited and other groups. Yet here they are breeding wild animals, year after year replenishing the stock, all for the sole purpose of selling and killing them, deer and bears and elephants so many products being readied for the market. Animals such as deer, we are told, have no predators in many areas, and therefore need systematic culling. Yet when attempts are made to reintroduce natural predators such as wolves and coyotes into these very areas, sport hunters themselves are the first to resist it. Weaker animals in the wild, we hear, will only die miserable deaths by starvation and exposure without sport hunters to control their population. Yet it's the bigger, stronger animals they're killing and wounding--the very opposite of natural selection--often with bows and pistols that only compound and prolong the victim's suffering." -- Matthew Scully]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287559-school-is-the-advertising-agency-which-makes-you-believe-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 09:04:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Noelle add a quote by Ivan Illich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287559-school-is-the-advertising-agency-which-makes-you-believe-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["School is the advertising agency which makes you believe that you need the society as it is." -- Ivan Illich]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
