<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1032127-helena-corder]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1032127-helena-corder" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 07:31:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228361-theological-formation-is-the-gradual-and-often-painful-discovery-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 07:31:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Henri Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228361-theological-formation-is-the-gradual-and-often-painful-discovery-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Theological formation is the gradual and often painful discovery of God's incomprehensibility.  You can be competent in many things, but you cannot be competent in God." -- Henri Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185068-we-are-all-clothed-with-fleece-of-sheep-i-keep</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 07:30:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Susan Howe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185068-we-are-all-clothed-with-fleece-of-sheep-i-keep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all clothed with fleece of sheep I keep saying as if

I were singing as these words do.  Throw a shawl over me

so you won't be afraid to sleep.  I have already shown that

space is God." -- Susan Howe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185070-following-someone-is-always-falling-in-love-with-you-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 07:30:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Virginia Adair]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185070-following-someone-is-always-falling-in-love-with-you-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Following

Someone is always falling in love with you:
men and women, infants and children,
octogenarians and adolescents.
A tenant of heaven-haven on the pearly doorstep
hopes you will wave your hand in passing.
Where you stood just now a white bird
has flown into a ponderosa pine
and a black bee hovers in a bush of yellow flowers.

People would like to discuss you, but hold back.
Mystery is a fragile substance, too easy to tear.
Several persons, however, have noticed that you are followed
not by the usual shadow but by a shaft of sunlight.
Even on a day of fog or light rain.
Even after sunset.

When you are not present, you still walk quietly
through our minds, and we tell ourselves little stories
or small poems about you, like this one.
When a bird sings, we listen carefully
hoping your name will be mentioned." -- Virginia Adair]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13454-i-turned-silences-and-nights-into-words-what-was-unutterable</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 20:44:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Arthur Rimbaud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13454-i-turned-silences-and-nights-into-words-what-was-unutterable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I turned silences and nights into words. What was unutterable, I wrote down. I made the whirling world stand still." -- Arthur Rimbaud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185071-a-bruise-blue-in-the-muscle-you-impinge-upon-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 07:30:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Li-Young Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185071-a-bruise-blue-in-the-muscle-you-impinge-upon-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["a bruise, blue
in the muscle, you
impinge upon me.
As bone hugs the ache home, so
I'm vexed to love you, your body

the shape of returns, your hair a torso
of light, your heat
I must have, your opening
I'd eat, each moment
of that soft-finned fruit,
inverted fountain in which I don't see me." -- Li-Young Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122273-service-which-is-rendered-without-joy-helps-neither-the-servant</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 12:48:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122273-service-which-is-rendered-without-joy-helps-neither-the-servant]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Service which is rendered without joy helps neither the servant nor the served. But all other pleasures and possessions pale into nothingness before service which is rendered in a spirit of joy." -- Mahatma Gandhi ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182364-murray-said-i-don-t-trust-anybody-s-nostalgia-but-my-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 12:48:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182364-murray-said-i-don-t-trust-anybody-s-nostalgia-but-my-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Murray said, ´I don´t trust anybody´s nostalgia but my own.  Nostalgia is a product of dissatisfaction and rage.  It´s a settling of grievances between the present and the past.  The more powerful the nostalgia, the closer you come to violence.  War is the form nostalgia takes when men are hard-pressed to say something good about their country.´" -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185375-in-the-poetry-of-attention-poems-are-not-problems</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 07:30:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Donald Revell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185375-in-the-poetry-of-attention-poems-are-not-problems]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the poetry of attention, poems are not problems." -- Donald Revell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187522-no-one-ever-became-excellent-in-any-exercise-whatsoever-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 07:30:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Giorgio Vasari]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187522-no-one-ever-became-excellent-in-any-exercise-whatsoever-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...no one ever became excellent in any exercise whatsoever without beginning from his childhood to endure heat, cold, hunger, thirst, and other discomforts; wherefore those men are entirely deceived who think to be able, at their ease and with all the comforts of the world, to attain an honorable rank.  It is not by sleeping but by waking and studying continually that progress is made. [on Luca Della Robbia]" -- Giorgio Vasari]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187847-the-good-bishop-of-assisi-expressed-a-sort-of-horror</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 07:30:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187847-the-good-bishop-of-assisi-expressed-a-sort-of-horror]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The good Bishop of Assisi expressed a sort of horror at the hard life which the Little Brothers lived at the Portiuncula, without comforts, without possessions, eating anything they could get and sleeping anyhow on the ground. St. Francis answered him with that curious and almost stunning shrewdness which the unworldly can sometimes wield like a club of stone. He said, 'If we had any possessions, we should need weapons and laws to defend them." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176971-for-loss-is-what-we-live-with-all-the-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:35:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by William Bronk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176971-for-loss-is-what-we-live-with-all-the-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For loss is what we live with all the time. / None knows this better than the mind should know, the mind / that wanders, and cannot tell our name, itself / all seeds and survivals, little else, poor blind." -- William Bronk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296713-why-should-a-man-marry-and-have-children-study-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 07:31:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296713-why-should-a-man-marry-and-have-children-study-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why should a man marry and have children, study and build a career; why should he invent new techniques, build new institutions, and develop new ideas--when he doubts if there will be a tomorrow which can guarantee the value of human effort?  
Crucial here for nuclear man is the lack of a sense of continuity, which is so vital for a creative life.  He finds himself part of a nonhistory in which only the sharp moment of the here and now is valuable.  For nuclear man life easily becomes a bow whose string is broken and from which no arrow can fly.  In his dislocated state he becomes paralyzed.  His reactions are not anxiety and joy, which were so much a part of existential man, but apathy and boredom." -- Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218417-however-we-resolve-the-issue-in-our-individual-homes-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 07:31:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Barbara Ehrenreich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218417-however-we-resolve-the-issue-in-our-individual-homes-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["However we resolve the issue in our individual homes, the moral challenge is, put simply, to make work visible again: not only the scrubbing and vacuuming, but all the hoeing, stacking, hammering, drilling, bending, and lifting that goes into creating and maintaining a livable habitat.  In an ever more economically unequal world, where so many of the affluent devote their lives to ghostly pursuits like stock trading, image making, and opinion polling, real work, in the old-fashioned sense of labor that engages hand as well as eye, that tires the body and directly alters the physical world tends to vanish from sight.  The feminists of my generation tried to bring some of it into the light of day, but, like busy professional women fleeing the house in the morning, they left the project unfinished, the debate broken off in mid-sentence, the noble intentions unfulfilled.  Sooner or later, someone else will have to finish the job." -- Barbara Ehrenreich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182141-what-really-matters-is-that-we-should-all-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 12:48:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Albert Schweitzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182141-what-really-matters-is-that-we-should-all-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What really matters is that we should all of us realize that we are guilty of inhumanity.  The horror of this realization should shakes us out of our lethargy so that we can direct our hopes and our intentions to the coming of an era in which war will have no place." -- Albert Schweitzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296714-when-two-people-have-become-present-to-each-other-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 07:31:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296714-when-two-people-have-become-present-to-each-other-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[...]when two people have become present to each other, the waiting of one must be able to cross the narrow line between the living or dying of the other." -- Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4942-the-only-obligation-to-which-in-advance-we-may-hold</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 12:46:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4942-the-only-obligation-to-which-in-advance-we-may-hold]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only obligation to which in advance we may hold a novel, without incurring the accusation of being arbitrary, is that it be interesting." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175977-the-most-difficult-subjects-can-be-explained-to-the-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 12:45:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175977-the-most-difficult-subjects-can-be-explained-to-the-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most difficult subjects can be explained to the most slow-
witted man if he has not formed any idea of them already; but the
simplest thing cannot be made clear to the most intelligent man if
he is firmly persuaded that he knows already, without a shadow of
doubt, what is laid before him." -- Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173608-the-opinions-prevalent-in-one-age-as-truths-above-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 07:00:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Samuel Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173608-the-opinions-prevalent-in-one-age-as-truths-above-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opinions prevalent in one age, as truths above the reach of controversy, are confuted and rejected in another, and rise again to reception in remoter times. Thus the human mind is kept in motion without progress. " -- Samuel Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173609-parts-are-not-to-be-examined-till-the-whole-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 12:45:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Samuel Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173609-parts-are-not-to-be-examined-till-the-whole-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Parts are not to be examined till the whole has been surveyed; there is a kind of intellectual remoteness necessary for the comprehension of any great work in its full design and its true proportions; a close approach shews the smaller niceties, but the beauty of the whole is discerned no longer." -- Samuel Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175834-truth-has-drawn-me-into-the-field-of-politics-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 14:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175834-truth-has-drawn-me-into-the-field-of-politics-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Truth has drawn me into the field of politics; and I can say without the slightest hesitation, and yet in all humility, that those who say that religion has nothing to do with politics do not know what religion means." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176409-the-old-superstition-about-fiction-being-wicked-has-doubtless-died</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 17:33:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176409-the-old-superstition-about-fiction-being-wicked-has-doubtless-died]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The old superstition about fiction being 'wicked' has doubtless died out in England; but the spirit of it lingers in a certain oblique regard directed toward any story which does not more or less admit that it is only a joke. Even the most jocular novel feels in some degree the weight of the proscription that was formerly directed against literary levity; the jocularity does not always succeed in passing for gravity. It is still expected, though perhaps people are ashamed to say it, that a production which is after all only a 'make believe' (for what else is a 'story'?) shall be in some degree apologetic-shall renounce the pretension of attempting really to compete with life. This, of course, any sensible wide-awake story declines to do, for it quickly perceives that the tolerance granted to it on such a condition is only an attempt to stifle it, disguised in the form of generosity. " -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176413-the-power-to-guess-the-unseen-from-the-seen-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 17:42:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176413-the-power-to-guess-the-unseen-from-the-seen-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The power to guess the unseen from the seen, to trace the implication of things, to judge the whole piece by the pattern, the condition of feeling life, in general, so completely that you are well on your way to knowing any particular corner of it-this cluster of gifts may almost be said to constitute experience, and they occur in country and in town, and in the most differing stages of education." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176415-it-is-as-difficult-to-suppose-a-person-intending-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 17:50:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176415-it-is-as-difficult-to-suppose-a-person-intending-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is as difficult to suppose a person intending to write a modern English, as to suppose him writing an ancient English, novel; that is a label which begs the question. One writes the novel, one paints the picture, of one's language and of one's time, and calling it modern English will not, alas! make the difficult task any easier." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176416-nothing-of-course-will-ever-take-the-place-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 17:53:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176416-nothing-of-course-will-ever-take-the-place-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing, of course, will ever take the place of the good old fashion of 'liking' a work of art or not liking it; the more improved criticism will not abolish that primitive, that ultimate, test." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176972-reality-is-what-we-are-ignorant-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 16:37:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by William Bronk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176972-reality-is-what-we-are-ignorant-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reality is what we are ignorant of.  " -- William Bronk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176975-caress-me-be-kind-we-have-no-history</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 16:43:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by William Bronk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176975-caress-me-be-kind-we-have-no-history]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Caress me, be kind.  We have no history." -- William Bronk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176977-i-want-to-be-that-tantalus-unfed-forever-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 16:46:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by William Bronk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176977-i-want-to-be-that-tantalus-unfed-forever-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to be that Tantalus, unfed / forever, that my want's agony declare / that such as we want has nothing to say to the world; / if the world wants, it nothing wants for us.  / Let me be unsatisfied." -- William Bronk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176980-a-light-this-side-of-the-hills-toward-argyle</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 16:52:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by William Bronk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176980-a-light-this-side-of-the-hills-toward-argyle]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A light, this side of the hills toward Argyle, / flowed like fog through the hollows, rose to the depth / of the hills, illumined me.  I faded in it / as the world faded in me, dissolved in the light. / No one to know and nothing knowable. / Oh, we know that knowing is not our way; / but, the choice is ours, would make it our way, would leave / the world for the same world made knowable." -- William Bronk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176981-landscape-is-metaphor-and-only-metaphor-but-oh-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 16:55:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by William Bronk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176981-landscape-is-metaphor-and-only-metaphor-but-oh-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Landscape is metaphor / and only metaphor. But, oh, I have loved it so." -- William Bronk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176982-i-want-to-tell-my-friends-how-beautiful-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 17:06:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helena add a quote by William Bronk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176982-i-want-to-tell-my-friends-how-beautiful-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to tell my friends how beautiful / the world is.  Not but what they know / it is terrible too--they know as well as I; / but nevertheless, I want to tell my friends. / Because they are.  And this is what they are; / and because it is and this is what it is. / You are my friend.  The world is beautiful. / Dear friend, you are.  I want to tell you so." -- William Bronk]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
