<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1032813-hannah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1032813-hannah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 14:38:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/661374-i-want-you-to-tell-me-about-every-person-you-ve</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 14:38:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Andrea Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/661374-i-want-you-to-tell-me-about-every-person-you-ve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want you to tell me about every person you've ever been in love with. Tell me why you loved them, then tell me why they loved you. Tell me about a day in your life you didn't think you’d live through. Tell me what the word “home” means to you and tell me in a way that I’ll know your mothers name just by the way you describe your bed room when you were 8. See, I wanna know the first time you felt the weight of hate and if that day still trembles beneath your bones. Do you kiss your friends on the cheek? Do you think that anger is a sincere emotion or just the timid motion of a fragile heart trying to beat away its pain? See, I wanna know what you think of your first name. And if you often lie awake at night and imagine your mothers joy when she spoke it for the very first time. I want you tell me all the ways you've been unkind. Tell me all the ways you've been cruel.Do you believe that Mary was really a virgin? Do you believe that Moses really parted the sea? And if you don’t believe in miracles, tell me, how would you explain the miracle of my life to me? And for all the times you've knelt before the temple of yourself, have the prayers you've asked come true? And if they didn't did you feel denied? And if you felt denied, denied by who[m]? I wanna know what you see when you look in the mirror on a day you’re feeling good. I wanna know what you see in the mirror on a day a day you’re feeling bad. I wanna know the first person who ever taught you your beauty could ever be reflected on a lousy piece of glass. If you ever reach enlightenment, will you remember how to laugh? Have you ever been a song? See, I wanna know more than what you do for a living. I wanna know how much of your life you spend just giving. And if you love yourself enough to also receive sometimes. I wanna know if you bleed sometimes through other people’s wounds. And if you dream sometimes that this life is just a balloon that if you wanted to you could pop—but you never would because you’d never want it to stop." -- Andrea Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/656838-before-i-die-i-want-to-be-somebody-s-favorite-hiding</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 14:38:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Andrea Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/656838-before-i-die-i-want-to-be-somebody-s-favorite-hiding]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Before I die, I want to be somebody’s favorite hiding place, the place they can put everything they know they need to survive, every secret, every solitude, every nervous prayer, and be absolutely certain I will keep it safe. I will keep it safe." -- Andrea Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522923-the-nutritionist-said-i-should-eat-root-vegetables-said-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 14:39:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Andrea Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522923-the-nutritionist-said-i-should-eat-root-vegetables-said-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The nutritionist said I should eat root vegetables.
Said if I could get down thirteen turnips a day
I would be grounded, rooted.
Said my head would not keep flying away
to where the darkness lives.
 
The psychic told me my heart carries too much weight.
Said for twenty dollars she’d tell me what to do.
I handed her the twenty. She said, “Stop worrying, darling.
You will find a good man soon.”
 
The first psycho therapist told me to spend
three hours each day sitting in a dark closet
with my eyes closed and ears plugged.
I tried it once but couldn’t stop thinking
about how gay it was to be sitting in the closet.
 
The yogi told me to stretch everything but the truth.
Said to focus on the out breath. Said everyone finds happiness
when they care more about what they give
than what they get.
 
The pharmacist said, “Lexapro, Lamicatl, Lithium, Xanax.”
 
The doctor said an anti-psychotic might help me
forget what the trauma said.
 
The trauma said, “Don’t write these poems.
Nobody wants to hear you cry
about the grief inside your bones.”
 
But my bones said, “Tyler Clementi jumped
from the George Washington Bridge
into the Hudson River convinced
he was entirely alone.”
 
My bones said, “Write the poems." -- Andrea Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/713699-i-want-you-to-tell-me-about-every-person-you-ve</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 14:39:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Andrea Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/713699-i-want-you-to-tell-me-about-every-person-you-ve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want you to tell me about every person you’ve ever been in love with.
Tell me why you loved them,
then tell me why they loved you.

Tell me about a day in your life you didn’t think you’d live through.
Tell me what the word home means to you
and tell me in a way that I’ll know your mother’s name
just by the way you describe your bedroom
when you were eight.

See, I want to know the first time you felt the weight of hate,
and if that day still trembles beneath your bones.

Do you prefer to play in puddles of rain
or bounce in the bellies of snow?
And if you were to build a snowman,
would you rip two branches from a tree to build your snowman arms
or would leave your snowman armless
for the sake of being harmless to the tree?
And if you would,
would you notice how that tree weeps for you
because your snowman has no arms to hug you
every time you kiss him on the cheek?

Do you kiss your friends on the cheek?
Do you sleep beside them when they’re sad
even if it makes your lover mad?
Do you think that anger is a sincere emotion
or just the timid motion of a fragile heart trying to beat away its pain?

See, I wanna know what you think of your first name,
and if you often lie awake at night and imagine your mother’s joy
when she spoke it for the very first time.

I want you to tell me all the ways you’ve been unkind.
Tell me all the ways you’ve been cruel.
Tell me, knowing I often picture Gandhi at ten years old
beating up little boys at school.

If you were walking by a chemical plant
where smokestacks were filling the sky with dark black clouds
would you holler “Poison! Poison! Poison!” really loud
or would you whisper
“That cloud looks like a fish,
and that cloud looks like a fairy!”

Do you believe that Mary was really a virgin?
Do you believe that Moses really parted the sea?
And if you don’t believe in miracles, tell me —
how would you explain the miracle of my life to me?

See, I wanna know if you believe in any god
or if you believe in many gods
or better yet
what gods believe in you.
And for all the times that you’ve knelt before the temple of yourself,
have the prayers you asked come true?
And if they didn’t, did you feel denied?
And if you felt denied,
denied by who?

I wanna know what you see when you look in the mirror
on a day you’re feeling good.
I wanna know what you see when you look in the mirror
on a day you’re feeling bad.
I wanna know the first person who taught you your beauty
could ever be reflected on a lousy piece of glass.

If you ever reach enlightenment
will you remember how to laugh?

Have you ever been a song?
Would you think less of me
if I told you I’ve lived my entire life a little off-key?
And I’m not nearly as smart as my poetry
I just plagiarize the thoughts of the people around me
who have learned the wisdom of silence.

Do you believe that concrete perpetuates violence?
And if you do —
I want you to tell me of a meadow
where my skateboard will soar.

See, I wanna know more than what you do for a living.
I wanna know how much of your life you spend just giving,
and if you love yourself enough to also receive sometimes.
I wanna know if you bleed sometimes
from other people’s wounds,
and if you dream sometimes
that this life is just a balloon —
that if you wanted to, you could pop,
but you never would
‘cause you’d never want it to stop.

If a tree fell in the forest
and you were the only one there to hear —
if its fall to the ground didn’t make a sound,
would you panic in fear that you didn’t exist,
or would you bask in the bliss of your nothingness?

And lastly, let me ask you this:

If you and I went for a walk
and the entire walk, we didn’t talk —
do you think eventually, we’d… kiss?

No, wait.
That’s asking too much —
after all,
this is only our first date." -- Andrea Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/623337-i-know-you-think-this-world-is-too-dark-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 14:40:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Andrea Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/623337-i-know-you-think-this-world-is-too-dark-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know you think this world is too dark to even dream in color,
but I’ve seen flowers bloom at midnight.
I’ve seen kites fly in gray skies
and they were real close to looking like the sunrise,
and sometime it takes the most wounded wings
the most broken things
to notice how strong the breeze is,
how precious the flight." -- Andrea Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221247-you-don-t-love-someone-for-their-looks-or-their-clothes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 15:11:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Helen Keller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221247-you-don-t-love-someone-for-their-looks-or-their-clothes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't love someone for their looks, or their clothes, or for their fancy car, but because they sing a song only you can hear." -- Helen Keller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15202-a-woman-s-heart-should-be-so-hidden-in-god-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 15:25:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Max Lucado]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15202-a-woman-s-heart-should-be-so-hidden-in-god-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A woman's heart should be so hidden in God that a man has to seek Him just to find her." -- Max Lucado]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14109-faith-is-not-the-belief-that-god-will-do-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 15:25:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Max Lucado]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14109-faith-is-not-the-belief-that-god-will-do-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Faith is not the belief that God will do what you want. It is the belief that God will do what is right." -- Max Lucado]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38382-when-you-are-in-the-final-days-of-your-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 15:26:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Max Lucado]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38382-when-you-are-in-the-final-days-of-your-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you are in the final days of your life, what will you want?

Will you hug that college degree in the walnut frame? Will you ask to be carried to the garage so you can sit in your car? Will you find comfort in rereading your financial statement? Of course not. What will matter then will be people. If relationships will matter most then, shouldn't they matter most now?" -- Max Lucado]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61786-you-weren-t-an-accident-you-weren-t-mass-produced-you-aren-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 15:26:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Max Lucado]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61786-you-weren-t-an-accident-you-weren-t-mass-produced-you-aren-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You weren't an accident.  You weren't mass produced.  You aren't an assembly-line product.  You were deliberately planned, specifically gifted, and lovingly positioned on the earth by the Master Craftsman." -- Max Lucado]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219593-if-god-had-a-refrigerator-your-picture-would-be-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 15:26:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Max Lucado]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219593-if-god-had-a-refrigerator-your-picture-would-be-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If God had a refrigerator, your picture would be on it. If He had a wallet, your photo would be in it. He sends you flowers every spring and a sunrise every morning... Face it, friend. He is crazy about you! " -- Max Lucado]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65927-to-lead-the-orchestra-you-have-to-turn-your-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 15:26:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Max Lucado]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65927-to-lead-the-orchestra-you-have-to-turn-your-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To lead the orchestra, you have to turn your back on the crowd." -- Max Lucado]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60503-he-saw-you-cast-into-a-river-of-life-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 15:26:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Max Lucado]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60503-he-saw-you-cast-into-a-river-of-life-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He saw you cast into a river of life you didn't request. He saw you betrayed by those you love. He saw you with a body that gets sick and a heart that grows weak. He saw you in your own garden of gnarled trees and sleeping friends. He saw you staring into the pit of your own failures and the mouth of your own grave. He saw you in your own garden of Gethsemane and he didn't want you to be alone ... He would rather go to hell for you than to heaven without you." -- Max Lucado]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62291-when-my-daughter-was-a-toddler-i-used-to-take</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 15:26:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Max Lucado]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62291-when-my-daughter-was-a-toddler-i-used-to-take]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When my daughter was a toddler, I used to take her to a park not far from our apartment. One day as she was playing in a sandbox, an ice-cream salesman approached us. I purchased her a treat, and when I turned to give it to her, I saw her mouth was full of sand. Where I had intended to put a delicacy, she had put dirt.

Did I love her with dirt in her mouth? Absolutely. Was she any less of my daughter with dirt in her mouth? Of course not. Was I going to allow her to keep the dirt in her mouth? No way. I loved her right where she was, but I refused to leave her there. I carried her over to the water fountain and washed out her mouth. Why? Because I love her.

God does the same for us. He holds us over the fountain. &quot;Spit out the dirt, honey,&quot; our Father urges. &quot;I've got something better for you.&quot; And so he cleanses us of filth; immorality, dishonesty, prejudice, bitterness, greed. We don't enjoy the cleansing; sometimes we even opt for the dirt over the ice cream. &quot;I can eat dirt if I want to!&quot; we pout and proclaim. Which is true—we can. But if we do, the loss is ours. God has a better offer." -- Max Lucado]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120854-i-choose-gentleness-nothing-is-won-by-force-i-choose</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 15:38:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Max Lucado]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120854-i-choose-gentleness-nothing-is-won-by-force-i-choose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I choose gentleness... Nothing is won by force. I choose to be gentle. If I raise my voice may it be only in praise. If I clench my fist, may it be only in prayer. If I make a demand, may it be only of myself." -- Max Lucado]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317479-though-we-are-incomplete-god-loves-us-completely-though-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 21:55:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317479-though-we-are-incomplete-god-loves-us-completely-though-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Though we are incomplete, God loves us completely. Though we are imperfect, He loves us perfectly. Though we may feel lost and without compass, God's love encompasses us completely. ... He loves every one of us, even those who are flawed, rejected, awkward, sorrowful, or broken." -- Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197388-what-we-love-determines-what-we-seek-what-we-seek</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 21:55:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197388-what-we-love-determines-what-we-seek-what-we-seek]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What we love determines what we seek.  What we seek determines what we think and do.  What we think and do determines who we are — and who we will become." -- Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70901-the-heavens-will-not-be-filled-with-those-who-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 21:55:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70901-the-heavens-will-not-be-filled-with-those-who-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The heavens will not be filled with those who never made mistakes but with those who recognized that they were off course and who corrected their ways to get back in the light of gospel truth." -- Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260289-true-love-requires-action-we-can-speak-of-love-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 21:55:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260289-true-love-requires-action-we-can-speak-of-love-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["True love requires action. We can speak of love all day long, we can write notes or poems that proclaim it, sing songs that praise it, and preach sermons that encourage it but until we manifest that love in action, our words are nothing but sounding brass, or a tinkling cymbal." -- Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284369-patience-is-not-passive-resignation-nor-is-it-failing-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 21:55:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284369-patience-is-not-passive-resignation-nor-is-it-failing-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Patience is not passive resignation, nor is it failing to act because of our fears. Patience means active waiting and enduring. It means staying with something and doing all that we can - working, hoping, and exercising faith; bearing hardship with fortitude, even when the desires of our hearts are delayed. patience is not simply enduring; it is enduring well!

Impatience, on the other hand, is a symptom of selfishness. It is a trait of the self-absorbed. It arises from the all too-prevalent condition called &quot;center of the universe&quot; syndrome, which leads people to believe that the world revolves around them and that all others are just supporting cast in the grand theater of mortality in which only they have the starring role." -- Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257975-as-you-take-the-normal-opportunities-of-your-daily-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 21:55:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257975-as-you-take-the-normal-opportunities-of-your-daily-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As you take the normal opportunities of your daily life and create something of beauty and helpfulness, you improve not only the world around you but also the world within you." -- Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273459-we-sometimes-confuse-sin-with-sinner-and-we-condemn-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 21:55:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273459-we-sometimes-confuse-sin-with-sinner-and-we-condemn-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We sometimes confuse sin with sinner, and we condemn too quickly and with too little compassion. We know from modern revelation that ‘the worth of souls is great in the sight of God.’ We cannot gauge the worth of another soul any more than we can measure the span of the universe." -- Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/327629-pause-for-a-moment-and-check-where-your-own-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 21:55:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/327629-pause-for-a-moment-and-check-where-your-own-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pause for a moment and check where your own heart and thoughts are. Are you focused on the things that matter most? How you spend your quiet time may provide a valuable clue. Where do your thoughts go when the pressure of deadlines is gone? Are your thoughts and heart focused on those short-lived fleeting things that matter only in the moment or on things that matter most?" -- Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360043-we-have-a-choice-we-can-seek-for-the-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 21:56:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360043-we-have-a-choice-we-can-seek-for-the-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have a choice. We can seek for the bad in others. Or we can make peace and work to extend to others the understanding, fairness, and forgiveness we so desperately desire for ourselves. It is our choice; for whatever we seek, that we will certainly find." -- Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227524-love-is-the-measure-of-our-faith-the-inspiration-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 21:56:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227524-love-is-the-measure-of-our-faith-the-inspiration-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is the measure of our faith, the inspiration for our obedience, and the true altitude of our discipleship." -- Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273479-may-i-invite-you-to-rise-to-the-great-potential</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 21:56:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273479-may-i-invite-you-to-rise-to-the-great-potential]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May I invite you to rise to the great potential within you. But don’t reach beyond your capacity. Don’t set goals beyond your capacity to achieve. Don’t feel guilty or dwell on thoughts of failure. Don’t compare yourself with others. Do the best you can, and the Lord will provide the rest. Have faith and confidence in Him, and you will see miracles happen in your life and the lives of your loved ones. The virtue of your own life will be a light to those who sit in darkness, because you are a living witness of the fulness of the gospel (see D&amp;C 45:28). Wherever you have been planted on this beautiful but often troubled earth of ours, you can be the one to “succor the weak, lift up the hands which hang down, and strengthen the feeble knees” (D&amp;C 81:5)." -- Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/655612-sometimes-we-become-so-focused-on-the-finish-line-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 21:57:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/655612-sometimes-we-become-so-focused-on-the-finish-line-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes we become so focused on the finish line, that we fail to find joy in the journey." -- Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42876-it-isn-t-as-bad-as-you-sometimes-think-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 22:06:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42876-it-isn-t-as-bad-as-you-sometimes-think-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It isn't as bad as you sometimes think it is. It all works out. Don't worry. I say that to myself every morning. It all works out in the end. Put your trust in God, and move forward with faith and confidence in the future. The Lord will not forsake us. He will not forsake us. If we will put our trust in Him, if we will pray to Him, if we will live worthy of His blessings, He will hear our prayers." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32631-you-have-not-failed-until-you-quit-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 22:06:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32631-you-have-not-failed-until-you-quit-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have not failed until you quit trying." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27611-aim-high-but-do-not-aim-so-high-that-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 22:07:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27611-aim-high-but-do-not-aim-so-high-that-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Aim high, but do not aim so high that you totally miss the target. What really matters is that he will love you, that he will respect you, that he will honor you, that he will be absolutely true to you, that he will give you the freedom of expression and let you fly in the development of your own talents. He is not going to be perfect, but if he is kind and thoughtful, if he knows how to work and earn a living, if he is honest and full of faith, the chances are you will not go wrong, that you will be immensely happy." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
