<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1032905-jenny]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1032905-jenny" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 16:41:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53166-the-best-fantasy-is-written-in-the-language-of-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 16:41:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53166-the-best-fantasy-is-written-in-the-language-of-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best fantasy is written in the language of dreams. It is alive as dreams are alive, more real than real ... for a moment at least ... that long magic moment before we wake.

     Fantasy is silver and scarlet, indigo and azure, obsidian veined with gold and lapis lazuli. Reality is plywood and plastic, done up in mud brown and olive drab. Fantasy tastes of habaneros and honey, cinnamon and cloves, rare red meat and wines as sweet as summer. Reality is beans and tofu, and ashes at the end. Reality is the strip malls of Burbank, the smokestacks of Cleveland, a parking garage in Newark. Fantasy is the towers of Minas Tirith, the ancient stones of Gormenghast, the halls of Camelot. Fantasy flies on the wings of Icarus, reality on Southwest Airlines. Why do our dreams become so much smaller when they finally come true?

     We read fantasy to find the colors again, I think. To taste strong spices and hear the songs the sirens sang. There is something old and true in fantasy that speaks to something deep within us, to the child who dreamt that one day he would hunt the forests of the night, and feast beneath the hollow hills, and find a love to last forever somewhere south of Oz and north of Shangri-La.

     They can keep their heaven. When I die, I'd sooner go to middle Earth." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34244-when-i-was-alive-i-believed-as-you-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 15:08:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34244-when-i-was-alive-i-believed-as-you-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was alive, I believed — as you do — that time was at least as real and solid as myself, and probably more so. I said 'one o'clock' as though I could see it, and 'Monday' as though I could find it on the map; and I let myself be hurried along from minute to minute, day to day, year to year, as though I were actually moving from one place to another. Like everyone else, I lived in a house bricked up with seconds and minutes, weekends and New Year's Days, and I never went outside until I died, because there was no other door. Now I know that I could have walked through the walls. (...) You can strike your own time, and start the count anywhere. When you understand that — then any time at all will be the right time for you." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1393-there-must-be-more-to-life-than-having-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 15:20:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Maurice Sendak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1393-there-must-be-more-to-life-than-having-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There must be more to life than having everything!" -- Maurice Sendak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73643-when-i-told-the-people-of-northern-ireland-that-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2009 17:55:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Quentin Crisp]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73643-when-i-told-the-people-of-northern-ireland-that-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I told the people of Northern Ireland that I was an atheist, a woman in the audience stood up and said, 'Yes, but is it the God of the Catholics or the God of the Protestants in whom you don't believe?" -- Quentin Crisp]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52419-the-most-difficult-thing-in-the-world-is-to-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 11:10:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by T. H. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52419-the-most-difficult-thing-in-the-world-is-to-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most difficult thing in the world is to know how to do a thing and to watch someone else do it wrong without comment." -- T. H. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4138-it-s-no-good-pretending-that-any-relationship-has-a-future</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 13:47:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4138-it-s-no-good-pretending-that-any-relationship-has-a-future]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's no good pretending that any relationship has a future if your record collections disagree violently or if your favorite films wouldn't even speak to each other if they met at a party." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112257-when-he-at-least-reached-the-door-the-handle-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 15:29:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Mervyn Peake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112257-when-he-at-least-reached-the-door-the-handle-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When he at least reached the door the handle had cease to vibrate. Lowering himself suddenly to his knees he placed his head and the vagaries of his left eye (which was for ever trying to dash up and down the vertical surface of the door), he was able by dint of concentration to observe, within three inches of his keyholed eye, an eye which was not his, being not only of a different colour to his own iron marble, but being, which is more convincing, on the other side of the door." -- Mervyn Peake]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11128-the-ships-hung-in-the-sky-in-much-the-same</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 12:26:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11128-the-ships-hung-in-the-sky-in-much-the-same]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The ships hung in the sky in much the same way that bricks don't." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331549-it-s-easy-to-confuse-a-woman-for-a-philosophy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 13:43:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331549-it-s-easy-to-confuse-a-woman-for-a-philosophy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's easy to confuse a woman for a philosophy" -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214373-i-am-from-the-kilburn-branch-of-the-keepers-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 13:44:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214373-i-am-from-the-kilburn-branch-of-the-keepers-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am from the Kilburn branch of the Keepers of the Eternal and Victorious Islamic Nation,&quot; said Hifan proudly.  

Irie inhaled.  

Keepers of the Eternal and Victorious Islamic Nation,&quot; repeated Millat, impressed.  &quot;That's a wicked name.  It's got a wicked kung-fu arse sound to it.&quot;  

Irie frowned.  &quot;KEVIN?&quot;

We are aware,&quot; said Hifan solemnly, pointing to the spot underneath the cupped flame where the initials were minutely embroidered, &quot;that we have an acronym problem." -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20112-when-adults-say-teenagers-think-they-are-invincible-with-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 12:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20112-when-adults-say-teenagers-think-they-are-invincible-with-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When adults say, &quot;Teenagers think they are invincible&quot; with that sly, stupid smile on their faces, they don't know how right they are. We need never be hopeless, because we can never be irreparably broken. We think that we are invincible because we are. We cannot be born, and we cannot die. Like all energy, we can only change shapes and sizes and manifestations. They forget that when they get old. They get scared of losing and failing. But that part of us greater than the sum of our parts cannot begin and cannot end, and so it cannot fail." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119386-sometimes-when-i-clean-a-kill-i-feed-buttercup-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 13:50:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119386-sometimes-when-i-clean-a-kill-i-feed-buttercup-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, when I clean a kill, I feed Buttercup the entrails. He has stopped hissing at me.
Entrails. No hissing. This is the closest we will ever come to love." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290804-they-had-a-year-of-joy-twelve-months-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 13:28:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by T.H. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290804-they-had-a-year-of-joy-twelve-months-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They had a year of joy, twelve months of the strange heaven which the salmon know on beds of river shingle, under the gin-clear water. For twenty-four years they were guilty, but this first year was the only one which seemed like happiness. Looking back on it, when they were old, they did not remember that in this year it had ever rained or frozen. The four seasons were coloured like the edge of a rose petal for them." -- T.H. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302478-you-could-not-give-up-a-human-heart-as-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 13:28:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by T.H. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302478-you-could-not-give-up-a-human-heart-as-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You could not give up a human heart as you could give up drinking. The drink was yours, and you could give it up: but your lover’s soul was not your own: it was not at your disposal; you had a duty towards it." -- T.H. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27992-do-you-remember-me-telling-you-we-are-practicing-non-verbal</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 13:33:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27992-do-you-remember-me-telling-you-we-are-practicing-non-verbal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you remember me telling you we are practicing non-verbal spells, Potter?&quot;
&quot;Yes,&quot; said Harry stiffly.
&quot;Yes, sir.&quot;
&quot;There's no need to call me &quot;sir&quot; Professor.&quot;
The words had escaped him before he knew what he was saying." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44293-another-belief-of-mine-that-everyone-else-my-age-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 08:30:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44293-another-belief-of-mine-that-everyone-else-my-age-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Another belief of mine: that everyone else my age is an adult, whereas I am merely in disguise." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290707-you-love-me-real-or-not-real-i-tell-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 08:30:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290707-you-love-me-real-or-not-real-i-tell-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You love me. Real or not real?&quot;
I tell him, &quot;Real." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31860-i-ve-lived-through-some-terrible-things-in-my-life-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 08:29:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31860-i-ve-lived-through-some-terrible-things-in-my-life-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've lived through some terrible things in my life, some of which actually happened." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25647-i-do-not-fear-death-i-had-been-dead-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 13:45:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25647-i-do-not-fear-death-i-had-been-dead-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not fear death. I had been dead for billions and billions of years before I was born, and had not suffered the slightest inconvenience from it." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19370-if-the-person-you-are-talking-to-doesn-t-appear-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 13:49:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19370-if-the-person-you-are-talking-to-doesn-t-appear-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the person you are talking to doesn't appear to be listening, be patient. It may simply be that he has a small piece of fluff in his ear." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626030-but-of-course-you-might-be-asking-yourself-am-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 11:16:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Caitlin Moran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626030-but-of-course-you-might-be-asking-yourself-am-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But, of course, you might be asking yourself, 'Am I a feminist? I might not be. I don't know! I still don't know what it is! I'm too knackered and confused to work it out. That curtain pole really still isn't up! I don't have time to work out if I am a women's libber! There seems to be a lot to it. WHAT DOES IT MEAN?'
I understand. 
So here is the quick way of working out if you're a feminist. Put your hand in your pants.

a) Do you have a vagina? and
b) Do you want to be in charge of it?

If you said 'yes' to both, then congratulations! You're a feminist." -- Caitlin Moran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14913-making-the-decision-to-have-a-child---it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 06:33:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Elizabeth Stone]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14913-making-the-decision-to-have-a-child---it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Making the decision to have a child - it is momentous. It is to decide forever to have your heart go walking around outside your body. " -- Elizabeth Stone]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2634-give-a-man-a-fire-and-he-s-warm-for-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 12:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2634-give-a-man-a-fire-and-he-s-warm-for-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Give a man a fire and he's warm for a day, but set fire to him and he's warm for the rest of his life." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
