<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/103377-layil-umbralux]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/103377-layil-umbralux" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 17:20:15 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170846-on-the-day-of-the-dead-when-the-year-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 17:20:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Layil add a quote by Susan Cooper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170846-on-the-day-of-the-dead-when-the-year-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the day of the dead, when the year too dies,
Must the youngest open the oldest hills
Through the door of the birds, where the breeze breaks.
There fire shall fly from the raven boy,
And the silver eyes that see the wind,
And the light shall have the harp of gold.

By the pleasant lake the Sleepers lie,
On Cadfan’s Way where the kestrels call;
Though grim from the Grey King shadows fall,
Yet singing the golden harp shall guide
To break their sleep and bid them ride.

When light from the lost land shall return,
Six Sleepers shall ride, six Signs shall burn,
And where the midsummer tree grows tall
By Pendragon’s sword the Dark shall fall.

Y maent yr mynyddoedd yn canu,
ac y mae’r arglwyddes yn dod." -- Susan Cooper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12988-for-ever-and-ever-we-say-when-we-are-young</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 17:20:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Layil add a quote by Susan Cooper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12988-for-ever-and-ever-we-say-when-we-are-young]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For ever and ever, we say when we are young, or in our prayers. Twice, we say it. Old One, do we not? For ever and ever ... so that a thing may be for ever, a life or a love or a quest, and yet begin again, and be for ever just as before. And any ending that may seem to come is not truly an ending, but an illusion. For Time does not die, Time has neither beginning nor end, and so nothing can end or die that has once had a place in Time." -- Susan Cooper]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
