<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1034604-kimberly]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1034604-kimberly" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 11:46:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/347487-if-you-haven-t-said-i-love-you-to-someone-today</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 11:46:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Lisa Lutz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/347487-if-you-haven-t-said-i-love-you-to-someone-today]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you haven't said 'I love you' to someone today, do it. You won't always be happy, but you should try to be. Don't be too afraid of germs. Those people have no fun. Remember to look around sometimes. You might see something you haven't seen before or at the very least avoid being hit by a flying object. Speaking of flying objects, don't spend your life looking for extraterrestrial life, unless you work for NASA. Remember that you always have to cooperate with someone. Life is an endless negotiation. Play fair. Stay out of jail. Don't live in the past. Eat breakfast. It really is the most important meal of the day. Try to make new friends, even when you think you're too old to do that. ...And finally, remember this&quot; 'Yes' is always a better work than 'no'. Unless, of course, someone has just asked you to commit a felony." -- Lisa Lutz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/347491-you-should-keep-dental-floss-on-you-at-all-times</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 11:47:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Lisa Lutz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/347491-you-should-keep-dental-floss-on-you-at-all-times]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["....You should keep dental floss on you at all times; when your eyesight goes, quit driving; don't keep too many secrets, eventually they'll eat away at you. But the most valuable lesson he taught me was this: Every day we get older, and some of us get wiser, but there's no end to our evolution. We are all a mess of contradictions; some of our traits work for us, some against us. And this is what I figured out on my own: Over the course of a lifetime, people change, but not as much as you'd think. Nobody really grows up." -- Lisa Lutz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/493946-closed-eyes-heart-not-beating-but-a-living-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 11:48:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Avis Corea]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/493946-closed-eyes-heart-not-beating-but-a-living-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Closed eyes, heart not beating, but a living love." -- Avis Corea]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116825-i-hope-that-one-day-you-will-have-the-experience</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 12:17:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116825-i-hope-that-one-day-you-will-have-the-experience]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hope that one day you will have the experience of doing something you do not understand for someone you love." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43014-it-s-the-tragedy-of-loving-you-can-t-love-anything-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 12:18:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43014-it-s-the-tragedy-of-loving-you-can-t-love-anything-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's the tragedy of loving, you can't love anything more than something you miss." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 12:26:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that no matter what happens, or how bad it seems today, life does go on, and it will be better tomorrow. I've learned that you can tell a lot about a person by the way he/she handles these three things: a rainy day, lost luggage, and tangled Christmas tree lights. I've learned that regardless of your relationship with your parents, you'll miss them when they're gone from your life. I've learned that making a &quot;living&quot; is not the same thing as making a &quot;life.&quot; I've learned that life sometimes gives you a second chance. I've learned that you shouldn't go through life with a catcher's mitt on both hands; you need to be able to throw something back. I've learned that whenever I decide something with an open heart, I usually make the right decision. I've learned that even when I have pains, I don't have to be one. I've learned that every day you should reach out and touch someone. People love a warm hug, or just a friendly pat on the back. I've learned that I still have a lot to learn. I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148003-there-are-women-who-make-things-better-simply-by-showing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 06:22:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Ashley Rice]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148003-there-are-women-who-make-things-better-simply-by-showing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are women who make things better... simply by showing up. There are women who make things happen. There are women who make their way. There are women who make a difference. And women who make us smile. There are women of wit and wisdom who- through strength and courage- make it through. There are women who change the world everyday... Women like you." -- Ashley Rice]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/755898-they-d-never-been-lovers-of-course-not-in-the-physical</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 13:42:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/755898-they-d-never-been-lovers-of-course-not-in-the-physical]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They'd never been lovers, of course, not in the physical sense. But they'd been lovers as most of us manage, loving through expressions and gestures and the palm set softly upon the bruise at the necessary moment. Lovers by inclination rather than by lust. Lovers, that is, by love." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137478-the-music-in-my-heart-i-bore-long-after-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 20:08:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by William Wordsworth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137478-the-music-in-my-heart-i-bore-long-after-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The music in my heart I bore
Long after it was heard no more." -- William Wordsworth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465202-the-moon-is-a-loyal-companion-it-never-leaves-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 20:11:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Tahereh Mafi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465202-the-moon-is-a-loyal-companion-it-never-leaves-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The moon is a loyal companion.
It never leaves. It’s always there, watching, steadfast, knowing us in our light and dark moments, changing forever just as we do. Every day it’s a different version of itself. Sometimes weak and wan, sometimes strong and full of light. The moon understands what it means to be human.
Uncertain. Alone. Cratered by imperfections." -- Tahereh Mafi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14724-may-you-have-warm-words-on-a-cold-evening-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 20:14:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Celtic salutation]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14724-may-you-have-warm-words-on-a-cold-evening-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May you have warm words on a cold evening, a full moon on a dark night, and the road downhill all the way to your door" -- Celtic salutation]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234070-i-saw-thee-once---only-once---years-ago</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 20:14:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234070-i-saw-thee-once---only-once---years-ago]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I saw thee once - only once - years ago:
I must not say how many - but not many.
It was a July midnight; and from out
A full-orbed moon, that, like thine own soul, soaring,
Sought a precipitate pathway up through heaven,
There fell a silvery-silken veil of light,
With quietude, and sultriness, and slumber,
Upon the upturn'd faces of a thousand
Roses that grew in an enchanted garden,
Where no wind dared stir, unless on tiptoe -
Fell on the upturn'd faces of these roses
That gave out, in return for the love-light,
Their odorous souls in an ecstatic death -
Fell on the upturn'd faces of these roses
That smiled and died in the parterre, enchanted
By thee, and by the poetry of thy presence.

Clad all in white, upon a violet bank
I saw thee half reclining; while the moon
Fell upon the upturn'd faces of the roses,
And on thine own, upturn'd - alas, in sorrow!

Was it not Fate, that, on this July midnight -
Was it not Fate, (whose name is also Sorrow,)
That bade me pause before that garden-gate,
To breathe the incense of those slumbering roses?
No footsteps stirred: the hated world all slept,
Save only thee and me. (Oh, Heaven! - oh, G**!
How my heart beats in coupling those two words!)
Save only thee and me. I paused - I looked -
And in an instant all things disappeared.
(Ah, bear in mind the garden was enchanted!)
The pearly lustre of the moon went out:
The mossy banks and the meandering paths,
The happy flowers and the repining trees,
Were seen no more: the very roses' odors
Died in the arms of the adoring airs.
All - all expired save thee - save less than thou:
Save only divine light in thine eyes -
Save but the soul in thine uplifted eyes.
I saw but them - they were the world to me.
I saw but them - saw only them for hours -
Saw only them until the moon went down.
What wild heart-histories seemed to lie enwritten
Upon those crystalline, celestial spheres!
How dark a wo! yet how sublime a hope!
How silently serene a sea of pride!
How daring an ambition! yet how deep -
How fathomless a capacity for love!
But now, at length, dear Dian sank from sight,
Into a western couch of thunder-cloud;
And thou, a ghost, amid the entombing trees
Didst glide away. Only thine eyes remained.
They would not go - they never yet have gone.
Lighting my lonely pathway home that night,
They have not left me (as my hopes have) since.
They follow me - they lead me through the years.
They are my ministers - yet I their slave.
Their office is to illumine and enkindle -
My duty, to be saved by their bright fire,
And purified in their electric fire,
And sanctified in their elysian fire.
They fill my soul with Beauty (which is Hope,)
And are far up in Heaven - the stars I kneel to
In the sad, silent watches of my night;
While even in the meridian glare of day
I see them still - two sweetly scintillant
Venuses, unextinguished by the sun!" -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248249-a-good-leg-will-fall-a-straight-back-will-stoop</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 20:18:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248249-a-good-leg-will-fall-a-straight-back-will-stoop]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A good leg will fall, a straight back will stoop, a black beard will turn white, a curled pate will grow bald, a fair face will wither, a full eye will wax hollow. But a good heart...is the sun and moon...for it shines bright and never changes, but keeps its course truly.

Henry V, Act V, Scene 2" -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/531666-the-moon-is-a-loyal-companion-it-never-leaves-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 20:19:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Tahereh Mafi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/531666-the-moon-is-a-loyal-companion-it-never-leaves-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The moon is a loyal companion.
It never leaves. It's always here, watching, steadfast, knowing us in our light and dark moments, changing forever just as we do. Every day it's a different version of itself. Sometimes weak and wan, sometimes strong and full of light. The moon understands what it means to be human.
Uncertain. Alone. Cratered by imperfections." -- Tahereh Mafi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30788-the-only-truth-is-music</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 16:24:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30788-the-only-truth-is-music]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only truth is music." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
