<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1036347-katherine]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1036347-katherine" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 13:15:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5012-man-is-condemned-to-be-free-because-once-thrown-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 13:15:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Jean-Paul Sartre]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5012-man-is-condemned-to-be-free-because-once-thrown-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man is condemned to be free; because once thrown into the world, he is responsible for everything he does. 
It is up to you to give [life] a meaning." -- Jean-Paul Sartre]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46741-i-never-sleep-like-the-dolphin-and-the-spiny-anteater</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2008 20:19:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Lyda Morehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46741-i-never-sleep-like-the-dolphin-and-the-spiny-anteater]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I never sleep.  Like the dolphin and the spiny anteater, I don't experience REM.  Unlike the dreamless mammals, I'm a construct.  I am a living program inside a vast network of electronic impulses known as the LINK.  In that datastream I've uncovered the meaning of another kind of dreaming--that of a fond hope or aspiration, a yearning, a desire, or a passion.  This much I have.  When I dream, I dream of Mecca." -- Lyda Morehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50057-almsgiving-is-a-major-tenet-of-islam-it-s-also-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 18:52:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Lyda Morehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50057-almsgiving-is-a-major-tenet-of-islam-it-s-also-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Almsgiving is a major tenet of Islam.  It's also a kick in the pants of the highest order.  Nothing is as cool as skimming off a couple of hundred thousand from some multinational corporation and handing it out to random strangers.  Or writing a harmless little virus that makes credit counters &quot;forget&quot; to send a surcharge back to the bank after each purchase.  Oh, sure, technically I'm supposed to give away my own money, but whatever.  I'm sure Allah gets the spirit of what I'm doing here.  " -- Lyda Morehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50061-where-was-this-written-i-wondered-where-in-the-talmud</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 18:56:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Lyda Morehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50061-where-was-this-written-i-wondered-where-in-the-talmud]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where was this written? I wondered.  Where in the Talmud or the Koran or the Bible did it say, &quot;Lo, and Satan fetcheth the coffee for the Antichrist and her minions&quot;?" -- Lyda Morehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2787-we-write-to-taste-life-twice-in-the-moment-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 11:56:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2787-we-write-to-taste-life-twice-in-the-moment-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We write to taste life twice, in the moment and in retrospect." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1894-this-is-not-a-novel-to-be-tossed-aside-lightly</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 19:49:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Dorothy Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1894-this-is-not-a-novel-to-be-tossed-aside-lightly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is not a novel to be tossed aside lightly. It should be thrown with great force." -- Dorothy Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28290-i-don-t-care-what-is-written-about-me-so-long</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 19:51:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Dorothy Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28290-i-don-t-care-what-is-written-about-me-so-long]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't care what is written about me so long as it isn't true." -- Dorothy Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11652-my-hair-had-grown-out-long-and-shaggy-not-in-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 19:16:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Jim Butcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11652-my-hair-had-grown-out-long-and-shaggy-not-in-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My hair had grown out long and shaggy—not in that sexy-young-rock-star kind of way but in that time-to-take-Rover-to-the-groomer kind of way." -- Jim Butcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 18:17:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love never dies a natural death. It dies because we don't know how to replenish its source. It dies of blindness and errors and betrayals. It dies of illness and wounds; it dies of weariness, of witherings, of tarnishings." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45328-there-are-two-ways-to-reach-me-by-way-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 18:19:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45328-there-are-two-ways-to-reach-me-by-way-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two ways to reach me: by way of kisses or by way of the imagination. But there is a hierarchy: the kisses alone don't work." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1398-i-love-deadlines-i-love-the-whooshing-noise-they-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2008 12:36:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1398-i-love-deadlines-i-love-the-whooshing-noise-they-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love deadlines. I love the whooshing noise they make as they go by." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14732-that-would-be-a-good-thing-for-them-to-cut</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 13:08:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Dorothy Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14732-that-would-be-a-good-thing-for-them-to-cut]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That would be a good thing for them to cut on my tombstone: Wherever she went, including here, it was against her better judgment." -- Dorothy Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165260-if-your-understanding-of-the-divine-made-you-kinder-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 18:32:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Karen Armstrong]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165260-if-your-understanding-of-the-divine-made-you-kinder-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If your understanding of the divine made you kinder, more empathetic, and impelled you to express sympathy in concrete acts of loving-kindness, this was good theology.  But if your notion of God made you unkind, belligerent, cruel, of self-righteous, or if it led you to kill in God's name, it was bad theology.  " -- Karen Armstrong]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114841-in-a-perfect-world-you-could-fuck-people-without-giving</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 05:48:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114841-in-a-perfect-world-you-could-fuck-people-without-giving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a perfect world, you could fuck people without giving them a piece of your heart. And every glittering kiss and every touch of flesh is another shard of heart you’ll never see again." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 05:50:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5251-sometimes-you-wake-up-sometimes-the-fall-kills-you-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 05:50:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5251-sometimes-you-wake-up-sometimes-the-fall-kills-you-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes you wake up. Sometimes the fall kills you. And sometimes, when you fall, you fly." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473772-fat-charlie-had-had-no-real-liking-for-the-police</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 16:26:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473772-fat-charlie-had-had-no-real-liking-for-the-police]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fat Charlie had had no real liking for the police, but until now, he had still managed to cling to a fundamental trust in the natural order of things, a conviction that there was some kind of power--a Victorian might have thought of it as Providence--that ensured that the guilty would be punished while the innocent would be set free.  This faith had collapsed in the face of recent events and had been replaced by the suspicion that he would spend the rest of his life pleading his innocence to a variety of implacable judges and tormenters, many of whom would look like Daisy, and that he would in all probability wake up in cell six the next morning to find that he had been transformed into an enormous cockroach.  He had definitely been transported to the kind of maleficent universe that transformed people into cockroaches." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24015-you-do-not-have-to-be-good-you-do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 08:53:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24015-you-do-not-have-to-be-good-you-do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You do not have to be good.
You do not have to walk on your knees
for a hundred miles through the desert, repenting.
You only have to let the soft animal of your body 
love what it loves.
Tell me about despair, yours, and I will tell you mine.
Meanwhile the world goes on.
Meanwhile the sun and the clear pebbles of the rain
are moving across the landscapes,
over the prairies and the deep trees,
the mountains and the rivers.
Meanwhile the wild geese, high in the clean blue air,
are heading home again.
Whoever you are, no matter how lonely,
the world offers itself to your imagination,
calls to you like the wild geese, harsh and exciting –
over and over announcing your place
in the family of things." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51566-and-that-s-when-she-put-her-book-down-and-looked</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 08:59:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51566-and-that-s-when-she-put-her-book-down-and-looked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And that's when she put her book down. And looked at me. And said it: &quot;Life isn't fair, Bill. we tell our children that it is, but it's a terrible thing to do. It's not only a lie, it's a cruel lie. Life is not fair, and it never has been, and it's never going to be." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217288-sometimes-i-need-only-to-stand-wherever-i-am-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 19:10:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217288-sometimes-i-need-only-to-stand-wherever-i-am-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I need
only to stand
wherever I am 
to be blessed." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83393-25-and-the-lord-spake-unto-the-angel-that-guarded</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 19:23:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Neil Gaiman &amp; Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83393-25-and-the-lord-spake-unto-the-angel-that-guarded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["25 And the Lord spake unto the Angel that guarded the eastern gate, saying 'Where is the flaming sword that was given unto thee?'
26 And the Angel said, 'I had it here only a moment ago, I must have put it down some where, forget my own head next.'
27 And the Lord did not ask him again." -- Neil Gaiman &amp; Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/479468-it-was-of-course-nothing-more-than-sexism-the-especially</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 20:02:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/479468-it-was-of-course-nothing-more-than-sexism-the-especially]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was, of course, nothing more than sexism, the especially virulent type espoused by male techies who sincerely believe that they are too smart to be sexists." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63346-stories-like-people-and-butterflies-and-songbirds-eggs-and-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2012 02:11:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63346-stories-like-people-and-butterflies-and-songbirds-eggs-and-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories, like people and butterflies and songbirds' eggs and human hearts and dreams, are also fragile things, made up of nothing stronger or more lasting than twenty-six letters and a handful of punctuation marks. Or they are words on the air, composed of sounds and ideas-abstract, invisible, gone once they've been spoken-and what could be more frail than that? But some stories, small, simple ones about setting out on adventures or people doing wonders, tales of miracles and monsters, have outlasted all the people who told them, and some of them have outlasted the lands in which they were created." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21847-there-is-nothing-i-would-not-do-for-those-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 16:39:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21847-there-is-nothing-i-would-not-do-for-those-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing I would not do for those who are really my friends. I have no notion of loving people by halves, it is not my nature." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492059-prune-these-alleged-friends-ruthlessly-from-your-life-you-need</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 16:56:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Cynthia Heimel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492059-prune-these-alleged-friends-ruthlessly-from-your-life-you-need]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Prune these alleged friends ruthlessly from your life.  You need all the positive reinforcement you can get.  You need friends who think you're fabulous, an angel in human shape, and a breath of springtime." -- Cynthia Heimel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 02:06:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 02:06:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that everything happens for a reason. People change so that you can learn to let go, things go wrong so that you appreciate them when they're right, you believe lies so you eventually learn to trust no one but yourself, and sometimes good things fall apart so better things can fall together." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162665-fuck-you-said-czernobog-fuck-you-and-fuck-your-mother</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2012 05:35:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162665-fuck-you-said-czernobog-fuck-you-and-fuck-your-mother]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fuck you,&quot; said Czernobog. &quot;Fuck you and fuck your mother and fuck the fucking horse you fucking rode in on. You will not even die in battle. No warrior will taste your blood. No one alive will take your life. You will die a soft, poor death. You will die with a kiss on your lips and a lie in your heart." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/519515-stories-are-like-spiders-with-all-they-long-legs-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2012 09:07:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/519515-stories-are-like-spiders-with-all-they-long-legs-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories are like spiders, with all they long legs, and stories are like spiderwebs, which man gets himself all tangled up in but which look so pretty when you see them under a leaf in the morning dew, and in the elegant way that they connect to one another, each to each.

What’s that? You want to know if Anansi looked like a spider? Sure he did, except when he looked like a man.

No, he never changed his shape. It’s just a matter of how you tell the story. That’s all." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/539731-and-life-is-a-good-thing-for-a-writer-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2012 09:07:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/539731-and-life-is-a-good-thing-for-a-writer-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And life is a good thing for a writer. It's where we get our raw material, for a start. We quite like to stop and watch it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
