<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1036385-joanne]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1036385-joanne" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 22:31:32 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369093-swathed-in-silk-i-feel-like-a-caterpillar-in-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 22:31:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanne add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369093-swathed-in-silk-i-feel-like-a-caterpillar-in-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Swathed in silk, I feel like a caterpillar in a cocoon awaiting metamorphosis. I always supposed that to be a peaceful condition. At first it is. But as I journey into the night, I feel more and more trapped, suffocated by the slippery bindings, unable to emerge until I have transformed into something of beauty. I squirm, trying to shed my ruined body and unlock the secret to growing flawless wings. Despite enormous effort, I remain a hideous creature, fired into my current form by the blast from the bombs." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25517-her-antiquity-in-preceding-and-surviving-succeeding-tellurian-generations-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 22:31:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanne add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25517-her-antiquity-in-preceding-and-surviving-succeeding-tellurian-generations-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her antiquity in preceding and surviving succeeding tellurian generations: her nocturnal predominance: her satellitic dependence: her luminary reflection: her constancy under all her phases, rising and setting by her appointed times, waxing and waning: the forced invariability of her aspect: her indeterminate response to inaffirmative interrogation: her potency over effluent and refluent waters: her power to enamour, to mortify, to invest with beauty, to render insane, to incite to and aid delinquency: the tranquil inscrutability of her visage: the terribility of her isolated dominant resplendent propinquity: her omens of tempest and of calm: the stimulation of her light, her motion and her presence: the admonition of her craters, her arid seas, her silence: her splendour, when visible: her attraction, when invisible." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30396-those-who-contemplate-the-beauty-of-the-earth-find-reserves</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 22:26:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanne add a quote by Rachel Carson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30396-those-who-contemplate-the-beauty-of-the-earth-find-reserves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who contemplate the beauty of the earth find reserves of strength that will endure as long as life lasts. There is something infinitely healing in the repeated refrains of nature -- the assurance that dawn comes after night, and spring after winter." -- Rachel Carson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20080-what-is-a-poet-an-unhappy-man-who-hides-deep</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 16:37:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanne add a quote by Soren Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20080-what-is-a-poet-an-unhappy-man-who-hides-deep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is a poet? An unhappy man who hides deep anguish in his heart, but whose lips are so formed that when the sigh and cry pass through them, it sounds like lovely music.... And people flock around the poet and say: 'Sing again soon' - that is, 'May new sufferings torment your soul but your lips be fashioned as before, for the cry would only frighten us, but the music, that is blissful." -- Soren Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
