<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1037366-jordan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1037366-jordan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 14:12:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12837-the-answer-is-that-we-don-t-choose-our-freaks-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 14:12:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jordan add a quote by Steve Almond]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12837-the-answer-is-that-we-don-t-choose-our-freaks-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The answer is that we don't choose our freaks, they choose us." -- Steve Almond]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19403-your-problem-isn-t-the-problem-it-s-your-attitude-about-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 14:08:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jordan add a quote by Ann Brashares]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19403-your-problem-isn-t-the-problem-it-s-your-attitude-about-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your problem isn't the problem, it's your attitude about the problem." -- Ann Brashares]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28966-through-rohan-over-fen-and-field-where-the-long-grass</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 14:09:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jordan add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28966-through-rohan-over-fen-and-field-where-the-long-grass]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Through Rohan over fen and field where the long grass grows
The West Wind goes walking, and about the walls it goes.
What news from the West, oh wandering wind, do you bring to me tonight?
Have you seen Boromir the Tall by moon or by starlight?
‘I saw him ride over seven streams, over waters wide and grey;
I saw him walk in empty lands, until he passed away
Into the shadows of the North. I saw him then no more.
The North Wind may have heard the horn of the son of Denethor.’
Oh, Boromir! From the high walls westward I looked afar.
But you came not from the empty lands where no men are.
	
From the mouth of the sea the South Wind flies,
From the sand hills and the stones;
The wailing of the gulls it bears, and at the gate it moans
What news from the South, oh sighing wind, do you bring to me at eve?
Where now is Boromir the Fair? He tarries and I grieve.
‘Ask me not where he doth dwell--so many bones there lie
On the white shores and on the black shores under the stormy sky;
So many have passed down Anduin to find the flowing sea.
Ask of the North Wind news of them the North Wind sends to me!’
Oh Boromir! Beyond the gate the Seaward road runs South,
But you came not with the wailing gulls from the grey seas mouth.
	
From the Gate of Kings the North Wind rides,
And past the roaring falls
And loud and cold about the Tower its loud horn calls.
What news from the North, oh mighty wind, do you bring to me today?
What news of Boromir the Bold? For he is long away.
‘Beneath Amon Hen I heard his cry. There many foes he fought
His cloven shield, his broken sword, they to the water brought.
His head so proud, his face so fair, his limbs they laid to rest;
And Rauros, Golden Rauros Falls, bore him upon its breast.’
Oh Boromir! The Tower of Guard shall ever northward gaze
To Rauros, Golden Rauros Falls until the end of days." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 16:02:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jordan add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1928-if-you-re-looking-for-sympathy-you-ll-find-it-between-shit</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 19:49:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jordan add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1928-if-you-re-looking-for-sympathy-you-ll-find-it-between-shit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're looking for sympathy you'll find it between shit and syphilis in the dictionary." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
