<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1037206-lindsey]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1037206-lindsey" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 09:31:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40805-in-a-world-where-billions-believe-their-deity-conceived-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 09:31:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40805-in-a-world-where-billions-believe-their-deity-conceived-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a world where billions believe their deity conceived a mortal child with a virgin human, it's stunning how little imagination most people display." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40806-just-keep-asking-yourself-what-would-jesus-not-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 09:31:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40806-just-keep-asking-yourself-what-would-jesus-not-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just keep asking yourself: What would Jesus not do?" -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40826-society-invents-a-spurious-convoluted-logic-tae-absorb-and-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 09:44:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Irvine Welsh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40826-society-invents-a-spurious-convoluted-logic-tae-absorb-and-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Society invents a spurious convoluted logic tae absorb and change people whae's behaviour is outside its mainstream. Suppose that ah ken aw the pros and cons, know that ah'm gaunnae huv a short life, am ah sound mind, ectetera, ectetera, but still want tae use smack? They won't let ye dae it. They won't let ye dae it, because it's seen as a sign ay thir ain failure. The fact that ye jist simply choose tae reject whut they huv tae offer. Choose us. Choose life. Choose mortgage payments; choose washing machines; choose cars; choose sitting oan a couch watching mind-numbing and spirit-crushing game shows, stuffing fuckin junk food intae yir mooth. Choose rotting away, pishing and shiteing yersel in a home, a total fuckin embarrassment tae the selfish, fucked-up brats ye've produced. Choose life. Well, ah choose no tae choose life. If the cunts cannae handle that, it's thair fuckin problem. As Harry Launder sais, ah jist intend tae keep right on to the end of the road..." -- Irvine Welsh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35176-it-is-known-that-there-are-an-infinite-number-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 09:56:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35176-it-is-known-that-there-are-an-infinite-number-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is known that there are an infinite number of worlds, simply because there is an infinite amount of space for them to be in. However, not every one of them is inhabited. Therefore, there must be a finite number of inhabited worlds. Any finite number divided by infinity is as near to nothing as makes no odds, so the average population of all the planets in the Universe can be said to be zero. From this it follows that the population of the whole Universe is also zero, and that any people you may meet from time to time are merely the products of a deranged imagination." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40836-i-collect-church-collapses-recreationally-did-you-see-the-recent</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 09:59:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Thomas Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40836-i-collect-church-collapses-recreationally-did-you-see-the-recent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I collect church collapses, recreationally. Did you see the recent one in Sicily? Marvelous! The facade fell on sixty-five grandmothers at a special mass. Was that evil? If so, who did it? If he's up there, he just loves it, Officer Starling. Typhoid and swans - it all comes from the same place." -- Thomas Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1398-i-love-deadlines-i-love-the-whooshing-noise-they-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 10:01:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1398-i-love-deadlines-i-love-the-whooshing-noise-they-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love deadlines. I love the whooshing noise they make as they go by." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40837-it-s-only-in-drugs-or-death-we-ll-see-anything-new</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 10:14:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40837-it-s-only-in-drugs-or-death-we-ll-see-anything-new]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's only in drugs or death we'll see anything new, and death is just too controlling." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40842-i-am-aware-that-there-is-a-world-out-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 10:23:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40842-i-am-aware-that-there-is-a-world-out-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am aware that there is a world out there that functions without regard to me. There are wars and budgets and bombings and vast dimensions of wealth and greed and ambition and corruption. And yet I don't feel a part of that world, and I wouldn't know how to join if I tried." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40844-i-felt-that-i-was-not-never-had-been-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 10:29:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by John Knowles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40844-i-felt-that-i-was-not-never-had-been-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I felt that I was not, never had been and never would be a living part of this overpoweringly solid and deeply meaningful world around me." -- John Knowles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40847-find-good-in-what-the-world-says-is-evil</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 10:35:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40847-find-good-in-what-the-world-says-is-evil]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Find good in what the world says is evil." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40848-i-mean-maybe-i-am-crazy-i-mean-maybe-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 10:38:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40848-i-mean-maybe-i-am-crazy-i-mean-maybe-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I mean, maybe I am crazy. I mean, maybe. But if this is all there is, then I don't want to be sane." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16261-life-is-a-disease-sexually-transmitted-and-invariably-fatal</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 10:39:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16261-life-is-a-disease-sexually-transmitted-and-invariably-fatal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is a disease: sexually transmitted, and invariably fatal." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 10:39:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 10:42:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40850-i-read-somewhere-that-all-the-digitized-announcers-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 10:46:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Keith Lowe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40850-i-read-somewhere-that-all-the-digitized-announcers-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read somewhere that all the digitized announcers on the tube have names." -- Keith Lowe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40851-christ-is-one-of-the-family-now-i-often-wonder</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 10:50:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40851-christ-is-one-of-the-family-now-i-often-wonder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Christ is one of the 'family' now. I often wonder if God recognizes his own son the way we've dressed him up, or is it dressed him down? He's regular peppermint stick now, all sugar crystal and saccharine - when he isn't making veiled references to certain commercial products that ever worshiper absolutely needs." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1981-my-experience-of-life-is-that-it-is-not-divided</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 12:47:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1981-my-experience-of-life-is-that-it-is-not-divided]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My experience of life is that it is not divided up into genres; it’s a horrifying, romantic, tragic, comical, science-fiction cowboy detective novel. You know, with a bit of pornography if you're lucky." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108556-it-s-actually-against-my-religion-to-laugh-at-men-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 12:38:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108556-it-s-actually-against-my-religion-to-laugh-at-men-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's actually against my religion to laugh at men who are toting guns." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8830-fiction-is-the-truth-inside-the-lie</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 05:27:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8830-fiction-is-the-truth-inside-the-lie]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fiction is the truth inside the lie." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108564-and-then-the-jamaican-guy-pulls-out-the-sauce-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 12:52:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by David Wong]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108564-and-then-the-jamaican-guy-pulls-out-the-sauce-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And then the Jamaican guy pulls out the sauce. &quot;It be opening doors to other worlds, mon,&quot; he days. We made him do it first, saw that he didn't die. It seemed to make him pretty happy and then - Dave, the guy, I know I didn't really see this, but the guy shrunk himself, made himself three feet tall. We all laughed our asses off, then he was back to normal again.'
And you still tried that shit?'
Are you kidding? How could I not?" -- David Wong]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12561-telling-me-i-can-do-anything-i-want-is-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 12:54:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12561-telling-me-i-can-do-anything-i-want-is-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Telling me I can do anything I want is like pulling the plug out of the bath and then telling the water it can go anywhere it wants. Try it, and see what happens." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/645-it-is-sometimes-an-appropriate-response-to-reality-to-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 18:54:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Philip K. Dick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/645-it-is-sometimes-an-appropriate-response-to-reality-to-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is sometimes an appropriate response to reality to go insane." -- Philip K. Dick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14555-because-today-we-live-in-a-society-in-which-spurious</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 18:55:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Philip K. Dick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14555-because-today-we-live-in-a-society-in-which-spurious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because today we live in a society in which spurious realities are manufactured by the media, by governments, by big corporations, by religious groups, political groups... So I ask, in my writing, What is real? Because unceasingly we are bombarded with pseudo-realities manufactured by very sophisticated people using very sophisticated electronic mechanisms. I do not distrust their motives; I distrust their power. They have a lot of it. And it is an astonishing power: that of creating whole universes, universes of the mind. I ought to know. I do the same thing." -- Philip K. Dick]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
