<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1039898-laura-rucker]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1039898-laura-rucker" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 14:26:56 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243605-if-you-can-see-a-thing-whole-he-said-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 14:26:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243605-if-you-can-see-a-thing-whole-he-said-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can see a thing whole,&quot; he said, &quot;it seems that it's always beautiful. Planets, lives. . . . But close up, a world's all dirt and rocks. And day to day, life's a hard job, you get tired, you loose the pattern. You need distance, interval. The way to see how beautiful earth is, is to see it from the moon. The way to see how beautiful life is, is from the vantage point of death.&quot;
    &quot;That's all right for Urras. Let it stay off there and be the moon-I don't want it! But I am not going to stand up on a gravestone and look down on life and say, 'O lovely!' I want to see it whole right in the middle of it, here, now. I don't give a hoot for eternity.&quot;
    &quot;It's nothing to do with eternity,&quot; said Shevek, grinning, a thin shaggy man of silver and shadow. &quot;All you have to do to see life as a whole is to see it as mortal. I'll die, you'll die; how could we love each other otherwise? The sun's going to burn out, what else keeps it shining?&quot;
  &quot;Ah! your talk, your damned philosophy!&quot;
  &quot;Talk? It's not talk. It's not reason. It's hand's touch. I touch the wholeness, I hold it. Which is moonlight, which is Takver? How shall I fear death? When I hold it, when I hold in my hands the light-&quot;
  &quot;Don't be propertarian,&quot; Takver muttered.
  &quot;Dear heart, don't cry.&quot;
  &quot;I'm not crying. You are. Those are your tears.&quot;
  &quot;I'm cold. The moonlight's cold.&quot;
  &quot;Lie down.&quot;
  A great shiver went through his body as she took him in her arms.
  &quot;I'm afraid, Takver,&quot; he whispered." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22798-the-trouble-is-that-we-have-a-bad-habit-encouraged</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 14:28:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Ursula K. LeGuin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22798-the-trouble-is-that-we-have-a-bad-habit-encouraged]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble is that we have a bad habit, encouraged by pendants and sophisticates, of considering happiness as something rather stupid. Only pain is intellectual, only evil interesting. This is the treason of the artist: a refusal to admit the banality of evil and the terrible boredom of pain." -- Ursula K. LeGuin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
