<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1042757-derek]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1042757-derek" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 19:35:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2125-did-you-ever-want-to-set-someone-s-head-on-fire</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 19:35:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Warren Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2125-did-you-ever-want-to-set-someone-s-head-on-fire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did you ever want to set someone's head on fire, just to see what it looked like? Did you ever stand in the street and think to yourself, I could make that nun go blind just by giving her a kiss? Did you ever lay out plans for stitching babies and stray cats into a Perfect New Human? Did you ever stand naked surrounded by people who want your gleaming sperm, squirting frankincense, soma and testosterone from every pore? If so, then you're the bastard who stole my drugs Friday night. And I'll find you. Oh, yes." -- Warren Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58288-i-couldn-t-think-of-one-clever-way-to-stop-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 19:36:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Grant Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58288-i-couldn-t-think-of-one-clever-way-to-stop-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I couldn't think of one clever way to stop this guy, so I just trusted to mindless violence." -- Grant Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50677-who-has-never-killed-an-hour-not-casually-or-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 19:38:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50677-who-has-never-killed-an-hour-not-casually-or-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who has never killed an hour? Not casually or without thought, but carefully: a premeditated murder of minutes. The violence comes from a combination of giving up, not caring, and a resignation that getting past it is all you can hope to accomplish. So you kill the hour. You do not work, you do not read, you do not daydream. If you sleep it is not because you need to sleep. And when at last it is over, there is no evidence: no weapon, no blood, and no body. The only clue might be the shadows beneath your eyes or a terribly thin line near the corner of your mouth indicating something has been suffered, that in the privacy of your life you have lost something and the loss is too empty to share." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5451-at-the-time-my-life-just-seemed-too-complete-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2009 09:00:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5451-at-the-time-my-life-just-seemed-too-complete-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the time, my life just seemed too complete, and maybe we have to break everything to make something better out of ourselves." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16041-the-only-difference-between-a-suicide-and-a-martyrdom-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2009 09:00:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16041-the-only-difference-between-a-suicide-and-a-martyrdom-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only difference between a suicide and a martyrdom really is the amount of press coverage." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16072-the-unreal-is-more-powerful-than-the-real-because-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2009 09:01:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16072-the-unreal-is-more-powerful-than-the-real-because-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The unreal is more powerful than the real. Because nothing is as perfect as you can imagine it. Because its only intangible ideas, concepts, beliefs, fantasies that last. Stone crumbles. Wood rots. People, well, they die. But things as fragile as a thought, a dream, a legend, they can go on and on. If you can change the way people think. The way they see themselves. The way they see the world. You can change the way people live their lives. That's the only lasting thing you can create." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17521-it-s-so-hard-to-forget-pain-but-it-s-even-harder</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2009 09:01:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17521-it-s-so-hard-to-forget-pain-but-it-s-even-harder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's so hard to forget pain, but it's even harder to remember sweetness.  We have no scar to show for happiness. We learn so little from peace." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49225-i-give-you-the-mausoleum-of-all-hope-and-desire-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2009 09:03:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49225-i-give-you-the-mausoleum-of-all-hope-and-desire-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...I give you the mausoleum of all hope and desire...I give it to you not that you may remember time, but that you might forget it now and then for a moment and not spend all of your breath trying to conquer it. Because no battle is ever won he said. They are not even fought. The field only reveals to man his own folly and despair, and victory is an illusion of philosophers and fools." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3085-the-truth-about-the-world-he-said-is-that-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2009 09:05:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3085-the-truth-about-the-world-he-said-is-that-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth about the world, he said, is that anything is possible. Had you not seen it all from birth and thereby bled it of its strangeness it would appear to you for what it is, a hat trick in a medicine show, a fevered dream, a trance bepopulate with chimeras having neither analogue nor precedent, an itinerant carnival, a migratory tentshow whose ultimate destination after many a pitch in many a mudded field is unspeakable and calamitous beyond reckoning. 

The universe is no narrow thing and the order within it is not constrained by any latitude in its conception to repeat what exists in one part in any other part. Even in this world more things exist without our knowledge than with it and the order in creation which you see is that which you have put there, like a string in a maze, so that you shall not lose your way. For existence has its own order and that no man's mind can compass, that mind itself being but a fact among others." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16485-whatever-in-creation-exists-without-my-knowledge-exists-without-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2009 09:05:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16485-whatever-in-creation-exists-without-my-knowledge-exists-without-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever in creation exists without my knowledge exists without my consent." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127555-i-am-the-sum-total-of-everything-that-went-before</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2009 09:07:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127555-i-am-the-sum-total-of-everything-that-went-before]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the sum total of everything that went before me, of all I have been seen done, of everything done-to-me. I am everyone everything whose being-in-the-world affected was affected by mine. I am anything that happens after I'm gone which would not have happened if I had not come." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
