<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1042703-tena]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1042703-tena" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 14:53:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518835-i-testify-that-the-tender-mercies-of-the-lord-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 14:53:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tena add a quote by David A. Bednar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518835-i-testify-that-the-tender-mercies-of-the-lord-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I testify that the tender mercies of the Lord are real and that they do not occur randomly or merely by coincidence.  Often, the Lord’s timing of his tender mercies helps us to both discern and acknowledge them….The Lord’s tender mercies are the very personal and individualized blessings, strength, protection, assurances, guidance, loving-kindnesses, consolation, support, and spiritual gifts which we receive from and because of and through the Lord Jesus Christ….Faithfulness, obedience and humility invite tender mercies into our lives, and it is often the Lord’s timing that enables us to recognize and treasure these important blessings….I testify that the tender mercies of the Lord are available to all of us and that the Redeemer of Israel is eager to bestow such gifts upon us….Each of us can have eyes to see clearly and ears to hear distinctly the tender mercies of the Lord as they strengthen and assist us in these latter days." -- David A. Bednar]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
