<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1042891-marie-antionette]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1042891-marie-antionette" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 17:58:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6407-our-lives-begin-to-end-the-day-we-become-silent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 17:58:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6407-our-lives-begin-to-end-the-day-we-become-silent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our lives begin to end the day we become silent about things that matter." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38891-and-because-i-had-been-a-hustler-i-knew-better</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2008 16:58:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Malcolm X]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38891-and-because-i-had-been-a-hustler-i-knew-better]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And because I had been a hustler, I knew better than all whites knew, and better than nearly all of the black 'leaders' knew, that actually the most dangerous black man in America was the ghetto hustler. Why do I say this? The hustler, out there in the ghetto jungles, has less respect for the white power structure than any other Negro in North America. The ghetto hustler is internally restrained by nothing. He has no religion, no concept of morality, no civic responsibility, no fear--nothing. To survive, he is out there constantly preying upon others, probing for any human weakness like a ferret. The ghetto hustler is forever frustrated, restless, and anxious for some 'action'. Whatever he undertakes, he commits himself to it fully, absolutely. What makes the ghetto hustler yet more dangerous is his 'glamour' image to the school-dropout youth in the ghetto.These ghetto teen-agers see the hell caught by their parents struggling to get somewhere, or see that they have given up struggling in the prejudiced, intolerant white man’s world. The ghetto teen-agers make up their own minds they would rather be like the hustlers whom they see dressed ‘sharp’ and flashing money and displaying no respect for anybody or anything. So the ghetto youth become attracted to the hustler worlds of dope, thievery, prostitution, and general crime and immorality." -- Malcolm X]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
