<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1043873-nick]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1043873-nick" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 11:55:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45628-ethically-they-had-arrived-at-the-conclusion-that-man-s-supremacy</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 11:55:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45628-ethically-they-had-arrived-at-the-conclusion-that-man-s-supremacy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ethically they had arrived at the conclusion  that man's supremacy over lower animals meant not that the former should prey upon the latter, but that the higher should protect the lower, and that there should be mutual aid between the two as between man and man. They had also brought out the truth that man eats not for enjoyment but to live." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1090-where-there-is-love-there-is-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 08:27:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1090-where-there-is-love-there-is-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where there is love there is life." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48869-the-tao-that-can-be-told-is-not-the-eternal</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 08:31:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Lao-Tzu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48869-the-tao-that-can-be-told-is-not-the-eternal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Tao that can be told is not the eternal Tao." -- Lao-Tzu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48870-nothing-external-to-you-has-any-power-over-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 08:31:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48870-nothing-external-to-you-has-any-power-over-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing external to you has any power over you." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8705-a-dream-you-dream-alone-is-only-a-dream-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 08:33:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8705-a-dream-you-dream-alone-is-only-a-dream-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A dream you dream alone is only a dream. A dream you dream together is reality." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48873-try-to-realize-it-s-all-within-yourself-no-one-else</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 08:35:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Harrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48873-try-to-realize-it-s-all-within-yourself-no-one-else]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Try to realize it's all within yourself no one else can make you change, and to see you're only very small and life flows on within you and without you." -- Harrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48874-with-every-mistake-we-must-surely-be-learning</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 08:35:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by George Harrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48874-with-every-mistake-we-must-surely-be-learning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With every mistake, we must surely be learning." -- George Harrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48875-everything-that-ever-has-been-always-will-be-and-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 08:39:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48875-everything-that-ever-has-been-always-will-be-and-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything that ever has been always will be, and everything that ever  will be  always has been." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48876-there-are-only-a-few-notes-just-variations-on-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 08:41:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48876-there-are-only-a-few-notes-just-variations-on-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are only a few notes. Just variations on a theme." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42035-and-in-the-end-the-love-you-take-is-equal</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 08:52:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Paul McCartney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42035-and-in-the-end-the-love-you-take-is-equal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And, in the end
The love you take
is equal to the love you make." -- Paul McCartney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17014-the-release-of-atomic-power-has-changed-everything-except-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 08:53:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17014-the-release-of-atomic-power-has-changed-everything-except-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The release of atomic power has changed everything except our way of thinking ... the solution to this problem lies in the heart of mankind. If only I had known, I should have become a watchmaker. (1945)" -- Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28432-it-is-easy-in-the-world-to-live-after-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2008 12:02:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28432-it-is-easy-in-the-world-to-live-after-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is easy in the world to live after the world's opinion; it is easy in solitude to live after our own; but the great man is he who in the midst of the crowd keeps with perfect sweetness the independence of solitude." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48897-to-be-a-philosopher-is-not-merely-to-have-subtle</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 09:08:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48897-to-be-a-philosopher-is-not-merely-to-have-subtle]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be a philosopher is not merely to have subtle thoughts, nor even to found a school, but so to love wisdom as to live according to its dictates, a life of simplicity, independence, magnanimity and trust." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48900-simplify-simplify</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 09:09:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48900-simplify-simplify]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Simplify, simplify." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49659-i-too-took-the-plunge---the-vow-to-observe</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 13:23:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49659-i-too-took-the-plunge---the-vow-to-observe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I too took the plunge - the vow to observe brahmacharya for life. I must confess that I had not then fully realized the magnitude and immensity of the task I undertook. The difficulties are even today staring me in the face. The importance of the vow is being more and more borne in upon me. Life without brahmacharya appears to me to be insipid and animal-like. The brute by nature knows no self-restraint. Man is man because he is capable of, and only in so far as he exercises, self-restraint. What formerly appeared to me to be extravagant praise of brahmacharya in our religious books seems now, with increasing clearness every day, to be absolutely proper and founded on experience." -- Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49661-ahimsa-is-a-comprehensive-principle-we-are-helpless-mortals-caught</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 13:29:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49661-ahimsa-is-a-comprehensive-principle-we-are-helpless-mortals-caught]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ahimsa is a comprehensive principle. We are helpless mortals caught in the conflagration of himsa. The saying that life lives on life has a deep meaning in it. Man cannot for a moment live without consciously or unconsciously committing outward himsa. The very fact of his living - eating, drinking and moving about - necessarily involves some himsa, destruction of life, be it ever so minute. A votary of ahimsa therefore remains true to his faith if the spring of all his actions is compassion, if he shuns to the best of his ability the destruction of the tiniest creature, tries to save it, and thus incessantly strives to be free from the deadly coil of himsa. He will be constantly growing in self-restraint and compassion, but he can never become entirely free from outward himsa.

Then again, because underlying ahimsa is the unity of all life, the error of one cannot but affect all, and hence man cannot be wholly free from himsa. So long as he continues to be a social being, he cannot but participate in the himsa that the very existence of society involves. When two nations are fighting, the duty of a votary of ahimsa is to stop the war. He who is not equal to that duty, he who has no power of resisting war, he who is not qualified to resist war, may take part in war, and yet wholeheartedly try to free himself, his nation and the world from war." -- Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49666-i-must-say-that-beyond-occasionally-exposing-me-to-laughter</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 13:35:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49666-i-must-say-that-beyond-occasionally-exposing-me-to-laughter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I must say that, beyond occasionally exposing me to laughter, my constitutional shyness has been no dis-advantage whatever. In fact I can see that, on the contrary, it has been all to my advantage. My hesitancy in speech, which was once an annoyance, is now a pleasure. Its greatest benefit has been that it has taught me the economy of words. I have naturally formed the habit of restraining my thoughts. And I can now give myself the certificate that a thoughtless word hardly ever escapes my tongue or pen. I do not recollect ever having had to regret anything in my speech or writing. I have thus been spared many a mishap and waste of time. Experience has taught me that silence is part of the spiritual discipline of a votary of truth. Proneness to exaggerate, to suppress or modify the truth, wittingly or unwittingly, is a natural weakness of man, and silence is necessary in order to surmount it. A man of few words will rarely be thoughtless in his speech; he will measure every word. We find so many people impatient to talk. There is no chairman of a meeting who is not pestered with notes for permission to speak. And whenever the permission is given the speaker generally exceeds the time-limit, asks for more time, and keeps on talking without permission. All this talking can hardly be said to be of any benefit to the world. It is so much waste of time. My shyness has been in reality my shield and buckler. It has allowed me to grow. It has helped me in my discernment of truth." -- Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49669-reader-will-you-not-admit-that-you-are-arguing-against</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 13:46:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49669-reader-will-you-not-admit-that-you-are-arguing-against]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reader: Will you not admit that you are arguing against yourself? You know that what the English obtained in their own country they obtained by using brute force. I know you have argued that what they have obtained is useless, but that does not affect my argument. They wanted useless things and they got them. My point is that their desire was fulfilled. What does it matter what means they adopted? Why should we not obtain our goal, which is good, by any means whatsoever, even by using violence? Shall I think of the means when I have to deal with a thief in the house? My duty is to drive him out anyhow. You seem to admit that we have received nothing, and that we shall receive nothing by petitioning. Why, then, may we do not so by using brute force? And, to retain what we may receive we shall keep up the fear by using the same force to the extent that it may be necessary. You will not find fault with a continuance of force to prevent a child from thrusting its foot into fire. Somehow or other we have to gain our end.

Editor: Your reasoning is plausible. It has deluded many. I have used similar arguments before now. But I think I know better now, and I shall endeavour to undeceive you. Let us first take the argument that we are justified in gaining our end by using brute force because the English gained theirs by using similar means. It is perfectly true that they used brute force and that it is possible for us to do likewise, but by using similar means we can get only the same thing that they got. You will admit that we do not want that. Your belief that there is no connection between the means and the end is a great mistake. Through that mistake even men who have been considered religious have committed grievous crimes. Your reasoning is the same as saying that we can get a rose through planting a noxious weed. If I want to cross the ocean, I can do so only by means of a vessel; if I were to use a cart for that purpose, both the cart and I would soon find the bottom. &quot;As is the God, so is the votary&quot;, is a maxim worth considering. Its meaning has been distorted and men have gone astray. The means may be likened to a seed, the end to a tree; and there is just the same inviolable connection between the means and the end as there is between the seed and the tree. I am not likely to obtain the result flowing from the worship of God by laying myself prostrate before Satan. If, therefore, anyone were to say : &quot;I want to worship God; it does not matter that I do so by means of Satan,&quot; it would be set down as ignorant folly. We reap exactly as we sow. The English in 1833 obtained greater voting power by violence. Did they by using brute force better appreciate their duty? They wanted the right of voting, which they obtained by using physical force. But real rights are a result of performance of duty; these rights they have not obtained. We, therefore, have before us in English the force of everybody wanting and insisting on his rights, nobody thinking of his duty. And, where everybody wants rights, who shall give them to whom? I do not wish to imply that they do no duties. They don't perform the duties corresponding to those rights; and as they do not perform that particular duty, namely, acquire fitness, their rights have proved a burden to them. In other words, what they have obtained is an exact result of the means they adapted. They used the means corresponding to the end. If I want to deprive you of your watch, I shall certainly have to fight for it; if I want to buy your watch, I shall have to pay you for it; and if I want a gift, I shall have to plead for it; and, according to the means I employ, the watch is stolen property, my own property, or a donation. Thus we see three different results from three different means. Will you still say that means do not matter?" -- Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3679-if-the-doors-of-perception-were-cleansed-every-thing-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 08:51:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by William Blake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3679-if-the-doors-of-perception-were-cleansed-every-thing-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the doors of perception were cleansed every thing would appear to man as it is, Infinite. For man has closed himself up, till he sees all things thro' narrow chinks of his cavern." -- William Blake]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140121-people-often-say-that-this-or-that-person-has-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 12:14:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Thomas Szasz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140121-people-often-say-that-this-or-that-person-has-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People often say that this or that person has not yet found [themself]. But the self is not something that one finds. It is something one creates" -- Thomas Szasz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11945-emancipate-yourselves-from-mental-slavery-none-but-ourselves-can-free</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 21:43:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11945-emancipate-yourselves-from-mental-slavery-none-but-ourselves-can-free]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Emancipate yourselves from mental slavery.
None but ourselves can free our minds." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143692-nothing-ends-adrian-nothing-ever-ends</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 20:44:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143692-nothing-ends-adrian-nothing-ever-ends]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing ends, Adrian. Nothing ever ends." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9180-stood-in-firelight-sweltering-bloodstain-on-chest-like-map-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 20:47:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9180-stood-in-firelight-sweltering-bloodstain-on-chest-like-map-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stood in firelight, sweltering. Bloodstain on chest like map of violent new continent. Felt cleansed. Felt dark planet turn under my feet and knew what cats know that makes them scream like babies in night.

Looked at sky through smoke heavy with human fat and God was not there. The cold, suffocating dark goes on forever and we are alone. Live our lives, lacking anything better to do. Devise reason later. Born from oblivion; bear children, hell-bound as ourselves, go into oblivion. There is nothing else.

Existence is random. Has no pattern save what we imagine after staring at it for too long. No meaning save what we choose to impose. This rudderless world is not shaped by vague metaphysical forces. It is not God who kills the children. Not fate that butchers them or destiny that feeds them to the dogs. It’s us. Only us. Streets stank of fire. The void breathed hard on my heart, turning its illusions to ice, shattering them. Was reborn then, free to scrawl own design on this morally blank world.

Was Rorschach.

Does that answer your Questions, Doctor?" -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143693-we-re-all-puppets-laurie-i-m-just-a-puppet-who-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 20:47:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143693-we-re-all-puppets-laurie-i-m-just-a-puppet-who-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're all puppets, Laurie. I'm just a puppet who can see the strings." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143694-there-is-no-future-there-is-no-past-do-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 20:48:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143694-there-is-no-future-there-is-no-past-do-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no future. There is no past. Do you see? Time is simultaneous, an intricately structured jewel that humans insist on viewing one edge at a time, when the whole design is visible in every facet." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61926-thermodynamic-miracles-events-with-odds-against-so-astronomical-they-re-effectively</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 20:49:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61926-thermodynamic-miracles-events-with-odds-against-so-astronomical-they-re-effectively]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thermodynamic miracles... events with odds against so astronomical they're effectively impossible, like oxygen spontaneously becoming gold. I long to observe such a thing.
And yet, in each human coupling, a thousand million sperm vie for a single egg. Multiply those odds by countless generations, against the odds of your ancestors being alive; meeting; siring this precise son; that exact daughter... Until your mother loves a man she has every reason to hate, and of that union, of the thousand million children competing for fertilization, it was you, only you, that emerged. To distill so specific a form from that chaos of improbability, like turning air to gold... that is the crowning unlikelihood. The thermodynamic miracle.

But...if me, my birth, if that's a thermodynamic miracle... I mean, you could say that about anybody in the world!.

Yes. Anybody in the world. ..But the world is so full of people, so crowded with these miracles that they become commonplace and we forget... I forget. We gaze continually at the world and it grows dull in our perceptions. Yet seen from the another's vantage point. As if new, it may still take our breath away. Come...dry your eyes. For you are life, rarer than a quark and unpredictable beyond the dreams of Heisenberg; the clay in which the forces that shape all things leave their fingerprints most clearly. Dry your eyes... and let's go home." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
