<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1044258-manuj]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1044258-manuj" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 03:43:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39581-nothing-can-be-accomplished-by-logic-and-ethics</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 03:43:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Manuj add a quote by Anton Chekhov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39581-nothing-can-be-accomplished-by-logic-and-ethics]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing can be accomplished by logic and ethics." -- Anton Chekhov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27566-these-people-have-learned-not-from-books-but-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 03:43:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Manuj add a quote by Anton Chekhov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27566-these-people-have-learned-not-from-books-but-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These people have learned not from books, but in the fields, in the wood, on the river bank. Their teachers have been the birds themselves, when they sang to them, the sun when it left a glow of crimson behind it at setting, the very trees, and wild herbs." -- Anton Chekhov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48165-you-have-lost-your-reason-and-taken-the-wrong-path</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 03:44:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Manuj add a quote by Anton Chekhov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48165-you-have-lost-your-reason-and-taken-the-wrong-path]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have lost your reason and taken the wrong path. You have taken lies for truth, and hideousness for beauty. You would marvel if, owing to strange events of some sorts, frogs and lizards suddenly grew on apple and orange trees instead of fruit, or if roses began to smell like a sweating horse; so I marvel at you who exchange heaven for earth. I don't want to understand you." -- Anton Chekhov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18991-what-is-a-country-a-country-is-a-piece-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 03:46:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Manuj add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18991-what-is-a-country-a-country-is-a-piece-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is a country? A country is a piece of land surrounded on all sides by boundaries, usually unnatural. Englishmen are dying for England, Americans are dying for America, Germans are dying for Germany, Russians are dying for Russia. There are now fifty or sixty countries fighting in this war. Surely so many countries can't all be worth dying for." -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61105-what-a-lousy-earth-he-wondered-how-many-people-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 03:46:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Manuj add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61105-what-a-lousy-earth-he-wondered-how-many-people-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a lousy earth! He wondered how many people were destitute that same night even in his own prosperous country, how many homes were shanties, how many husbands were drunk and wives socked, and how many children were bullied, abused, or abandoned. How many families hungered for food they could not afford to buy? How many hearts were broken? How many suicides would take place that same night, how many people would go insane? How many cockroaches and landlords would triumph? How many winners were losers, successes failures, and rich men poor men? How many wise guys were stupid? How many happy endings were unhappy endings? How many honest men were liars, brave men cowards, loyal men traitors, how many sainted men were corrupt, how many people in positions of trust had sold their souls to bodyguards, how many had never had souls? How many straight-and-narrow paths were crooked paths? How many best families were worst families and how many good people were bad people? When you added them all up and then subtracted, you might be left with only the children, and perhaps with Albert Einstein and an old violinist or sculptor somewhere." -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79386-they-re-trying-to-kill-me-yossarian-told-him-calmly-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 03:46:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Manuj add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79386-they-re-trying-to-kill-me-yossarian-told-him-calmly-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They're trying to kill me,&quot; Yossarian told him calmly.
No one's trying to kill you,&quot; Clevinger cried.
Then why are they shooting at me?&quot; Yossarian asked.
They're shooting at everyone,&quot; Clevinger answered.  &quot;They're trying to kill everyone.&quot;
And what difference does that make?" -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22225-you-know-that-might-be-the-answer-to-act</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 03:47:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Manuj add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22225-you-know-that-might-be-the-answer-to-act]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know, that might be the answer – to act boastfully about something we ought to be ashamed of.  That’s a trick that never seems to fail.”  --Colonel Korn, Catch-22" -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63575-there-s-nothing-mysterious-about-it-he-s-not-working-at-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 03:47:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Manuj add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63575-there-s-nothing-mysterious-about-it-he-s-not-working-at-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's nothing mysterious about it, He's not working at all. He's playing. Or else He's forgotten all about us. That's the kind of God you people talk about, a country bumpkin, a clumsy, bungling, brainless, conceited, uncouth hayseed. Good God, how much reverence can you have for a Supreme Being who finds it necessary to include such phenomena as phlegm and tooth decay in His divine system of Creation? What in the world was running through that warped, evil, scatological mind of His when He robbed old people of the power to control their bowel movements? Why in the world did He ever create pain?" -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125177-what-would-they-do-to-me-he-asked-in-confidential</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 03:49:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Manuj add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125177-what-would-they-do-to-me-he-asked-in-confidential]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What would they do to me,&quot; he asked in confidential tones, &quot;if I refused to fly them?&quot;
We'd probably shoot you,&quot; ex-P.F.C. Wintergreen replied.
We?&quot; Yossarian cried in surprise. &quot;What do you mean, we? Since when are you on their side?&quot;
If you're going to be shot, whose side do you expect me to be on?&quot; ex-P.F.C. Wintergreen retorted" -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42537-man-was-matter-that-was-snowden-s-secret-drop-him-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 06:44:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Manuj add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42537-man-was-matter-that-was-snowden-s-secret-drop-him-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man was matter, that was Snowden's secret. Drop him out a window, and he'll fall. Set fire to him and he'll burn. Bury him and he'll rot, like other kinds of garbage. The spirit gone, man is garbage. That was Snowden's secret. Ripeness was all." -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103238-the-secret-to-life-is-meaningless-unless-you-discover-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 11:21:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Manuj add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103238-the-secret-to-life-is-meaningless-unless-you-discover-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The secret to life is meaningless unless you discover it yourself." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
