<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1045752-lane]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1045752-lane" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 02:15:10 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 02:15:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the only people for me are the mad ones, the ones who are mad to live, mad to talk, mad to be saved, desirous of everything at the same time, the ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn like fabulous yellow roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17754-i-m-not-interested-in-preserving-the-status-quo-i-want</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 02:17:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Machiavelli Niccolo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17754-i-m-not-interested-in-preserving-the-status-quo-i-want]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not interested in preserving the status quo; I want to overthrow it." -- Machiavelli Niccolo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23769-where-the-willingness-is-great-the-difficulties-cannot-be-great</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 02:18:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Niccolo Machiavelli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23769-where-the-willingness-is-great-the-difficulties-cannot-be-great]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where the willingness is great, the difficulties cannot be great. " -- Niccolo Machiavelli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15722-no-life-is-a-waste-the-blue-man-said-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 02:22:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15722-no-life-is-a-waste-the-blue-man-said-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No life is a waste,&quot; the Blue Man said. &quot;The only time we waste is the time we spend thinking we're alone." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8449-well-for-one-thing-the-culture-we-have-does-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 02:23:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8449-well-for-one-thing-the-culture-we-have-does-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, for one thing, the culture we have does not make people feel good about themselves. We're teaching the wrong things. And you have to be strong enough to say if the culture doesn't work, don't buy it. Create your own. Most people can't do it." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42914-ladies-let-me-give-you-some-advice-you-can-throw</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 02:24:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Tucker Max]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42914-ladies-let-me-give-you-some-advice-you-can-throw]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ladies, let me give you some advice. You can throw all your stupid fucking chick-lit, self-help, why-doesn't-he-love-me books out, because this is all you need to know: Men will treat you the way you let them. There is no such thing as &quot;deserving&quot; respect; you get what you demand from people.. if you demand respect, he will either respect you or he won't associate with you. It really is that simple." -- Tucker Max]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12841-everyone-thinks-of-changing-the-world-but-no-one-thinks</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 02:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12841-everyone-thinks-of-changing-the-world-but-no-one-thinks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone thinks of changing the world, but no one thinks of changing himself." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50677-who-has-never-killed-an-hour-not-casually-or-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 02:30:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50677-who-has-never-killed-an-hour-not-casually-or-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who has never killed an hour? Not casually or without thought, but carefully: a premeditated murder of minutes. The violence comes from a combination of giving up, not caring, and a resignation that getting past it is all you can hope to accomplish. So you kill the hour. You do not work, you do not read, you do not daydream. If you sleep it is not because you need to sleep. And when at last it is over, there is no evidence: no weapon, no blood, and no body. The only clue might be the shadows beneath your eyes or a terribly thin line near the corner of your mouth indicating something has been suffered, that in the privacy of your life you have lost something and the loss is too empty to share." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15849-make-a-radical-change-in-your-lifestyle-and-begin-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 02:31:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15849-make-a-radical-change-in-your-lifestyle-and-begin-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["make a radical change in your lifestyle and begin to boldly do things which you may previously never have thought of doing, or been too hesitant to attempt. So many people live within unhappy circumstances and yet will not take the initiative to change their situation because they are conditioned to a life of security, conformity, and conservation, all of which may appear to give one peace of mind, but in reality nothing is more damaging to the adventurous spirit within a man than a secure future. The very basic core of a man's living spirit is his passion for adventure. The joy of life comes from our encounters with new experiences, and hence there is no greater joy than to have an endlessly changing horizon, for each day to have a new and different sun. If you want to get more out of life, you must lose your inclination for monotonous security and adopt a helter-skelter style of life that will at first appear to you to be crazy. But once you become accustomed to such a life you will see its full meaning and its incredible beauty." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11814-when-a-young-person-is-moved-by-a-passion-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 02:32:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11814-when-a-young-person-is-moved-by-a-passion-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a young person is moved by a passion and feels compelled to go on this sort of quest, I think you have to let him. You can't stop him. In our culture we don't have formal rights of passage like in some ancient cultures. Subjecting yourself to risk... may be something you have to go through to be a man or a woman." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1928-if-you-re-looking-for-sympathy-you-ll-find-it-between-shit</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 02:33:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1928-if-you-re-looking-for-sympathy-you-ll-find-it-between-shit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're looking for sympathy you'll find it between shit and syphilis in the dictionary." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29269-we-were-not-a-hugging-people-in-terms-of-emotional</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 02:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29269-we-were-not-a-hugging-people-in-terms-of-emotional]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We were not a hugging people. In terms of emotional comfort it was our belief that no amount of physical contact could match the healing powers of a well made cocktail." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51320-he-took-a-sip-of-my-father-s-weak-coffee-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 02:34:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51320-he-took-a-sip-of-my-father-s-weak-coffee-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He took a sip of my father’s weak coffee and spit it back into the mug. &quot;This shit’s like making love in a canoe.&quot;
&quot;Excuse me?&quot;
&quot;It’s fucking near water." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35682-all-of-us-take-pride-and-pleasure-in-the-fact</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 02:35:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35682-all-of-us-take-pride-and-pleasure-in-the-fact]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All of us take pride and pleasure in the fact that we are unique, but I'm afraid that when all is said and done the police are right: it all comes down to fingerprints." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308389-a-mother-s-body-remembers-her-babies--the-folds-of-soft-flesh</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 00:38:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308389-a-mother-s-body-remembers-her-babies--the-folds-of-soft-flesh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A mother's body remembers her babies--the folds of soft flesh, the softly furred scalp against her nose. Each child has its own entreaties to body and soul. It's the last one, though, that overtakes you. I can't dare say I loved the others less, but my first three were all babies at once, and motherhood dismayed me entirely. . . . That's how it is with the firstborn, no matter what kind of mother you are--rich, poor, frazzled half to death or sweetly content. A first child is your own best food forward, and how you do cheer those little feet as they strike out. You examine every turn of flesh for precocity, and crow it to the world. 

But the last one: the baby who trails her scent like a flag of surrender through your life when there will be no more coming after--oh, that's love by a different name. She is the babe you hold in your arms for an hour after she's gone to sleep. If you put her down in the crib, she might wake up changed and fly away. So instead you rock by the window, drinking the light from her skin, breathing her exhaled dreams. Your heart bays to the double crescent moons of closed lashes on her cheeks. She's the one you can't put down." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3160-today-you-are-you-that-is-truer-than-true-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 06:11:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3160-today-you-are-you-that-is-truer-than-true-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today you are You, that is truer than true. There is no one alive who is Youer than You." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4907-unless-someone-like-you-cares-a-whole-awful-lot-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 06:11:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4907-unless-someone-like-you-cares-a-whole-awful-lot-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Unless someone like you cares a whole awful lot,
Nothing is going to get better. It's not." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9787-i-have-heard-there-are-troubles-of-more-than-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 06:11:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9787-i-have-heard-there-are-troubles-of-more-than-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have heard there are troubles of more than one kind. Some come from ahead and some come from behind. But I've bought a big bat. I'm all ready you see. Now my troubles are going to have troubles with me!" -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15307-sometimes-people-are-beautiful-not-in-looks-not-in-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 10:06:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15307-sometimes-people-are-beautiful-not-in-looks-not-in-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes people are beautiful.
Not in looks.
Not in what they say.
Just in what they are." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 10:09:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26963-if-you-can-t-fly-then-run-if-you-can-t-run</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 10:11:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26963-if-you-can-t-fly-then-run-if-you-can-t-run]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can't fly then run, if you can't run then walk, if you can't walk then crawl, but whatever you do you have to keep moving forward." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17266-never-never-be-afraid-to-do-what-s-right-especially-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 10:12:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lane add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17266-never-never-be-afraid-to-do-what-s-right-especially-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never, never be afraid to do what's right, especially if the well-being of a person or animal is at stake. Society's punishments are small compared to the wounds we inflict on our soul when we look the other way." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
