<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1046887-lynn-joshua]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1046887-lynn-joshua" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 20:29:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6439-if-we-find-ourselves-with-a-desire-that-nothing-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 20:29:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6439-if-we-find-ourselves-with-a-desire-that-nothing-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we find ourselves with a desire that nothing in this world can satisfy, the most probable explanation is that we were made for another world." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/472430-christian-rebellion-arises-from-the-doctrine-of-mankind-made-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 15:28:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by John Stott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/472430-christian-rebellion-arises-from-the-doctrine-of-mankind-made-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Christian rebellion] arises from the doctrine of mankind made in the image of God, and therefore protests against all forms of dehumanization. It sets itself against the social injustices which insult God the Creator, seeks to protect human beings from oppression and longs to liberate them… it protests against every authoritarian regime, whether of the left or of the right, which discriminates against minorities, denies people their civil rights, forbids the free expression of opinions or imprisons people for their views alone." -- John Stott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/684173-but-to-reject-marginalize-trivialize-or-be-suspicious-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2013 15:41:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by N.T. Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/684173-but-to-reject-marginalize-trivialize-or-be-suspicious-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But to reject, marginalize, trivialize, or be suspicious of the sacraments (and quasi-sacramental acts such as lighting a candle, bowing, washing feet, raising hands in the air, crossing oneself and so forth) on the grounds that such things CAN be superstitious or idolatrous or that some people might suppose they are putting God in their debt, is like rejecting sexual relations in marriage on the grounds that it's the same act that in other circumstances constitutes immorality." -- N.T. Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/823030-when-human-beings-give-their-heartfelt-allegiance-to-and-worship</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2013 15:53:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by N.T. Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/823030-when-human-beings-give-their-heartfelt-allegiance-to-and-worship]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When human beings give their heartfelt allegiance to and worship that which is not God, they progressively cease to reflect the image of God. One of the primary laws of human life is that you become like what you worship; what’s more, you reflect what you worship not only to the object itself but also outward to the world around. Those who worship money increasingly define themselves in terms of it and increasingly treat other people as creditors, debtors, partners, or customers rather than as human beings. Those who worship sex define themselves in terms of it (their preferences, their practices, their past histories) and increasingly treat other people as actual or potential sex objects. Those who worship power define themselves in terms of it and treat other people as either collaborators, competitors, or pawns. These and many other forms of idolatry combine in a thousand ways, all of them damaging to the image-bearing quality of the people concerned and of those whose lives they touch." -- N.T. Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135126-the-point-of-the-resurrection-is-that-the-present-bodily-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 20:58:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by N.T. Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135126-the-point-of-the-resurrection-is-that-the-present-bodily-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The point of the resurrection…is that the present bodily life is not valueless just because it will die…What you do with your body in the present matters because God has a great future in store for it…What you do in the present—by painting, preaching, singing, sewing, praying, teaching, building hospitals, digging wells, campaigning for justice, writing poems, caring for the needy, loving your neighbor as yourself—will last into God's future. These activities are not simply ways of making the present life a little less beastly, a little more bearable, until the day when we leave it behind altogether (as the hymn so mistakenly puts it…). They are part of what we may call building for God's kingdom." -- N.T. Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241988-you-can-t-go-on-seeing-through-things-forever-the-whole</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 20:49:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241988-you-can-t-go-on-seeing-through-things-forever-the-whole]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can’t go on “seeing through” things forever. The whole point of seeing through something is to see something through it. To “see through” all things is the same as not to see." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/994126-it-is-better-to-arm-and-strengthen-your-hero-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 17:51:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by Anne Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/994126-it-is-better-to-arm-and-strengthen-your-hero-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to arm and strengthen your hero, than to disarm and enfeeble your foe." -- Anne Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/459379-to-control-the-future-requires-the-control-of-education-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 20:30:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by R.J. Rushdoony]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/459379-to-control-the-future-requires-the-control-of-education-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To control the future requires the control of education and of the child. Hence, for Christians to tolerate statist education, or to allow their children to be trained thereby, means to renounce power in society, to renounce their children, and to deny Christ's Lordship over all of life." -- R.J. Rushdoony]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/443331-there-are-no-boring-subjects-only-disinterested-minds</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 20:30:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/443331-there-are-no-boring-subjects-only-disinterested-minds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are no boring subjects, only disinterested minds." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207409-the-secret-of-happiness-is-not-in-doing-what-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 20:30:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by James Matthew Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207409-the-secret-of-happiness-is-not-in-doing-what-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The secret of happiness is not in doing what one likes, but in liking what one does." -- James Matthew Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32552-assumptions-are-dangerous-things-to-make-and-like-all-dangerous</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 12:11:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32552-assumptions-are-dangerous-things-to-make-and-like-all-dangerous]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Assumptions are dangerous things to make, and like all dangerous things to make -- bombs, for instance, or strawberry shortcake -- if you make even the tiniest mistake you can find yourself in terrible trouble. Making assumptions simply means believing things are a certain way with little or no evidence that shows you are correct, and you can see at once how this can lead to terrible trouble. For instance, one morning you might wake up and make the assumption that your bed was in the same place that it always was, even though you would have no real evidence that this was so. But when you got out of your bed, you might discover that it had floated out to sea, and now you would be in terrible trouble all because of the incorrect assumption that you'd made. You can see that it is better not to make too many assumptions, particularly in the morning." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5479-taking-one-s-chances-is-like-taking-a-bath-because-sometimes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 12:24:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5479-taking-one-s-chances-is-like-taking-a-bath-because-sometimes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Taking one’s chances is like taking a bath, because sometimes you end up feeling comfortable and warm, and sometimes there is something terrible lurking around that you cannot see until it is too late and you can do nothing else but scream and cling to a plastic duck." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41534-one-word-ma-am-he-said-coming-back-from-the-fire</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 07:34:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41534-one-word-ma-am-he-said-coming-back-from-the-fire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One word, Ma'am,&quot; he said, coming back from the fire; limping, because of the pain. &quot;One word. All you've been saying is quite right, I shouldn't wonder. I'm a chap who always liked to know the worst and then put the best face I can on it. So I won't deny any of what you said. But there's one more thing to be said, even so. Suppose we have only dreamed, or made up, all those things-trees and grass and sun and moon and stars and Aslan himself. Suppose we have. Then all I can say is that, in that case, the made-up things seem a good deal more important than the real ones. Suppose this black pit of a kingdom of yours is the only world. Well, it strikes me as a pretty poor one. And that's a funny thing, when you come to think of it. We're just babies making up a game, if you're right. But four babies playing a game can make a play-world which licks your real world hollow. That's why I'm going to stand by the play world. I'm on Aslan's side even if there isn't any Aslan to lead it. I'm going to live as like a Narnian as I can even if there isn't any Narnia. So, thanking you kindly for our supper, if these two gentlemen and the young lady are ready, we're leaving your court at once and setting out in the dark to spend our lives looking for Overland. Not that our lives will be very long, I should think; but that's a small loss if the world's as dull a place as you say." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178371-our-task-as-image-bearing-god-loving-christ-shaped-spirit-filled-christians-following-christ</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 15:38:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by N.T. Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178371-our-task-as-image-bearing-god-loving-christ-shaped-spirit-filled-christians-following-christ]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our task as image-bearing, God-loving, Christ-shaped, Spirit-filled Christians, following Christ and shaping our world, is to announce redemption to a world that has discovered its fallenness, to announce healing to a world that has discovered its brokenness, to proclaim love and trust to a world that knows only exploitation, fear and suspicion...The gospel of Jesus points us and indeed urges us to be at the leading edge of the whole culture, articulating in story and music and art and philosophy and education and poetry and politics and theology and even--heaven help us--Biblical studies, a worldview that will mount the historically-rooted Christian challenge to both modernity and postmodernity, leading the way...with joy and humor and gentleness and good judgment and true wisdom.  I believe if we face the question, &quot;if not now, then when?&quot; if we are grasped by this vision we may also hear the question, &quot;if not us, then who?&quot;  And if the gospel of Jesus is not the key to this task, then what is?" -- N.T. Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2056-cowards-die-many-times-before-their-deaths-the-valiant-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 10:37:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2056-cowards-die-many-times-before-their-deaths-the-valiant-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cowards die many times before their deaths; 
The valiant never taste of death but once. 
Of all the wonders that I yet have heard, 
It seems to me most strange that men should fear; 
Seeing that death, a necessary end, 
Will come when it will come." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/631542-oh-yet-we-trust-that-somehow-good-will-be-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 11:43:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by Alfred Tennyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/631542-oh-yet-we-trust-that-somehow-good-will-be-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh yet we trust that somehow good
Will be the final goal of ill,
To pangs of nature, sins of will,
Defects of doubt, and taints of blood;


That nothing walks with aimless feet;
That not one life shall be destroy'd,
Or cast as rubbish to the void,
When God hath made the pile complete;


That not a worm is cloven in vain;
That not a moth with vain desire
Is shrivell'd in a fruitless fire,
Or but subserves another's gain.


Behold, we know not anything;
I can but trust that good shall fall
At last—far off—at last, to all,
And every winter change to spring.


So runs my dream: but what am I?
An infant crying in the night:
An infant crying for the light:
And with no language but a cry." -- Alfred Tennyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
