<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1048635-amanda]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1048635-amanda" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 19:45:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92240-we-women-have-a-lot-to-learn-about-simplifying-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 19:45:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92240-we-women-have-a-lot-to-learn-about-simplifying-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We women have a lot to learn about simplifying our lives.  We have to decide what is important and then move along at a pace that is comfortable for us.  We have to develop the maturity to stop trying to prove something.  We have to learn to be content with what we are." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141191-think-about-your-particular-assignment-at-this-time-in-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 19:46:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141191-think-about-your-particular-assignment-at-this-time-in-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Think about your particular assignment at this time in your life.  It may be to get an education, it may be to rear children, it may be to be a grandparent, it may be to care for an relieve the suffering of someone you love, it may be to do a job in the most excellent way possible, it may be to support someone who has a difficult assignment of their own.  Our assignments are varied and they change from time to time.  Don't take them lightly.  Give them your full heart and energy.  Do them with enthusiasm.  Do whatever you have to do this week with your whole heart and soul.  To do less than this will leave you with an empty feeling." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26665-i-don-t-want-to-drive-up-to-the-pearly-gates</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 19:47:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26665-i-don-t-want-to-drive-up-to-the-pearly-gates]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't want to drive up to the pearly gates in a shiny sports car, wearing beautifully, tailored clothes, my hair expertly coiffed, and with long, perfectly manicured fingernails.
I want to drive up in a station wagon that has mud on the wheels from taking kids to scout camp.
I want to be there with a smudge of peanut butter on my shirt from making sandwiches for a sick neighbors children.
I want to be there with a little dirt under my fingernails from helping to weed someone's garden.
I want to be there with children's sticky kisses on my cheeks and the tears of a friend on my shoulder.
I want the Lord to know I was really here and that I really lived." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
