<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1048305-kaylee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1048305-kaylee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 11:31:32 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34716-suicide-is-a-form-of-murder---premeditated-murder-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 11:31:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaylee add a quote by Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34716-suicide-is-a-form-of-murder---premeditated-murder-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suicide is a form of murder - premeditated murder. It isn't something you do the first time you think of doing it. It takes getting used to. And you need the means, the opportunity, the motive. A successful suicide demands good organization and a cool head, both of which are usually incompatible with the suicidal state of mind." -- Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52693-the-debate-was-wearing-me-out-once-you-ve-posed-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 11:34:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaylee add a quote by Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52693-the-debate-was-wearing-me-out-once-you-ve-posed-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The debate was wearing me out. Once you've posed that question, it won't go away. I think many
people kill themselves simply to stop the debate about whether they will or they won't.
Anything I thought or did was immediately drawn into the debate. Made a stupid remark--why not kill
myself? Missed the bus--better put an end to it all. Even the good got in there. I liked that movie--maybe
I shouldn't kill myself." -- Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126463-why-did-she-do-it-nobody-dared-to-ask-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 13:01:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaylee add a quote by Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126463-why-did-she-do-it-nobody-dared-to-ask-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why did she do it? Nobody dared to ask. Because - what courage! Who had the courage to burn herself? Twenty aspirin, a little slit alongside the veins of the arm, maybe even a bad half hour standing on a roof: We've all had those. And somewhat more dangerous things, like putting a gun in your mouth. But you put it there, you taste it, it's cold and greasy, your finger is on the trigger, and you find that a whole world lies between this moment and the moment you've been planning, when you'll pull the trigger. That world defeats you. You put the gun back in the drawer. You'll have to find another way.

What was that moment like for her? The moment she lit the match. Had she already tried roofs and guns and aspirins? Or was it just an inspiration?

I had an inspiration once. I woke up one morning and I knew that today I had to swallow fifty aspirin. It was my task: my job for the day. I lined them up on my desk and took them one by one, counting. But it's not the same as what she did. I could have stopped, at ten, or at thirty. And I could have done what I did do, which was go onto the street and faint. Fifty aspirin is a lot of aspirin, but going onto the street and fainting is like putting the gun back in the drawer.

She lit the match." -- Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149274-scar-tissue-has-no-character-it-s-not-like-skin-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 13:01:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaylee add a quote by Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149274-scar-tissue-has-no-character-it-s-not-like-skin-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Scar tissue has no character. It's not like skin. It doesn't show age or illness or pallor or tan. It has no pores, no hair, no wrinkles. It's like a slip cover. It shields and disguises what's beneath. That's why we grow it; we have something to hide. " -- Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52694-actually-it-was-only-part-of-myself-i-wanted-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 13:02:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaylee add a quote by Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52694-actually-it-was-only-part-of-myself-i-wanted-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Actually, it was only part of myself I wanted to kill: the part that wanted to kill herself, that dragged me into the suicide debate and made every window, kitchen implement, and subway station a rehearsal for tragedy." -- Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170276-if-being-sane-is-thinking-there-s-something-wrong-with-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 13:04:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaylee add a quote by Angelina Jolie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170276-if-being-sane-is-thinking-there-s-something-wrong-with-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If being sane is thinking there's something wrong with being different....I'd rather be completely fucking mental." -- Angelina Jolie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116936-i-m-with-a-man-who-s-evolved-enough-to-look-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 13:05:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaylee add a quote by Angelina Jolie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116936-i-m-with-a-man-who-s-evolved-enough-to-look-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm with a man who's evolved enough to look at my body and see it as more beautiful because of the journey it has taken. " -- Angelina Jolie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150324-where-ever-i-am-i-always-find-myself-looking-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 13:05:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaylee add a quote by Angelina Jolie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150324-where-ever-i-am-i-always-find-myself-looking-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where ever I am I always find myself looking out the window wishing I was somewhere else. " -- Angelina Jolie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186335-barefoot-or-first-thing-in-the-morning-i-feel-beautiful</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 13:06:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaylee add a quote by Angelina Jolie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186335-barefoot-or-first-thing-in-the-morning-i-feel-beautiful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Barefoot or first thing in the morning, I feel beautiful. I didn't always feel that way, but I feel that way now. When somebody loves you, and when you make somebody else happy, when your presence seems to make them happy, you suddenly feel like the most beautiful person in the world." -- Angelina Jolie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116859-it-was-easy-enough-to-kill-yourself-in-a-fit</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 13:09:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaylee add a quote by Erica Jong]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116859-it-was-easy-enough-to-kill-yourself-in-a-fit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was easy enough to kill yourself in a fit of despair. It was easy enough to play the martyr. It was harder to do nothing. To endure your life. To wait." -- Erica Jong]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111870-once-on-a-yellow-piece-of-paper-with-green-lines</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 13:11:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaylee add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111870-once-on-a-yellow-piece-of-paper-with-green-lines]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once on a yellow piece of paper with green lines
	he wrote a poem
And he called it &quot;Chops&quot;
	because that was the name of his dog

And that's what it was all about
And his teacher gave him an A
	and a gold star
And his mother hung it on the kitchen door
	and read it to his aunts
That was the year Father Tracy
	took all the kids to the zoo

And he let them sing on the bus
And his little sister was born
	with tiny toenails and no hair
And his mother and father kissed a lot
And the girl around the corner sent him a
Valentine signed with a row of X's

	and he had to ask his father what the X's meant
And his father always tucked him in bed at night
And was always there to do it

Once on a piece of white paper with blue lines
	he wrote a poem
And he called it &quot;Autumn&quot;

	because that was the name of the season
And that's what it was all about
And his teacher gave him an A
	and asked him to write more clearly
And his mother never hung it on the kitchen door
	because of its new paint

And the kids told him
	that Father Tracy smoked cigars
And left butts on the pews
And sometimes they would burn holes
That was the year his sister got glasses
	with thick lenses and black frames
And the girl around the corner laughed

	when he asked her to go see Santa Claus
And the kids told him why
	his mother and father kissed a lot
And his father never tucked him in bed at night
And his father got mad
	when he cried for him to do it.


Once on a paper torn from his notebook
	he wrote a poem
And he called it &quot;Innocence: A Question&quot;
	because that was the question about his girl
And that's what it was all about
And his professor gave him an A

	and a strange steady look
And his mother never hung it on the kitchen door
	because he never showed her
That was the year that Father Tracy died
And he forgot how the end
	of the Apostle's Creed went

And he caught his sister
	making out on the back porch
And his mother and father never kissed
	or even talked
And the girl around the corner
	wore too much makeup
That made him cough when he kissed her

	but he kissed her anyway
	because that was the thing to do
And at three a.m. he tucked himself into bed
	his father snoring soundly

That's why on the back of a brown paper bag
	he tried another poem

And he called it &quot;Absolutely Nothing&quot;
Because that's what it was really all about
And he gave himself an A
	and a slash on each damned wrist
And he hung it on the bathroom door
	because this time he didn't think

	he could reach the kitchen." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286606-i-am-forever-engaged-in-a-silent-battle-in-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 23:51:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaylee add a quote by Jena Morrow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286606-i-am-forever-engaged-in-a-silent-battle-in-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am forever engaged in a silent battle in my head over whether or not to lift the fork to my mouth, and when I talk myself into doing so, I taste only shame. I have an eating disorder." -- Jena Morrow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144360-we-turn-skeletons-into-goddesses-and-look-to-them-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 23:51:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaylee add a quote by Marya Hornbacher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144360-we-turn-skeletons-into-goddesses-and-look-to-them-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We turn skeletons into goddesses and look to them as if they might teach us how not to need." -- Marya Hornbacher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/554153-anorexia-is-not-an-illness-of-the-body-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 23:54:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaylee add a quote by Lynn Crilly]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/554153-anorexia-is-not-an-illness-of-the-body-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anorexia is not an illness of the body; it is an illness of the mind." -- Lynn Crilly]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/554155-anorexia-cannot-be-cured-by-treating-the-physical-symptoms-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 23:54:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaylee add a quote by Lynn Crilly]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/554155-anorexia-cannot-be-cured-by-treating-the-physical-symptoms-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anorexia cannot be cured by treating the physical symptoms alone; it is the mind which must be treated." -- Lynn Crilly]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/613425-in-that-six-months-so-much-happened-that-death-seemed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 23:59:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaylee add a quote by Marya Hornbacher (Wasted: A Memoir Of Anorexia And Bulimia)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/613425-in-that-six-months-so-much-happened-that-death-seemed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In that six months, so much happened that death seemed, primarily, inconvenient. The trial period was extended.  I seem to keep extending it.  There are many things to do.  There are books to write and naps to take.  There are movies to see and scrambled eggs to eat.  Life is essentially trivial.  You either decide you will take the trite business of life and give yourself the option of doing something really cool, or you decide you will opt for the Grand Epic of eating disorders and dedicate your life to being seriously trivial." -- Marya Hornbacher (Wasted: A Memoir Of Anorexia And Bulimia)]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
