<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1048202-paulah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1048202-paulah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 08:29:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77822-the-following-day-the-editor-presided-over-a-sudued-meeting</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 08:29:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paulah add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77822-the-following-day-the-editor-presided-over-a-sudued-meeting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The following day the editor presided over a sudued meeting with his senior staff. Tony Montano sat to one side, a silent observer. 
&quot;It's time we ran more regular columns. They're cheap, and everyone else is doing them. You know, we hire someone of low to medium intelligence, possibly female, to write about, well, nothing much. You've seen that sort of thing. Goes to a party and can't remember anyone's name. Twelve hundred words.&quot;
&quot;Sort of naval gazing,&quot; Jeremy Ball suggested.
&quot;Not quite. Gazing is too intellectual. More like naval chat." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85060-that-a-thing-made-by-hand-the-work-and-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2008 15:38:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paulah add a quote by Susan Vreeland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85060-that-a-thing-made-by-hand-the-work-and-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That a thing made by hand, the work and thought of a single craftsman, can endure much longer than its maker, through centuries in fact, can survive natural catastrophe, neglect, and even mistreatment, has always filled me with wonder. Sometimes in museums, looking at a humble piece of pottery from ancient Persia or Pompeii, or a finely wrought page from a medieval illuminated manuscript toiled over by a nameless monk, or a primitive tool with a carved handle, I am moved to tears. The unknown life of the maker is evanescent in its brevity, but the work of his or her hands and heart remains." -- Susan Vreeland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104894-it-was-strange-when-you-reduced-even-a-fledgling-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2008 15:42:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paulah add a quote by Susan Vreeland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104894-it-was-strange-when-you-reduced-even-a-fledgling-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was strange: When you reduced even a fledgling love affair to its essentials--I loved her, she maybe loved me, I was foolish, I suffered--it became vacuous and trite, meaningless to anyone else. In the end, it's only the moments that we have, the kiss on the palm, the joint wonder at the furrowed texture of a fir trunk or at the infinitude of grains of sand in a dune. Only the moments." -- Susan Vreeland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109881-everything-is-connected-the-wing-of-the-corn-beetle-affects</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 08:11:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paulah add a quote by Tony Hillerman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109881-everything-is-connected-the-wing-of-the-corn-beetle-affects]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything is connected. The wing of the corn beetle affects the direction of the wind, the way the sand drifts, the way the light reflects into the eye of man beholding his reality. All is part of totality, and in this totality man finds his hozro, his way of walking in harmony, with beauty all around him." -- Tony Hillerman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
