<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1049622-amanda]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1049622-amanda" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 13:47:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3735-it-is-funny-how-mortals-always-picture-us-as-putting</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 13:47:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3735-it-is-funny-how-mortals-always-picture-us-as-putting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is funny how mortals always picture us as putting things into their minds: in reality our best work is done by keeping things out." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79741-nothing-is-very-strong-strong-enough-to-steal-away-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 13:52:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79741-nothing-is-very-strong-strong-enough-to-steal-away-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing is very strong: strong enough to steal away a man's best years not in sweet sins but in a dreary flickering of the mind over it knows not what and knows not why, in the gratification of curiosities so feeble that the man is only half aware of them, in drumming of fingers and kicking of heels, in whistling tunes that he does not like, or in the long, dim labyrinth of reveries that have not even lust or ambition to give them a relish, but which, once chance association has started them, the creature is took weak and fuddled to shake off." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79742-the-man-who-truly-and-disinterestedly-enjoys-any-one-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 13:53:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79742-the-man-who-truly-and-disinterestedly-enjoys-any-one-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who truly and disinterestedly enjoys any one thing in the world, for its own sake, and without caring two-pence what other people say about it, is by that very fact forewarmed against some of our subtlest modes of attack." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79743-by-this-method-thousands-of-humans-have-been-brought-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 13:55:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79743-by-this-method-thousands-of-humans-have-been-brought-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By this method thousands of humans have been brought to think that humility means pretty women trying to believe they are ugly and clever men trying to believe they are fools. And since what they are trying to believe may, in some cases, be manifest nonsense, they cannot succeed in believing it and we have the chance of keeping their minds endlessly revolving on themselves in an effort to achieve the the impossible." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79746-the-enemy-wants-to-bring-the-man-to-a-state</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 13:58:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79746-the-enemy-wants-to-bring-the-man-to-a-state]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Enemy wants to bring the man to a state of mind in which he could design the best cathedral in the world, and know it to be the best, and rejoice in the fact, without being any more (or less) or otherwise glad at having done it than he would be if it had been done by another.  The Enemy wants him, in the end, to be so free from any bias in his own favour that he can rejoice in his own talents as frankly and gratefully as in his neighbour's talents--or in a sunrise, an elephant, or a waterfall." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79748-you-must-therefore-zealously-guard-in-his-mind-the-curious</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 14:01:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79748-you-must-therefore-zealously-guard-in-his-mind-the-curious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must therefore zealously guard in his mind the curious assumption 'My time is my own'.  Let him have the feeling that he starts each day as the lawful possessor of twenty-four hours.  Let him feel as a grievous tax that portion of this property which he has to make over to him employers, and as a generous donation that further portion which h allows to religious duties.  But what he must never be permitted to doubt is that the total from which these deductions have been made was, in some mysterious sense, his own personal birthright." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79750-the-man-can-neither-man-nor-retain-one-moment-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 14:02:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79750-the-man-can-neither-man-nor-retain-one-moment-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man can neither man, nor retain, one moment of time; it all comes to him by pure gift; he might as well regard the sun and moon as his chattels." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79751-the-game-is-to-have-them-all-running-about-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 14:04:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79751-the-game-is-to-have-them-all-running-about-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The game is to have them all running about with fire extinguishers when there is a flood, and all crowding to that side of the boat which is already nearly gunwale under." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79752-whatever-he-says-let-his-inner-resolution-be-not-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 14:06:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79752-whatever-he-says-let-his-inner-resolution-be-not-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever he says, let his inner resolution be not to bear whatever comes to him, but to bear it 'for a reasonable period'--and let the reasonable period be shorter than the trial is likely to last.  It need not be much shorter; in attacks on patience, chastity, and fortitude, the fun is to make the man yield just when (had he but known it) relief was almost in sight." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79753-the-general-rule-which-we-have-pretty-much-established-among</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 14:07:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79753-the-general-rule-which-we-have-pretty-much-established-among]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The general rule which we have pretty much established among them is that in all experiences which can make them happier or better only the physical facts are 'real' while the spiritual elements are 'subjective'; in all experiences which can discourage or corrupt them the spiritual elements are the main reality and to ignore them is to be an escapist." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117316-her-magic-formula-for-dealing-with-children-is-ignoring-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2008 15:20:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Betty MacDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117316-her-magic-formula-for-dealing-with-children-is-ignoring-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her magic formula for dealing with children is ignoring all faults and accenting tiny virtues.  She says, &quot;Instead of telling Tommy day in and day out that he is the naughtiest boy in the United States of America, which could very well be true, take an aspirin and comment on his neatly tied shoes.  Almost anybody would rather be known for expert shoe-tying than for kicking the cat.&quot; She always tells whiners how charming they are--bullies how brave--bad sports how good--sneaks how honest!" -- Betty MacDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366226-with-every-choice-even-the-choice-of-inactivity-we-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2011 13:01:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Michael David Lukas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366226-with-every-choice-even-the-choice-of-inactivity-we-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With every choice, even the choice of inactivity, we must shut the door to a host of alternate futures.  Each step we take along the path of fate represents a narrowing of potential, the death of a parallel world. The path of fate was more like a tunnel, and it was constricting about her with ever step she took." -- Michael David Lukas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366229-you-are-a-very-special-child-the-old-handmaid-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2011 13:03:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Michael David Lukas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366229-you-are-a-very-special-child-the-old-handmaid-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are a very special child,&quot; the old handmaid said, stroking Eleonora's hair. &quot;You know that don't you?&quot;

Eleonora mumbled a yes.

&quot;You know you are special, but I think that you aren't sure how.&quot;

She nodded.  That was, indeed, the crux of it." -- Michael David Lukas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366231-she-hadn-t-lied-she-hadn-t-betrayed-anyone-s-trust-still-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2011 13:05:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Michael David Lukas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366231-she-hadn-t-lied-she-hadn-t-betrayed-anyone-s-trust-still-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She hadn't lied. She hadn't betrayed anyone's trust; still, she felt she had done something wrong. Or rather, she had not yet done the right thing. Was there a difference between these two sins?" -- Michael David Lukas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/450878-when-you-love-someone-you-do-not-love-them-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 14:31:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/450878-when-you-love-someone-you-do-not-love-them-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you love someone you do not love them, all the time, in the exact same way, from moment to moment. It is an impossibility. It is a lie to pretend to. And yet this is exactly what most of us demand. We have so little faith in the ebb and flow of life, of love, of relationships." -- Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
