<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1050785-rachel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1050785-rachel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 09:36:18 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335-when-someone-shows-you-who-they-are-believe-them-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 09:36:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335-when-someone-shows-you-who-they-are-believe-them-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When someone shows you who they are believe them; the first time." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/614087-but-feelings-no-matter-how-strong-or-ugly-are-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 18:18:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Augusten Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/614087-but-feelings-no-matter-how-strong-or-ugly-are-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But feelings, no matter how strong or “ugly,” are not a part of who you are. They are the radio stations your mind listens to if you don’t give it something better to do. Feelings are fluid and dynamic; they change frequently.
Feelings are something you HAVE, not something you ARE. Like physical beauty, a cold sore, or an opinion.

Admitting you feel rage or terrible pain or regret or some old, rotten blame does not mean these feelings are part of who you are as a person. What these feelings mean is, you have to change your thinking to be free of them." -- Augusten Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/552819-this-is-how-you-survive-the-unsurvivable-this-is-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 09:39:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Augusten Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/552819-this-is-how-you-survive-the-unsurvivable-this-is-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is how you survive the unsurvivable, this is how you lose that which you cannot bear to lose, this is how you reinvent yourself, overcome your abusers, fulfill your ambitions and meet the love of your life: by following what is true, no matter where it leads you." -- Augusten Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/773066-kindness-covers-all-of-my-political-beliefs-no-need-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:48:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Roger Ebert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/773066-kindness-covers-all-of-my-political-beliefs-no-need-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kindness’ covers all of my political beliefs. No need to spell them out. I believe that if, at the end, according to our abilities, we have done something to make others a little happier, and something to make ourselves a little happier, that is about the best we can do. To make others less happy is a crime. To make ourselves unhappy is where all crime starts. We must try to contribute joy to the world. That is true no matter what our problems, our health, our circumstances. We must try. I didn’t always know this and am happy I lived long enough to find it out." -- Roger Ebert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/479961-because-that-s-really-something-i-can-t-stand-when-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 00:38:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/479961-because-that-s-really-something-i-can-t-stand-when-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because that’s really something I can’t stand — when people refer to themselves as crazy. The truly crazy are labeled so on the grounds that they see nothing wrong with their behavior. They forge ahead, lighting fires in public buildings and defecating in frying pans without the slightest notion that they are out of step with the rest of society. That, to me, is crazy." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606755-travel-tip-the-term-is-in-situ----in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 11:17:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Vivian Swift]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606755-travel-tip-the-term-is-in-situ----in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Travel Tip:  The term is &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;in situ&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; -- in the place of origin. We travel to put ourselves &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;in situ&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, in a place where we &lt;i&gt;belong&lt;/i&gt;.  The feeling that one was born in the wrong place is an ancient an universal experience, such that I suspect (a) it is part of our human DNA; and (b) is why our kind are born wanderers.  We travel to find the place where we can &lt;b&gt;recognize ourselves&lt;/b&gt; for once.  Be on the lookout for that jolt of unexpected familiarity in a foreign land: that's how you'll know &lt;b&gt;you&lt;/b&gt; are &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;in situ&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;." -- Vivian Swift]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606784-i-am-acutely-aware-that-i-am-now-the-middle-aged</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 11:18:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Vivian Swift]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606784-i-am-acutely-aware-that-i-am-now-the-middle-aged]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am acutely aware that I am now the middle-aged traveler that I used to consider to lame, so embarrassing.  And I have something to say to my 20-year-old self:&lt;br&gt;
You cannot possibly know how much time it takes to learn to treasure this world, how many years it takes to properly cherish your place in it.&lt;br&gt;
As you age, you will find it more and more remarkable, a &lt;b&gt;miracle&lt;/b&gt; really, that any of us -- you, me -- are here at all, the result of an undeserved, infinite gift.&lt;br&gt;
And the older you get, the more you know how much you will miss all this when you are gone. &lt;br&gt;
In the end, the world was not all that changed by your coming, you were not all that crucial to &lt;i&gt;it&lt;/i&gt;.  But the world, &lt;i&gt;this world&lt;/i&gt;, which you will one day travel in homage and gratitude, &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; world was &lt;b&gt;everything&lt;/b&gt; to you." -- Vivian Swift]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
