<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1051666-rachna-r]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1051666-rachna-r" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 09:19:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371993-gilbert-i-m-afraid-i-m-scandalously-in-love-with-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 09:19:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371993-gilbert-i-m-afraid-i-m-scandalously-in-love-with-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Gilbert, I'm afraid I'm scandalously in love with you." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238138-it-s-not-reasonable-to-love-people-who-are-only-going</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2012 19:00:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Kristin Cashore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238138-it-s-not-reasonable-to-love-people-who-are-only-going]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not reasonable to love people who are only going to die,&quot; she said.
Nash thought about that for a moment, stroking Small's neck with great deliberation, as if the fate of the Dells depended on that smooth, careful movement.
&quot;I have two responses to that,&quot; he said finally. &quot;First, everyone's going to die. Second, love is stupid. It has  nothing to do with reason. You love whomever you love. Against all reasons I loved my father.&quot; He looked at her keenly. &quot;Did you love yours?&quot;
&quot;Yes,&quot; she whispered.
He stroked Small's nose. &quot;I love you,&quot; he said, &quot;even knowing you'll never have me. And I love my brother, more than I ever realized before you came along. You can't help whom you love, Lady. Nor can you know what it's liable to cause you to do.&quot;
She made a connection then. Surprised she sat back from him and studied his face, soft with shadows and light. She saw a part of him she hadn't seen before.
&quot;You came to me for lessons to guard your mind,&quot; she said, &quot;and you stopped asking me to marry you, both at the same time. You did those things out of love for your brother.&quot;
&quot;Well&quot; he said, looking a bit sheepishly at the floor. &quot;I also took a few swings at him, but that's neither here nor there.&quot;
&quot;You're good at love,&quot; she said simply, because it seemed to her that it was true. &quot;I'm not so good at love. I'm like a barbed creature. I push everyone I love away.&quot;
He shrugged. &quot;I don't mind you pushing me away if it means you love me, little sister." -- Kristin Cashore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224102-mom-says-each-of-us-has-a-veil-between-ourselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 22:01:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Rebecca Stead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224102-mom-says-each-of-us-has-a-veil-between-ourselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mom says each of us has a veil between ourselves and the rest of the world, like a bride wears on her wedding day, except this kind of veil is invisible. We walk around happily with these invisible veils hanging down over our faces. The world is kind of blurry, and we like it that way. But sometimes our veils are pushed away for a few moments, like there's a wind blowing it from our faces. And when the veil lifts, we can see the world as it really is, just for those few seconds before it settles down again. We see all the beauty, and cruelty, and sadness, and love. But mostly we are happy not to. Some people learn to lift the veil themselves. Then they don't have to depend on the wind anymore." -- Rebecca Stead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58211-i-think-i-ll-move-to-australia</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 01:33:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Judith Viorst]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58211-i-think-i-ll-move-to-australia]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think I'll move to Australia." -- Judith Viorst]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205892-it-s-not-reasonable-to-love-people-who-are-only-going</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 19:10:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Kristin Cashore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205892-it-s-not-reasonable-to-love-people-who-are-only-going]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not reasonable to love people who are only going to die,&quot; she said.
Nash thought about that for a moment, stroking Small's neck with great deliberation, as if the fate of the Dells depended on that smooth, careful movement.
&quot;I have two responses to that,&quot; He said at last. &quot;First, everyone is going to die. Second, love is stupid. It has nothing to do with reason. You love whomever you love. Against all reason I loved my father.&quot; He looked at her keenly. &quot;Did you love yours?&quot;
&quot;Yes,&quot; she whispered.
He stroked Small's nose. &quot;I love you,&quot; he said, &quot;even knowing you'll never have me. And I love my brother, more than I ever realized before you came along. You can't help whom you love, Lady. Nor can you know what it's liable to cause you to do." -- Kristin Cashore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253006-all-right-clara-said-we-have-our-swordsman-so-let-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 19:15:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Kristin Cashore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253006-all-right-clara-said-we-have-our-swordsman-so-let-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All right,&quot; Clara said.  &quot;We have our swordsman, so let's get moving.  Brigan, could you attempt, at least, to make yourself presentable?  I know this is a war, but the rest of us are trying to pretend it's a party." -- Kristin Cashore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/727207-i-want-to-have-the-heart-and-mind-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 20:14:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Kristin Cashore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/727207-i-want-to-have-the-heart-and-mind-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to have the heart and mind of a queen,” she whispered. “I want it more than anything. But I’m only pretending. I can’t find the feeling of it inside me.”

Fire considered her quietly. &lt;i&gt;You want me to look for it inside you.&lt;/i&gt;

“I just want to know,” Bitterblue said. “If it’s there, it would be a great comfort for me to know.”

Fire said, &lt;i&gt;I can tell you already that it’s there.&lt;/i&gt;

“Really?” Bitterblue whispered.

&lt;i&gt;Queen Bitterblue&lt;/i&gt;, Fire said, &lt;i&gt;shall I share with you the feeling of your own strength?&lt;/i&gt;" -- Kristin Cashore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132361-oh-will-she-said-what-can-we-do-whatever-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 10:24:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132361-oh-will-she-said-what-can-we-do-whatever-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh, Will,&quot; she said, &quot;What can we do? Whatever can we do? I want to live with you forever. I want to kiss you and lie down with you and wake up with you every day of my life till I die, years and years and years away. I don't want a memory, just a memory...&quot;

&quot;No,&quot; he said. &quot;Memory's a poor thing to have. It's your own real hair and mouth and arms and eyes and hands I want. I didn't know I could ever love anything so much. Oh, Lyra, I wish this night would never end! If only we could stay here like this, and the world could stop turning, and everyone else could fall into a sleep...&quot;

&quot;Everyone except us! And you and I could live here forever and just love each other.&quot;

&quot;I will love you forever; whatever happens. Till I die and after I die, and when I find my way out of the land of the dead, I'll drift about forever, all my atoms, till I find you again...&quot;

&quot;I'll be looking for you, Will, every moment, every single moment. And when we do find each other again, we'll cling together so tight that nothing and no one'll ever tear us apart. Every atom of me and every atom of you...We'll live in birds and flowers and dragonflies and pin trees and in clouds and in those little specks of light you see floating in sunbeams...And when they use our atoms to make new lives, they won't just be able to take one, they'll have to take two, one of you and one of me, we'll be joined so tight...&quot;

They lay side by side, hand in hand, looking at the sky." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/704359-but-how-can-she-change-a-person-like-that-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 03:06:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Claire Legrand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/704359-but-how-can-she-change-a-person-like-that-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But how can she change a person like that? said Victoria.

She just can. I'd never have thought before, ever, that I could hate music and want to leave it behind, but now--

Lawrence Prewitt, said Victoria. Her voice was shaking, but she stood up and put on such a fierce dazzle that even Donovan seemed to wake up. Don't you dare ever start talking like that again, or when I get out of here, I'll leave you behind with the gofers. Lawrence smiled. I've missed your threats, Vicky." -- Claire Legrand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269187-oh-god-frankie-i-breathe-in-rhythm-with-that-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 11:03:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269187-oh-god-frankie-i-breathe-in-rhythm-with-that-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh God, Frankie, I breathe in rhythm with that man. You think that's not my flesh and blood after all these years?" -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/471506-once-she-made-him-watch-pride-and-prejudice-and-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 07:19:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/471506-once-she-made-him-watch-pride-and-prejudice-and-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once she made him watch Pride and Prejudice and for ages he would re-word Mr Bingley's apology to Jane Bennet, saying, 'I've been an inexplicable fool', for anything from losing his keys to burping out loud. Her reply to anything she wanted to do was Jane Bennet's response to Bingley's marriage proposal, 'A thousand times yes." -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269390-it-s-a-weird-smile-but-it-reaches-his-eyes-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 08:17:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269390-it-s-a-weird-smile-but-it-reaches-his-eyes-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's a weird smile, but it reaches his eyes and I bottle it. And I put it in my ammo pack that's kept right next to my soul and Justine's spirit and Siobhan's hope and Tara's passions. Because if I'm going to wake up one morning and not be able to get out of bed, I'm going to need everything I've got to fight this disease that could be sleeping inside of me." -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217016-this-is-the-best-night-of-my-life-raffy-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 08:18:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217016-this-is-the-best-night-of-my-life-raffy-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is the best night of my life,&quot; Raffy says, crying.
&quot;Raffy, half our House has burnt down,&quot; I say wearily.  &quot;We don't have a kitchen.&quot;
&quot;Why do you always have to be so pessimistic?&quot;  she asks.  &quot;We can double up in our rooms and have a barbecue every night like the Cadets.&quot;
Silently I vow to keep Raffy around for the rest of my life." -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432224-do-you-think-people-have-noticed-that-i-m-around-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 08:19:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432224-do-you-think-people-have-noticed-that-i-m-around-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you think people have noticed that I'm around?&quot;
&quot;I notice when you're not. Does that count?" -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/604105-you-seem-to-have-a-problem-with-me-he-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 19:29:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/604105-you-seem-to-have-a-problem-with-me-he-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You seem to have a problem with me,&quot; he says in typical Griggs fashion.

I can tell he regrets saying it when he is treated to one of Hannah's long cold gazes.

&quot;I think it will be a while before I forgive the trip to Sydney,&quot; she says flatly.

&quot;Fair enough. I think it will be a while before I forgive you for what you put her through over the past six weeks.&quot;

I watch them both and for the first time it occurs to me that I'm no longer flying solo and that I have no intention of pretending that I am. I have an aunt and I have a Griggs and this is what it's like to have connections with people.

&quot;Do you know what?&quot; I ask both of them. &quot;If you don't build a bridge and get over it, I'll never forgive either of you." -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53486-all-the-secrets-of-the-world-are-contained-in-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 00:23:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53486-all-the-secrets-of-the-world-are-contained-in-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All the secrets of the world are contained in books. Read at your own risk." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99095-when-you-get-tired-of-worrying-and-mourning-your-horse</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 10:19:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Shannon Hale]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99095-when-you-get-tired-of-worrying-and-mourning-your-horse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you get tired of worrying and mourning your horse and trying not to be afraid, tell me and I'll do it for you a while so you can shut your eyes and sleep peaceful." -- Shannon Hale]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295283-geric-she-called-he-turned-back-around-what-kind-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 10:20:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Shannon Hale]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295283-geric-she-called-he-turned-back-around-what-kind-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Geric,&quot; she called.
He turned back around.
&quot;What kind of flowers were they?&quot;
&quot;I don't rightly know,&quot; he said. He made faltering gestures with his hands, forming their size and shape from the air. &quot;They were yellow, and smallish, and had lots of petals.&quot;
&quot;Thank you,&quot; she said. &quot;They were beautiful." -- Shannon Hale]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/708681-you-guys-know-about-vampires-you-know-vampires-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 08:27:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Junot Díaz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/708681-you-guys-know-about-vampires-you-know-vampires-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You guys know about vampires? … You know, vampires have no reflections in a mirror? There’s this idea that monsters don’t have reflections in a mirror. And what I’ve always thought isn’t that monsters don’t have reflections in a mirror. It’s that if you want to make a human being into a monster, deny them, at the cultural level, any reflection of themselves. And growing up, I felt like a monster in some ways. I didn’t see myself reflected at all. I was like, “Yo, is something wrong with me? That the whole society seems to think that people like me don’t exist?&quot; And part of what inspired me, was this deep desire that before I died, I would make a couple of mirrors. That I would make some mirrors so that kids like me might see themselves reflected back and might not feel so monstrous for it." -- Junot Díaz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/667447-alas-poor-yorick-he-said-she-heard-mermaids-so-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 07:45:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Diana Wynne Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/667447-alas-poor-yorick-he-said-she-heard-mermaids-so-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alas, poor Yorick!&quot; he said. &quot;She heard mermaids, so it follows that there is something rotten in the state of Denmark. I have caught an everlasting cold, but luckily I am terribly dishonest. I cling to that." -- Diana Wynne Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101464-go-to-bed-you-fool-calcifer-said-sleepily-you-re-drunk</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 07:45:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Diana Wynne Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101464-go-to-bed-you-fool-calcifer-said-sleepily-you-re-drunk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Go to bed, you fool,&quot; Calcifer said sleepily. &quot;You're drunk.&quot;
&quot;Who, me?&quot; said Howl. &quot;I assure you, my friends, I am cone sold stober.&quot; He got up and stalked upstairs, feeling for the wall as if he thought it might escape him unless he kept in touch with it. His bedroom door did escape him." -- Diana Wynne Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130327-typical-i-break-my-neck-trying-to-get-here-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 07:45:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Diana Wynne Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130327-typical-i-break-my-neck-trying-to-get-here-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Typical! I break my neck trying to get here, and I find you peacefully tidying up!" -- Diana Wynne Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143420-i-can-t-believe-i-said-it-out-loud-the-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 21:42:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143420-i-can-t-believe-i-said-it-out-loud-the-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can't believe I said it out loud. The truth doesn't set you free, you know. It makes you feel awkward and embarrassed and defenseless and red in the face and horrified and petrified and vulnerable. But free? I don't feel free. I feel like shit." -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269387-when-i-grow-i-m-going-to-be-my-mother</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 21:42:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269387-when-i-grow-i-m-going-to-be-my-mother]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I grow, I'm going to be my mother." -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/589182-i-think-i-m-a-bit-in-love-with-these-girls</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 21:43:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/589182-i-think-i-m-a-bit-in-love-with-these-girls]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think I'm a bit in love with these girls.  They make me feel giddy.  Like I haven't a care in the world.  Like I'm fearless.

Like I used to be." -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1260723-isn-t-it-nice-the-older-lady-said-leaning-in-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 04:33:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Julia Quinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1260723-isn-t-it-nice-the-older-lady-said-leaning-in-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't it nice,&quot; the older lady said, leaning in so that only Penelope could hear her words, &quot;to discover that we're not exactly what we thought we were?&quot;  

And then she walked away, leaving Penelope wondering if maybe she wasn't quite what she'd thought she was.  

Maybe—just maybe—she was something a little bit more." -- Julia Quinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325491-more-about-howl-sophie-thought-desperately-i-have-to-blacken</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 04:17:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachna add a quote by Diana Wynne Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325491-more-about-howl-sophie-thought-desperately-i-have-to-blacken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["More about Howl? Sophie thought desperately. I have to blacken his name! Her mind was such a blank that for a second it actually seemed to her that Howl had no faults at all. How stupid! 'Well, he's fickle, careless, selfish, and hysterical,' she said. 'Half the time I think he doesn't care what happens to anyone as long as &lt;i&gt;he's&lt;/i&gt; alright--but then I find out how awfully kind he's been to someone. Then I think he's kind just when it suits him--only then I find out he undercharges poor people. I don't know, Your Majesty. He's a mess." -- Diana Wynne Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
