<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1054156-aaron-typographical-era]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1054156-aaron-typographical-era" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 19:49:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42133-tv-and-the-internet-are-good-because-they-keep-stupid</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 19:49:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42133-tv-and-the-internet-are-good-because-they-keep-stupid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["TV and the Internet are good because they keep stupid people from spending too much time out in public." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49829-lists-only-spell-out-the-things-that-can-be-taken</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 22:00:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49829-lists-only-spell-out-the-things-that-can-be-taken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lists only spell out the things that can be taken away from us by moths and rust and thieves. If something is valuable, don't put it in a list. Don't even say the words." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50339-there-is-a-proverbial-saying-chiefly-concerned-with-warning-against</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 14:04:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50339-there-is-a-proverbial-saying-chiefly-concerned-with-warning-against]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a proverbial saying chiefly concerned with warning against too closely calculating the numerical value of un-hatched chicks." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53906-time-ticks-by-we-grow-older-before-we-know-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2008 11:15:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53906-time-ticks-by-we-grow-older-before-we-know-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time ticks by; we grow older. Before we know it, too much time has passed and we've missed the chance to have had other people hurt us. To a younger me this sounded like luck; to an older me this sounds like a quiet tragedy." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63607-anyway-it-seems-to-me-that-the-way-most-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2008 05:32:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63607-anyway-it-seems-to-me-that-the-way-most-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyway, it seems to me that the way most people go on living (I suppose there are a few exceptions), they think that the world of life (or whatever) is this place where everything is (or is supposed to be) basically logical and consistent.... It's like when you put instant rice pudding mix in a bowl in the microwave and push the button, and you take the cover off when it rings, and there you've got rice pudding. I mean, what happens in between the time when you push the switch and when the microwave rings? You can't tell what's going on under the cover. Maybe the instant rice pudding first turns into macaroni gratin in the darkness when nobody's looking and only then turns back into rice pudding. We think it's natural to get rice pudding after we put rice pudding mix in the microwave and the bell rings, but to me that's just a presumption. I would be kind of relieved if, every once in a while, after you put rice pudding mix in the microwave and it rang and you opened the top, you got macaroni gratin." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67170-what-i-will-tell-you-son-of-sons-is-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 03:29:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67170-what-i-will-tell-you-son-of-sons-is-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I will tell you, son of sons, is this: shortly, if not already, you will begin noticing the blackness inside us all. You will develop black secrets and commit black actions. You will be shocked at the insensitivities and transgressions you are capable of, yet you will be unable to stop them. And by the time you are thirty, your friends will all have black secrets, too, but it will be years before you learn exactly *what* their black secrets are. Life at that point will become like throwing a Frisbee in a graveyard; much of the pleasure of your dealings with your friends will stem from the contrast between your sparkling youth and the ink you now know lies at your feet.
Later, as you get to be my age, you will see your friends begin to die, to lose their memories, to see their skins turn wrinkled and sick. You will see the effects of dark secrets making themslves know - via their minds and bodies and via the stories your friends - yes, Harmony, Gaia, Mei-lin, Davidson, and the rest - will begin telling you at three-thirty in the morning as you put iodine on their bruises, arrange for tetanus shots, dial 911, and listen to them cry. The only payback for all of this - for the conversion of their once-young hearts into tar - will be that you will love your friends more, even though they have made you see the universe as an emptier and scarier place - and they will love you more, too." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69882-the-moral-conscience-that-so-many-thoughtless-people-have-offended</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 03:10:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by José Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69882-the-moral-conscience-that-so-many-thoughtless-people-have-offended]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The moral conscience that so many thoughtless people have offended against and many more have rejected, is something that exists and has always existed. It was not an invention of the philosophers of the Quartenary, when the soul was little more than a muddled proposition. With the passing of time, as well as then social evolution and genetic exchange, we ended up putting our conscience in the colour of blood and in the salt of tears, and, as if that were not enough, we made our eyes into a kind of mirror turned inwards, with the result that they often show without reserve what we are verbally trying to deny. Add to this general observation, the particular circumstance that in simple spirits, the remorse caused by committing some evil act often becomes confused with ancestral fears of every kind, and the result will be that the punishment of the prevaricator ends up being, without mercy or pity, twice what he deserved." -- José Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81530-during-the-first-world-war-i-told-her-hitler-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 06:23:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81530-during-the-first-world-war-i-told-her-hitler-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["During the First World War, I told her, Hitler had been a runner, delivering messages between the German trenches, and he was disgusted by seeing his fellow soldiers visit French brothels. To keep the Aryan bloodlines pure,and prevent the spread of venereal disease, he commissioned an inflatable doll that Nazi troops could take into battle. Hitler himself designed the dolls to have blond hair and large breasts. The Allied firebombing of Dresden destroyed the factory before the dolls could ever go into wide distribution." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83421-at-a-certain-point-in-our-lives-when-we-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 06:19:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83421-at-a-certain-point-in-our-lives-when-we-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At a certain point in our lives, when we really need a clear-cut solution, the person who knocks at our door is, more likely than not, a messenger bearing bad news. This isn’t always the case, but from experience I’d say the gloomy reports far outnumber the others. The messenger touches his hand to his cap and looks apologetic, but that does nothing to improve the contents of the message. It isn’t the messenger’s fault. No good to blame him, no good to grab him by the collar and shake him. The messenger is just conscientiously doing the job his boss assigned him. And this boss? That would be none other than our old friend Reality." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85500-okay-he-said-would-i-be-twisting-you-words-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2008 06:42:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Peter Ferry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85500-okay-he-said-would-i-be-twisting-you-words-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Okay,&quot; he said, &quot;would I be twisting you words too much if I said that you are mad at Lydia because she loves you?&quot;
I had to think about that for a while. &quot;I suppose not.  We weren't supposed to fall in love with each other.&quot;
So she's violated your agreement?&quot; Then he wanted to know why Lydia would have ever agreed to such a thing in the first place.  Why would she want to be in a relationship not based on love?  We decided the only reason would be if she was afraid of love.  And if she was no longer afraid of love, wasn't that good?  Didn't it say that she was healthier and more mature?  And why had I ever wanted to be with someone who was neither of these things?  Was I, too, afraid of love?" -- Peter Ferry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87251-in-a-matter-of-a-moment-the-amount-of-sand</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 09:35:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Jose Saragamo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87251-in-a-matter-of-a-moment-the-amount-of-sand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a matter of a moment the amount of sand in the upper part of the hour-glass had dwindled dramatically, the tiny grains were rushing through the opening, each grain more eager to leave then the last, time is just like people, sometimes it’s all it can do to drag itself along, but at others, it runs like a deer and leaps like a young goat, which, when you think about it, is not saying much, since the cheetah is the fastest of all the animals, and yet it has never occurred to anyone to say of another person He runs and jumps like a cheetah, perhaps because that first comparison comes from the magical late middle ages, when gentlemen went deer-hunting and no one had ever seen a cheetah running or even heard of its existence.  Languages are conservative, they always carry their archives with them and hate having to be updated." -- Jose Saragamo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94255-dreams-don-t-come-true-dreams-die-dreams-get-compromised-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 05:34:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94255-dreams-don-t-come-true-dreams-die-dreams-get-compromised-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dreams don't come true.  Dreams die.  Dreams get compromised.  Dreams end up dealing meth in a booth at the back of the Olive Garden.  Dreams choke to death on bay leaves.  Dreams get spleen cancer." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94256-but-even-in-september-thursday-was-a-big-money-night</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 05:37:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Andre Dubus III]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94256-but-even-in-september-thursday-was-a-big-money-night]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But even in September, Thursday was a big money night, seven to eight hundred take-home, and that's what April concentrated on as she drove, Franny's chin starting to loll against her chest—April made herself think of that fat roll of tens and twenties she'd have at closing, how she'd fold it into the front pocket of her jeans then go to the house mom's office off the dressing room and give Tina a hundred before she found Franny in her pj's on Tina's brown vinyl couch, and she'd try not to think of the walls above Tina's desk covered with dancers' schedules and audition Polaroids of naked women, some of them under postcards from girls who came and went." -- Andre Dubus III]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95651-trying-to-exhaust-himself-vaughan-devised-an-endless-almanac-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 07:52:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by J.G. Ballard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95651-trying-to-exhaust-himself-vaughan-devised-an-endless-almanac-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Trying to exhaust himself, Vaughan devised an endless almanac of terrifying wounds and insane collisions: The lungs of elderly men punctured by door-handles; the chests of young women impaled on steering-columns; the cheek of handsome youths torn on the chromium latches of quarter-lights. To Vaughan, these wounds formed the key to a new sexuality, born from a perverse technology. The images of these wounds hung in the gallery of his mind, like exhibits in the museum of a slaughterhouse." -- J.G. Ballard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96279-when-someone-tells-you-they-ve-just-bought-a-house-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 05:46:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96279-when-someone-tells-you-they-ve-just-bought-a-house-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When someone tells you they’ve just bought a house, they might as well tell you they no longer have a personality.  You can immediately assume so many things: that they’re locked into jobs they hate; that they’re broke; that they spend every night watching videos; that they’re fifteen pounds overweight; that they no longer listen to new ideas.  It’s profoundly depressing. " -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96280-what-else-i-also-believe-that-if-someone-comes-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 05:53:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96280-what-else-i-also-believe-that-if-someone-comes-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What else? I also believe that if someone comes up behind you on the freeway and flashes their lights to get you to move into the slow lane, they deserve whatever punishment you dole out to them. I promptly slow down and drive at the same speed as the car beside me so that I can punish Speed Racer for his impertinence.

Actually, it’s not the impertinence I’m punishing him for, it’s that he let other people know what he wanted.

Speed Racer, my friend, never ever let people know what you want. Because if you do, you might as well send them engraved invitations saying, “Hi, this is what I want you to prevent me from ever having." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97382-i-m-kind-of-a-low-key-guy-the-spotlight-doesn-t-suit</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 11:14:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97382-i-m-kind-of-a-low-key-guy-the-spotlight-doesn-t-suit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm kind of a low-key guy.  The spotlight doesn't suit me.  I'm more of a side dish--cole slaw or French fries or a Wham! backup singer." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14904-some-say-it-is-best-not-to-go-near-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 09:22:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Alan Lightman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14904-some-say-it-is-best-not-to-go-near-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some say it is best not to go near the center of time.  Life is a vessel of sadness, but is noble to live life and without time there is no life.  Others disagree.  They would rather have an eternity of contentment, even if that eternity were fixed and frozen, like a butterfly mounted in a case." -- Alan Lightman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98290-you-know-what-i-think-she-says-that-people-s-memories</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 06:16:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98290-you-know-what-i-think-she-says-that-people-s-memories]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know what I think?&quot; she says. &quot;That people's memories are maybe the fuel they burn to stay alive. Whether those memories have any actual importance or not, it doesn't matter as far as the maintenance of life is concerned. They're all just fuel. Advertising fillers in the newspaper, philosophy books, dirty pictures in a magazine, a bundle of ten-thousand-yen bills: when you feed 'em to the fire, they're all just paper. The fire isn't thinking 'Oh, this is Kant,' or 'Oh, this is the Yomiuri evening edition,' or 'Nice tits,' while it burns. To the fire, they're nothing but scraps of paper.  It's the exact same thing. Important memories, not-so-important memories, totally useless memories: there's no distinction--they're all just fuel." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99933-from-a-distance-it-makes-perfect-sense-that-the-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 17:45:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Tom Perrotta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99933-from-a-distance-it-makes-perfect-sense-that-the-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From a distance, it makes perfect sense that the people and the things you think will save you are the very ones that have the power to disappoint you most bitterly, but up close it can hit you as a bewildering surprise." -- Tom Perrotta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87207-talent-was-not-rare-the-ability-to-survive-having-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 08:14:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87207-talent-was-not-rare-the-ability-to-survive-having-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Talent was not rare; the ability to survive having it was." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105147-you-re-alive-bod-that-means-you-have-infinite-potential-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 18:58:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105147-you-re-alive-bod-that-means-you-have-infinite-potential-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're alive, Bod. That means you have infinite potential. You can do anything, make anything, dream anything. If you can change the world, the world will change. Potential. Once you're dead, it's gone. Over. You've made what you've made, dreamed your dream, written your name. You may be buried here, you may even walk. But that potential is finished." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110132-the-junk-merchant-doesn-t-sell-his-product-to-the-consumer</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2008 05:29:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110132-the-junk-merchant-doesn-t-sell-his-product-to-the-consumer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The junk merchant doesn't sell his product to the consumer, he sells the consumer to his product. He does not improve and simplify his merchandise. He degrades and simplifies the client." -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110353-i-don-t-live-in-either-my-past-or-my-future</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 05:39:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110353-i-don-t-live-in-either-my-past-or-my-future]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don’t live in either my past or my future. I’m interested only in the present. If you can concentrate always on the present, you’ll be a happy man. Life will be a party for you, a grand festival, because life is the moment we’re living now." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40826-society-invents-a-spurious-convoluted-logic-tae-absorb-and-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2008 04:52:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Irvine Welsh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40826-society-invents-a-spurious-convoluted-logic-tae-absorb-and-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Society invents a spurious convoluted logic tae absorb and change people whae's behaviour is outside its mainstream. Suppose that ah ken aw the pros and cons, know that ah'm gaunnae huv a short life, am ah sound mind, ectetera, ectetera, but still want tae use smack? They won't let ye dae it. They won't let ye dae it, because it's seen as a sign ay thir ain failure. The fact that ye jist simply choose tae reject whut they huv tae offer. Choose us. Choose life. Choose mortgage payments; choose washing machines; choose cars; choose sitting oan a couch watching mind-numbing and spirit-crushing game shows, stuffing fuckin junk food intae yir mooth. Choose rotting away, pishing and shiteing yersel in a home, a total fuckin embarrassment tae the selfish, fucked-up brats ye've produced. Choose life. Well, ah choose no tae choose life. If the cunts cannae handle that, it's thair fuckin problem. As Harry Launder sais, ah jist intend tae keep right on to the end of the road..." -- Irvine Welsh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115448-ye-see-rab-it-s-due-to-the-way-we-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2008 17:15:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Irvine Welsh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115448-ye-see-rab-it-s-due-to-the-way-we-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ye see, Rab, it's due to the way we feel about our arseholes.  We now believe, as a species, if our soul is located anywhere in our bodies, it's up our arses.  That's where it all goes.  It makes sense.  That's why we're obsessed with anal jokes, anal sex, anal hobbies...the arsehole - not the brain, not space - is the last frontier.  That's what makes us revolutionaries." -- Irvine Welsh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128182-technology-is-crucial-to-civilization-why-because-it-helps-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 06:00:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128182-technology-is-crucial-to-civilization-why-because-it-helps-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Technology is crucial to civilization why?  Because it helps us make our fate.  We don't need God or miracles or the flight of the bumble bee.  But it is also crouched and undecidable.  It can go either way." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134645-lost-opportunities-lost-possibilities-feelings-we-can-never-get-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 05:23:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134645-lost-opportunities-lost-possibilities-feelings-we-can-never-get-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lost opportunities, lost possibilities, feelings we can never get back.  That's part of what it means to be alive.  But inside our heads - at least that's where I imagine it - there's a little room where we store those memories.  A room like the stacks in this library.  And to understand the workings of our own heart we have to keep on making new reference cards.  We have to dust things off every once in awhile, let in fresh air, change the water in the flower vases.  In other words, you'll live forever in your own private library." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136500-the-upshot-was-that-she-lost-her-religion---with</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 07:46:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Jonathan Coe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136500-the-upshot-was-that-she-lost-her-religion---with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The upshot was that she lost her religion - with a vengeance - and walked out on him, taking these three daughters with her. Faith, Hope and Brenda." -- Jonathan Coe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142511-what-not-coins-in-the-bank-does-your-purse-hang</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 05:14:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aaron (Typographical Era)   add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142511-what-not-coins-in-the-bank-does-your-purse-hang]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What, not coins in the bank?  Does your purse hang as flaccid as a gelding's scrotum?" -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
