<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1054762-carrie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1054762-carrie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 03:55:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3583-passion-makes-a-person-stop-eating-sleeping-working-feeling-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 03:55:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3583-passion-makes-a-person-stop-eating-sleeping-working-feeling-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Passion makes a person stop eating, sleeping, working, feeling at peace. A lot of people are frightened because, when it appears, it demolishes all the old things it finds in its path. 

No one wants their life thrown into chaos. That is why a lot of people keep that threat under control, and are somehow capable of sustaining a house or a structure that is already rotten. They are the engineers of the superseded. 

Other people think exactly the opposite: they surrender themselves without a second thought, hoping to find in passion the solutions to all their problems. They make the other person responsible for their happiness and blame them for their possible unhappiness. They are either euphoric because something marvelous has happened or depressed because something unexpected has just ruined everything. 

Keeping passion at bay or surrendering blindly to it - which of these two attitudes is the least destructive? 

I don't know." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105196-how-could-i-be-sleeping-with-this-particular-man-surely</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 03:59:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105196-how-could-i-be-sleeping-with-this-particular-man-surely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How could I be sleeping with this particular man.... Surely only true love could justify my lack of taste." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173710-people-cry-at-weddings-for-the-same-reason-they-cry</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 04:02:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173710-people-cry-at-weddings-for-the-same-reason-they-cry]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People cry at weddings for the same reason they cry at happy endings: because they so desperately want to believe in something they know is not credible." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80642-if-you-want-what-s-in-the-package-you-should-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 04:09:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80642-if-you-want-what-s-in-the-package-you-should-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want what's in the package you should at least know how to get the string off, is what I say." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2011 11:59:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that's what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that is holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life.  

A true soul mate is probably the most important person you'll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake.  But to live with a soul mate forever?  Nah. Too painful.  Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then leave.  

A soul mates purpose is to shake you up, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light can get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you have to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 13:45:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17533-i-carry-your-heart-with-me-i-carry-it-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 13:53:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by E.E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17533-i-carry-your-heart-with-me-i-carry-it-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I carry your heart with me (I carry it in my heart)I am never without it (anywhere
I go you go,my dear; and whatever is done by only me is your doing,my darling)
I fear no fate (for you are my fate,my sweet)I want no world (for beautiful you are my world,my true)
and it's you are whatever a moon has always meant and whatever a sun will always sing is you

here is the deepest secret nobody knows
(here is the root of the root and the bud of the bud and the sky of the sky of a tree called life; which grows
higher than the soul can hope or mind can hide)
and this is the wonder that's keeping the stars apart

I carry your heart (I carry it in my heart)" -- E.E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205260-as-your-girlfriend-you-ve-just-pissed-me-off-as-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 14:14:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by P.C. Cast, Kristin Cast]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205260-as-your-girlfriend-you-ve-just-pissed-me-off-as-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As your girlfriend, you've just pissed me off. As your High Priestess, you've just insulted me. And as someone with a working brain, you've made me wonder if you've lost every bit of your sense. (Zoey Redbird)" -- P.C. Cast, Kristin Cast]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58808-good-night-westley-good-work-sleep-well-i-ll-most-likely</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 14:16:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58808-good-night-westley-good-work-sleep-well-i-ll-most-likely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good night, Westley. Good work. Sleep well. I'll most likely kill you in the morning." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241743-you-re-lying-through-your-fangs-iggy-accused-fang-tried-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 14:23:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by James Patterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241743-you-re-lying-through-your-fangs-iggy-accused-fang-tried-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're lying through your fangs,&quot; Iggy accused.
Fang tried to play innocent--but &quot;innocent Fang&quot; is an oxymoron, so it didn't work." -- James Patterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74917-have-you-ever-lost-yourself-in-a-kiss-i-mean</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 20:20:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Saul Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74917-have-you-ever-lost-yourself-in-a-kiss-i-mean]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever lost yourself in a kiss? I mean pure psychedelic inebriation. Not just lustful petting but transcendental metamorphosis when you became aware that the greatness of this being was breathing into you. Licking the sides and corners of your mouth, like sealing a thousand fleshy envelopes filled with the essence of your passionate being and then opened by the same mouth and delivered back to you, over and over again - the first kiss of the rest of your life. A kiss that confirms that the universe is aligned, that the world's greatest resource is love, and maybe even that God is a woman. With or without a belief in God, all kisses are metaphors decipherable by allocations of time, circumstance, and understanding" -- Saul Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98109-even-when-i-try-to-stir-myself-up-i-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2011 19:09:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Banana Yoshimoto]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98109-even-when-i-try-to-stir-myself-up-i-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even when I try to stir myself up, I just get irritated because I can't make anything come out. And in the middle of the night I lie here thinking about all this. If I don't get back on track somehow, I'm dead, that's the sense I get. There isn't a single strong emotion inside me." -- Banana Yoshimoto]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1978-the-highest-function-of-love-is-that-it-makes-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2011 07:02:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1978-the-highest-function-of-love-is-that-it-makes-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The highest function of love is that it makes the loved one a unique and irreplaceable being." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
