<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1054594-joanne-g]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1054594-joanne-g" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 23:25:38 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204145-books-cats-life-is-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 23:25:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanne G. add a quote by Edward Gorey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204145-books-cats-life-is-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books, Cats, Life is Good." -- Edward Gorey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12747-wherever-you-are-be-all-there-live-to-the-hilt</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 00:35:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanne G. add a quote by Jim Elliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12747-wherever-you-are-be-all-there-live-to-the-hilt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wherever you are, be all there! Live to the hilt every situation you believe to be the will of God." -- Jim Elliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34015-for-age-is-opportunity-no-less-than-youth-itself-though</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 13:36:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanne G. add a quote by Henry Wadsworth Longfellow ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34015-for-age-is-opportunity-no-less-than-youth-itself-though]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For age is opportunity no less Than youth itself, though in another dress, And as the evening twilight fades away The sky is filled with stars, invisible by day." -- Henry Wadsworth Longfellow ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338927-every-year-kansas-watches-the-world-die-civilizations-of-wheat</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 05:36:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanne G. add a quote by N.D. Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338927-every-year-kansas-watches-the-world-die-civilizations-of-wheat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every year, Kansas watches the world die. Civilizations of wheat grow tall and green; they grow old and golden, and then men shaped from the same earth as the crop cut those lives down. And when the grain is threshed, and the dances and festivals have come and gone, then the fields are given over to fire, and the wheat stubble ascends into the Kansas sky, and the moon swells to bursting above a blackened earth.

The fields around Henry, Kansas, had given up their gold and were charred. Some had already been tilled under, waiting for the promised life of new seed. Waiting for winter, and for spring, and another black death.

The harvest had been good. Men, women, boys and girls had found work, and Henry Days had been all hot dogs and laughter, even without Frank Willis's old brown truck in the parade.

The truck was over on the edge of town, by a lonely barn decorated with new No Trespassing signs and a hole in the ground where the Willis house had been in the spring and the early summer. Late summer had now faded into fall, and the pale blue farm house was gone. Kansas would never forget it." -- N.D. Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11796-i-m-on-aslan-s-side-even-if-there-isn-t-any-aslan</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 16:21:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanne G. add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11796-i-m-on-aslan-s-side-even-if-there-isn-t-any-aslan]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm on Aslan's side even if there isn't any Aslan to lead it. I'm going to live as like a Narnian as I can even if there isn't any Narnia." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 20:19:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanne G. add a quote by Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not the critic who counts; not the man who points out how the strong man stumbles, or where the doer of deeds could have done them better. The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the arena, whose face is marred by dust and sweat and blood; who strives valiantly; who errs, who comes short again and again, because there is no effort without error and shortcoming; but who does actually strive to do the deeds; who knows great enthusiasms, the great devotions; who spends himself in a worthy cause; who at the best knows in the end the triumph of high achievement, and who at the worst, if he fails, at least fails while daring greatly, so that his place shall never be with those cold and timid souls who neither know victory nor defeat." -- Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198387-so-the-small-things-came-into-their-own-small-acts</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 16:21:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanne G. add a quote by Alexander McCall Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198387-so-the-small-things-came-into-their-own-small-acts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So the small things came into their own: small acts of helping others, if one could; small ways of making one's own life better: acts of love, acts of tea, acts of laughter. Clever people might laugh at such simplicity, but, she asked herself, what was their own solution?" -- Alexander McCall Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11465-but-better-to-get-hurt-by-the-truth-than-comforted</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 08:17:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanne G. add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11465-but-better-to-get-hurt-by-the-truth-than-comforted]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But better to get hurt by the truth than comforted with a lie." -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34333-reading-a-book-is-like-re-writing-it-for-yourself-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2012 13:19:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanne G. add a quote by Angela Carter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34333-reading-a-book-is-like-re-writing-it-for-yourself-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reading a book is like re-writing it for yourself. You bring to a novel, anything you read, all your experience of the world. You bring your history and you read it in your own terms." -- Angela Carter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6439-if-we-find-ourselves-with-a-desire-that-nothing-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 22:48:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanne G. add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6439-if-we-find-ourselves-with-a-desire-that-nothing-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we find ourselves with a desire that nothing in this world can satisfy, the most probable explanation is that we were made for another world." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4952-everywhere-i-go-i-m-asked-if-i-think-the-university</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2013 18:25:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanne G. add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4952-everywhere-i-go-i-m-asked-if-i-think-the-university]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everywhere I go I'm asked if I think the university stifles writers. My opinion is that they don't stifle enough of them. There's many a best-seller that could have been prevented by a good teacher." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21829-laws-alone-can-not-secure-freedom-of-expression-in-order</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2013 18:24:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanne G. add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21829-laws-alone-can-not-secure-freedom-of-expression-in-order]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Laws alone can not secure freedom of expression; in order that every man present his views without penalty there must be spirit of tolerance in the entire population." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/850598-i-am-only-one-but-i-am-one-i-can-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 12:35:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanne G. add a quote by Edward Everett Hale]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/850598-i-am-only-one-but-i-am-one-i-can-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am only one, but I am one. I can't do everything, but I can do something. The something I ought to do, I can do. And by the grace of God, I will." -- Edward Everett Hale]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1007181-most-people-live-in-fear-of-some-terrible-event-changing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 01:19:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanne G. add a quote by Jamie Weisman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1007181-most-people-live-in-fear-of-some-terrible-event-changing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most people live in fear of some terrible event changing their lives, the death of a loved one or a serious illness. For the chronically ill, this terrible event has already happened, and we have been let in on an amazing secret: You survive. You adapt, and your life changes, but in the end you go on, with whatever compromises you have been forced to make, whatever losses you have been forced to endure. You learn to balance your fears with the simple truth that you must go on living." -- Jamie Weisman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1132256-when-you-are-not-feeling-particularly-friendly-but-know-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 17:03:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanne G. add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1132256-when-you-are-not-feeling-particularly-friendly-but-know-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you are not feeling particularly friendly but know you ought to be, the best thing you can do, very often, is to put on a friendly manner and behave as if you were a nicer person than you actually are. And in a few minutes, as we have all noticed, you will be really feeling friendlier than you were." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
