<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1055270-challis]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1055270-challis" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 12:42:55 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206034-health-is-normal-the-human-body-is-a-self-repairing-self-defending</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 12:42:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Challis add a quote by Joel Fuhrman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206034-health-is-normal-the-human-body-is-a-self-repairing-self-defending]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Health is normal. The human body is a self-repairing, self-defending, self-healing marvel. Disease is relatively difficult to induce, considering the body's powerful immune system. However, this complicated and delicate machinery can be damaged if fed the wrong fuel during the formative years. ... Healthy living with nutritional excellence throughout life can slow the decline of aging. It can prevent the years and years of suffering in ill health that is so common today as people get older and become dependent on medical treatments, drugs, and surgery. Nutritional excellence is the only real fountain of youth." -- Joel Fuhrman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222355-the-incinerate-corpses-shrunk-to-the-size-of-a-child</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 10:45:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Challis add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222355-the-incinerate-corpses-shrunk-to-the-size-of-a-child]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The incinerate corpses shrunk to the size of a child and propped on the bare springs of the seats. Ten thousand dreams ensepulchred within their crozzled hearts." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222358-he-walked-out-into-the-road-and-stood-the-silence</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 10:52:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Challis add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222358-he-walked-out-into-the-road-and-stood-the-silence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He walked out into the road and stood. The silence. The salitter drying from the earth. The mudstained shapes of flooded cities burned to th waterline. At a crossroads a ground set with dolmen stones where the spoken bones of oracles lay moldering. No sound but the wind. What will you say? A living man spoke these lines? He sharpened a quill with his small pen knife to scribe these things in sloe or lampblack? At some reckonable and entabled moment? He is coming to steal my eyes. To seal my mouth with dirt." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
