<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1055889-caitlin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1055889-caitlin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 10:44:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45931-he-thought-he-would-become-accustomed-to-the-idea-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 10:44:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45931-he-thought-he-would-become-accustomed-to-the-idea-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He thought he would become accustomed to the idea, not yet understanding that it is useless to become accustomed to the loss of a father, for it will never happen a second time: might as well leave the wound open. " -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48325-i-don-t-want-enlightenment-i-want-him-sorry-buddha-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 10:00:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by John Burdett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48325-i-don-t-want-enlightenment-i-want-him-sorry-buddha-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't want enlightenment, I want him. Sorry Buddha, I loved him more than you." -- John Burdett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48326-get-dressed-bina-says-and-do-yourself-a-favor-clean</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 10:03:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48326-get-dressed-bina-says-and-do-yourself-a-favor-clean]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Get dressed,' Bina says. 'And do yourself a favor? Clean this shit up. Look at this dump. I can't believe you're living like this. Sweet God, aren't you ashamed of yourself?'

     Once Bina Gelbfish believed in Meyer Landsman. Or she believed from the moment she met him, that there was a sense in that meeting, that some detectable intention lay behind their marriage. They were twisted like a pair of chromosomes, of course they were, but where Landsman saw in that twisting together only a tangle, a chance snarling of lines, Bina saw the hand of the Maker of Knots. And for her faith, Landsman repaid her with his faith in Nothing itself.

     'Only every time I see your face,' Landsman says." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48327-like-most-policemen-landsman-sails-double-hulled-against-tragedy-stabilized-against</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 10:04:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48327-like-most-policemen-landsman-sails-double-hulled-against-tragedy-stabilized-against]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like most policemen, Landsman sails double-hulled against tragedy, stabilized against heave and storm. It's the shallows he has to worry about, the hairline fissures, the little freaks of torque. The memory of that summer, for example, or the thought that he had long since exhausted the patience of a kid who once would have waited a thousand years to spend an hour with him shooting cans off a fence with an air rifle. The sight of the Longhouse breaks some small, as yet unbroken facet of Landman's heart. All of the things they made, during their minute in this corner of the map, dissolved in brambles of salmonberry and oblivion." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48328-every-messiah-fails-the-moment-he-tries-to-redeem-himself</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 10:05:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48328-every-messiah-fails-the-moment-he-tries-to-redeem-himself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every Messiah fails, the moment he tries to redeem himself. " -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50361-but-roberto-already-knew-what-the-jesuit-s-real-objection-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 14:56:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50361-but-roberto-already-knew-what-the-jesuit-s-real-objection-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But Roberto already knew what the Jesuit's real objection would be. Like that of the abbe on that evening of the duel when Saint-Savin provoked him: If there are infinite worlds, the Redemption can no longer have any meaning, and we are obliged either to imagine infinite Calvaries or to look on our terrestrial flowerbed as a priveleged spot of the Cosmos, on which God permitted His Son to descend and free us from sin, while the other worlds were not granted this grace--to the discredit of His infinite goodness. " -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50363-into-this-wild-abyss-the-womb-of-nature-and-perhaps</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 15:07:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by John Milton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50363-into-this-wild-abyss-the-womb-of-nature-and-perhaps]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Into this wild Abyss/ The womb of Nature, and perhaps her grave--/ Of neither sea, nor shore, nor air, nor fire,/ But all these in their pregnant causes mixed/ Confusedly, and which thus must ever fight,/ Unless the Almighty Maker them ordain/ His dark materials to create more worlds,--/ Into this wild Abyss the wary Fiend/ Stood on the brink of Hell and looked a while,/ Pondering his voyage; for no narrow frith/ He had to cross. " -- John Milton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50899-we-can-only-add-to-the-world-where-we-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 08:59:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50899-we-can-only-add-to-the-world-where-we-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...we can only add to the world, where we believe it ends, more parts similar to those we already know (an expanse made again and always of water and land, stars and skies)." -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50902-here-he-was-holding-the-clear-proof-of-the-existence</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 09:06:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50902-here-he-was-holding-the-clear-proof-of-the-existence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here he was holding the clear proof of the existence of other skies, but at the same time without having to ascend beyond the celestial spheres, for he intuited many worlds in a piece of coral. Was there any need to calculate the number of forms which the atoms of the Universe could create--burning at the stake all those who said their number was not finite--when it sufficed to meditate for years on one of these marine objects to realize how the deviation of a single atom, whether willed by God or prompted by Chance, could generate inconceivable Milky Ways?" -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43825-no-he-could-be-ruined-again-and-again-by-hope</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 09:09:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43825-no-he-could-be-ruined-again-and-again-by-hope]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No; he could be ruined again and again by hope, but he would never be capable of belief." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17950-when-men-stop-believing-in-god-it-isn-t-that-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 09:12:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17950-when-men-stop-believing-in-god-it-isn-t-that-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When men stop believing in God, it isn't that they then believe in nothing: they believe in everything." -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29925-it-s-the-only-condition-i-know-bitter-love-loneliness-contempt</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 09:18:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29925-it-s-the-only-condition-i-know-bitter-love-loneliness-contempt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's the only condition I know. Bitter Love, Loneliness, contempt for corruption, blind hope. It's where I live. A permanent state of bereavement. This is nothing new." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9081-to-absent-friends-lost-loves-old-gods-and-the-season</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 09:20:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9081-to-absent-friends-lost-loves-old-gods-and-the-season]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To absent friends, lost loves, old gods, and the season of mists; and may each and every one of us always give the devil his due." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8298-so-what-i-want-to-know-is-why-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 09:22:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8298-so-what-i-want-to-know-is-why-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So what I want to know is why it is that I can no longer find you, in my mind. You are still there, just, but you are there like a ghost, a will o' the wisp. Not long ago you burned--your heart burned--in my mind like silver fire. But after that night in the inn it became patchy and dim, and now it is not there at all.&quot;

&quot;Could it be that the heart that you seek is no longer my own? I have given my heart to another.&quot;

&quot;The boy? The one in the inn? With the unicorn?&quot;

&quot;Yes.&quot;

&quot;You should have let me take it back then, for my sisters and me. We could have been young again, well into the next age of the world. Your boy will break it, or waste it, or lose it. They all do.&quot;

&quot;Nonetheless, he has my heart. I hope your sisters will not be too hard on you, when you return to them without it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/889-the-sky-above-the-port-was-the-color-of-television</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 09:30:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by William Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/889-the-sky-above-the-port-was-the-color-of-television]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sky above the port was the color of television, tuned to a dead channel." -- William Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8526-memories-warm-you-up-from-the-inside-but-they-also</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 09:30:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8526-memories-warm-you-up-from-the-inside-but-they-also]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Memories warm you up from the inside. But they also tear you apart." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38086-the-sky-grew-darker-painted-blue-on-blue-one-stroke</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 09:32:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38086-the-sky-grew-darker-painted-blue-on-blue-one-stroke]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sky grew darker, painted blue on blue, one stroke at a time, into deeper and deeper shades of night." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4739-i-often-recall-these-words-when-i-am-writing-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 09:33:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4739-i-often-recall-these-words-when-i-am-writing-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I often recall these words when I am writing, and I think to myself, “It’s true. There aren’t any new words. Our job is to give new meanings and special overtones to absolutely ordinary words.” I find the thought reassuring. It means that vast, unknown stretches still lie before us, fertile territories just waiting for us to cultivate them." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49488-so-that-s-how-we-live-our-lives-no-matter-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 09:35:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49488-so-that-s-how-we-live-our-lives-no-matter-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So that's how we live our lives. No matter how deep and fatal the loss, no matter how important the thing that's stolen from us--that's snatched right out of our hands--even if we are left completely changed, with only the outer layer of skin from before, we continue to play out our lives this way, in silence. We draw ever nearer to the end of our allotted span of time, bidding it farewell as it trails off behind. Repeating, often adroitly, the endless deeds of the everyday. Leaving behind a feeling of immeasurable emptiness." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 09:36:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes fate is like a small sandstorm that keeps changing directions. You change direction but the sandstorm chases you. You turn again, but the storm adjusts. Over and over you play this out, like some ominous dance with death just before dawn. Why? Because this storm isn't something that blew in from far away, something that has nothing to do with you. This storm is you. Something &lt;i&gt;inside&lt;/i&gt; of you. So all you can do is give in to it, step right inside the storm, closing your eyes and plugging up your ears so the sand doesn't get in, and walk through it, step by step. There's no sun there, no moon, no direction, no sense of time. Just fine white sand swirling up into the sky like pulverized bones. That's the kind of sandstorm you need to imagine.

An you really will have to make it through that violent, metaphysical, symbolic storm. No matter how metaphysical or symbolic it might be, make no mistake about it: it will cut through flesh like a thousand razor blades. People will bleed there, and &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; will bleed too. Hot, red blood. You'll catch that blood in your hands, your own blood and the blood of others.

And once the storm is over you won't remember how you made it through, how you managed to survive. You won't even be sure, in fact, whether the storm is really over. But one thing is certain. When you come out of the storm you won't be the same person who walked in. That's what this storm's all about." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2755-the-man-in-black-fled-across-the-desert-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 09:36:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2755-the-man-in-black-fled-across-the-desert-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man in black fled across the desert, and the gunslinger followed." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50914-living-the-same-sorrows-three-times-was-a-suffering-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 10:12:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50914-living-the-same-sorrows-three-times-was-a-suffering-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...living the same sorrows three times was a suffering, but it was a suffering to relive even the same joys. The joy of life is born from feeling, whether it be joy or grief, always of short duration, and woe to those who know they will enjoy eternal bliss." -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50927-i-am-not-i-who-thinks-but-i-am-the-void</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 11:39:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50927-i-am-not-i-who-thinks-but-i-am-the-void]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...I am not I who thinks,but I am the Void, or extension, that thinks me. And so this composite is an accident, in which Void and extension linger for the blink of an eye, to be able afterwards to return to thinking otherwise. In this great Void of the Void, the one thing that truly is, is the history of this evolution in numberless transitory compositions...Compositions of what? Of the one great Nothingness, which is the substance of the whole.

Substance governed by a majestic necessity, which leads it to create and destroy worlds, to weave our pale lives. I must accept this, succeed in loving this Necessity, return to it, and bow to its future will, for this is the condition of Happiness. Only by accepting its law will I find my freedom. To flow back into It will be Salvation, fleeing from passions into the sole passion, the Intellectual Love of God. 

If I truly succeeded in understanding this, I would be the one man who has found the True Philosophy, and I would know everything about the God that is hidden. But who would have the heart to go about the world and proclaim such a philosophy? This is the secret I will carry with me to my grave, in the Antipodes." -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50932-we-never-cease-hoping--and-thus-did-our-judge-condemn-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 11:50:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50932-we-never-cease-hoping--and-thus-did-our-judge-condemn-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...we never cease hoping--and thus did our Judge condemn us to suffer in saecula.'

Ferrante asked: 'But what is it that you hope for?'

You might as well ask what you will hope for yourself. ...You will hope that a wisp of wind, the slightest swell of the tide, the arrival of a single hungry leech, can return us, atom by atom, to the great Void of the Universe, where we would somehow again participate in the cycle of life." -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56426-but-there-was-always-a-shortfall-wasn-t-there-between-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2008 09:26:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56426-but-there-was-always-a-shortfall-wasn-t-there-between-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But there was always a shortfall, wasn't there? Between the match that the Holy One, blessed be He, envisioned and the reality of the situation under the chuppah. Between commandment and observance, heaven and earth, husband and wife, Zion and Jew. They called that shortfall 'the world.' Only when Messiah came would the breach be closed, all separations, distinctions, and distances collapsed. Until then, thanks be unto His Name, sparks, bright sparks, might leap across the gap, as between electric poles. And we must be grateful for their momentary light." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56433-but-the-boy-had-a-gift-and-it-was-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2008 09:45:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56433-but-the-boy-had-a-gift-and-it-was-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the boy had a gift. And it was in the nature of a gift that it be endlessly given. " -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56775-landsman-recognizes-the-expression-on-dick-s-face-the-face-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 07:40:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56775-landsman-recognizes-the-expression-on-dick-s-face-the-face-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Landsman recognizes the expression on Dick's face...The face of a man who feels he was born into the wrong world. A mistake has been made; he is not where he belongs. Every so often he feels his heart catch, like a kite on a telephone wire, on something that seems to promise him a home in the world or a means of getting there. An American car manufactured in his far-off boyhood, say, or a motorcycle that once belonged to the future king of England, or the face of a woman worthier than himself of being loved." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56784-the-exaltation-of-understanding-then-understanding-s-bottomless-regret</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 08:44:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56784-the-exaltation-of-understanding-then-understanding-s-bottomless-regret]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The exaltation of understanding; then understanding's bottomless regret." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56796-bina-rolls-her-eyes-hands-on-her-hips-glances-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 09:15:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56796-bina-rolls-her-eyes-hands-on-her-hips-glances-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bina rolls her eyes, hands on her hips, glances at the door. Then she comes over and drops her bag and plops down beside him. How many times, he wonders, can she have enough of him, already, and still have not quite enough?" -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59032-landsman-doesn-t-buy-that-bina-never-stopped-wanting-to-redeem</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 11:04:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caitlin add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59032-landsman-doesn-t-buy-that-bina-never-stopped-wanting-to-redeem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...Landsman doesn't buy that. Bina never stopped wanting to redeem the world. She just let the world she was trying to redeem get smaller and smaller until at one point, it could be bounded in the hat of a hopeless policeman." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
