<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1056326-mtbear-tolbert]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1056326-mtbear-tolbert" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 14:57:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9187-those-who-know-do-not-speak-those-who-speak-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 14:57:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtbear add a quote by Lao Tsu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9187-those-who-know-do-not-speak-those-who-speak-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who know do not speak. Those who speak do not know." -- Lao Tsu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103083-wise-men-have-regarded-the-earth-as-a-tragedy-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2008 19:07:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtbear add a quote by Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103083-wise-men-have-regarded-the-earth-as-a-tragedy-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wise men have regarded the earth as a tragedy, a farce, even an illusionist's trick; but all, if they are truly wise, and not merely intellectual rapists, recognize that it is certainly some kind of stage in which we all play roles, most of us being very poorly coached and totally unrehearsed before the curtain rises.  Is it too much if I ask, tentatively, that we agree to look upon it as a circus, a touring carnival wandering about the sun for a record season of four billion years and producing new monsters and miracles, hoaxes and bloody mishaps, wonders and blunders, but never quite entertaining the customers well enough to prevent them from leaving, one by one, and returning to their homes for a long and bored winter's sleep under the dust?" -- Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12871-when-the-going-gets-weird-the-weird-turn-professional</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 08:19:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtbear add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12871-when-the-going-gets-weird-the-weird-turn-professional]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the going gets weird, the weird turn professional." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12051-a-human-being-should-be-able-to-change-a-diaper</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 08:20:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtbear add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12051-a-human-being-should-be-able-to-change-a-diaper]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A human being should be able to change a diaper, plan an invasion, butcher a hog, conn a ship, design a building, write a sonnet, balance accounts, build a wall, set a bone, comfort the dying, take orders, give orders, cooperate, act alone, solve equations, analyze a new problem, pitch manure, program a computer, cook a tasty meal, fight efficiently, die gallantly. Specialization is for insects." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58278-the-universe-is-an-intelligence-test</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 08:26:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtbear add a quote by Timothy Leary]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58278-the-universe-is-an-intelligence-test]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The universe is an intelligence test." -- Timothy Leary]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1935-quotation-is-a-serviceable-substitute-for-wit</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 08:31:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtbear add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1935-quotation-is-a-serviceable-substitute-for-wit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Quotation is a serviceable substitute for wit." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50687-toto-i-have-a-feeling-we-re-not-in-kansas-anymore</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 15:00:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtbear add a quote by L. Frank Baum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50687-toto-i-have-a-feeling-we-re-not-in-kansas-anymore]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Toto, I have a feeling we're not in Kansas anymore." -- L. Frank Baum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1074-strange-memories-on-this-nervous-night-in-las-vegas-five</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 15:30:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtbear add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1074-strange-memories-on-this-nervous-night-in-las-vegas-five]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Strange memories on this nervous night in Las Vegas. Five years later? Six? It seems like a lifetime, or at least a Main Era—the kind of peak that never comes again. San Francisco in the middle sixties was a very special time and place to be a part of. Maybe it meant something. Maybe not, in the long run . . . but no explanation, no mix of words or music or memories can touch that sense of knowing that you were there and alive in that corner of time and the world. Whatever it meant. . . .

History is hard to know, because of all the hired bullshit, but even without being sure of “history” it seems entirely reasonable to think that every now and then the energy of a whole generation comes to a head in a long fine flash, for reasons that nobody really understands at the time—and which never explain, in retrospect, what actually happened.

My central memory of that time seems to hang on one or five or maybe forty nights—or very early mornings—when I left the Fillmore half-crazy and, instead of going home, aimed the big 650 Lightning across the Bay Bridge at a hundred miles an hour wearing L. L. Bean shorts and a Butte sheepherder's jacket . . . booming through the Treasure Island tunnel at the lights of Oakland and Berkeley and Richmond, not quite sure which turn-off to take when I got to the other end (always stalling at the toll-gate, too twisted to find neutral while I fumbled for change) . . . but being absolutely certain that no matter which way I went I would come to a place where people were just as high and wild as I was: No doubt at all about that. . . .

There was madness in any direction, at any hour. If not across the Bay, then up the Golden Gate or down 101 to Los Altos or La Honda. . . . You could strike sparks anywhere. There was a fantastic universal sense that whatever we were doing was right, that we were winning. . . .

And that, I think, was the handle—that sense of inevitable victory over the forces of Old and Evil. Not in any mean or military sense; we didn’t need that. Our energy would simply prevail. There was no point in fighting—on our side or theirs. We had all the momentum; we were riding the crest of a high and beautiful wave. . . .

So now, less than five years later, you can go up on a steep hill in Las Vegas and look West, and with the right kind of eyes you can almost see the high-water mark—that place where the wave finally broke and rolled back." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/890-no-wife-no-horse-no-mustache</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2009 08:53:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtbear add a quote by Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/890-no-wife-no-horse-no-mustache]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No wife, no horse, no mustache" -- Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123509-think-for-yourself-question-authority</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 18:40:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtbear add a quote by Timothy Leary]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123509-think-for-yourself-question-authority]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Think for yourself.  Question authority." -- Timothy Leary]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 18:41:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtbear add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 18:42:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtbear add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71-the-fool-doth-think-he-is-wise-but-the-wise</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 18:43:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtbear add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71-the-fool-doth-think-he-is-wise-but-the-wise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fool doth think he is wise, but the wise man knows himself to be a fool." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19051-politics-is-the-art-of-looking-for-trouble-finding-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 18:45:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtbear add a quote by Groucho Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19051-politics-is-the-art-of-looking-for-trouble-finding-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Politics is the art of looking for trouble, finding it everywhere, diagnosing it incorrectly and applying the wrong remedies." -- Groucho Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50980-i-don-t-believe-anything-but-i-have-many-suspicions</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 07:24:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtbear add a quote by Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50980-i-don-t-believe-anything-but-i-have-many-suspicions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't believe anything, but I have many suspicions." -- Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
