<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/106419-julie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/106419-julie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 20:46:29 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9180-stood-in-firelight-sweltering-bloodstain-on-chest-like-map-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 20:46:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9180-stood-in-firelight-sweltering-bloodstain-on-chest-like-map-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stood in firelight, sweltering. Bloodstain on chest like map of violent new continent. Felt cleansed. Felt dark planet turn under my feet and knew what cats know that makes them scream like babies in night.

Looked at sky through smoke heavy with human fat and God was not there. The cold, suffocating dark goes on forever and we are alone. Live our lives, lacking anything better to do. Devise reason later. Born from oblivion; bear children, hell-bound as ourselves, go into oblivion. There is nothing else.

Existence is random. Has no pattern save what we imagine after staring at it for too long. No meaning save what we choose to impose. This rudderless world is not shaped by vague metaphysical forces. It is not God who kills the children. Not fate that butchers them or destiny that feeds them to the dogs. It’s us. Only us. Streets stank of fire. The void breathed hard on my heart, turning its illusions to ice, shattering them. Was reborn then, free to scrawl own design on this morally blank world.

Was Rorschach.

Does that answer your Questions, Doctor?" -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148834-a-man-cannot-realize-that-above-such-shattered-bodies-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 14:16:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Erich Maria Remarque]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148834-a-man-cannot-realize-that-above-such-shattered-bodies-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man cannot realize that above such shattered bodies there are still human faces in which life goes its daily round. And this is only one hospital, a single station; there are hundreds of thousands in Germany, hundreds of thousands in France, hundreds of thousands in Russia. How senseless is everything that can ever be written, done, or thought, when such things are possible. It must be all lies and of no account when the culture of a thousand years could not prevent this stream of blood being poured out, these torture chambers in their hundreds of thousands. A hospital alone shows what war is." -- Erich Maria Remarque]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2638-both-destiny-s-kisses-and-its-dope-slaps-illustrate-an-individual-person-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2009 19:48:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2638-both-destiny-s-kisses-and-its-dope-slaps-illustrate-an-individual-person-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Both destiny's kisses and its dope-slaps illustrate an individual person's basic personal powerlessness over the really meaningful events in his life: i.e. almost nothing important that ever happens to you happens because you engineer it.  Destiny has no beeper; destiny always leans trenchcoated out of an alley with some sort of Psst that you usually can't even hear because you're in such a rush to or from something important you've tried to engineer." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
