<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/107024-george]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/107024-george" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 12:49:58 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/741-if-you-could-only-love-enough-you-could-be-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 12:49:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Emmet Fox]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/741-if-you-could-only-love-enough-you-could-be-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you could only love enough, you could be the most powerful person in the world." -- Emmet Fox]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32234-seven-deadly-sins-wealth-without-work-pleasure-without-conscience-science</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2013 12:53:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32234-seven-deadly-sins-wealth-without-work-pleasure-without-conscience-science]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Seven Deadly Sins

Wealth without work
Pleasure without conscience
Science without humanity
Knowledge without character
Politics without principle
Commerce without morality
Worship without sacrifice." -- Mahatma Gandhi ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2105-what-i-am-is-good-enough-if-i-would-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2013 21:56:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Carl R. Rogers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2105-what-i-am-is-good-enough-if-i-would-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I am is good enough if I would only be it openly." -- Carl R. Rogers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309485-nobody-tells-this-to-people-who-are-beginners-i-wish</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2013 16:57:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Ira Glass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309485-nobody-tells-this-to-people-who-are-beginners-i-wish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody tells this to people who are beginners, I wish someone told me. All of us who do creative work, we get into it because we have good taste. But there is this gap. For the first couple years you make stuff, it’s just not that good. It’s trying to be good, it has potential, but it’s not. But your taste, the thing that got you into the game, is still killer. And your taste is why your work disappoints you. A lot of people never get past this phase, they quit. Most people I know who do interesting, creative work went through years of this. We know our work doesn’t have this special thing that we want it to have. We all go through this. And if you are just starting out or you are still in this phase, you gotta know its normal and the most important thing you can do is do a lot of work. Put yourself on a deadline so that every week you will finish one story. It is only by going through a volume of work that you will close that gap, and your work will be as good as your ambitions. And I took longer to figure out how to do this than anyone I’ve ever met. It’s gonna take awhile. It’s normal to take awhile. You’ve just gotta fight your way through." -- Ira Glass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222733-always-say-yes-to-the-present-moment-what-could-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 21:34:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222733-always-say-yes-to-the-present-moment-what-could-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Always say “yes” to the present moment. What could be more futile, more insane, than to create inner resistance to what already is? what could be more insane than to oppose life itself, which is now and always now? Surrender to what is. Say “yes” to life — and see how life suddenly starts working for you rather than against you." -- Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24667-action-expresses-priorities</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 19:26:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24667-action-expresses-priorities]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Action expresses priorities." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/375347-do-not-be-too-timid-and-squeamish-about-your-actions</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 09:28:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/375347-do-not-be-too-timid-and-squeamish-about-your-actions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not be too timid and squeamish about your actions.  All life is an experiment.  The more experiments you make the better.  What if they are a little coarse and you may get your coat soiled or torn?  What if you do fail, and get fairly rolled in the dirt once or twice?  Up again, you shall never be so afraid of a tumble." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/759-at-the-end-of-life-we-will-not-be-judged</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 12:21:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/759-at-the-end-of-life-we-will-not-be-judged]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the end of life we will not be judged by how many diplomas we have received, how much money we have made, how many great things we have done.
We will be judged by &quot;I was hungry, and you gave me something to eat, I was naked and you clothed me. I was homeless, and you took me in." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11416-the-best-way-to-find-yourself-is-to-lose-yourself</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 10:32:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11416-the-best-way-to-find-yourself-is-to-lose-yourself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173494-how-many-ills-how-many-infirmities-does-man-owe-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 13:17:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Allan Kardec]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173494-how-many-ills-how-many-infirmities-does-man-owe-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How many ills, how many infirmities, does man owe to his excesses, his ambition – in a word, to the indulgence of his various passions! He who should live soberly in all respects, who should never run into excesses of any kind, who should be always simple in his tastes, modest in his desires, would escape a large proportion of the tribulations of human life. It is the same with regard to spirit-life, the sufferings of which are always the consequence of the manner in which a spirit has lived upon the earth. In that life undoubtedly he will no longer suffer from gout or rheumatism; but his wrong-doing down here will cause him to experience other sufferings no less painful. We have seen that those sufferings are the result of the links which exist between a spirit and matter; that the more completely he is freed from the influence of matter – in other words, the more dematerialized he is – the fewer are the painful sensations experienced by him. It depends, therefore, on each of us to free ourselves from the influence of matter by our action in this present life. Man possesses free-will, and, consequently, the power of electing to do or not to do. Let him conquer his animal passions; let him rid himself of hatred, envy, jealousy, pride; let him throw off the yoke of selfishness; let him purify his soul by cultivating noble sentiments; let him do good; let him attach to the things of this world only the degree of importance which they deserve – and he will, even under his present corporeal envelope, have effected his purification, and achieved his deliverance from the influence of matter, which will cease for him on his quitting that envelope. For such a one the remembrance of physical sufferings endured by him in the life he has quitted has nothing painful, and produces no disagreeable impression, because they affected his body only, and left no trace in his soul. He is happy to be relieved from them; and the calmness of a good conscience exempts him from all moral suffering." -- Allan Kardec]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14132-cultivate-the-habit-of-being-grateful-for-every-good-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2014 13:34:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14132-cultivate-the-habit-of-being-grateful-for-every-good-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cultivate the habit of being grateful for every good thing that comes to you, and to give thanks continuously. And because all things have contributed to your advancement, you should include all things in your gratitude." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7777-if-you-think-you-are-too-small-to-make-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 15:27:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by The Dalai Lama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7777-if-you-think-you-are-too-small-to-make-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you think you are too small to make a difference, try sleeping with a mosquito." -- The Dalai Lama]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
