<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1075773-skrot]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1075773-skrot" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 14:37:46 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127733-there-s-a-book-here-in-which-i-read-about-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 14:37:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Skrot add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127733-there-s-a-book-here-in-which-i-read-about-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There’s a book here in which I read about the trial of a Jew, who took a child of four years old and cut off the fingers from both hands, and then crucified him on the wall, hammered nails into him and crucified him, and afterwards, when he was tried, he said that the child died soon, within four hours. That was ‘soon’! He said the child moaned, kept on moaning and he stood admiring it. That’s nice!”

“Nice?”

“Nice; I sometimes imagine that it was I who crucified him. He would hang there moaning and I would sit opposite him eating pineapple compote. I am awfully fond of pineapple compote. Do you like it?”

Alyosha looked at her in silence. Her pale, sallow face was suddenly contorted, her eyes burned.

“You know, when I read about that Jew I shook with sobs all night. I kept fancying how the little thing cried and moaned (a child of four years old understands, you know), and all the while the thought of pineapple compote haunted me. In the morning I wrote a letter to a certain person, begging him particularly to come and see me. He came and I suddenly told him all about the child and the pineapple compote. All about it, all, and said that it was nice. He laughed and said it really was nice. Then he got up and went away. He was only here five minutes. Did he despise me? Did he despise me? Tell me, tell me, Alyosha, did he despise me or not?” She sat up on the couch, with flashing eyes." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127731-by-the-way-a-bulgarian-i-met-lately-in-moscow</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 14:38:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Skrot add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127731-by-the-way-a-bulgarian-i-met-lately-in-moscow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By the way, a Bulgarian I met lately in Moscow,” Ivan went on, seeming not to hear his brother’s words, “told me about the crimes committed by Turks and Circassians in all parts of Bulgaria through fear of a general rising of the Slavs. They burn villages, murder, outrage women and children, they nail their prisoners by the ears to the fences, leave them so till morning, and in the morning they hang them — all sorts of things you can’t imagine. People talk sometimes of bestial cruelty, but that’s a great injustice and insult to the beasts; a beast can never be so cruel as a man, so artistically cruel. The tiger only tears and gnaws, that’s all he can do. He would never think of nailing people by the ears, even if he were able to do it. These Turks took a pleasure in torturing children, too; cutting the unborn child from the mother's womb, and tossing babies up in the air and catching them on the points of their bayonets before their mothers’ eyes. Doing it before the mothers’ eyes was what gave zest to the amusement. Here is another scene that I thought very interesting. Imagine a trembling mother with her baby in her arms, a circle of invading Turks around her. They’ve planned a diversion: they pet the baby, laugh to make it laugh. They succeed, the baby laughs. At that moment a Turk points a pistol four inches from the baby’s face. The baby laughs with glee, holds out its little hands to the pistol, and he pulls the trigger in the baby’s face and blows out its brains. Artistic, wasn’t it? By the way, Turks are particularly fond of sweet things, they say." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132875-the-infinite-exists-it-is-there-if-the-infinite-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 19:39:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Skrot add a quote by Victor Hugo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132875-the-infinite-exists-it-is-there-if-the-infinite-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The infinite exists. It is there. If the infinite had no &lt;i&gt;me,&lt;/i&gt; the &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; would be its limit; it would not be the infinite; in other words, it would not be. But it is. Then it has a &lt;i&gt;me.&lt;/i&gt; This &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; of the infinite is God." -- Victor Hugo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157047-posterity-was-a-vaudeville-joke-audible-only-to-those-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 10:46:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Skrot add a quote by Roberto Bolano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157047-posterity-was-a-vaudeville-joke-audible-only-to-those-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...posterity was a vaudeville joke audible only to those with front-row seats..." -- Roberto Bolano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188789-from-the-first-day-i-met-his-daughter-all-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 10:49:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Skrot add a quote by Peter Matthiessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188789-from-the-first-day-i-met-his-daughter-all-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From the first day I met his daughter, all I could think about was snuffling up under that sweet dimity like some bad old bear, just crawling up into that honeycomb, nose twitching, and never come out of there till early spring. Think that’s disgusting? Dammit, I do, too, but that’s the way male animals are made. Those peculiar delights were created to entrap us, and anybody who disapproves can take it up with God.

In their wondrous capacity of knowing the Lord’s mind, churchly folks will tell you that He would purely hate to hear such dirty talk. My idea is, He wouldn’t mind it half so much as they would have us think, because even according to their own queer creed, we are God’s handiwork, created in His image, lust, piss, shit, and all. Without that magnificent Almighty lust that we mere mortals dare to call a sin, there wouldn’t be any more mortals, and God’s grand design for the human race, if He exists and if He ever had one, would turn to dust, and dust unto dust, forever and amen. Other creatures would step up and take over, realizing that man was too weak and foolish to properly reproduce himself. I nominate hogs to inherit the Earth, because hogs love to eat any old damned thing God sets in front of them, and they’re ever so grateful for God’s green earth even when it’s all rain and mud, and they just plain adore to feed and fuck and frolic and fulfill God’s holy plan. For all we know, it’s hogs which are created in God’s image, who’s to say?" -- Peter Matthiessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511872-waves-of-desert-heat</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 16:59:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Skrot add a quote by Ryan Boudinot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511872-waves-of-desert-heat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[". . . waves of desert heat . . . I must’ve passed out, because when I woke up I was shivering and stars wheeled above a purple horizon. . . . Then the sun came up, casting long shadows. . . . I heard a vehicle coming. Something coming from far away, gradually growing louder. There was the sound of an engine, rocks under tires. . . . Finally it reached me, the door opened, and Dirk Bickle stepped out. . . .

But anyway so Bickle said, “Miracles, Luke. Miracles were once the means to convince people to abandon reason for faith. But the miracles stopped during the rise of the neocortex and its industrial revolution. Tell me, if I could show you one miracle, would you come with me and join Mr. Kirkpatrick?”

I passed out again, and came to. He was still crouching beside me. He stood up, walked over to the battered refrigerator, and opened the door. Vapor poured out and I saw it was stocked with food. Bickle hunted around a bit, found something wrapped in paper, and took a bottle of beer from the door. Then he closed the fridge, sat down on the old tire, and unwrapped what looked like a turkey sandwich.

He said, “You could explain the fridge a few ways. One, there’s some hidden outlet, probably buried in the sand, that leads to a power source far away. I figure there’d have to be at least twenty miles of cable involved before it connected to the grid. That’s a lot of extension cord. Or, this fridge has some kind of secret battery system. If the empirical details didn’t bear this out, if you thoroughly studied the refrigerator and found neither a connection to a distant power source nor a battery, you might still argue that the fridge had some super-insulation capabilities and that the food inside had been able to stay cold since it was dragged out here. But say this explanation didn’t pan out either, and you observed the fridge staying the same temperature week after week while you opened and closed it. Then you’d start to wonder if it was powered by some technology beyond your comprehension. But pretty soon you’d notice something else about this refrigerator. The fact that it never runs out of food. Then you’d start to wonder if somehow it didn’t get restocked while you slept. But you’d realize that it replenished itself all the time, not just while you were sleeping. All this time, you’d keep eating from it. It would keep you alive out here in the middle of nowhere. And because of its mystery you’d begin to hate and fear it, and yet still it would feed you. Even though you couldn’t explain it, you’d still need it. And you’d assume that you simply didn’t understand the technology, rather than ascribe to it some kind of metaphysical power. You wouldn’t place your faith in the hands of some unknowable god. You’d place it in the technology itself. Finally, in frustration, you’d come to realize you’d exhausted your rationality and the only sensible thing to do would be to praise the mystery. You’d worship its bottles of Corona and jars of pickled beets. You’d make up prayers to the meats drawer and sing about its light bulb. And you’d start to accept the mystery as the one undeniable thing about it. That, or you’d grow so frustrated you’d push it off this cliff.”

“Is Mr. Kirkpatrick real?” I asked.

After a long gulp of beer, Bickle said, “That’s the neocortex talking again." -- Ryan Boudinot]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
