<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1076479-tanya]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1076479-tanya" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 15:01:53 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 15:01:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2887-if-you-judge-people-you-have-no-time-to-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 15:01:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2887-if-you-judge-people-you-have-no-time-to-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you judge people, you have no time to love them." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 19:21:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love never dies a natural death. It dies because we don't know how to replenish its source. It dies of blindness and errors and betrayals. It dies of illness and wounds; it dies of weariness, of witherings, of tarnishings." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4964-love-is-that-condition-in-which-the-happiness-of-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 19:27:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4964-love-is-that-condition-in-which-the-happiness-of-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is that condition in which the happiness of another person is essential to your own." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 19:39:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22457-todo-lo-que-sabemos-del-amor-es-que-el-amor</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 19:40:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Emily Dickinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22457-todo-lo-que-sabemos-del-amor-es-que-el-amor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Todo lo que sabemos del amor es que el amor es todo lo que hay." -- Emily Dickinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5342-el-amor-es-sufrido-es-benigno-el-amor-no-tiene</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 19:40:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5342-el-amor-es-sufrido-es-benigno-el-amor-no-tiene]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["El amor es sufrido, es benigno;
el amor no tiene envidia, el amor no es
jactancioso, no se envanece; no hace nada
indebido, no busca lo suyo, no se irrita, no
guarda rencor; no se goza de la injusticia, más
se goza de la verdad. Todo lo sufre, todo lo
espera, todo lo soporta. El amor nunca deja de
ser..." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6267-and-by-the-way-everything-in-life-is-writable-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 19:43:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6267-and-by-the-way-everything-in-life-is-writable-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And by the way, everything in life is writable about if you have the outgoing guts to do it, and the imagination to improvise. The worst enemy to creativity is self-doubt." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24138-love-is-patient-love-is-kind-it-does-not-envy</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 12:39:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24138-love-is-patient-love-is-kind-it-does-not-envy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is patient, love is kind. It does not envy, it does not boast, it is not proud. It is not rude, it is not self-seeking, it is not easily angered, it keeps no record of wrongs. Love does not delight in evil but rejoices with the truth. It always protects, always trusts, always hopes, always perseveres." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 12:39:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Kent M. Keith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Paradoxical Commandments

People are illogical, unreasonable, and self-centered.
Love them anyway.

If you do good, people will accuse you of selfish ulterior motives.
Do good anyway.

If you are successful, you will win false friends and true enemies.
Succeed anyway.

The good you do today will be forgotten tomorrow.
Do good anyway.

Honesty and frankness make you vulnerable.
Be honest and frank anyway.

The biggest men and women with the biggest ideas can be shot down by the smallest men and women with the smallest minds.
Think big anyway.

People favor underdogs but follow only top dogs.
Fight for a few underdogs anyway.

What you spend years building may be destroyed overnight.
Build anyway.

People really need help but may attack you if you do help them.
Help people anyway.

Give the world the best you have and you'll get kicked in the teeth.
Give the world the best you have anyway." -- Kent M. Keith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22510-en-un-mundo-superior-puede-ser-de-otra-manera-pero</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 11:27:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by John Henry Newman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22510-en-un-mundo-superior-puede-ser-de-otra-manera-pero]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["En un mundo superior puede ser de otra manera, pero aquí abajo, vivir es cambiar y ser perfecto es haber cambiado muchas veces." -- John Henry Newman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 11:27:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that everything happens for a reason. People change so that you can learn to let go, things go wrong so that you appreciate them when they're right, you believe lies so you eventually learn to trust no one but yourself, and sometimes good things fall apart so better things can fall together." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36668-true-freedom-is-not-advanced-in-the-permissive-society-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 11:29:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Pope John Paul II]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36668-true-freedom-is-not-advanced-in-the-permissive-society-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["True freedom is not advanced in the permissive society, which confuses freedom with license to do anything whatever and which in the name of freedom proclaims a kind of general amorality. It is a caricature of freedom to claim that people are free to organize their lives with no reference to moral values, and to say that society does not have to ensure the protection and advancement of ethical values. Such an attitude is destructive of freedom and peace." -- Pope John Paul II]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5343-qui-n-ama-ha-vencido-el-mundo-y-no-teme-perder</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 11:33:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5343-qui-n-ama-ha-vencido-el-mundo-y-no-teme-perder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Quién ama ha vencido el mundo y no teme perder nada, el verdadero amor supone un acto de entrega total. " -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58875-en-el-caso-de-la-mayor-a-de-los-seres-los</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 11:39:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Marguerite Yourcenar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58875-en-el-caso-de-la-mayor-a-de-los-seres-los]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["En el caso de la mayoría de los seres, los contactos más ligeros y superficiales bastan para contentar nuestro deseo, y aún para hartarlo. Si insisten, multiplicándose en torno de una criatura única hasta envolverla por entero; si cada parcela de su cuerpo se llena para nosotros de tantas significaciones trastornadoras como los rasgos de un rostro; si un solo ser, en vez de inspirarnos irritación, placer o hastío, nos hostiga como una música y nos atormenta como un problema; si pasa de la periferia de nuestro universo a su centro, llegando a sernos más indispensables que nuestro propio ser, entonces tiene lugar el asombroso prodigio en el que veo, mas que un simple juego de la carne, una invasión de la carne por el espíritu" -- Marguerite Yourcenar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53540-el-amor-es-una-amistad-con-momentos-er-ticos</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 11:40:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Antonio Gala]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53540-el-amor-es-una-amistad-con-momentos-er-ticos]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["El amor es una amistad con momentos eróticos." -- Antonio Gala]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22483-los-amigos-son-esa-parte-de-la-raza-humana-con</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 11:41:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Jorge Santayana.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22483-los-amigos-son-esa-parte-de-la-raza-humana-con]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Los amigos son esa parte de la raza humana
con la que uno puede ser humano.


" -- Jorge Santayana.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81601-live-up-to-your-convictions-you-walk-in-grace-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 12:03:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Carlos Santana]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81601-live-up-to-your-convictions-you-walk-in-grace-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Live up to your convictions.  You walk in grace or you walk in fear.  You can't have it both ways." -- Carlos Santana]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81602-happiness-is-not-a-destination-or-an-experience-it-s-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 12:03:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Carlos Santana]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81602-happiness-is-not-a-destination-or-an-experience-it-s-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is not a destination or an experience.  It's a decision.
" -- Carlos Santana]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153181-quem-nunca-sofreu-por-amor-nunca-aprender-a-amar-amar</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 15:08:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Miguel Sousa Tavares]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153181-quem-nunca-sofreu-por-amor-nunca-aprender-a-amar-amar]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Quem nunca sofreu por amor nunca aprenderá a amar. Amar é o terror de perder o outro, é o medo do silêncio e do quarto deserto, de tudo o que se pensa sem puder falar, do que se murmura a sós sem ter a quem dizer em voz alta. É preciso sentir esse terror para saber o que é amar. E, quando enfim tudo desaba, quando o outro partiu e deixou atrás de si o silêncio e o quarto deserto por entre os escombros e a humilhação de uma felicidade desfeita, resta o orgulho de saber que se amou." -- Miguel Sousa Tavares]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151917-que-significa-amar-durante-anios-he-pensado-que-significa-conocer</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 15:12:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Sandor Maraï]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151917-que-significa-amar-durante-anios-he-pensado-que-significa-conocer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Que significa 'amar'? Durante anios he pensado que significa conocer a la otra persona..., conocerla perfectamente, con todos sus secretos; conocer cada rincon de su cuerpo, cada reflejo; conocer a fondo su alma, cada una de sus emociones... Quizas sea eso, quizas conocer sea lo mismo que amar. Pero eso solo es una teoria. Despues de todo, que quiere decir conocer? Cuanto se puede conocer a un ser humano? Hasta donde se puede seguir a un alma desconocida? Hasta sus suenios? Y luego adonde? No se puede acompaniar a nadie a su inconsciente. Ni siquiera es necesario esperar a que ella cierre los ojos, se despida de mi y se retire a ese otro mundo, al mundo que llamamos de la noche... Porque existen dos mundos y uno esta mas alla del espacio conocido en el que vivimos, y quizas en ese otro mundo vivamos de manera mas real que en el espacio y en el tiempo...Ahora ya se con certeza que hay otro lugar que es solo nuestro, la propiedad privada de cada uno. (...) Aunque  todavia sigo sin saber lo que significa amar... Acaso se puede saber? Y de que sirve saberlo? No tiene nada que ver con la razon. Seguramente el amor es algo mas que el conocimiento. Conocer a alguien no es mucho, tiene unos limites... Amar debe ser algo parecido a seguir el mismo ritmo, una casualidad tan maravillosa como si en el universo hubiese dos meteoros con la misma trayectoria, la misma orbita y la misma materia. Una casualidad tal que no se puede ni calcular ni prever. Tal vez ni exista siquiera (...) Dos personas a las que les gustan las mismas comidas y la misma musica, que caminan al mismo ritmo por la calley que se buscan al mismo ritmo en la cama: quizas sea eso el amor. Que cosa mas rara debe de ser! Como un milagro... Yo imagino que los encuentros de ese tipo deben de ser misticos. La vida real no se basa en tales probabilidades. Creo que las personas que siguen el mismo ritmo, que segregan sus hormonas al mismo tiempo, que piensan lo mismo de las cosas y lo expresan con palabras identicas... bueno, creo que eso no existe. Una de las dos sera mas lenta y la otra mas rapida, una es timida, la otra osada, una ardiente, la otra tibia. Asi es como hay que tomar la vida, los encuentros... Hay que aceptar la felicidad asi, en su estado imperfecto." -- Sandor Maraï]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128815-ela-aproveitou-para-se-aproximar-silenciosa-como-se-caminhasse-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 15:13:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Joaquim Mestre]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128815-ela-aproveitou-para-se-aproximar-silenciosa-como-se-caminhasse-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ela aproveitou para se aproximar, silenciosa, como se caminhasse no sonho daquela tarde, com se tivesse medo de fazer um ruído e que a sua visão desaparecesse, como quando estamos a sonhar e não queremos acordar, queremos estar naquela felicidade sonâmbula, naquele tempo sem palavras, mas onde as imagens estão dentro de nós, e nós vemo-las. Ou sentimo-las?" -- Joaquim Mestre]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66512-i-believe-in-pink-i-believe-that-laughing-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 15:23:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66512-i-believe-in-pink-i-believe-that-laughing-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in pink. I believe that laughing is the best calorie burner. I believe in kissing, kissing a lot. I believe in being strong when everything seems to be going wrong. I believe that happy girls are the prettiest girls. I believe that tomorrow is another day and I believe in miracles." -- Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19152-i-think-the-only-way-to-get-through-this-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 15:23:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Shannon Hale]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19152-i-think-the-only-way-to-get-through-this-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think the only way to get through this life is laughing hard and constantly, mostly at myself." -- Shannon Hale]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12507-i-love-people-who-make-me-laugh-i-honestly-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 15:24:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12507-i-love-people-who-make-me-laugh-i-honestly-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love people who make me laugh. I honestly think it's the thing I like most, to laugh. It cures a multitude of ills. It's probably the most important thing in a person." -- Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5609-if-we-couldn-t-laugh-we-would-all-go-insane</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 15:24:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5609-if-we-couldn-t-laugh-we-would-all-go-insane]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we couldn't laugh we would all go insane." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34685-the-only-way-to-get-through-life-is-to-laugh</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 15:24:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34685-the-only-way-to-get-through-life-is-to-laugh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only way to get through life is to laugh your way through it. You either have to laugh or cry. I prefer to laugh. Crying gives me a headache." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 15:25:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know you're in love when you can't fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1816-you-may-say-i-m-a-dreamer-but-i-m-not-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 15:26:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1816-you-may-say-i-m-a-dreamer-but-i-m-not-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may say I'm a dreamer, but I'm not the only one. I hope someday you'll join us. And the world will live as one." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118594-faith-without-doubt-is-addiction</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 10:42:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanya add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118594-faith-without-doubt-is-addiction]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["faith without doubt is addiction" -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
