<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1077805-dana]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1077805-dana" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 11:24:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158252-i-m-not-afraid-to-compete-it-s-just-the-opposite-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 11:24:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158252-i-m-not-afraid-to-compete-it-s-just-the-opposite-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not afraid to compete. It's just the opposite. Don't you see that? I'm afraid I will compete — that's what scares me. That's why I quit the Theatre Department. Just because I'm so horribly conditioned to accept everybody else's values, and just because I like applause and people to rave about me, doesn't make it right. I'm ashamed of it. I'm sick of it. I'm sick of not having the courage to be an absolute nobody. I'm sick of myself and everybody else that wants to make some kind of a splash." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14471-many-people-need-desperately-to-receive-this-message-i-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2010 14:40:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14471-many-people-need-desperately-to-receive-this-message-i-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many people need desperately to receive this message: 'I feel and think much as you do, care about many of the things you care about, although most people do not care about them. You are not alone." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148829-for-if-a-lover-s-face-survives-emblazoned-on-your-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2010 14:52:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Orhan Pamuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148829-for-if-a-lover-s-face-survives-emblazoned-on-your-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For if a lover's face survives emblazoned on your heart, the world is still your home." -- Orhan Pamuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109672-i-just-don-t-want-you-to-feel-uncomfortable-about-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 09:58:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Lorrie Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109672-i-just-don-t-want-you-to-feel-uncomfortable-about-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I just don't want you to feel uncomfortable about this,&quot; he says.

Say: &quot;Hey.  I am a very cool person.  I am tough.&quot;  Show him your bicep." -- Lorrie Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33542-i-believe-that-we-learn-by-practice-whether-it-means</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 14:55:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Martha Graham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33542-i-believe-that-we-learn-by-practice-whether-it-means]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that we learn by practice.  Whether it means to learn to dance by practicing dancing or to learn to live by practicing living, the principles are the same.  In each, it is the performance of a dedicated precise set of acts, physical or intellectual, from which comes shape of achievement, a sense of one's being, a satisfaction of spirit.  One becomes, in some area, an athlete of God.  Practice means to perform, over and over again in the face of all obstacles, some act of vision, of faith, of desire.  Practice is a means of inviting the perfection desired." -- Martha Graham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31000-what-does-it-feel-like-to-be-alive-living-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 15:08:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31000-what-does-it-feel-like-to-be-alive-living-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What does it feel like to be alive?
Living, you stand under a waterfall. You leave the sleeping shore deliberately; you shed your dusty clothes, pick your barefoot way over the high, slippery rocks, hold your breath, choose your footing, and step into the waterfall. The hard water pelts your skull, bangs in bits on your shoulders and arms. The strong water dashes down beside you and you feel it along your calves and thighs rising roughly backup, up to the roiling surface, full of bubbles that slide up your skin or break on you at full speed. Can you breathe here? Here where the force is the greatest and only the strength of your neck holds the river out of your face. Yes, you can breathe even here. You could learn to live like this. And you can, if you concentrate, even look out at the peaceful far bank where you try to raise your arms. What a racket in your ears, what a scattershot pummeling!
It is time pounding at you, time. Knowing you are alive is watching on every side your generation's short time falling away as fast as rivers drop through air, and feeling it hit." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
