<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1078794-anush-shetty]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1078794-anush-shetty" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 22:08:32 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71-the-fool-doth-think-he-is-wise-but-the-wise</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 22:08:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71-the-fool-doth-think-he-is-wise-but-the-wise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fool doth think he is wise, but the wise man knows himself to be a fool." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6375-men-have-died-from-time-to-time-and-worms-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 18:54:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6375-men-have-died-from-time-to-time-and-worms-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men have died from time to time, and worms have eaten them, but not for love." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1844-perhaps-there-is-more-understanding-and-beauty-in-life-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 18:58:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by Virginia M. Axline]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1844-perhaps-there-is-more-understanding-and-beauty-in-life-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps there is more understanding and beauty in life when the glaring sunlight is softened by the patterns of shadows. Perhaps there is more depth in a relationship that has weathered some storms. Experience that never disappoints or saddens or stirs up feeling is a bland experience with little challenge or variation of color. Perhaps it's when we experience confidence and faith and hope that we see materialize before our eyes this builds up within us a feeling of inner strength, courage, and security. We are all personalities that grow and develop as a result of our experiences, relationships, thoughts, and emotions. We are the sum total of all the parts that go into the making of a life." -- Virginia M. Axline]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/435650-it-is-impossible-to-grasp-another-human-s-inner-world-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 04:36:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by Krupakar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/435650-it-is-impossible-to-grasp-another-human-s-inner-world-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is impossible to grasp another human's inner world. But even in the  darkness of the densest forest, there can always be the light of a firefly." -- Krupakar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/576437-a-man-lives-by-believing-something-not-by-debating-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 20:25:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by Thomas Carlyle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/576437-a-man-lives-by-believing-something-not-by-debating-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man lives by believing something; not by debating and arguing about many things." -- Thomas Carlyle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27688-for-me-trees-have-always-been-the-most-penetrating-preachers</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 22:54:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by Herman Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27688-for-me-trees-have-always-been-the-most-penetrating-preachers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For me, trees have always been the most penetrating preachers. I revere them when they live in tribes and families, in forests and groves. And even more I revere them when they stand alone. They are like lonely persons. Not like hermits who have stolen away out of some weakness, but like great, solitary men, like Beethoven and Nietzsche. In their highest boughs the world rustles, their roots rest in infinity; but they do not lose themselves there, they struggle with all the force of their lives for one thing only: to fulfil themselves according to their own laws, to build up their own form, to represent themselves. Nothing is holier, nothing is more exemplary than a beautiful, strong tree. When a tree is cut down and reveals its naked death-wound to the sun, one can read its whole history in the luminous, inscribed disk of its trunk: in the rings of its years, its scars, all the struggle, all the suffering, all the sickness, all the happiness and prosperity stand truly written, the narrow years and the luxurious years, the attacks withstood, the storms endured. And every young farmboy knows that the hardest and noblest wood has the narrowest rings, that high on the mountains and in continuing danger the most indestructible, the strongest, the ideal trees grow.

     Trees are sanctuaries. Whoever knows how to speak to them, whoever knows how to listen to them, can learn the truth. They do not preach learning and precepts, they preach, undeterred by particulars, the ancient law of life.

     A tree says: A kernel is hidden in me, a spark, a thought, I am life from eternal life. The attempt and the risk that the eternal mother took with me is unique, unique the form and veins of my skin, unique the smallest play of leaves in my branches and the smallest scar on my bark. I was made to form and reveal the eternal in my smallest special detail.

     A tree says: My strength is trust. I know nothing about my fathers, I know nothing about the thousand children that every year spring out of me. I live out the secret of my seed to the very end, and I care for nothing else. I trust that God is in me. I trust that my labor is holy. Out of this trust I live.

     When we are stricken and cannot bear our lives any longer, then a tree has something to say to us: Be still! Be still! Look at me! Life is not easy, life is not difficult. Those are childish thoughts. Let God speak within you, and your thoughts will grow silent. You are anxious because your path leads away from mother and home. But every step and every day lead you back again to the mother. Home is neither here nor there. Home is within you, or home is nowhere at all.

     A longing to wander tears my heart when I hear trees rustling in the wind at evening. If one listens to them silently for a long time, this longing reveals its kernel, its meaning. It is not so much a matter of escaping from one's suffering, though it may seem to be so. It is a longing for home, for a memory of the mother, for new metaphors for life. It leads home. Every path leads homeward, every step is birth, every step is death, every grave is mother.

     So the tree rustles in the evening, when we stand uneasy before our own childish thoughts: Trees have long thoughts, long-breathing and restful, just as they have longer lives than ours. They are wiser than we are, as long as we do not listen to them. But when we have learned how to listen to trees, then the brevity and the quickness and the childlike hastiness of our thoughts achieve an incomparable joy. Whoever has learned how to listen to trees no longer wants to be a tree. He wants to be nothing except what he is. That is home. That is happiness." -- Herman Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/811-for-instance-on-the-planet-earth-man-had-always-assumed</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 09:39:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/811-for-instance-on-the-planet-earth-man-had-always-assumed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For instance, on the planet Earth, man had always assumed that he was more intelligent than dolphins because he had achieved so much&amp;mdash;the wheel, New York, wars and so on&amp;mdash;whilst all the dolphins had ever done was muck about in the water having a good time. But conversely, the dolphins had always believed that they were far more intelligent than man&amp;mdash;for precisely the same reasons." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128956-have-you-really-read-all-those-books-in-your-room</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 02:28:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128956-have-you-really-read-all-those-books-in-your-room]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you really read all those books in your room?”

Alaska laughing- “Oh God no. I’ve maybe read a third of ‘em. But I’m going to read them all. I call it my Life’s Library. Every summer since I was little, I’ve gone to garage sales and bought all the books that looked interesting. So I always have something to read." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14598-paths-are-made-by-walking</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 02:32:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14598-paths-are-made-by-walking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Paths are made by walking" -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/679864-the-new-dam-of-course-will-improve-things-if-ever</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2012 19:23:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/679864-the-new-dam-of-course-will-improve-things-if-ever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The new dam, of course, will improve things. If ever filled it will back water to within sight of the Bridge, transforming what was formerly an adventure into a routine motorboat excursion. Those who see it then will not understand that half the beauty of Rainbow Bridge lay in its remoteness, its relative difficulty of access, and in the wilderness surrounding it, of which it was an integral part. When these aspects are removed the Bridge will be no more than an isolated geological oddity, an extension of that museumlike diorama to which industrial tourism tends to reduce the natural world." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74018-sing-loud-for-the-sunshine-pray-hard-for-the-rain</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2012 23:25:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by Led Zeppelin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74018-sing-loud-for-the-sunshine-pray-hard-for-the-rain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sing loud for the sunshine. Pray hard for the rain." -- Led Zeppelin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16537-these-are-the-seasons-of-emotion-and-like-the-winds</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2012 23:25:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by Led Zeppelin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16537-these-are-the-seasons-of-emotion-and-like-the-winds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These are the seasons of emotion,
and like the winds, they rise and fall." -- Led Zeppelin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484925-when-the-spirits-are-low-when-the-day-appears-dark</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2012 01:49:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by Arthur Conan Doyle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484925-when-the-spirits-are-low-when-the-day-appears-dark]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the spirits are low, when the day appears dark, when work becomes monotonous, when hope hardly seems worth having, just mount a bicycle and go out for a spin down the road, without thought on anything but the ride you are taking." -- Arthur Conan Doyle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156323-ever-bike-now-that-s-something-that-makes-life-worth-living-oh</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2012 01:49:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by Jack London]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156323-ever-bike-now-that-s-something-that-makes-life-worth-living-oh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ever bike? Now that's something that makes life worth living!...Oh, to just grip your handlebars and lay down to it, and go ripping and tearing through streets and road, over railroad tracks and bridges, threading crowds, avoiding collisions, at twenty miles or more an hour, and wondering all the time when you're going to smash up. Well, now, that's something! And then go home again after three hours of it...and then to think that tomorrow I can do it all over again!" -- Jack London]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/510586-i-want-to-go-about-like-the-light-footed-goats</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2013 02:43:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by Johanna Spyri]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/510586-i-want-to-go-about-like-the-light-footed-goats]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to go about like the light-footed goats." -- Johanna Spyri]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182464-lying-the-telling-of-beautiful-untrue-things-is-the-proper</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 00:35:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182464-lying-the-telling-of-beautiful-untrue-things-is-the-proper]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lying, the telling of beautiful untrue things, is the proper aim of Art." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1244-friendship-is-unnecessary-like-philosophy-like-art-it-has-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2013 10:01:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1244-friendship-is-unnecessary-like-philosophy-like-art-it-has-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is unnecessary, like philosophy, like art.... It has no survival value; rather it is one of those things which give value to survival." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/861118-it-s-a-funny-thing-in-my-job-you-remain-perpetually</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 02:25:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by Brian W. Aldiss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/861118-it-s-a-funny-thing-in-my-job-you-remain-perpetually]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's a funny thing in my job: you remain perpetually lonely in a world where loneliness is the rarest commodity." -- Brian W. Aldiss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626-knowing-trees-i-understand-the-meaning-of-patience-knowing-grass</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 03:49:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by Hal Borland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626-knowing-trees-i-understand-the-meaning-of-patience-knowing-grass]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Knowing trees, I understand the meaning of patience. Knowing grass, I can appreciate persistence." -- Hal Borland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417798-the-cure-for-anything-is-salt-water---tears-sweat</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 10:58:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anush add a quote by Isak Dinesen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417798-the-cure-for-anything-is-salt-water---tears-sweat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The cure for anything is salt water   - tears, sweat, or the sea." -- Isak Dinesen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
