<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1080752-kristin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1080752-kristin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 10:56:28 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44950-if-someone-who-wanted-to-learn-to-dance-were-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 10:56:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Kierkegaard Soren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44950-if-someone-who-wanted-to-learn-to-dance-were-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If someone who wanted to learn to dance were to say: For centuries, one generation after the other has learned the positions, and it is high time that I take advantage of this and promptly begin with the quadrille--people would presumably laugh a little at him, but in the world of spirit this is very plausible. What, then, is education? I believed it is the course the individual goes through in order to catch up with himself, and the person who will not go through this course is not much helped by being born in the most enlightened age." -- Kierkegaard Soren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107326-we-must-remember-that-intelligence-is-not-enough-intelligence-plus</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2009 16:55:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107326-we-must-remember-that-intelligence-is-not-enough-intelligence-plus]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must remember that intelligence is not enough. Intelligence plus character-that is the goal of true education. The complete education gives one not only power of concentration, but worthy objectives upon which to concentrate. " -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/707992-no-there-s-more-to-life-than-this-that-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 08:27:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Clifford Odets]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/707992-no-there-s-more-to-life-than-this-that-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No, there's more to life than this. . .That was the past, but there is a future.

Now we know. We dare to understand. Truly. Truly, the past was a dream. But this, this is real. To know from this that something must be done, that is real.

We searched. We were confused, but we searched. And now the search has ended, for the truth has found us. For the first time in our lives, for the first time, our house has a real foundation . . . 


Everywhere now, men are rising from their sleep. Men-- men are understanding the bitter, black total of their lives. Their whispers are growing to shouts. They become an ocean of understanding. No man fights alone.

Oh, if you could see with me the greatness of men. I tremble like a bride to see the time when they'll use it. No, my dear, we must have one regret-- that life is so short, that we must die so soon.

Yes, I-- I want to see that new world. I want to kiss all those future men and women. What's all this talk about bankruptcies, failures, hatreds? They won't know what that means.

I tell you, the whole world is for men to possess. Heartbreak and terror are not the heritage of mankind. The world is beautiful. No fruit tree wears a lock and key. Men will sing at their work, men will love. Oh, darling, the world is in its morning. And no man fights alone.

Let's have air. Open the windows. 

--From &lt;i&gt;Paradise Lost&lt;/i&gt;" -- Clifford Odets]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
