<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1082796-karissa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1082796-karissa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2008 11:27:25 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1816-you-may-say-i-m-a-dreamer-but-i-m-not-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2008 11:27:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karissa add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1816-you-may-say-i-m-a-dreamer-but-i-m-not-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may say I'm a dreamer, but I'm not the only one. I hope someday you'll join us. And the world will live as one." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7357-you-talk-when-you-cease-to-be-at-peace-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2008 11:28:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karissa add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7357-you-talk-when-you-cease-to-be-at-peace-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You talk when you cease to be at peace with your thoughts." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9131-if-you-tell-the-truth-you-don-t-have-to-remember</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2008 11:30:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karissa add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9131-if-you-tell-the-truth-you-don-t-have-to-remember]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you tell the truth, you don't have to remember anything." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2008 11:32:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karissa add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32947-the-clearest-way-into-the-universe-is-through-a-forest</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2008 12:00:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karissa add a quote by John Muir]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32947-the-clearest-way-into-the-universe-is-through-a-forest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The clearest way into the Universe is through a forest wilderness." -- John Muir]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27688-for-me-trees-have-always-been-the-most-penetrating-preachers</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2008 12:04:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karissa add a quote by Herman Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27688-for-me-trees-have-always-been-the-most-penetrating-preachers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For me, trees have always been the most penetrating preachers. I revere them when they live in tribes and families, in forests and groves. And even more I revere them when they stand alone. They are like lonely persons. Not like hermits who have stolen away out of some weakness, but like great, solitary men, like Beethoven and Nietzsche. In their highest boughs the world rustles, their roots rest in infinity; but they do not lose themselves there, they struggle with all the force of their lives for one thing only: to fulfil themselves according to their own laws, to build up their own form, to represent themselves. Nothing is holier, nothing is more exemplary than a beautiful, strong tree. When a tree is cut down and reveals its naked death-wound to the sun, one can read its whole history in the luminous, inscribed disk of its trunk: in the rings of its years, its scars, all the struggle, all the suffering, all the sickness, all the happiness and prosperity stand truly written, the narrow years and the luxurious years, the attacks withstood, the storms endured. And every young farmboy knows that the hardest and noblest wood has the narrowest rings, that high on the mountains and in continuing danger the most indestructible, the strongest, the ideal trees grow.

     Trees are sanctuaries. Whoever knows how to speak to them, whoever knows how to listen to them, can learn the truth. They do not preach learning and precepts, they preach, undeterred by particulars, the ancient law of life.

     A tree says: A kernel is hidden in me, a spark, a thought, I am life from eternal life. The attempt and the risk that the eternal mother took with me is unique, unique the form and veins of my skin, unique the smallest play of leaves in my branches and the smallest scar on my bark. I was made to form and reveal the eternal in my smallest special detail.

     A tree says: My strength is trust. I know nothing about my fathers, I know nothing about the thousand children that every year spring out of me. I live out the secret of my seed to the very end, and I care for nothing else. I trust that God is in me. I trust that my labor is holy. Out of this trust I live.

     When we are stricken and cannot bear our lives any longer, then a tree has something to say to us: Be still! Be still! Look at me! Life is not easy, life is not difficult. Those are childish thoughts. Let God speak within you, and your thoughts will grow silent. You are anxious because your path leads away from mother and home. But every step and every day lead you back again to the mother. Home is neither here nor there. Home is within you, or home is nowhere at all.

     A longing to wander tears my heart when I hear trees rustling in the wind at evening. If one listens to them silently for a long time, this longing reveals its kernel, its meaning. It is not so much a matter of escaping from one's suffering, though it may seem to be so. It is a longing for home, for a memory of the mother, for new metaphors for life. It leads home. Every path leads homeward, every step is birth, every step is death, every grave is mother.

     So the tree rustles in the evening, when we stand uneasy before our own childish thoughts: Trees have long thoughts, long-breathing and restful, just as they have longer lives than ours. They are wiser than we are, as long as we do not listen to them. But when we have learned how to listen to trees, then the brevity and the quickness and the childlike hastiness of our thoughts achieve an incomparable joy. Whoever has learned how to listen to trees no longer wants to be a tree. He wants to be nothing except what he is. That is home. That is happiness." -- Herman Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23573-how-happy-is-the-little-stone-that-rambles-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 13:43:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karissa add a quote by Emily Dickinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23573-how-happy-is-the-little-stone-that-rambles-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How happy is the little stone
That rambles in the road alone,
And doesn't care about careers,
And exigencies never fears;
Whose coat of elemental brown
A passing universe put on;
And independent as the sun,
Associates or glows alone,
Fulfilling absolute decree
In casual simplicity." -- Emily Dickinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3713-simplicity-patience-compassion-these-three-are-your-greatest-treasures-simple</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 13:44:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karissa add a quote by Lao Tzu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3713-simplicity-patience-compassion-these-three-are-your-greatest-treasures-simple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Simplicity, patience, compassion.
These three are your greatest treasures.
Simple in actions and thoughts, you return to the source of being.
Patient with both friends and enemies,
you accord with the way things are.
Compassionate toward yourself,
you reconcile all beings in the world." -- Lao Tzu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6970-to-have-humility-is-to-experience-reality-not-in-relation</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 13:45:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karissa add a quote by Dag Hammarskjöld]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6970-to-have-humility-is-to-experience-reality-not-in-relation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To have humility is to experience reality, not in relation to ourselves, but in its sacred independence.  It is to see, judge, and act from the point of rest in ourselves.  Then, how much disappears, and all that remains falls into place.

In the point of rest at the center of our being, we encounter a world where all things are at rest in the same way.  Then a tree becomes a mystery, a cloud a revelation, each man a cosmos of whose riches we can only catch glimpses.  The life of simplicity is simple, but it opens to us a book in which we never get beyond the first syllable." -- Dag Hammarskjöld]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/849-our-task-must-be-to-free-ourselves-by-widening-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 13:56:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karissa add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/849-our-task-must-be-to-free-ourselves-by-widening-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our task must be to free ourselves... by widening our circle of compassion to embrace all living creatures and the whole of nature and it's beauty." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26411-there-are-two-basic-motivating-forces-fear-and-love-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2008 15:44:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karissa add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26411-there-are-two-basic-motivating-forces-fear-and-love-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two basic motivating forces: fear and love. When we are afraid, we pull back from life. When we are in love, we open to all that life has to offer with passion, excitement, and acceptance. We need to learn to love ourselves first, in all our glory and our imperfections. If we cannot love ourselves, we cannot fully open to our ability to love others or our potential to create. Evolution and all hopes for a better world rest in the fearlessness and open-hearted vision of people who embrace life." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
