<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1082697-deanna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1082697-deanna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:29:23 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:29:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are bored and disgusted by politics and don't bother to vote, you are in effect voting for the entrenched Establishments of the two major parties, who please rest assured are not dumb, and who are keenly aware that it is in their interests to keep you disgusted and bored and cynical and to give you every possible reason to stay at home doing one-hitters and watching MTV on primary day.  By all means stay home if you want, but don't bullshit yourself that you're not voting.  In reality, there is &lt;i&gt;no such thing as not voting:&lt;/i&gt; you either vote by voting, or you vote by staying home and tacitly doubling the value of some Diehard's vote." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18719-the-truth-will-set-you-free-but-not-until-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:29:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18719-the-truth-will-set-you-free-but-not-until-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth will set you free. But not until it is finished with you." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23624-i-read-i-say-i-study-and-read-i-bet</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:30:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23624-i-read-i-say-i-study-and-read-i-bet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read,&quot; I say. &quot;I study and read. I bet I've read everything you read. Don't think I haven't. I consume libraries. I wear out spines and ROM-drives. I do things like get in a taxi and say, &quot;The library, and step on it.&quot; My instincts concerning syntax and mechanics are better than your own, I can tell, with all due respect. But it transcends the mechanics. I'm not a machine. I feel and believe. I have opinions. Some of them are interesting. I could, if you'd let me, talk and talk." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2638-both-destiny-s-kisses-and-its-dope-slaps-illustrate-an-individual-person-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:31:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2638-both-destiny-s-kisses-and-its-dope-slaps-illustrate-an-individual-person-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Both destiny's kisses and its dope-slaps illustrate an individual person's basic personal powerlessness over the really meaningful events in his life: i.e. almost nothing important that ever happens to you happens because you engineer it.  Destiny has no beeper; destiny always leans trenchcoated out of an alley with some sort of Psst that you usually can't even hear because you're in such a rush to or from something important you've tried to engineer." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28675-i-have-filled-3-mead-notebooks-trying-to-figure-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:31:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28675-i-have-filled-3-mead-notebooks-trying-to-figure-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have filled 3 Mead notebooks trying to figure out whether it was Them or Just Me." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98274-fiction-is-one-of-the-few-experiences-where-loneliness-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:34:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98274-fiction-is-one-of-the-few-experiences-where-loneliness-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fiction is one of the few experiences where loneliness can be both confronted and relieved. Drugs, movies where stuff blows up, loud parties -- all these chase away loneliness by making me forget my name's Dave and I live in a one-by-one box of bone no other party can penetrate or know. Fiction, poetry, music, really deep serious sex, and, in various ways, religion -- these are the places (for me) where loneliness is countenanced, stared down, transfigured, treated." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100888-because-here-s-something-else-that-s-weird-but-true-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:36:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by David Foster Wallace  ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100888-because-here-s-something-else-that-s-weird-but-true-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because here's something else that's weird but true: in the day-to day trenches of adult life, there is actually no such thing as atheism. There is no such thing as not worshipping. Everybody worships. The only choice we get is what to worship. And the compelling reason for maybe choosing some sort of god or spiritual-type thing to worship -- be it JC or Allah, be it YHWH or the Wiccan Mother Goddess, or the Four Noble Truths, or some inviolable set of ethical principles -- is that pretty much anything else you worship will eat you alive. If you worship money and things, if they are where you tap real meaning in life, then you will never have enough, never feel you have enough. It's the truth. Worship your body and beauty and sexual allure and you will always feel ugly. And when time and age start showing, you will die a million deaths before they finally grieve you. On one level, we all know this stuff already. It's been codified as myths, proverbs, clichés, epigrams, parables; the skeleton of every great story. The whole trick is keeping the truth up front in daily consciousness." -- David Foster Wallace  ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49274-if-what-s-always-distinguished-bad-writing--flat-characters-a-narrative-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:39:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49274-if-what-s-always-distinguished-bad-writing--flat-characters-a-narrative-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If what's always distinguished bad writing--flat characters, a narrative world that's clichéd and not recognizably human, etc.--is also a description of today's world, then bad writing becomes an ingenious mimesis of a bad world. If readers simply believe the world is stupid and shallow and mean, then [Bret] Ellis can write a mean shallow stupid novel that becomes a mordant deadpan commentary on the badness of everything. Look man, we'd probably most of us agree that these are dark times, and stupid ones, but do we need fiction that does nothing but dramatize how dark and stupid everything is? In dark times, the definition of good art would seem to be art that locates and applies CPR to those elements of what's human and magical that still live and glow despite the times' darkness. Really good fiction could have as dark a worldview as it wished, but it'd find a way both to depict this world and to illuminate the possibilities for being alive and human in it.

Postmodern irony and cynicism's become an end in itself, a measure of hip sophistication and literary savvy. Few artists dare to try to talk about ways of working toward redeeming what's wrong, because they'll look sentimental and naive to all the weary ironists. Irony's gone from liberating to enslaving. There's some great essay somewhere that has a line about irony being the song of the prisoner who's come to love his cage… The postmodern founders' patricidal work was great, but patricide produces orphans, and no amount of revelry can make up for the fact that writers my age have been literary orphans throughout our formative years.

We enter a spiritual puberty where we snap to the fact that the great transcendent horror is loneliness, excluded encagement in the self. Once we’ve hit this age, we will now give or take anything, wear any mask, to fit, be part-of, not be Alone, we young. The U.S. arts are our guide to inclusion. A how-to. We are shown how to fashion masks of ennui and jaded irony at a young age where the face is fictile enough to assume the shape of whatever it wears. And then it’s stuck there, the weary cynicism that saves us from gooey sentiment and unsophisticated naïveté. Sentiment equals naïveté on this continent.

You burn with hunger for food that does not exist.

A U. S. of modern A. where the State is not a team or a code, but a sort of sloppy intersection of desires and fears, where the only public consensus a boy must surrender to is the acknowledged primacy of straight-line pursuing this flat and short-sighted idea of personal happiness." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62349-in-dark-times-the-definition-of-good-art-would-seem</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:41:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62349-in-dark-times-the-definition-of-good-art-would-seem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In dark times, the definition of good art would seem to be art that locates and applies CPR to those elements of what's human and magical that still live and glow despite the times' darkness. Really good fiction could have as dark a worldview as it wished, but it'd find a way both to depict this world and to illuminate the possibilities for being alive and human in it." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98815-whatever-you-get-paid-attention-for-is-never-what-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:41:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98815-whatever-you-get-paid-attention-for-is-never-what-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever you get paid attention for is never what you think is most important about yourself." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98166-an-ad-that-pretends-to-be-art-is----at</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:42:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98166-an-ad-that-pretends-to-be-art-is----at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An ad that pretends to be art is -- at absolute best -- like somebody who smiles warmly at you only because he wants something from you. This is dishonest, but what's sinister is the cumulative effect that such dishonesty has on us: since it offers a perfect facsimile or simulacrum of goodwill without goodwill's real spirit, it messes with our heads and eventually starts upping our defenses even in cases of genuine smiles and real art and true goodwill. It makes us feel confused and lonely and impotent and angry and scared. It causes despair." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118882-in-real-life-i-always-seem-to-have-a-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:43:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118882-in-real-life-i-always-seem-to-have-a-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...in real life I always seem to have a hard time winding up a conversation or asking somebody to leave, and sometimes the moment becomes so delicate and fraught with social complexity that I'll get overwhelmed trying to sort out all the different possible ways of saying it and all the different implications of each option and will just sort of blank out and do it totally straight -- 'I want to terminate the conversation and not have you be in my apartment anymore' -- which evidently makes me look either as if I'm very rude and abrupt or as if I'm semi-autistic and have no sense of how to wind up a conversation gracefully...I've actually lost friends this way." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127092-mario-what-do-you-get-when-you-cross-an-insomniac</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:43:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127092-mario-what-do-you-get-when-you-cross-an-insomniac]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mario, what do you get when you cross an insomniac, an unwilling agnostic and a dyslexic?&quot;

&quot;I give.&quot;

&quot;You get someone who stays up all night torturing himself mentally over the question of whether or not there's a dog." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93352-te-occidere-possunt-sed-te-edere-non-possunt-nefas-est</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:44:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93352-te-occidere-possunt-sed-te-edere-non-possunt-nefas-est]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Te Occidere Possunt Sed Te Edere Non Possunt Nefas Est&quot; (&quot;They can kill you, but the legalities of eating you are quite a bit dicier&quot;)." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110175-this-is-apparently-a-little-promotional-where-we-re-supposed</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:49:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110175-this-is-apparently-a-little-promotional-where-we-re-supposed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is apparently a little promotional ¶ where we’re supposed to explain “how and why we came to” the subject of our GD series book (the stuff in quotations is the editor’s words). The overall idea is to humanize the series and make the books and their subjects seem warmer and more accessible. So that people will be more apt to buy the books. I’m pretty sure this is how it works. The obvious objection to such promotional ¶s is that, if the books are any good at all, then the writers’ interest and investment in their subjects will be so resoundingly obvious in the texts themselves that these little pseudo-intimate Why I Cared Enough About Transfinite Math and Where It Came From to Spend a Year Writing a Book About It blurblets are unnecessary; whereas, if the books aren’t any good, it’s hard to see how my telling somebody that as a child I used to cook up what amounted to simplistic versions of Zeno’s Dichotomy and ruminate on them until I literally made myself sick, or that I once almost flunked a basic calc course and have seethed with dislike for conventional higher-math education ever since, or that the ontology and grammar of abstractions have always struck me as one of the most breathtaking problems in human consciousness—how any such stuff will help. The logic of this objection seems airtight to me. In fact, the only way the objection doesn’t apply is if these ¶s are really nothing more than disguised ad copy, in which case I don’t see why anyone reading them should even necessarily believe that the books’ authors actually wrote them—I mean, maybe somebody in the ad-copy department wrote them and all we did was sort of sign off on them. There’d be a kind of twisted integrity about that, though—at least no one would be pretending to pretend." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123190-the-interesting-thing-is-why-we-re-so-desperate-for-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:49:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123190-the-interesting-thing-is-why-we-re-so-desperate-for-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The interesting thing is why we're so desperate for this anesthetic against loneliness." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158520-she-would-defend-herself-saying-that-love-no-matter-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 07:00:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[deanna add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158520-she-would-defend-herself-saying-that-love-no-matter-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She would defend herself, saying that love, no matter what else it might be, was a natural talent. She would say: You are either born knowing how, or you never know." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
