<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1083426-mandy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1083426-mandy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 03:29:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10847-if-you-care-about-something-you-have-to-protect-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 03:29:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mandy add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10847-if-you-care-about-something-you-have-to-protect-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you care about something you have to protect it – If you’re lucky enough to find a way of life you love, you have to find the courage to live it." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1961-the-road-not-taken-two-roads-diverged-in-a-yellow</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 09:31:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mandy add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1961-the-road-not-taken-two-roads-diverged-in-a-yellow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Road Not Taken

Two roads diverged in a yellow wood,
And sorry I could not travel both	
And be one traveler, long I stood	
And looked down one as far as I could	
To where it bent in the undergrowth;	        
 
Then took the other, as just as fair,	
And having perhaps the better claim,	
Because it was grassy and wanted wear;	
Though as for that the passing there	
Had worn them really about the same,	        
 
And both that morning equally lay	
In leaves no step had trodden black.	
Oh, I kept the first for another day!	
Yet knowing how way leads on to way,	
I doubted if I should ever come back.	        
 
I shall be telling this with a sigh	
Somewhere ages and ages hence:	
Two roads diverged in a wood, and I—	
I took the one less traveled by,	
And that has made all the difference." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 15:08:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mandy add a quote by Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened." -- Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 15:10:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mandy add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the world were merely seductive, that would be easy. If it were merely challenging, that would be no problem. But I arise in the morning torn between a desire to improve the world and a desire to enjoy the world. This makes it hard to plan the day." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7299-i-ll-hold-on-to-the-world-tight-some-day-i-ve</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 15:12:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mandy add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7299-i-ll-hold-on-to-the-world-tight-some-day-i-ve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'll hold on to the world tight some day. I've got one finger on it now; that's a beginning." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11241-everyone-must-leave-something-behind-when-he-dies-my-grandfather</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 15:13:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mandy add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11241-everyone-must-leave-something-behind-when-he-dies-my-grandfather]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone must leave something behind when he dies, my grandfather said. A child or a book or a painting or a house or a wall built or a pair of shoes made. Or a garden planted. Something your hand touched some way so your soul has somewhere to go when you die, and when people look at that tree or that flower you planted, you're there. 

It doesn't matter what you do, he said, so long as you change something from the way it was before you touched it into something that's like you after you take your hands away. The difference between the man who just cuts lawns and a real gardener is in the touching, he said. The lawn-cutter might just as well not have been there at all; the gardener will be there a lifetime." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10894-so-we-dream-on-thus-we-invent-our-lives-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 17:51:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mandy add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10894-so-we-dream-on-thus-we-invent-our-lives-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So we dream on.  Thus we invent our lives.  We give ourselves a sainted mother, we make our father a hero; and someone’s older brother and someone’s older sister – they become our heroes too.  We invent what we love and what we fear.  There is always a brave lost brother – and a little lost sister, too.  We dream on and on: the best hotel, the perfect family, the resort life.  And our dreams escape us almost as vividly as we can imagine them…  That’s what happens, like it or not.  And because that’s what happens, this is what we need: we need a good, smart bear…  Coach Bob knew it all along: you’ve got to get obsessed and stay obsessed. You have to keep passing the open windows." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
