<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1083197-jeanne]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1083197-jeanne" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 13:10:56 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23350-but-you-see-said-roark-quietly-i-have-let-s-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 13:10:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeanne add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23350-but-you-see-said-roark-quietly-i-have-let-s-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But you see,&quot; said Roark quietly, &quot;I have, let’s say, sixty years to live. Most of that time will be spent working. I’ve chosen the work I want to do. If I find no joy in it, then I’m only condemning myself to sixty years of torture. And I can find the joy only if I do my work in the best way possible to me. But the best is a matter of standards—and I set my own standards. I inherit nothing. I stand at the end of no tradition. I may, perhaps, stand at the beginning of one." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217252--bdb-on-the-board--knitter-s-anonimous-may-8-2006-rhage</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 13:13:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeanne add a quote by J.R. Ward]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217252--bdb-on-the-board--knitter-s-anonimous-may-8-2006-rhage]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["-BDB on the board-
Knitter's Anonimous
May 8, 2006
Rhage (in his bedroom posting in V's room on the board)
Hi, my name is V.
(&quot;Hi, V&quot;)
I've been knitting for 125 years now.
(*gasping noises*)
It's begun to impact my personal relationships: my brothers think I'm a nancy. It's begun to affect my health: I'm getting a callus on my forefinger and I find bits of yarn in all my pockets and I'm starting to smell like wool. I can't concentrate at work: I keep picturing all these lessers in Irish sweaters and thick socks.
(*sounds of sympathy*)
I've come seeking a community of people who, like me, are trying not to knit. 
Can you help me?
(*We're with you*)
Thank you (*takes out hand-knitted hankie in pink*)
(*sniffles*)
(&quot;We embrace you, V&quot;)

Vishous (in the pit): Oh hell no...you did not just put that up. And nice spelling in the title. Man...you just have to roll up on me, don't you. I got four words for you, my brother.

Rhage: Four words? Okay...lemme see... Rhage, you're so sexy.
hmmm....
Rhage, you're SO smart. No wait! Rhage, you're SO right! That's it, isn't it...g'head. You can tell me. 

Vishous: First one starts with a &quot;P&quot;
Use your head for the other three. 
Bastard.

Rhage: P? Hmm... Please pass the yarn

Vishous: Payback is a bitch!

Rhage: Ohhhhhhhhhhhh
I'm so scuuuuuurred. 
Can you whip me up a blanket to hide under?" -- J.R. Ward]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244779-his-hand-was-on-my-throat-and-he-was-crushing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 13:14:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeanne add a quote by Karen Marie Moning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244779-his-hand-was-on-my-throat-and-he-was-crushing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His hand was on my throat, and he was crushing me back with his body into the cold steel beam behind me. &quot;Yes, I have loved, Ms. Lane, and although it‘s none of your business, I have lost. Many things. And no, I am not like any other player in this game and I will never be like V‘lane, and I get a hard-on a great deal more often than occasionally.&quot; He leaned fully against me and I gasped. 

&quot;Sometimes it‘s over a spoiled little girl, not a woman at all. And yes, I trashed the bookstore when I couldn‘t find you. You‘ll have to choose a new bedroom, too. And I‘m sorry your pretty little world got all screwed up, but everybody‘s does, and you go on. It‘s how you go on that defines you.&quot; His hand relaxed on my throat. &quot;And I am going to tattoo you, Ms. Lane, however and wherever I please." -- Karen Marie Moning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238873-and-then-tohr-said-softly-i-m-lucky-to-have-found</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 13:16:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeanne add a quote by J.R. Ward]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238873-and-then-tohr-said-softly-i-m-lucky-to-have-found]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And then Tohr said softly, &quot;I'm lucky to have found love, I thank the Scribe Virgin every day that Wellsie is in my life.&quot;

Wrath's Temper surged, set off by something he couldn't put his finger on. &quot;You're&lt;i&gt; pathetic&lt;/i&gt;.&quot;

Tohr hissed. &quot;And you've been dead for hundreds of years.  You're just too mean to find a grave and lie down.&quot;

Wrath threw the leather jacket on the floor.  &quot;At least I'm not pussy whipped.&quot;

Nice. F*cking. Suit." -- J.R. Ward]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135987-you-re-going-to-find-this-hard-to-believe-but-cops</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 13:17:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeanne add a quote by Janet Evanovich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135987-you-re-going-to-find-this-hard-to-believe-but-cops]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're going to find this hard to believe, but cops aren't required to carry emergency condoms.&quot;
Joe Morelli" -- Janet Evanovich]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
