<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1083458-allison-adams]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1083458-allison-adams" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 12:51:53 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30052-a-book-is-more-than-a-verbal-structure-or-series</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 12:51:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30052-a-book-is-more-than-a-verbal-structure-or-series]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book is more than a verbal structure or series of verbal structures; it is the dialogue it establishes with its reader and the intonation it imposes upon his voice and the changing and durable images it leaves in his memory. A book is not an isolated being: it is a relationship, an axis of innumerable relationships." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48844-i-mean-what-they-and-their-hired-psychiatrists-call-delusional</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 07:48:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48844-i-mean-what-they-and-their-hired-psychiatrists-call-delusional]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I mean what they and their hired psychiatrists call delusional systems.  Needless to say, ‘delusions’ are always officially defined.  We do not have to worry about questions of real or unreal.  They only talk out of expediency.  It’s the system that matters.  How the data arrange themselves inside it.  Some are consistent, others fall apart.  " -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48845-in-recent-weeks-in-true-messianic-style-it-has-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 07:50:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48845-in-recent-weeks-in-true-messianic-style-it-has-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In recent weeks, in true messianic style, it has come clear to her that her real identity is literally, the force of gravity.  
I am Gravity, I am That against which the Rocket must struggle, to which prehistoric wastes submit and are transmuted to the very substance of History." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48846-darkness-invades-the-dreams-of-the-glassblower-of-all-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 07:52:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48846-darkness-invades-the-dreams-of-the-glassblower-of-all-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Darkness invades the dreams of the glassblower.  Of all the unpleasantries his dreams grab in out of the night air, an extinguished light is the worst.  Light in his dreams, was always hope: the basic moral hope.  As the contacts break helically away, hope turns to darkness, and the glassblower wakes sharply tonight crying, Who?  Who?" -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48847-there-is-no-real-direction-here-neither-lines-of-power</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 07:53:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48847-there-is-no-real-direction-here-neither-lines-of-power]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no real direction here, neither lines of power nor cooperation.  Decisions are never really made – at best they manage to emerge, from a chaos of peeves, whims, hallucinations and all around assholery.  " -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48849-there-is-nothing-so-loathsome-as-a-sentimental-surrealist</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 07:56:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48849-there-is-nothing-so-loathsome-as-a-sentimental-surrealist]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing so loathsome as a sentimental surrealist." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48850-shit-now-is-the-color-white-folks-are-afraid-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 07:58:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48850-shit-now-is-the-color-white-folks-are-afraid-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Shit now is the color white folks are afraid of.  Shit is the presence of death, not some abstract-arty character with a scythe but the stiff and rotting corpse inside the whiteman’s warm and private own asshole, which is getting pretty intimate.  That’s what the toilet is for.  You see many brown toilets?  Nope, toilet’s the color of gravestones, classical columns of mausoleums, that white emblems the very emblem of Odorless and Official death." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48853-so-generation-after-generation-of-men-in-love-with-pain</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 07:59:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48853-so-generation-after-generation-of-men-in-love-with-pain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So generation after generation of men in love with pain and passivity serve out their time in the Zone, silent, redolent of faded sperm, terrified of dying, desperately addicted to the comforts others sell them, however useless, ugly or shallow, willing to have life defined for them by men whose only talent is for death." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48883-so-the-city-became-the-material-expression-of-a-particular</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 08:55:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48883-so-the-city-became-the-material-expression-of-a-particular]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So the city became the material expression of a particular loss of innocence – not sexual or political innocence but somehow a shared dream of what a city might at its best prove to be – its inhabitants became, and have remained, an embittered and amnesiac race, wounded but unable to connect through memory to the moment of injury, unable to summon the face of their violator." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48935-there-may-be-as-many-people-taking-pictures-as-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 11:31:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Don Delillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48935-there-may-be-as-many-people-taking-pictures-as-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There may be as many people taking pictures as there are brides and grooms.  One of them for every one of us.  Clickety-click.  The thought makes the couples a little giddy.  They feel that space is contagious.  They are here but also there, already in albums and slide projectors, filling picture frames with their microcosmic bodies, the minikin selves they are trying to become." -- Don Delillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49102-he-wanted-paper-and-something-to-write-with-some-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 18:23:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Don Delillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49102-he-wanted-paper-and-something-to-write-with-some-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He wanted paper and something to write with, some way to sustain a thought, to place it in the world." -- Don Delillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49104-crowds-scott-said-people-trudging-along-wide-streets-pushing-carts</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 18:26:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49104-crowds-scott-said-people-trudging-along-wide-streets-pushing-carts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Crowds, Scott said.  People trudging along wide streets, pushing carts or riding bikes, crowd after crowd in the long lens of the camera so they seem even closer together than they really are, totally jampacked, and I think of how they merge with the future, how the future makes room for the non-achiever, the trudger, the nonagressor, the nonindividual.  Totally calm in the long lens, crowd on top of crowd, pedaling, trudging, faceless, sort of surviving nicely." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49122-this-spiritualist-this-statistician-what-are-you-anyway</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 18:46:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49122-this-spiritualist-this-statistician-what-are-you-anyway]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This spiritualist, this statistician, what are you anyway?" -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49127-pavlov-was-fascinated-with-the-ideas-of-the-opposite-call</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 18:49:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49127-pavlov-was-fascinated-with-the-ideas-of-the-opposite-call]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pavlov was fascinated with the “ideas of the opposite”.  Call it a cluster of cells, somewhere on the cortex of the brain.  Helping to disintiguish pleasure from pain, light from dark, dominance from submission….but when somehow – starve them, traumatize, castrate them send them over into one of the transmarginal phases, past borders of their waking selves, past equivalent and paradoxical phases – you weaken this idea of the opposite, and here all at once is the paranoid patient, who would be master, yet now feels himself a slave…..who would be loved, but suffers his world’s indifference, and “I think”, Pavlov writing to Janet, “it is precisely the ultraparadoxical phase which is the base of the weakening of the idea of the opposite in our patients.  Our madmen, , our paranoid, maniac, schizoid, morally imbecilic.
Spectro shakes his head.  “You are putting response before stimulus.  Not at all.  Think about it.  He is out there, he can feel them coming, days in advance, but it is a reflex.  A reflex to something that is in the air right now, something were too coarsely put together to sense, but Slothrop can." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49130-what-s-this-what-are-the-antagonists-doing-here-infiltrating</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 19:03:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49130-what-s-this-what-are-the-antagonists-doing-here-infiltrating]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What’s this?  What are the antagonists doing here – infiltrating their own audience?  Well, they’re not really.  It’s somebody else’s audience at the moment, and these nightly spectacles are an appreciable part of the darkside hours of life of the rocket capital.  The chances for any paradox here, really, are less than you think." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49154-as-the-day-light-left-the-city-that-night-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 19:32:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49154-as-the-day-light-left-the-city-that-night-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As the day light left the city that night, the streetlamps were not up to anything like their usual candle-power.  It was difficult to make anything out clearly.  Ordinary social restraints were apt to be defective or not there at all.  The screaming that went on all night, ignored as background murmur during the day, now, absent the clamor of street traffic, had taken on urgency and despair – a chorale of pain just about to pass from its realm of the invisible into something that might actually have to be dealt with.  Figures which late at night appeared only in levels of grey were now seen to possess color, not the fashionable shades of daytime but blood reds, morgue yellows, and poison greens." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49161-but-a-few-choosing-to-venture-deeper-into-the-painful</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 19:42:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49161-but-a-few-choosing-to-venture-deeper-into-the-painful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But a few choosing to venture deeper into the painful corridors of their affliction, found after a while that they could now grind and polish ever more exotic surfaces, hyperboloidial and even stranger, eventually including what we must term ‘imaginary’ shapes (which some preferred to term invisible)." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49164-laboring-through-a-world-every-day-more-stultified-which-expected</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 19:51:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49164-laboring-through-a-world-every-day-more-stultified-which-expected]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Laboring through a world every day more stultified, which expected salvation in codes and governments, ever more willing to settle for suburban narratives and diminished payoffs--what were the chances of finding anyone else seeking to transcend that, and not even particularly aware of it?" -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49171-how-can-we-ultimately-fail-to-twig-that-the-apparent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 20:23:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Paul Virilio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49171-how-can-we-ultimately-fail-to-twig-that-the-apparent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How can we ultimately fail to twig that the apparent impiety of contemporary art is only ever the inverted image of sacred art, the reversal of the creator's initial  question: why is there something instead of nothing?" -- Paul Virilio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49274-if-what-s-always-distinguished-bad-writing--flat-characters-a-narrative-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 10:39:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49274-if-what-s-always-distinguished-bad-writing--flat-characters-a-narrative-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If what's always distinguished bad writing--flat characters, a narrative world that's clichéd and not recognizably human, etc.--is also a description of today's world, then bad writing becomes an ingenious mimesis of a bad world. If readers simply believe the world is stupid and shallow and mean, then [Bret] Ellis can write a mean shallow stupid novel that becomes a mordant deadpan commentary on the badness of everything. Look man, we'd probably most of us agree that these are dark times, and stupid ones, but do we need fiction that does nothing but dramatize how dark and stupid everything is? In dark times, the definition of good art would seem to be art that locates and applies CPR to those elements of what's human and magical that still live and glow despite the times' darkness. Really good fiction could have as dark a worldview as it wished, but it'd find a way both to depict this world and to illuminate the possibilities for being alive and human in it.

Postmodern irony and cynicism's become an end in itself, a measure of hip sophistication and literary savvy. Few artists dare to try to talk about ways of working toward redeeming what's wrong, because they'll look sentimental and naive to all the weary ironists. Irony's gone from liberating to enslaving. There's some great essay somewhere that has a line about irony being the song of the prisoner who's come to love his cage… The postmodern founders' patricidal work was great, but patricide produces orphans, and no amount of revelry can make up for the fact that writers my age have been literary orphans throughout our formative years.

We enter a spiritual puberty where we snap to the fact that the great transcendent horror is loneliness, excluded encagement in the self. Once we’ve hit this age, we will now give or take anything, wear any mask, to fit, be part-of, not be Alone, we young. The U.S. arts are our guide to inclusion. A how-to. We are shown how to fashion masks of ennui and jaded irony at a young age where the face is fictile enough to assume the shape of whatever it wears. And then it’s stuck there, the weary cynicism that saves us from gooey sentiment and unsophisticated naïveté. Sentiment equals naïveté on this continent.

You burn with hunger for food that does not exist.

A U. S. of modern A. where the State is not a team or a code, but a sort of sloppy intersection of desires and fears, where the only public consensus a boy must surrender to is the acknowledged primacy of straight-line pursuing this flat and short-sighted idea of personal happiness." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49275-within-sixty-minute-limits-or-one-hundred-yard-limits-or-the-limits-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 10:40:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49275-within-sixty-minute-limits-or-one-hundred-yard-limits-or-the-limits-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Within sixty-minute limits or one-hundred-yard limits or the limits of a game board, we can look for perfect moments or perfect structures. In my fiction I think this search sometimes turns out to be a cruel delusion.

No optimism, no pessimism. No homesickness for lost values or for the way fiction used to be written. 

Everybody seems to know everything. Subjects surface and are totally exhausted in a matter of days or weeks, totally played out by the publishing industry and the broadcast industry. Nothing is too arcane to escape the treatment, the process. Making things difficult for the reader is less an attack on the reader than it is on the age and its facile knowledge-market.  

The writer is the person who stands outside society, independent of affiliation and independent of influence. The writer is the man or woman who automatically takes a stance against his or her government. There are so many temptations for American writers to become part of the system and part of the structure that now, more than ever, we have to resist. American writers ought to stand and live in the margins, and be more dangerous. Writers in repressive societies are considered dangerous. That’s why so many of them are in jail.

Some people prefer to believe in conspiracy because they are made anxious by random acts. Believing in conspiracy is almost comforting because, in a sense, a conspiracy is a story we tell each other to ward off the dread of chaotic and random acts. Conspiracy offers coherence.

I see contemporary violence as a kind of sardonic response to the promise of consumer fulfillment in America...  I see this desperation against the backdrop of brightly colored packages and products and consumer happiness and every promise that American life makes day by day and minute by minute everywhere we go.  

Discarded pages mark the physical dimensions of a writer’s labor. 

Film allows us to examine ourselves in ways earlier societies could not—examine ourselves, imitate ourselves, extend ourselves, reshape our reality. It permeates our lives, this double vision, and also detaches us, turns some of us into actors doing walk-throughs. 

Every new novel stretches the term of the contract—let me live long enough to do one more book.

You become a serious novelist by living long enough." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49276-we-are-not-witnessing-the-flow-of-information-so-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 10:41:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49276-we-are-not-witnessing-the-flow-of-information-so-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are not witnessing the flow of information so much as pure spectacle, or information made sacred, ritually unreadable. The small monitors of the office, home and car become a kind of idolatry here, where crowds might gather in astonishment.

“Hysteria at high speeds, day to day, minute to minute. People in free societies don’t have to fear the pathology of the state. We create our own frenzy, our own mass convulsions, driven by thinking machines that we have no final authority over. The frenzy is barely noticeable most of the time. It’s simply how we live.” She finished with a laugh…

THE TRUTH WAS MAPPED IN SLOW AND CERTAIN DECLINE.

He was seeing something elaborately different from what he encountered step by step in the ordinary run of hours. He had to learn how to see it correctly, find a crack in the world where it might fit." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49277-the-worst-thing-is-not-that-the-world-is-unfree</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 10:42:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49277-the-worst-thing-is-not-that-the-world-is-unfree]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worst thing is not that the world is unfree, but that people have unlearned their liberty.

The more indifferent people are to politics, to the interests of others, the more obsessed they become with their own faces. The individualism of our time.

Not being able to fall asleep and not allowing oneself to move: the marital bed.

If high culture is coming to an end, it is also the end of you and your paradoxical ideas, because paradox as such belongs to high culture and not to childish prattle. You remind me of the young men who supported the Nazis or communists not out of cowardice or out of opportunism but out of an excess of intelligence. For nothing requires a greater effort of thought than arguments to justify the rule of nonthought… You are the brilliant ally of your own gravediggers.

In the world of highways, a beautiful landscape means: an island of beauty connected by a long line with other islands of beauty.

How to live in a world with which you disagree? How to live with people when you neither share their suffering nor their joys? When you know that you don’t belong among them?... our century refuses to acknowledge anyone’s right to disagree with the world…All that remains of such a place is the memory, the ideal of a cloister, the dream of a cloister… 

Humor can only exist when people are still capable of recognizing some border between the important and the unimportant. And nowadays this border has become unrecognizable.

The majority of people lead their existence within a small idyllic circle bounded by their family, their home, and their work... They live in a secure realm somewhere between good and evil. They are sincerely horrified by the sight of a killer. And yet all you have to do is remove them from this peaceful circle and they, too, turn into murderers, without quite knowing how it happened.

The longing for order is at the same time a longing for death, because life is an incessant disruption of order. Or to put it the other way around: the desire for order is a virtuous pretext, an excuse for virulent misanthropy.

A long time a go a certain Cynic philosopher proudly paraded around Athens in a moth-eaten coat, hoping that everyone would admire his contempt for convention. When Socrates met him, he said: Through the hole in your coat I see your vanity. Your dirt, too, dear sir, is self-indulgent and your self-indulgence is dirty.

You are always living below the level of true existence, you bitter weed, you anthropomorphized vat of vinegar! You’re full of acid, which bubbles inside you like an alchemist’s brew. Your highest wish is to be able to see all around you the same ugliness as you carry inside yourself. That’s the only way you can feel for a few moments some kind of peace between yourself and the world. That’s because the world, which is beautiful, seems horrible to you, torments you and excludes you.

If the novel is successful, it must necessarily be wiser than its author. This is why many excellent French intellectuals write mediocre novels. They are always more intelligent than their books.

By a certain age, coincidences lose their magic, no longer surprise, become run-of-the-mill.

Any new possibility that existence acquires, even the least likely, transforms everything about existence." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49278-in-order-to-generate-ideological-paradigms-sufficient-to-explain-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 10:43:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Russell Berman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49278-in-order-to-generate-ideological-paradigms-sufficient-to-explain-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In order to generate ideological paradigms sufficient to explain the demands for military sacrifice, intellectuals rearticulate the cultural project: the battle for culture becomes the battle for the people’s culture which in turn endows participation in the war effort with a democratic appearance. The de facto defense of the empire and imperialism is inverted, by the magic of culture, into a defense of the people." -- Russell Berman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49280-it-s-easier-and-sociabler-to-talk-technique-than-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 10:44:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by John Barth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49280-it-s-easier-and-sociabler-to-talk-technique-than-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s easier and sociabler to talk technique than it is to make art." -- John Barth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49281-a-perceptive-french-critic-has-argued-that-in-an-age</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 10:45:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by George Steiner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49281-a-perceptive-french-critic-has-argued-that-in-an-age]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A perceptive French critic has argued that in an age of deepening illiteracy, when even the educated have only a smattering of classical or theological knowledge, erudition is of itself a kind of fantasy, a surrealistic construct." -- George Steiner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49282-logic-and-morality-made-it-impossible-to-accept-an-illogical</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 10:46:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Primo Levi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49282-logic-and-morality-made-it-impossible-to-accept-an-illogical]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Logic and morality made it impossible to accept an illogical and immoral reality; they engendered a rejection of reality which as a rule led the cultivated man rapidly to despair. But the varieties of the man-animal are innumerable, and I saw and have described men of refined culture, especially if young, throw all this overboard, simplify and barbarize themselves, and survive. A simple man, accustomed not to ask questions of himself, was beyond the reach of the useless torment of asking himself why.

The harsher the oppression, the more widespread among the oppressed is the willingness, with all its infinite nuances and motivations, to collaborate: terror, ideological seduction, servile imitation of the victor, myopic desire for any power whatsoever… Certainly, the greatest responsibility lies with the system, the very structure of the totalitarian state; the concurrent guilt on the part of individual big and small collaborators is always difficult to evaluate… they are the vectors and instruments of the system’s guilt… the room for choices (especially moral choices) was reduced to zero" -- Primo Levi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49283-the-strains-and-stresses-suffered-by-the-individual-in-society</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 10:46:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Herbert Marcuse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49283-the-strains-and-stresses-suffered-by-the-individual-in-society]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The strains and stresses suffered by the individual in society are grounded in the normal functioning of that society (and of the individual!) rather than in its disturbances and diseases." -- Herbert Marcuse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49284-when-an-innocent-youth-can-have-his-eyes-destroyed-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 10:48:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49284-when-an-innocent-youth-can-have-his-eyes-destroyed-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When an innocent youth can have his eyes destroyed, a Christian should either lose his faith or consent to having his eyes destroyed.

Thus, in a middle course between these heights and depths, they drifted through life rather than lived, the prey of aimless days and sterile memories, like wandering shadows that could have acquired substance only by consenting to root themselves in the solid earth of their distress. Thus, too, they came to know the incorrigible sorrow of all prisoners and exiles, which is to live in company with a memory that serves no purpose." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49285-with-the-industrial-proliferation-of-visual-and-audiovisual-prostheses-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 10:49:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Paul Virilio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49285-with-the-industrial-proliferation-of-visual-and-audiovisual-prostheses-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With the industrial proliferation of visual and audiovisual prostheses and unrestrained use of instantaneous-transmission equipment from earliest childhood onwards, we now routinely see the encoding of increasingly elaborate mental images together with a steady decline in retention rates and recall. In other words we are looking at the rapid collapse of mnemonic consolidation.  This collapse seems only natural, if one remembers a contrario that seeing, and its spatio-temporal organization, precede gesture and speech and their coordination in knowing, recognizing, making known (as images of our thoughts), our thoughts themselves and cognitive functions, which are never ever passive." -- Paul Virilio]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
