<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1085208-bonnie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1085208-bonnie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 12:23:58 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19274-ozymandias-i-met-a-traveller-from-an-antique-land-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 12:23:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bonnie add a quote by Percy Bysshe Shelley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19274-ozymandias-i-met-a-traveller-from-an-antique-land-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;b&gt;Ozymandias&lt;/b&gt;

I met a traveller from an antique land
Who said: &quot;Two vast and trunkless legs of stone
Stand in the desert. Near them on the sand,
Half sunk, a shattered visage lies, whose frown
And wrinkled lip and sneer of cold command
Tell that its sculptor well those passions read
Which yet survive, stamped on these lifeless things,
The hand that mocked them and the heart that fed.
And on the pedestal these words appear:
'My name is Ozymandias, King of Kings:
Look on my works, ye mighty, and despair!'
Nothing beside remains. Round the decay
Of that colossal wreck, boundless and bare,
The lone and level sands stretch far away." -- Percy Bysshe Shelley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22323-all-things-are-subject-to-interpretation-whichever-interpretation-prevails-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 11:41:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bonnie add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22323-all-things-are-subject-to-interpretation-whichever-interpretation-prevails-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All things are subject to interpretation. Whichever interpretation prevails at a given time is a function of power and not truth." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99345-i-am-somehow-less-interested-in-the-weight-and-convolutions</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 10:37:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bonnie add a quote by Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99345-i-am-somehow-less-interested-in-the-weight-and-convolutions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am, somehow, less interested in the weight and convolutions of Einstein’s brain than in the near certainty that people of equal talent have lived and died in cotton fields and sweatshops." -- Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315932-once-a-little-boy-sent-me-a-charming-card-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 13:49:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bonnie add a quote by Maurice Sendak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315932-once-a-little-boy-sent-me-a-charming-card-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once a little boy sent me a charming card with a little drawing on it. I loved it. I answer all my children’s letters — sometimes very hastily — but this one I lingered over. I sent him a card and I drew a picture of a Wild Thing on it. I wrote, “Dear Jim: I loved your card.” Then I got a letter back from his mother and she said, “Jim loved your card so much he ate it.” That to me was one of the highest compliments I’ve ever received. He didn’t care that it was an original Maurice Sendak drawing or anything. He saw it, he loved it, he ate it." -- Maurice Sendak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1166336-so-long-as-i-confine-my-activities-to-social-service</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 19:21:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bonnie add a quote by Helen Keller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1166336-so-long-as-i-confine-my-activities-to-social-service]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So long as I confine my activities to social service and the blind, they compliment me extravagantly, calling me ‘arch priestess of the sightless,’ ‘wonder woman,’ and a ‘modern miracle.’ But when it comes to a discussion of poverty, and I maintain that it is the result of wrong economics—that the industrial system under which we live is at the root of much of the physical deafness and blindness in the world—that is a different matter! It is laudable to give aid to the handicapped. Superficial charities make smooth the way of the prosperous; but to advocate that all human beings should have leisure and comfort, the decencies and refinements of life, is a Utopian dream, and one who seriously contemplates its realization indeed must be deaf, dumb, and blind." -- Helen Keller]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
