<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1086141-troy-gibson]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1086141-troy-gibson" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:15:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45228-all-truth-is-given-by-revelation-either-general-or-special</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:15:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Troy add a quote by Jonathan Edwards]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45228-all-truth-is-given-by-revelation-either-general-or-special]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All truth is given by revelation, either general or special, and it must be received by reason. Reason is the God-given means for discovering the truth that God discloses, whether in his world or his Word. While God wants to reach the heart with truth, he does not bypass the mind." -- Jonathan Edwards]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45234-to-square-the-records-however-it-should-be-said-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:32:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Troy add a quote by A.W. Tozer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45234-to-square-the-records-however-it-should-be-said-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To square the records, however, it should be said that if the Calvinist does not rise as high, he usually stays up longer. He places more emphasis on the Holy Scriptures which never change, while his opposite number (as the newspapers say) tends to judge his spiritual condition by the state of his feelings, which change constantly. This may be the reason that so many Calvinistic churches remain orthodox for centuries, at least in doctrine, while many churches of the Arminian persuasion often go liberal in one generation." -- A.W. Tozer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45237-there-are-two-kinds-of-people-in-the-world-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:36:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Troy add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45237-there-are-two-kinds-of-people-in-the-world-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two kinds of people in the world, the conscious dogmatists and the unconscious dogmatists. I have always found myself that the unconscious dogmatists were by far the most dogmatic." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45241-christians-simply-haven-t-developed-christian-tools-of-analysis-to-examine</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:38:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Troy add a quote by Os Guinness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45241-christians-simply-haven-t-developed-christian-tools-of-analysis-to-examine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Christians simply haven't developed Christian tools of analysis to examine culture properly. Or rather, the tools the church once had have grown rusty or been mislaid. What often happens is that Christians wake up to some incident or issue and suddenly realize they need to analyze what's going on. Then, having no tools of their own, they lean across and borrow the tools nearest them.

They don't realize that, in their haste, they are borrowing not an isolated tool but a whole philosophical toolbox laden with tools which have their own particular bias to every problem (a Trojan horse in the toolbox, if you like). The toolbox may be Freudian, Hindu or Marxist. Occasionally, the toolbox is right-wing; more often today it is liberal or left-wing (the former mainly in North America, the latter mainly in Europe). Rarely - and this is all that matters to us - is it consistently or coherently Christian.

When Christians use tools for analysis (or bandy certain terms of description) which have non-Christian assumptions embedded within them, these tools (and terms) eventually act back on them like wearing someone else's glasses or walking in someone else's shoes. The tools shape the user. Their recent failure to think critically about culture has made Christians uniquely susceptible to this." -- Os Guinness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45242-the-curse-should-no-longer-rest-upon-the-world-itself</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:39:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Troy add a quote by Abraham Kuyper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45242-the-curse-should-no-longer-rest-upon-the-world-itself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The curse should no longer rest upon the world itself, but upon that which is sinful in it, and instead of monastic flight  from the world the duty is now emphasized of serving God  in the world, in every position in life." -- Abraham Kuyper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45244-it-sounds-as-if-you-supposed-that-argument-was-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:40:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Troy add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45244-it-sounds-as-if-you-supposed-that-argument-was-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It sounds as if you supposed that argument was the way to keep him out of the Enemy's clutches. That might have been so if he had lived a few centuries earlier. At that time the humans still knew pretty well when a thing was proved and when it was not; and if it was proved they really believed it. They still connected thinking with doing and were prepared to alter their way of life as the result of a chain of reasoning. But what with the weekly press and other such weapons we have largely altered that. Your man has been accustomed, ever since he was a boy, to have a dozen incompatible philosophies dancing about together inside his head. He doesn't think of doctrines as primarily 'true' or 'false', but as 'academic' or 'practical', 'outworn' or 'contemporary', 'conventional' or 'ruthless'. Jargon, not argument, is your best ally in keeping him from the Church." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45246-what-is-today-a-matter-of-academic-speculation-begins-tomorrow</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:41:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Troy add a quote by J. Gresham Machen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45246-what-is-today-a-matter-of-academic-speculation-begins-tomorrow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is today a matter of academic speculation begins tomorrow to move armies and pull down empires." -- J. Gresham Machen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45250-those-who-have-not-discovered-that-worldview-is-the-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:43:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Troy add a quote by Richard Weaver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45250-those-who-have-not-discovered-that-worldview-is-the-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who have not discovered that worldview is the most important thing about a man… should consider the train of circumstances which have with perfect logic proceeded from this. The denial of universals carries with it the denial of everything transcending experience. The denial of everything transcending experience means inevitably… the denial of truth. With the denial of objective truth there is not escape from the relativism of “man the measure of all things." -- Richard Weaver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45251-faith-is-indeed-intellectual-it-involves-an-apprehension-of-certain</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:44:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Troy add a quote by J. Gresham Machen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45251-faith-is-indeed-intellectual-it-involves-an-apprehension-of-certain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Faith is indeed intellectual; it involves an apprehension of certain things as facts; and vain is the modern effort to divorce faith from knowledge. But although faith is intellectual, it is not only intellectual. You cannot have faith without having knowledge; but you will not have faith if you have only knowledge." -- J. Gresham Machen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45253-if-religious-books-are-not-widely-circulated-among-the-masses</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:45:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Troy add a quote by Daniel Webster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45253-if-religious-books-are-not-widely-circulated-among-the-masses]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If religious books are not widely circulated among the masses in this country, I do not know what is going to become of us as a nation. If truth be not diffused, then error will be. If God and His Word are not known and received, the devil and his works will gain the ascendency. If the evangelical volume does not reach every hamlet, the pages of a corrupt and licentious literature will. If the power of the gospel is not felt throughout the length and breadth of this land, anarchy and misrule, degradation and misery, corruption and darkness will reign without mitigation or end." -- Daniel Webster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45254-god-helps-those-who-cannot-help-themselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:46:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Troy add a quote by Charles H. Spurgeon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45254-god-helps-those-who-cannot-help-themselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God helps those who cannot help themselves." -- Charles H. Spurgeon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45257-there-is-an-appearance-of-humility-in-the-protestation-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:51:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Troy add a quote by Leslie Newbigin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45257-there-is-an-appearance-of-humility-in-the-protestation-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is an appearance of humility in the protestation that the truth is much greater than any one of us can grasp, but if this is used to invalidate all claims to discern the truth it is in fact an arrogant claim to a kind of knowledge which is superior to [all others]...We have to ask: 'What is the [absolute] vantage ground from which you claim to be able to relativize all the absolute claims these different scriptures make?" -- Leslie Newbigin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45258-how-could-you-possibly-know-that-no-religion-can-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:52:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Troy add a quote by Tim Keller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45258-how-could-you-possibly-know-that-no-religion-can-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How could you possibly know that no religion can see the whole truth unless you yourself have the superior, comprehensive knowledge of spiritual reality you just claimed non of the religions have?" -- Tim Keller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45260-suppose-we-concede-that-if-i-had-been-born-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:55:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Troy add a quote by Alvin Plantinga]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45260-suppose-we-concede-that-if-i-had-been-born-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suppose we concede that if I had been born of Muslim parents in Morocco rather than Christian parents in Michigan, my beliefs would be quite different.  [But] the same goes for the pluralist...If the pluralist had been born in [Morocco] he probably wouldn't be a pluralist.  Does it follow that...his pluralist beliefs are produced in him by an unreliable belief-producing process?" -- Alvin Plantinga]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45262-a-religion-can-be-judged-only-on-the-basis-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 09:06:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Troy add a quote by C. John Sommerville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45262-a-religion-can-be-judged-only-on-the-basis-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A religion can be judged only on the basis of another religion." -- C. John Sommerville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45264-it-is-no-more-narrow-to-claim-that-one-religion</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 09:06:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Troy add a quote by Tim Keller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45264-it-is-no-more-narrow-to-claim-that-one-religion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is no more narrow to claim that one religion is right than to claim that one way to think about all religions (namely that all are equal) is right.  We are all exclusive in our beliefs about religion, but in different ways." -- Tim Keller]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
