<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1086583-emmily-bristol]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1086583-emmily-bristol" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:35:50 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176379-the-four-noble-truths-that-there-is-suffering-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:35:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Sid Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176379-the-four-noble-truths-that-there-is-suffering-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["... the four noble truths: that there is suffering, that it has an origin, that there is a cessation of suffering, and that there is a path to that cessation." -- Sid Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20376-the-master-s-tools-will-never-dismantle-the-master-s-house</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 15:26:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20376-the-master-s-tools-will-never-dismantle-the-master-s-house]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The master's tools will never dismantle the master's house" -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10837-happiness-is-the-consequence-of-personal-effort-you-fight-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 15:47:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10837-happiness-is-the-consequence-of-personal-effort-you-fight-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is the consequence of personal effort.  You fight for it, strive for it, insist upon it, and sometimes even travel around the world looking for it.  You have to participate relentlessly in the manifestations of your own blessings.  And once you have achieved a state of happiness, you must never become lax about maintaining it.  You must make a mighty effort to keep swimming upward into that happiness forever, to stay afloat on top of it." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32091-having-a-baby-is-like-getting-a-tattoo-on-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 15:49:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32091-having-a-baby-is-like-getting-a-tattoo-on-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Having a baby is like getting a tattoo on your face. You really need to be certain it's what you want before you commit." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43060-we-search-for-happiness-everywhere-but-we-are-like-tolstoy-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 15:50:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43060-we-search-for-happiness-everywhere-but-we-are-like-tolstoy-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We search for happiness everywhere, but we are like Tolstoy's fabled beggar who spent his life sitting on a pot of gold, under him the whole time.  Your treasure--your perfection--is within you already.  But to claim it, you must leave the buy commotion of the mind and abandon the desires of the ego and enter into the silence of the heart." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65002-when-you-re-lost-in-those-woods-it-sometimes-takes-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 15:51:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65002-when-you-re-lost-in-those-woods-it-sometimes-takes-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you're lost in those woods, it sometimes takes you a while to realize that you are lost. For the longest time, you can convince yourself that you've just wandered off the path, that you'll find your way back to the trailhead any moment now. Then night falls again and again, and you still have no idea where you are, and it's time to admit that you have bewildered yourself so far off the path that you don't even know from which direction the sun rises anymore." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176412-the-augusteum-warns-me-not-to-get-attached-to-any</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 17:41:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176412-the-augusteum-warns-me-not-to-get-attached-to-any]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Augusteum warns me not to get attached to any obsolete ideas about who I am, what I represent, whom I belong to, or what function I may once have intended to serve." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176414-because-no-retreat-from-the-world-can-mask-what-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 17:43:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176414-because-no-retreat-from-the-world-can-mask-what-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because no retreat from the world can mask what is in your face." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371653-first-lord-no-tattoos-may-neither-chinese-symbol-for-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 00:55:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371653-first-lord-no-tattoos-may-neither-chinese-symbol-for-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First, Lord: No tattoos. May neither Chinese symbol for truth nor Winnie-the-Pooh holding the FSU logo stain her tender haunches.

May she be Beautiful but not Damaged, for it’s the Damage that draws the creepy soccer coach’s eye, not the Beauty.

When the Crystal Meth is offered, May she remember the parents who cut her grapes in half And stick with Beer.

Guide her, protect her

When crossing the street, stepping onto boats, swimming in the ocean, swimming in pools, walking near pools, standing on the subway platform, crossing 86th Street, stepping off of boats, using mall restrooms, getting on and off escalators, driving on country roads while arguing, leaning on large windows, walking in parking lots, riding Ferris wheels, roller-coasters, log flumes, or anything called “Hell Drop,” “Tower of Torture,” or “The Death Spiral Rock ‘N Zero G Roll featuring Aerosmith,” and standing on any kind of balcony ever, anywhere, at any age.

Lead her away from Acting but not all the way to Finance. Something where she can make her own hours but still feel intellectually fulfilled and get outside sometimes And not have to wear high heels.

What would that be, Lord? Architecture? Midwifery? Golf course design? I’m asking You, because if I knew, I’d be doing it, Youdammit.

May she play the Drums to the fiery rhythm of her Own Heart with the sinewy strength of her Own Arms, so she need Not Lie With Drummers.

Grant her a Rough Patch from twelve to seventeen. Let her draw horses and be interested in Barbies for much too long, For childhood is short – a Tiger Flower blooming Magenta for one day – And adulthood is long and dry-humping in cars will wait.

O Lord, break the Internet forever, That she may be spared the misspelled invective of her peers And the online marketing campaign for Rape Hostel V: Girls Just Wanna Get Stabbed.

And when she one day turns on me and calls me a Bitch in front of Hollister, Give me the strength, Lord, to yank her directly into a cab in front of her friends, For I will not have that Shit. I will not have it.

And should she choose to be a Mother one day, be my eyes, Lord, that I may see her, lying on a blanket on the floor at 4:50 A.M., all-at-once exhausted, bored, and in love with the little creature whose poop is leaking up its back.

“My mother did this for me once,” she will realize as she cleans feces off her baby’s neck. “My mother did this for me.” And the delayed gratitude will wash over her as it does each generation and she will make a Mental Note to call me. And she will forget. But I’ll know, because I peeped it with Your God eyes." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/368050-by-the-way-when-oprah-winfrey-is-suggesting-you-may</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 00:55:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/368050-by-the-way-when-oprah-winfrey-is-suggesting-you-may]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By the way, when Oprah Winfrey is suggesting you may have overextended yourself, you need to examine your fucking life." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369960-lesson-learned-when-people-say-you-really-really-must-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 00:56:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369960-lesson-learned-when-people-say-you-really-really-must-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lesson learned? When people say, &quot;You really, really must&quot; do something, it means you don't really have to. No one ever says, &quot;You really, really must deliver the baby during labor.&quot; When it's true, it doesn't need to be said." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/373001-to-say-i-m-an-overrated-troll-when-you-have-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 00:56:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/373001-to-say-i-m-an-overrated-troll-when-you-have-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To say I’m an overrated troll, when you have never even seen me guard a bridge, is patently unfair." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369811-a-coworker-at-snl-dropped-an-angry-c-bomb-on-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 00:56:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369811-a-coworker-at-snl-dropped-an-angry-c-bomb-on-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A coworker at SNL dropped an angry c-bomb on me and i had the weirdest reaction. To my surprise, I blurted, &quot;No. You don't get to call me that. My parents love me. I'm not some Adult Child of an Alcoholic that's going to take that shit." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369872-read-when-your-baby-is-finally-down-for-the-night</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 00:57:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369872-read-when-your-baby-is-finally-down-for-the-night]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Read! When your baby is finally down for the night, pick up a juicy book like &lt;i&gt;Eat, Pray, Love&lt;/i&gt; or &lt;i&gt;Pride and Prejudice&lt;/i&gt; or my personal favorite, &lt;i&gt;Understanding Sleep Disorders: Narcolepsy and Apnea; A Clinical Study&lt;/i&gt;. Taking some time to read each night really taught me how to feign narcolepsy when my husband asked me what my “plan” was for taking down the Christmas tree." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372989-i-experienced-car-creepery-at-thirteen-i-was-walking-home</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 00:57:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372989-i-experienced-car-creepery-at-thirteen-i-was-walking-home]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I experienced car creepery at thirteen. I was walking home from middle school past a place called the World’s Largest Aquarium—which, legally, I don’t know how they could call it that, because it was obviously an average-sized aquarium. Maybe I should start referring to myself as the World’s Tallest Man and see how that goes? Anyway, I was walking home alone from school and I was wearing a dress. A dude drove by and yelled, “Nice tits.” Embarrassed and enraged, I screamed after him, “Suck my dick.” Sure, it didn’t make any sense, but at least I don’t hold in my anger." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391203-it-s-like-being-a-little-kid-again-parading-around-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 00:57:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391203-it-s-like-being-a-little-kid-again-parading-around-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's like being a little kid again, parading around in a nightgown tucked into your underpants, believing it looks terrific." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372991-don-t-waste-your-energy-trying-to-educate-or-change-opinions</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 00:58:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372991-don-t-waste-your-energy-trying-to-educate-or-change-opinions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don’t waste your energy trying to educate or change opinions; go over, under, through, and opinions will change organically when you’re the boss. Or they won’t. Who cares? Do your thing, and don’t care if they like it." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384189-you-could-put-a-blond-wig-on-a-hot-water-heater</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 00:58:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384189-you-could-put-a-blond-wig-on-a-hot-water-heater]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You could put a blond wig on a hot-water heater and some dude would try to fuck it." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372995-so-my-unsolicited-advice-to-women-in-the-workplace-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 00:59:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372995-so-my-unsolicited-advice-to-women-in-the-workplace-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So, my unsolicited advice to women in the workplace is this. When faced with sexism, or ageism, or lookism, or even really aggressive Buddhism, ask yourself the following question: “Is this person in between me and what I want to do?” If the answer is no, ignore it and move on. Your energy is better used doing your work and outpacing people that way. Then, when you’re in charge, don’t hire the people who were jerky to you." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372984-my-ability-to-turn-good-news-into-anxiety-is-rivaled</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 00:59:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372984-my-ability-to-turn-good-news-into-anxiety-is-rivaled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My ability to turn good news into anxiety is rivaled only by my ability to turn anxiety into chin acne." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372994-i-ve-always-been-able-to-tell-a-lot-about-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 01:00:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372994-i-ve-always-been-able-to-tell-a-lot-about-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’ve always been able to tell a lot about people by whether they ask me about my scar. Most people never ask, but if it comes up naturally somehow and I offer up the story, they are quite interested. Some people are just dumb: 'Did a cat scratch you?' God bless. Those sweet dumdums I never mind. Sometimes it is a fun sociology litmus test, like when my friend Ricky asked me, 'Did they ever catch the black guy that did that to you?' Hmmm. It was not a black guy, Ricky, and I never said it was." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394284-gay-people-don-t-actually-try-to-convert-people-that-s-jehovah-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 01:01:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394284-gay-people-don-t-actually-try-to-convert-people-that-s-jehovah-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Gay people don’t actually try to convert people. That’s Jehovah’s Witnesses you’re thinking of." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/387407-this-is-what-i-tell-young-women-who-ask-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 01:01:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/387407-this-is-what-i-tell-young-women-who-ask-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what I tell young women who ask me for career advice. People are going to try to trick you. To make you feel that you are in competition with one another. &quot;You're up for a promotion. If they go for a woman, it'll be between you and Barbara.&quot; Don't be fooled. You're not in competition with other women. You're in competition with &lt;i&gt;everyone&lt;/i&gt;." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394312-it-s-a-burden-being-able-to-control-situations-with-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 01:02:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394312-it-s-a-burden-being-able-to-control-situations-with-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s a burden, being able to control situations with my hyper-vigilance, but it’s my lot in life." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394285-make-statements-also-applies-to-us-women-speak-in-statements</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 01:02:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394285-make-statements-also-applies-to-us-women-speak-in-statements]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["MAKE STATEMENTS also applies to us women: Speak in statements instead of apologetic questions. No one wants to go to a doctor who says, “I’m going to be your surgeon? I’m here to talk to you about your procedure? I was first in my class at Johns Hopkins, so?” Make statements, with your actions and your voice." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398794-obviously-as-an-adult-i-realize-this-girl-on-girl-sabotage-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 01:03:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398794-obviously-as-an-adult-i-realize-this-girl-on-girl-sabotage-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Obviously, as an adult I realize this girl-on-girl sabotage is the third worst kind of female behavior, right behind saying &quot;like&quot; all the time and leaving your baby in a dumpster." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414466-some-people-say-never-let-them-see-you-cry-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 01:03:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414466-some-people-say-never-let-them-see-you-cry-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people say, “Never let them see you cry.” I say, if you’re so mad you could just cry, then cry. It terrifies everyone." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153863-when-prescribing-one-of-the-drugs-i-take-my-doctor</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 01:05:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Michael J. Fox]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153863-when-prescribing-one-of-the-drugs-i-take-my-doctor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When prescribing one of the drugs I take, my doctor warned me of a common side effect: exaggerated, intensely vivid dreams. To be honest, I've never really noticed the difference. I've always dreamt big." -- Michael J. Fox]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/168415-chris-topher-reeve-wisely-parsed-the-difference-between-optimism-and-hope</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 01:06:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Michael J. Fox]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/168415-chris-topher-reeve-wisely-parsed-the-difference-between-optimism-and-hope]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chris[topher] Reeve wisely parsed the difference between optimism and hope. Unlike optimism, he said, 'Hope is the product of knowledge and the projection of where the knowledge can take us." -- Michael J. Fox]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314479-the-only-thing-that-separates-any-one-of-us-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 01:07:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmily add a quote by Michael J. Fox]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314479-the-only-thing-that-separates-any-one-of-us-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only thing that separates any one of us from excellence is fear and the opposite of fear is faith. I am careful not to confuse excellence with perfection. Excellence I can reach for, perfection is God’s business." -- Michael J. Fox]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
