<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1087615-rachel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1087615-rachel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 00:59:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 00:59:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We accept the love we think we deserve." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 01:00:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 01:00:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467-life-is-what-happens-to-you-while-you-re-busy-making</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 01:02:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Allen Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467-life-is-what-happens-to-you-while-you-re-busy-making]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is what happens to you while you're busy making other plans." -- Allen Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2852-art-is-the-reason-i-get-up-in-the-morning</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 01:02:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Ani DiFranco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2852-art-is-the-reason-i-get-up-in-the-morning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Art is the reason I get up in the morning, but the definition ends there. It doesn't seem fair that I'm living for something I can't even define." -- Ani DiFranco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35446-what-about-little-microphones-what-if-everyone-swallowed-them-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 01:04:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35446-what-about-little-microphones-what-if-everyone-swallowed-them-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What about little microphones? What if everyone swallowed them, and they played the sounds of our hearts through little speakers, which could be in the pouches of our overalls? When you skateboarded down the street at night you could hear everyone's heartbeat, and they could hear yours, sort of like sonar. One weird thing is, I wonder if everyone's hearts would start to beat at the same time, like how women who live together have their menstrual periods at the same time, which I know about, but don't really want to know about. That would be so weird, except that the place in the hospital where babies are born would sound like a crystal chandelier in a houseboat, because the babies wouldn't have had time to match up their heartbeats yet. And at the finish line at the end of the New York City Marathon it would sound like war." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
