<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1087189-ashley-cale]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1087189-ashley-cale" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 20:10:40 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338274-love-feels-no-burden-thinks-nothing-of-its-trouble-attempts</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 20:10:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by Thomas A. Kempis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338274-love-feels-no-burden-thinks-nothing-of-its-trouble-attempts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love feels no burden, thinks nothing of its trouble, attempts what is above its strength, pleads no excuse for impossibility, for it thinks all things are lawful for itself and all things are possible" -- Thomas A. Kempis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/348383-love-is-a-mighty-power-a-great-and-complete-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 20:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by Thomas à Kempis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/348383-love-is-a-mighty-power-a-great-and-complete-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a mighty power, a great and complete good; Love alone lightens every burden, and makes the rough places smooth. It bears every hardship as though it were nothing, and renders all bitterness sweet and acceptable. The love of Jesus is noble, and inspires us to great deeds; it moves us always to desire perfection. Love aspires to high things, and is held back by nothing base. Love longs to be free, a stranger to every worldly desire, lest its inner vision become dimmed, and lest worldly self-interest hinder it or ill-fortune cast it down. Nothing is sweeter than love, nothing stronger, nothing higher, nothing wider, nothing more pleasant, nothing fuller or better in heaven or earth; for love is born of God, and can rest only in God above all created things.

Love flies, runs, leaps for joy; it is free and unrestrained. Love gives all for all, resting in One who is highest above all things, from whom every good flows and proceeds. Love does not regard the gifts, but turns to the Giver of all good gifts. Love knows no limits, but ardently transcends all bounds. Love feels no burden, takes no account of toil, attempts things beyond its strength; love sees nothing as impossible, for it feels able to achieve all things. Love therefore does great things; it is strange and effective; while he who lacks love faints and fails." -- Thomas à Kempis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53905-be-not-angry-that-you-cannot-make-others-as-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 20:11:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by Thomas a Kempis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53905-be-not-angry-that-you-cannot-make-others-as-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be not angry that you cannot make others as you wish them to be, since you cannot make yourself as you wish to be." -- Thomas a Kempis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5920-hope-is-the-thing-with-feathers-that-perches-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 20:11:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by Emily Dickinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5920-hope-is-the-thing-with-feathers-that-perches-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hope is the thing with feathers 
That perches in the soul 
And sings the tune without the words 
And never stops at all." -- Emily Dickinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11780-the-best-moments-in-reading-are-when-you-come-across</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 20:13:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by Alan Bennett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11780-the-best-moments-in-reading-are-when-you-come-across]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best moments in reading are when you come across something - a thought, a feeling, a way of looking at things - which you had thought special and particular to you. And now, here it is, set down by someone else, a person you have never met, someone even who is long dead. And it is as if a hand has come out, and taken yours" -- Alan Bennett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64538-that-mercy-towards-one-set-of-creatures-was-cruelty-towards</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 20:18:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by Thomas Hardy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64538-that-mercy-towards-one-set-of-creatures-was-cruelty-towards]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That mercy towards one set of creatures was cruelty towards another sickened his sense of harmony. As you got older, and felt yourself to be at the center of your time, and not at a point in its circumference, as you had felt when you were little, you were seized with a sort of shuddering, he perceived. All around you there seemed to be something glaring, garish, rattling, and the noises and glares hit upon the little cell called your life, and shook it, and warped it." -- Thomas Hardy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55819-people-who-know-little-are-usually-great-talkers-while-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 20:19:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by Jean Jacques Rousseau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55819-people-who-know-little-are-usually-great-talkers-while-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People who know little are usually great talkers, while men who know much say little." -- Jean Jacques Rousseau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159806-this-i-believe-is-the-appropriate-image-of-human-intercourse</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 20:21:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by Michael Joseph Oakeshott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159806-this-i-believe-is-the-appropriate-image-of-human-intercourse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This, I believe, is the appropriate image of human intercourse -- appropriate because it recognizes the qualities, the diversities, and the proper relationships of human utterances.  As civilized human beings, we are the inheritors, neither of an inquiry about ourselves and the world, nor of an accumulating body of information, but of a conversation, begun in the primeval forests and extended and made more articulate in the course of centuries.  It is a conversation which goes on both in public and within each of ourselves." -- Michael Joseph Oakeshott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247878-never-apologise-for-showing-feeling-when-you-do-so-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 20:21:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by Edmund Burke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247878-never-apologise-for-showing-feeling-when-you-do-so-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never apologise for showing feeling. When you do so, you apologise for the truth." -- Edmund Burke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50191-reading-furnishes-the-mind-only-with-materials-of-knowledge-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 21:46:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by John Locke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50191-reading-furnishes-the-mind-only-with-materials-of-knowledge-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reading furnishes the mind only with materials of knowledge; it is thinking that makes what we read ours." -- John Locke]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
