<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1087162-jardley]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1087162-jardley" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 10:12:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1776-remember-if-the-time-should-come-when-you-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 10:12:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1776-remember-if-the-time-should-come-when-you-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember, if the time should come when you have to make a choice between what is right and what is easy, remember what happened to a boy who was good, and kind, and brave, because he strayed across the path of Lord Voldemort.  Remember Cedric Diggory." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3670-it-does-not-do-to-dwell-on-dreams-and-forget</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 16:11:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3670-it-does-not-do-to-dwell-on-dreams-and-forget]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It does not do to dwell on dreams and forget to live." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24991-do-not-pity-the-dead-harry-pity-the-living-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 16:13:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24991-do-not-pity-the-dead-harry-pity-the-living-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not pity the dead, Harry. Pity the living, and, above all those who live without love." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30727-it-is-the-unknown-we-fear-when-we-look-upon</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 16:15:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30727-it-is-the-unknown-we-fear-when-we-look-upon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is the unknown we fear when we look upon death and darkness, nothing more." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19787-but-you-make-me-happy-it-s-living-up-to-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 18:03:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19787-but-you-make-me-happy-it-s-living-up-to-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But you make me happy. It's living up to being happy that's the difficult part." -- Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29282-i-wish-for-a-moment-that-time-would-lift-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 18:03:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29282-i-wish-for-a-moment-that-time-would-lift-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish for a moment that time would lift me out of this day, and into some more benign one. But then I feel guilty for wanting to avoid the sadness; dead people need us to remember them, even if it eats us, even if all we can do is say &quot;I'm sorry&quot; until it is as meaningless air." -- Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22293-long-ago-men-went-to-sea-and-women-waited-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 18:03:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22293-long-ago-men-went-to-sea-and-women-waited-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Long ago, men went to sea, and women waited for them, standing on the edge of the water, scanning the horizon for the tiny ship. Now I wait for Henry. He vanishes unwillingly, without warning. I wait for him. Each moment that I wait feels like a year, an eternity. Each moment is as slow and transparent as glass. Through each moment I can see infinite moments lined up, waiting. Why has he gone where I cannot follow?" -- Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11981-i-hate-to-be-where-she-is-not-when-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 18:03:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11981-i-hate-to-be-where-she-is-not-when-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hate to be where she is not, when she is not. And yet, I am always going. - Henry deTamble" -- Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38750-and-that-s-the-thing-about-people-who-mean-everything-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 21:57:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38750-and-that-s-the-thing-about-people-who-mean-everything-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And that's the thing about people who mean everything they say. They think everyone else does too." -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1401-i-would-give-them-aspiring-writers-the-oldest-advice-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 21:57:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1401-i-would-give-them-aspiring-writers-the-oldest-advice-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would give them (aspiring writers) the oldest advice in the craft: Read and write. Read a lot. Read new authors and established ones, read people whose work is in the same vein as yours and those whose genre is totally different. You've heard of chain-smokers. Writers, especially beginners, need to be chain-readers. And lastly, write every day. Write about things that get under your skin and keep you up at night." -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2476-to-morrow-and-to-morrow-and-to-morrow-creeps-in-this-petty-pace</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 17:24:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2476-to-morrow-and-to-morrow-and-to-morrow-creeps-in-this-petty-pace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To-morrow, and to-morrow, and to-morrow,
Creeps in this petty pace from day to day,
To the last syllable of recorded time;
And all our yesterdays have lighted fools
The way to dusty death. Out, out, brief candle!
Life's but a walking shadow, a poor player,
That struts and frets his hour upon the stage,
And then is heard no more. It is a tale
Told by an idiot, full of sound and fury,
Signifying nothing." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 17:26:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I went to the woods because I wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and see if I could not learn what it had to teach, and not, when I came to die, discover that I had not lived. I did not wish to live what was not life, living is so dear; nor did I wish to practise resignation, unless it was quite necessary. I wanted to live deep and suck out all the marrow of life, to live so sturdily and Spartan-like as to put to rout all that was not life, to cut a broad swath and shave close, to drive life into a corner, and reduce it to its lowest terms." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 17:28:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finish each day and be done with it. You have done what you could.  Some blunders and absurdities no doubt crept in; forget them as soon as you can. Tomorrow is a new day.  You shall begin it serenely and with too high a spirit to be encumbered with your old nonsense." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4339-is-it-so-bad-then-to-be-misunderstood-pythagoras-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 17:28:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4339-is-it-so-bad-then-to-be-misunderstood-pythagoras-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is it so bad, then, to be misunderstood? Pythagoras was misunderstood, and Socrates, and Jesus, and Luther, and Copernicus, and Galileo, and Newton, and every pure and wise spirit that ever took flesh. To be great is to be misunderstood." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6910-it-didn-t-matter-in-the-end-how-old-they-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 17:25:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6910-it-didn-t-matter-in-the-end-how-old-they-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It didn't matter in the end how old they had been, or that they were girls, but only that we had loved them, and that they hadn't heard us calling, still do not hear us, up here in the tree house, with our thinning hair and soft bellies, calling them out of those rooms where they went to be alone for all time, alone in suicide, which is deeper than death, and where we will never find the pieces to put them back together." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49921-in-the-end-the-tortures-tearing-the-lisbon-girls-pointed</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 17:26:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49921-in-the-end-the-tortures-tearing-the-lisbon-girls-pointed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the end, the tortures tearing the Lisbon girls pointed to a simple reasoned refusal to accept the world as it was handed down to them, so full of flaws." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29310-in-the-end-it-wasn-t-death-that-surprised-her-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 17:27:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29310-in-the-end-it-wasn-t-death-that-surprised-her-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the end, it wasn't death that surprised her but the stubbornness of life." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14260-there-is-divine-beauty-in-learning-to-learn-means-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 13:17:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14260-there-is-divine-beauty-in-learning-to-learn-means-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is divine beauty in learning...  To learn means to accept the postulate that life did not begin at my birth.  Others have been here before me, and I walk in their footsteps.  The books I have read were composed by generations of fathers and sons, mothers and daughters, teachers and disciples.  I am the sum total of their experiences, their quests.  And so are you." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18490-we-must-always-take-sides-neutrality-helps-the-oppressor-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2008 12:00:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18490-we-must-always-take-sides-neutrality-helps-the-oppressor-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must always take sides.  Neutrality helps the oppressor, never the victim.  Silence encourages the tormentor, never the tormented." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 13:19:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9831-i-m-sorry-for-my-inability-to-let-unimportant-things-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 13:20:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9831-i-m-sorry-for-my-inability-to-let-unimportant-things-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm sorry for my inability to let unimportant things go, for my inability to hold on to the important things." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 13:21:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I can hear my bones straining under the weight of all the lives I'm not living." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12278-i-think-and-think-and-think-i-ve-thought-myself-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 13:21:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12278-i-think-and-think-and-think-i-ve-thought-myself-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think and think and think, I‘ve thought myself out of happiness one million times, but never once into it." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 03:48:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Emotions, in my experience, aren't covered by single words. I don't believe in &quot;sadness,&quot; &quot;joy,&quot; or &quot;regret.&quot; Maybe the best proof that the language is patriarchal is that it oversimplifies feeling. I'd like to have at my disposal complicated hybrid emotions, Germanic train-car constructions like, say, &quot;the happiness that attends disaster.&quot; Or: &quot;the disappointment of sleeping with one's fantasy.&quot; I'd like to show how &quot;intimations of mortality brought on by aging family members&quot; connects with &quot;the hatred of mirrors that begins in middle age.&quot; I'd like to have a word for &quot;the sadness inspired by failing restaurants&quot; as well as for &quot;the excitement of getting a room with a minibar.&quot; I've never had the right words to describe my life, and now that I've entered my story, I need them more than ever. " -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58483-the-last-thing-the-hockey-ball-symbolized-was-time-itself</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 03:56:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58483-the-last-thing-the-hockey-ball-symbolized-was-time-itself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The last thing the hockey ball symbolized was Time itself, the unstoppability of it, the way we're chained to our bodies, which are chained to Time." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62558-suicide-is-just-a-moment-lexy-told-me-this-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 21:38:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62558-suicide-is-just-a-moment-lexy-told-me-this-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suicide is just a moment, Lexy told me. This is how she described it to me. For just a moment, it doesn't matter that you've got people who love you and the sun is shining and there's a movie coming out this weekend that you've been dying to see. It hits you all of a sudden that nothing is ever going to be okay, ever, and you kind of dare yourself. You pick up a knife and press it gently to your skin, you look out a nineteenth-story window and you think, I could just do it. I could just do it. And most of the time, you look at the height and you get scared, or you think about the poor people on the sidewalk below - what if there are kids coming home from school and they have to spend the rest of their lives trying to forget this terrible thing you're going to make them see? And the moment's over. You think about how sad it would've been if you never got to see that movie, and you look at your dog and wonder who would've taken care of her if you had gone. And you go back to normal. But you keep it there in your mind. Even if you never take yourself up on it, it gives you a kind of comfort to know that the day is yours to choose. You tuck it away in your brain like sour candy tucked in your cheek, and the puckering memory it leaves behind, the rough pleasure of running your tongue over its strange terrain, is exactly the same.... The day was hers to choose, and perhaps in that treetop moment when she looked down and saw the yard, the world, her life, spread out below her, perhaps she chose to plunge toward it headlong. Perhaps she saw before her a lifetime of walking on the ruined earth and chose instead a single moment in the air" -- Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63107-all-this-to-say-i-am-forty-three-years-old-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2008 16:01:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63107-all-this-to-say-i-am-forty-three-years-old-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All this to say: I am forty-three years old. I may yet live another forty. What do I do with those years? How do I fill them without Lexy? When I come to tell the story of my life, there will be a line, creased and blurred and soft with age, where she stops. If I win the lottery, if I father a child, if I lose the use of my legs, it will be after she has finished knowing me. &quot;When I get to Heaven&quot;, my grandmother used to say, widowed at thirty-nine, &quot;your grandfather won't even recognize me." -- Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63108-go-on-lexy-said-what-do-you-want-to-be-today</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2008 16:11:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63108-go-on-lexy-said-what-do-you-want-to-be-today]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Go on,&quot;Lexy said. &quot;What do you want to be today?" -- Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63171-and-sitting-here-now-with-all-of-lexy-s-dreams-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2008 21:19:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63171-and-sitting-here-now-with-all-of-lexy-s-dreams-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And sitting here now, with all of Lexy's dreams in my lap, I realize there are things about her I will never know. It's not the content of our dreams that gives our second heart its dark color; it's the thoughts that go through our heads in those wakeful moments when sleep won't come. And those are the things we never tell anyone at all." -- Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69573-miriam-wished-for-so-much-in-those-final-moments-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2008 13:35:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jardley add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69573-miriam-wished-for-so-much-in-those-final-moments-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Miriam wished for so much in those final moments. Yet as she closed her eyes, it was not regret any longer but a sensation of abundant peace that washed over her. She thought of her entry into this world, the harami child of a lowly villager, an unintended thing, a pitiable, regrettable accident. A weed. And yet she was leaving the world as a woman who had loved and been loved back. She was leaving it as a friend, a companion, a guardian. A mother. A person of consequence at last. No. It was not so bad, Miriam thought, that she should die this way. Not so bad. This was a legitimate end to a life of illegitimate belongings." -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
