<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1088579-richard]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1088579-richard" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:27:52 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4502-the-president-of-the-united-states-has-claimed-on-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:27:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4502-the-president-of-the-united-states-has-claimed-on-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The president of the United States has claimed, on more than one occasion, to be in dialogue with God. If he said that he was talking to God through his hairdryer, this would precipitate a national emergency. I fail to see how the addition of a hairdryer makes the claim more ridiculous or offensive." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72135-i-know-of-no-society-in-human-history-that-ever</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:28:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72135-i-know-of-no-society-in-human-history-that-ever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know of no society in human history that ever suffered because its people became too desirous of evidence in support of their core beliefs." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21737-the-fact-that-my-continuous-and-public-rejection-of-christianity</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:28:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21737-the-fact-that-my-continuous-and-public-rejection-of-christianity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fact that my continuous and public rejection of Christianity does not worry me in the least should suggest to you just how inadequate I think your reasons for being a Christian are." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12043-we-know-enough-at-this-moment-to-say-that-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:29:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12043-we-know-enough-at-this-moment-to-say-that-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We know enough at this moment to say that the God of Abraham is not only unworthy of the immensity of creation; he is unworthy even of man." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41764-we-read-the-golden-rule-and-judge-it-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:29:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41764-we-read-the-golden-rule-and-judge-it-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We read the Golden Rule and judge it to be a brilliant distillation of many of our ethical impulses. And then we come across another of God’s teachings on morality: if a man discovers on his wedding night that his bride is not a virgin, he must stone her to death on her father’s doorstep (Deuteronomy 22:13-21)." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96324-it-is-merely-an-accident-of-history-that-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:29:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96324-it-is-merely-an-accident-of-history-that-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is merely an accident of history that it is considered normal in our society to believe that the Creator of the universe can hear your thoughts while it is demonstrative of mental illness to believe that he is communicating with you by having the rain tap in Morse code on your bedroom window." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129692-the-moral-truth-here-is-obvious-anyone-who-feels-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:30:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129692-the-moral-truth-here-is-obvious-anyone-who-feels-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The moral truth here is obvious: anyone who feels that the interests of a blastocyst just might supersede the interests of a child with a spinal cord injury has had his moral sense blinded by religious metaphysics." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41763-according-to-the-most-common-interpretation-of-biblical-prophecy-jesus</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:34:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41763-according-to-the-most-common-interpretation-of-biblical-prophecy-jesus]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["According to the most common interpretation of biblical prophecy, Jesus will return only after things have gone horribly awry. Imagine the consequences if any significant component of the U.S. government believed that the world was about to end and that its ending would be glorious. The fact that nearly half of the American population apparently believes this should be considered a moral and intellectual emergency." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129701-in-fact-atheism-is-a-term-that-should-not-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:36:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129701-in-fact-atheism-is-a-term-that-should-not-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In fact, &quot;atheism&quot; is a term that should not even exist. No one ever needs to identify himself as a &quot;non-astrologer&quot; or a &quot;non-alchemist.&quot; We do not have words for people who doubt that Elvis is still alive or that aliens have traversed the galaxy only to molest ranchers and their cattle. Atheism is nothing more than the noises reasonable people make in the presence of unjustified religious beliefs." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101077-what-is-so-unnerving-about-the-candidacy-of-sarah-palin</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:37:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101077-what-is-so-unnerving-about-the-candidacy-of-sarah-palin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is so unnerving about the candidacy of Sarah Palin is the degree to which she represents—and her supporters celebrate—the joyful marriage of confidence and ignorance . . . Ask yourself: how has &quot;elitism&quot; become a bad word in American politics? There is simply no other walk of life in which extraordinary talent and rigorous training are denigrated. We want elite pilots to fly our planes, elite troops to undertake our most critical missions, elite athletes to represent us in competition and elite scientists to devote the most productive years of their lives to curing our diseases. And yet, when it comes time to vest people with even greater responsibilities, we consider it a virtue to shun any and all standards of excellence. When it comes to choosing the people whose thoughts and actions will decide the fates of millions, then we suddenly want someone just like us, someone fit to have a beer with, someone down-to-earth—in fact, almost anyone, provided that he or she doesn't seem too intelligent or well educated.
" -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12508-when-considering-the-truth-of-a-proposition-one-is-either</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:38:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12508-when-considering-the-truth-of-a-proposition-one-is-either]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When considering the truth of a proposition, one is either engaged in an honest appraisal of the evidence and logical arguments, or one isn't. Religion is one area of our lives where people imagine that some other standard of intellectual integrity applies." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67295-we-will-see-that-the-greatest-problem-confronting-civilization-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:39:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67295-we-will-see-that-the-greatest-problem-confronting-civilization-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We will see that the greatest problem confronting civilization is not merely religious extremism: rather, it is the larger set of cultural and intellectual accommodations we have made to faith itself." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173326-consider-it-every-person-you-have-ever-met-every-person</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:40:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173326-consider-it-every-person-you-have-ever-met-every-person]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Consider it: every person you have ever met, every person will suffer the loss of his friends and family. All are going to lose everything they love in this world. Why would one want to be anything but kind to them in the meantime?" -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151423-tell-a-devout-christian-that-his-wife-is-cheating-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:41:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151423-tell-a-devout-christian-that-his-wife-is-cheating-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tell a devout Christian that his wife is cheating on him, or that frozen yogurt can make a man invisible, and he is likely to require as much evidence as anyone else, and to be persuaded only to the extent that you give it. Tell him that the book he keeps by his bed was written by an invisible deity who will punish him with fire for eternity if he fails to accept its every incredible claim about the universe, and he seems to require no evidence what so ever." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96411-it-is-time-we-admitted-from-kings-and-presidents-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:42:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96411-it-is-time-we-admitted-from-kings-and-presidents-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is time we admitted, from kings and presidents on down, that there is no evidence that any of our books was authored by the Creator of the universe. The Bible, it seems certain, was the work of sand-strewn men and women who thought the earth was flat and for whom a wheelbarrow would have been a breathtaking example of emerging technology. To rely on such a document as the basis for our worldview-however heroic the efforts of redactors- is to repudiate two thousand years of civilizing insights that the human mind has only just begun to inscribe upon itself through secular politics and scientific culture. We will see that the greatest problem confronting civilization is not merely religious extremism: rather, it is the larger set of cultural and intellectual accommodations we have made to faith itself." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129697-you-are-using-your-own-moral-intuitions-to-authenticate-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:45:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129697-you-are-using-your-own-moral-intuitions-to-authenticate-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are using your own moral intuitions to authenticate the wisdom of the Bible - and then, in the next moment, you assert that we human beings cannot possibly rely upon our own intuitions to rightly guide us in the world." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129702-it-is-time-that-we-admitted-that-faith-is-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:45:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129702-it-is-time-that-we-admitted-that-faith-is-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is time that we admitted that faith is nothing more than the license religious people give one another to keep believing when reasons fail." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142651-every-one-of-the-world-s-great-religions-utterly-trivializes-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:46:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142651-every-one-of-the-world-s-great-religions-utterly-trivializes-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every one of the world's &quot;great&quot; religions utterly trivializes the immensity and beauty of the cosmos. Books like the Bible and the Koran get almost every significant fact about us and our world wrong. Every scientific domain -- from cosmology to psychology to economics -- has superseded and surpassed the wisdom of Scripture.

Everything of value that people get from religion can be had more honestly, without presuming anything on insufficient evidence. The rest is self-deception, set to music." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66165-rather-than-bring-the-full-force-of-our-creativity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:49:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66165-rather-than-bring-the-full-force-of-our-creativity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Rather than bring the full force of our creativity and rationality to bear on the problems of ethics, social cohesion, and even spiritual experience, moderates merely ask that we relax our standard of adherence to ancient superstitions and taboos, while otherwise maintaining a belief system that was passed down to us from men and women whose lives were simply ravaged by their basic ignorance about the world." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172702-the-men-who-committed-the-atrocities-of-september-11-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:50:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172702-the-men-who-committed-the-atrocities-of-september-11-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The men who committed the atrocities of September 11 were certainly not 'cowards,' as they were repeatedly described in the Western media, nor were they lunatics in any ordinary sense. They were men of faith—perfect faith, as it turns out—and this, it must finally be acknowledged, is a terrible thing to be." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160693-people-who-harbor-strong-convictions-without-evidence-belong-at-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:51:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by sam harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160693-people-who-harbor-strong-convictions-without-evidence-belong-at-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People who harbor strong convictions without evidence belong at the margins of our societies, not in our halls of power.  The only thing we should respect in a person’s faith is his desire for a better life in this world;  we need never have respected his certainty that one awaits him in the next." -- sam harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191182-indeed-religion-allows-people-to-imagine-that-their-concerns-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:53:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191182-indeed-religion-allows-people-to-imagine-that-their-concerns-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Indeed, religion allows people to imagine that their concerns are moral when they are highly immoral - that is, when pressing these concerns inflicts unnecessary and appalling suffering on innocent human beings.  This explains why Christians like yourself expend more &quot;moral&quot; energy opposing abortion than fighting genocide.  It explains why you are more concerned about human embryos than about the lifesaving promise of stem-cell research.  And it explains why you can preach against condom use in sub-Saharan Africa while millions die from AIDS there each year." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172836-incompatible-religious-doctrines-have-balkanized-our-world-into-separate-moral</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:54:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172836-incompatible-religious-doctrines-have-balkanized-our-world-into-separate-moral]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Incompatible religious doctrines have balkanized our world into separate moral communities, and these divisions have become a continuous source of bloodshed. Indeed, religion is as much a living spring of violence today as it has been at any time in the past. The recent conflicts in Palestine (Jews vs. Muslims), the Balkans (Orthodox Serbians vs. Catholic Croatians; Orthodox Serbians vs. Bosnian and Albanian Muslims), Northern Ireland (Protestants vs. Catholics), Kashmir (Muslims vs. Hindus), Sudan (Muslims vs. Christians and animists), Nigeria (Muslims vs. Christians), Ethiopia and Eritrea (Muslims vs. Christians), Sri Lanka (Sinhalese Buddhists vs. Tamil Hindus), Indonesia (Muslims vs. Timorese Christians), Iran and Iraq (Shiite vs. Sunni Muslims), and the Caucasus (Orthodox Russians vs. Chechen Muslims; Muslim Azerbaijanis vs. Catholic and Orthodox Armenians) are merely a few cases in point. These are places where religion has been the explicit cause of literally millions of deaths in recent decades.

Why is religion such a potent source of violence? There is no other sphere of discourse in which human beings so fully articulate their differences from one another, or cast these differences in terms of everlasting rewards and punishments. Religion is the one endeavor in which us–them thinking achieves a transcendent significance. If you really believe that calling God by the right name can spell the difference between eternal happiness and eternal suffering, then it becomes quite reasonable to treat heretics and unbelievers rather badly. The stakes of our religious differences are immeasurably higher than those born of mere tribalism, racism, or politics." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75304-is-is-therefore-not-an-exaggeration-to-say-that-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:56:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75304-is-is-therefore-not-an-exaggeration-to-say-that-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is is, therefore, not an exaggeration to say that if the city of New York were suddenly replaced by a ball of fire, some significant percentage of the American population would see a silver-lining in the subsequent mushroom cloud, as it would suggest to them that the best thing that is ever going to happen was about to happen: the return of Christ.  It should be blindingly obvious that beliefs of this sort will do little to help us create a durable future for ourselves - socially, economically, environmentally, or geopolitically.  Imagine the consequences if any significant component of the US government actually believed that the world was about to end and that its ending would be glorious.  The fact that nearly half of the American population apparently believes this, purely on the basis of religion dogma, should be considered a moral and intellectual emergency." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129704-religious-moderation-is-the-direct-result-of-taking-scripture-less</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:56:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129704-religious-moderation-is-the-direct-result-of-taking-scripture-less]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Religious moderation is the direct result of taking scripture less and less seriously. So why not take it less seriously still? Why not admit the the Bible is merely a collection of imperfect books written by highly fallible human beings." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117170-where-we-have-reasons-for-what-we-believe-we-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 08:57:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117170-where-we-have-reasons-for-what-we-believe-we-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where we have reasons for what we believe, we have no need of faith; where we have no reasons, we have lost both our connection to the world and to one another." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191181-if-you-think-that-it-would-be-impossible-to-improve</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 10:49:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191181-if-you-think-that-it-would-be-impossible-to-improve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you think that it would be impossible to improve upon the Ten Commandments as a statement of morality,  you really owe it to yourself to read some other scriptures.  Once again, we need look no further than the Jains:  [author:Mahavira|7061021], the Jain patriarch, surpassed the morality of the Bible with a single sentence:  'Do not injure, abuse, oppress, enslave, insult, torment, torture, or kill any creature or living being.' Imagine how different our world might be if the Bible contained this as its central precept.  Christians have abused, oppressed, enslaved, insulted, tormented, tortured, and killed people in the name of God for centuries, on the basis of a theologically defensible reading of the Bible." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191185-a-three-day-old-human-embryo-is-a-collection-of-150-cells</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 10:51:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191185-a-three-day-old-human-embryo-is-a-collection-of-150-cells]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A three-day-old human embryo is a collection of 150 cells called a blastocyst.  There are, for the sake of comparison, more than 100,000 cells in the brain of a fly.  The human embryos that are destroyed in stem-cell research do not have brains, or even neurons.  Consequently, there is no reason to believe they can suffer their destruction in any way at all.  It is worth remembered, in this context, that when a person's brain has died, we currently deem it acceptable to harvest his organs (provided he has donated them for this purpose) and bury him in the ground.  If it is acceptable to treat a person whose brain has died as something less than a human being, it should be acceptable to treat a blastocyst as such.  If you are concerned about suffering in this universe, killing a fly should present you with greater moral difficulties than killing a human blastocyst.

Perhaps you think that the crucial difference between a fly and a human blastocyst is to be found in the latter's potential to become a fully developed human being.  But almost every cell in your body is a potential human being, given our recent advances in genetic engineering.  Every time you scratch your nose, you have committed a Holocaust of potential human beings." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153830-are-you-really-surprised-by-the-endurance-of-religion-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 10:53:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153830-are-you-really-surprised-by-the-endurance-of-religion-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Are you really surprised by the endurance of religion? What ideology is likely to be more durable than one that conforms, at every turn, to our powers of wishful thinking? Hope is easy; knowledge is hard. Science is the one domain in which we human beings make a truly heroic effort to counter our innate biases and wishful thinking. Science is the one endeavor in which we have developed a refined methodology for separating what a person hopes is true from what he has good reason to believe. The methodology isn't perfect, and the history of science is riddled with abject failures of scientific objectivity. But that is just the point-these have been failures of science, discovered and corrected by-what, religion? No, by good science." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173337-this-is-not-as-you-have-charged-to-paint-religion</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 10:55:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173337-this-is-not-as-you-have-charged-to-paint-religion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is not (as you have charged) to paint religion with a broad brush. I am very quick to distinguish gradations of bad ideas; some clearly have no consequences at all (or at least not yet); some put civilization itself in peril. The problem with dogmatism, however, is that one can never quite predict how terrible its costs will be. To use one of my favorite examples, consider the Christian dogma that human life begins at the moment of conception: On its face, this belief seems likely to only improve our world. After all, it is the very quintessence of a life-affirming doctrine.

Enter embryonic stem-cell research. Suddenly, this “life begins at the moment of conception” business becomes the chief impediment to medical progress. Who would have thought that such an innocuous idea could unnecessarily prolong the agony of tens of millions of people? This is the problem with dogmatism, no matter how seemingly benign: it is unresponsive to reality. Dogmatism is a failure of cognition (as well as a commitment to such failure); it is the state of being closed to new evidence and new arguments. And this frame of mind is rightly despised in every area of culture, on every subject, except where it goes by the name of “religious faith.” In this guise, parading its most grotesque faults as virtues, it is granted a special dispensation, even in the pages of &lt;i&gt;Nature&lt;/i&gt;." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
