<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1089199-morgan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1089199-morgan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 04:32:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39872-once-you-have-given-up-the-ghost-everything-follows-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 04:32:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39872-once-you-have-given-up-the-ghost-everything-follows-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once you have given up the ghost, everything follows with dead certainty, even in the midst of chaos." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73879-nothing-can-be-given-or-taken-away-nothing-has-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 04:33:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73879-nothing-can-be-given-or-taken-away-nothing-has-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing can be given or taken away; nothing has been added or subtracted; nothing increased or diminished.  We stand on the same shore before the same mighty ocean.  The ocean of love.  There it is - in perpetuum.  As much in a broken blossom, the sound of a waterfall, the swoop of a carrion bird as in the thunderous artillery of the prophet.
We move with eyes shut and ears stopped; we smash walls where doors are waiting to open to the touch; we grope for ladders, forgetting that we have wings; we pray as if God were deaf and blind, as if He were in a space.  No wonder the angels in our midst are unrecognizable.
One day it will be pleasant to remember these things." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76722-and-with-that-he-began-to-laugh-not-a-laugh</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 04:38:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76722-and-with-that-he-began-to-laugh-not-a-laugh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...and with that he began to laugh, not a laugh either, but a cackle, a hideous cackle like a rooster with its head on the block. It got him so badly that he had to stop and hold his guts; the tears were streaming down his eyes and between the cackles he let out the most terrible heartrending sobs." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76724-one-thing-is-certain-that-when-you-die-and-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 04:40:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76724-one-thing-is-certain-that-when-you-die-and-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One thing is certain, that when you die and are resurrected you belong to the earth and whatever is of the earth is yours inalienably. You become an anomaly of nature, a being without shadow; you will never die again but only pass away like the phenomena about you." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76725-the-city-grows-like-a-cancer-i-must-grow-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 04:41:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76725-the-city-grows-like-a-cancer-i-must-grow-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The city grows like a cancer; I must grow like a sun. The city eats deeper and deeper into the red; it is an insatiable white louse which must die eventually of inanition. I am going to starve the white louse which is eating me up. I am going to die as a city in order to become again a man. Therefore I close my ears, my eyes, my mouth." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63545-the-three-saddest-things-are-the-ill-wanting-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2008 05:04:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by E.E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63545-the-three-saddest-things-are-the-ill-wanting-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The three saddest things are the ill wanting to be well, the poor wanting to be rich, and the constant traveler saying 'anywhere but here'." -- E.E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77027-we-can-never-be-born-enough</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2008 05:25:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by E. E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77027-we-can-never-be-born-enough]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can never be born enough." -- E. E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32540-people-in-general-attach-too-much-importance-to-words-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 11:21:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by Theodore Dreiser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32540-people-in-general-attach-too-much-importance-to-words-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People in general attach too much importance to words.  They are under the illusion that talking effects great results.  As a matter of fact, words are, as a rule, the shallowest portion of all the argument.  They but dimly represent the great surging feelings and desires which lie behind.  When the distraction of the tongue is removed, the heart listens." -- Theodore Dreiser]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17177-those-who-believe-in-telekinetics-raise-my-hand</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 18:02:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17177-those-who-believe-in-telekinetics-raise-my-hand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who believe in telekinetics, raise my hand." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32049-when-a-reader-falls-in-love-with-a-book-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 05:41:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32049-when-a-reader-falls-in-love-with-a-book-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a reader falls in love with a book, it leaves its essence inside him, like radioactive fallout in an arable field, and after that there are certain crops that will no longer grow in him, while other, stranger, more fantastic growths may occasionally be produced.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;Books vs. Goons&lt;/i&gt;, L.A. Times, April 24, 2005]" -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11144-an-intellectual-yes-and-never-deny-it-an-intellectual-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 19:21:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11144-an-intellectual-yes-and-never-deny-it-an-intellectual-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An intellectual? Yes. And never deny it. An intellectual is someone whose mind watches itself. I like this, because I am happy to be both halves, the watcher and the watched. &quot;Can they be brought together?&quot; This is a practical question. We must get down to it. &quot;I despise intelligence&quot; really means: &quot;I cannot bear my doubts." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14742-at-the-heart-of-all-beauty-lies-something-inhuman</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 19:22:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14742-at-the-heart-of-all-beauty-lies-something-inhuman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the heart of all beauty lies something inhuman." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5623-a-man-s-work-is-nothing-but-this-slow-trek-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 19:22:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5623-a-man-s-work-is-nothing-but-this-slow-trek-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man's work is nothing but this slow trek to rediscover, through the detours of art, those two or three great and simple images in whose presence his heart first opened." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29516-there-is-but-one-truly-serious-philosophical-problem-and-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 19:29:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29516-there-is-but-one-truly-serious-philosophical-problem-and-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is but one truly serious philosophical problem and that is suicide. Judging whether life is or is not worth living amounts to answering the fundamental question of philosophy. All the rest — whether or not the world has three dimensions, whether the mind has nine or twelve categories — comes afterwards. These are games; one must first answer." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60230-every-time-i-hear-a-political-speech-or-i-read</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 19:30:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60230-every-time-i-hear-a-political-speech-or-i-read]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every time I hear a political speech or I read those of our leaders, I am horrified at having, for years, heard nothing which sounded human. It is always the same words telling the same lies. And the fact that men accept this, that the people’s anger has not destroyed these hollow clowns, strikes me as proof that men attribute no importance to the way they are governed; that they gamble – yes, gamble – with a whole part of their life and their so called 'vital interests." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14207-she-was-breathing-deeply-she-forgot-the-cold-the-weight</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 19:31:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14207-she-was-breathing-deeply-she-forgot-the-cold-the-weight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was breathing deeply, she forgot the cold, the weight of beings, the insane or static life, the long anguish of living or dying. After so many years running from fear, fleeing crazily, uselessly, she was finally coming to a halt. At the same time she seemed to be recovering her roots, and the sap rose anew in her body, which was no longer trembling. Pressing her whole belly against the parapet, leaning toward the wheeling sky, she was only waiting for her pounding heart to settle down, and for the silence to form in her. The last constellations of stars fell in bunches a little lower on the horizon of the desert, and stood motionless. Then, with an unbearable sweetness, the waters of the night began to fill her, submerging the cold, rising gradually to the center of her being, and overflowing wave upon wave to her moaning mouth.  A moment later, the whole sky stretched out above her as she lay with her back against the cold earth." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80772-in-different-degrees-in-every-part-of-the-town-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 19:34:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80772-in-different-degrees-in-every-part-of-the-town-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In different degrees, in every part of the town, men and women had been yearning for a reunion, not of the same kind for all, but for all alike ruled out. Most of them had longed intensely for an absent one, for the warmth of a body, for love, or merely a life that habit had endeared. Some, often without knowing it, suffered from being deprived of the company of friends and from their inability to get in touch with them through the usual channels of friendship—letters, trains, and boats. Others, fewer these... had desired a reunion with something they couldn’t have defined, but which seemed to them the only desirable thing on earth. For want of a better name, they sometimes called it peace." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32016-as-long-as-we-re-young-we-manage-to-find-excuses</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2009 22:48:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Morgan add a quote by Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32016-as-long-as-we-re-young-we-manage-to-find-excuses]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As long as we're young, we manage to find excuses for the stoniest indifference, the most blatant caddishness, we put them down to emotional eccentricity or some sort of romantic inexperience.  But later on, when life shows us how much cunning, cruelty, and malice are required just to keep the body at ninety-eight point six, we catch on, we know the scene, we begin to understand how much swinishness it takes to make up a past.  Just take a close look at yourself and the degree of rottenness you've come to.  There's no mystery about it, no more room for fairy tales; if you've lived this long, it's because you've squashed any poetry you had in you." -- Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
