<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1089756-andrea]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1089756-andrea" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 06:49:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 06:49:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8287-i-have-not-failed-i-ve-just-found-10-000-ways-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2008 16:13:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Thomas A. Edison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8287-i-have-not-failed-i-ve-just-found-10-000-ways-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work." -- Thomas A. Edison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14821-what-you-re-supposed-to-do-when-you-don-t-like-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2008 16:15:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14821-what-you-re-supposed-to-do-when-you-don-t-like-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What you're supposed to do when you don't like a thing is change it. If you can't change it, change the way you think about it. Don't complain." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1649-a-book-without-words-is-like-love-without-a-kiss</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2008 16:17:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Andrew Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1649-a-book-without-words-is-like-love-without-a-kiss]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book without words is like love without a kiss; it's empty." -- Andrew Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10780-try-a-little-harder-to-be-a-little-better</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2008 16:17:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10780-try-a-little-harder-to-be-a-little-better]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Try a little harder to be a little better." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25-we-are-all-in-the-gutter-but-some-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2008 16:20:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25-we-are-all-in-the-gutter-but-some-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all in the gutter, but some of us are looking at the stars." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18169-it-takes-courage-to-endure-the-sharp-pains-of-self-discovery</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 19:33:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18169-it-takes-courage-to-endure-the-sharp-pains-of-self-discovery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It takes courage...to endure the sharp pains of self discovery rather than choose to take the dull pain of unconsciousness that would last the rest of our lives." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1132-deserves-it-i-daresay-he-does-many-that-live-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 12:00:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1132-deserves-it-i-daresay-he-does-many-that-live-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Deserves it! I daresay he does. Many that live deserve death. And some that die deserve life. Can you give it to them? Then do not be too eager to deal out death in judgement. For even the very wise cannot see all ends." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116375-you-are-confused-because-the-bible-describes-god-as-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 12:01:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Dan Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116375-you-are-confused-because-the-bible-describes-god-as-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are confused because the Bible describes God as an omnipotent and benevolent deity…Omnipotent-benevolent simply means that God is all-powerful and well-meaning.”
I understand the concept.  It’s just…there seems to be a contradiction.”
Yes. The contradiction is pain.  Man’s starvation, war, sickness…”
Exactly!”  Chartrand knew the camerlengo would understand. “Terrible things happen in this world.  Human tragedy seems like proof that God could not possibly be both all-powerful and well-meaning.  If He loves us and has the power to change our situation, He would prevent our pain, wouldn’t He?”
The Camerlengo frowned. “Would He?”
Chartrand felt uneasy.  Had he overstepped his bounds?  Was this one of those religious questions you just didn’t ask?  “Well…if God loves us, and He can protect us, He would have to.  It seems He is either omnipotent and uncaring, or benevolent and powerless to help.”
Do you have children, Lieutenant?”
Chartrand flushed.  “No, signore.”
Imagine you had an eight-year-old son…would you love him?”
Of course.”
Would you let him skateboard?”
Chartrand did a double take.  The camerlengo always seemed oddly “in touch” for a clergyman.  “Yeah, I guess,” Chartrand said. “Sure, I’d let him skateboard, but I’d tell him to be careful.”
So as this child’s father, you would give him some basic, good advice and then let him go off and make his own mistakes?”
I wouldn’t run behind him and mollycoddle him if that’s what you mean.”
But what if he fell and skinned his knee?”
He would learn to be more careful.”
The camerlengo smiled.  “So although you have the power to interfere and prevent your child’s pain, you would choose to show your love by letting him learn his own lessons?”
Of course.  Pain is part of growing up.  It’s how we learn.”
The camerlengo nodded. “Exactly." -- Dan Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
