<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1091291-kent]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1091291-kent" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2011 03:43:25 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156917-the-tea-ritual-such-a-precise-repetition-of-the-same</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2011 03:43:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kent add a quote by Muriel Barbery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156917-the-tea-ritual-such-a-precise-repetition-of-the-same]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The tea ritual: such a precise repetition of the same gestures and the same tastes; accession to simple, authentic and refined sensations, a license given to all, at little cost, to become aristocrats of taste, because tea is the beverage of the wealthy and the poor; the tea ritual, therefore, has the extraordinary virtue of introducing into the absurdity of our lives an aperture of serene harmony. Yes, the world may aspire to vacuousness, lost souls mourn beauty, insignificance surrounds us. Then let us drink a cup of tea. Silence descends, one hears the wind outside, autumn leaves rustle and take flight, the cat sleeps in a warm pool of light. And, with each swallow, time is sublimed." -- Muriel Barbery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417390-i-define-connection-as-the-energy-that-exists-between-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 21:16:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kent add a quote by Brené Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417390-i-define-connection-as-the-energy-that-exists-between-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I define connection as the energy that exists between people when they feel seen, heard, and valued; when they can give and receive without judgment; and when they derive sustenance and strength from the relationship." -- Brené Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156836-we-are-all-so-much-together-but-we-are-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 21:17:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kent add a quote by Albert Schweitzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156836-we-are-all-so-much-together-but-we-are-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all so much together, but we are all dying of loneliness." -- Albert Schweitzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/993753-it-is-lonely-behind-these-boundaries-some-people-particularly-those-whom</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 17:28:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kent add a quote by M. Scott Peck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/993753-it-is-lonely-behind-these-boundaries-some-people-particularly-those-whom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is lonely behind these boundaries. Some people-particularly those whom psychiatrists call schizoid-because of unpleasant, traumatizing experiences in childhood, perceive the world outside of themselves as unredeemably dangerous, hostile, confusing and unnurturing. Such people feel their boundaries to be protecting and comforting and find a sense of safety in their loneliness. But most of us feel our loneliness to be painful and yearn to escape from behind the walls of our individual identities to a condition in which we can be more unified with the world outside of ourselves. The experience of falling in love allows us this escapetemporarily. The essence of the phenomenon of falling in love is a sudden collapse of a section of an individual's ego boundaries, permitting one to merge his or her identity with that of another person. The sudden release of oneself from oneself, the explosive pouring out of oneself into the beloved, and the dramatic surcease of loneliness accompanying this collapse of ego boundaries is experienced by most of us as ecstatic. We and our beloved are one! Loneliness is no more! 

In some respects (but certainly not in all) the act of falling in love is an act of regression. The experience of merging with the loved one has in it echoes from the time when we were merged with our mothers in infancy. Along with the merging we also reexperience the sense of omnipotence which we had to give up in our journey out of childhood. All things seem possible! United with our beloved we feel we can conquer all obstacles. We believe that the strength of our love will cause the forces of opposition to bow down in submission and melt away into the darkness. All problems will be overcome. The future will be all light. The unreality of these feelings when we have fallen in love is essentially the same as the unreality of the two-year-old who feels itself to be king of the family and the world with power unlimited. 

Just as reality intrudes upon the two-year-old's fantasy of omnipotence so does reality intrude upon the fantastic unity of the couple who have fallen in love. Sooner or later, in response to the problems of daily living, individual will reasserts itself. He wants to have sex; she doesn't. She wants to go to the movies; he doesn't. He wants to put money in the bank; she wants a dishwasher. She wants to talk about her job; he wants to talk about his. She doesn't like his friends; he doesn't like hers. So both of them, in the privacy of their hearts, begin to come to the sickening realization that they are not one with the beloved, that the beloved has and will continue to have his or her own desires, tastes, prejudices and timing different from the other's. One by one, gradually or suddenly, the ego boundaries snap back into place; gradually or suddenly, they fall out of love. Once again they are two separate individuals. At this point they begin either to dissolve the ties of their relationship or to initiate the work of real loving." -- M. Scott Peck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225003-the-only-noise-now-was-the-rain-pattering-softly-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 19:22:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kent add a quote by Sherwood Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225003-the-only-noise-now-was-the-rain-pattering-softly-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only noise now was the rain, pattering softly with the magnificent indifference of nature for the tangled passions of humans." -- Sherwood Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511842-rain-amplifies-your-mistakes-and-water-on-the-track-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 19:26:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kent add a quote by Garth Stein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511842-rain-amplifies-your-mistakes-and-water-on-the-track-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Rain amplifies your mistakes, and water on the track can make your car handle unpredictably. When something unpredictable happens you have to react to it; if you’re reacting at speed, you’re reacting too late. And so you should be afraid." -- Garth Stein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1175432-misery-is-a-routine-you-can-learn-to-live-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 19:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kent add a quote by Alan Gibbons]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1175432-misery-is-a-routine-you-can-learn-to-live-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Misery is a routine you can learn to live with. It's like rain. Once you're soaked to the skin, you can't get any wetter." -- Alan Gibbons]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
