<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1091236-imee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1091236-imee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 21:29:58 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 21:29:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Imee add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be yourself in a world that is constantly trying to make you something else is the greatest accomplishment." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 21:30:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Imee add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know you're in love when you can't fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 21:34:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Imee add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128997-how-many-times-already-had-i-encountered-the-painful-lesson</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 22:01:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Imee add a quote by Arthur Golden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128997-how-many-times-already-had-i-encountered-the-painful-lesson]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How many times already had I encountered the painful lesson that although we may wish for the barb to be pulled from our flesh, it leaves a welt that doesn't heal?" -- Arthur Golden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 22:02:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Imee add a quote by Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened." -- Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 22:02:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Imee add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 02:08:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Imee add a quote by Bob Moorehead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The paradox of our time in history is that we have taller buildings but 
shorter tempers, wider Freeways, but narrower viewpoints.  We spend more, 
but have less, we buy more, but enjoy less. We have bigger houses and 
smaller families, more conveniences, but less time.  We have more degrees 
but less sense, more knowledge, but less judgment, more experts, yet more 
problems, more medicine, but less wellness.

We drink too much, smoke too much, spend too recklessly, laugh too little, 
drive too fast, get too angry, stay up too late, get up too tired, read too 
little, watch TV too much, and pray too seldom.  We have multiplied our 
possessions, but reduced our values.  We talk too much, love too seldom, and 
hate too often.

We've learned how to make a living, but not a life. We've added years to 
life not life to years.  We've been all the way to the moon and back, but 
have trouble crossing the street to meet a new neighbor.  We conquered outer 
space but not inner space.  We've done larger things, but not better things.

We've cleaned up the air, but polluted the soul. We've conquered the atom, 
but not our prejudice.  We write more, but learn less.  We plan more, but 
accomplish less.  We've learned to rush, but not to wait.  We build more 
computers to hold more information, to produce more copies than ever, but we 
communicate less and less.

These are the times of fast foods and slow digestion, big men and small 
character, steep profits and shallow relationships.

These are the days of two incomes but more divorce, fancier houses, but 
broken homes.  These are days of quick trips, disposable diapers, throwaway 
morality, one night stands, overweight bodies, and pills that do everything 
from cheer, to quiet, to kill.  It is a time when there is much in the 
showroom window and nothing in the stockroom.  A time when technology can 
bring this letter to you, and a time when you can choose either to share 
this insight, or to just hit delete...

Remember, to spend some time with your loved ones, because they are not 
going to be around forever.  Remember, say a kind word to someone who looks 
up to you in awe, because that little person soon will grow up and leave 
your side.

Remember, to give a warm hug to the one next to you, because that is the 
only treasure you can give with your heart and it doesn't cost a cent.

Remember, to say, &quot;I love you&quot; to your partner and your loved ones, but most 
of all mean it.  A kiss and an embrace will mend hurt when it comes from 
deep inside of you.

Remember to hold hands and cherish the moment for someday that person might 
not be there again.  Give time to love, give time to speak! And give time to 
share the precious thoughts in your mind." -- Bob Moorehead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6130-a-woman-should-have-enough-money-within-her-control</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 02:08:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Imee add a quote by Pamela Redmond Satran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6130-a-woman-should-have-enough-money-within-her-control]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  enough money within her control to move out
  and rent a place of her own even if she never wants
  to or needs to...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  something perfect to wear if the employer or date of her
  dreams wants to see her in an hour...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ...
  a youth she's content to leave behind....
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a past juicy enough that she's looking forward to
  retelling it in her old age....
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE .....
  a set of screwdrivers, a cordless drill, and a black
  lace bra...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  one friend who always makes her laugh... and one who
  lets her cry...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a good piece of furniture not previously owned by anyone
  else in her family...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  eight matching plates, wine glasses with stems, and a
  recipe for a meal that will make her guests feel honored...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a feeling of control over her destiny...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  how to fall in love without losing herself..
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  HOW TO QUIT A JOB,
  BREAK UP WITH A LOVER,
  AND CONFRONT A FRIEND WITHOUT RUINING THE FRIENDSHIP...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  when to try harder... and WHEN TO WALK AWAY...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  that she can't change the length of her calves,
  the width of her hips, or the nature of her parents..
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  that her childhood may not have been perfect...but it's over...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  what she would and wouldn't do for love or more...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  how to live alone... even if she doesn't like it...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  whom she can trust,
  whom she can't,
  and why she shouldn't
  take it personally...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  where to go...
  be it to her best friend's kitchen table...
  or a charming inn in the woods...
  when her soul needs soothing...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  what she can and can't accomplish in a day...
  a month...and a year..." -- Pamela Redmond Satran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103606-ladies-and-gentlemen-of-the-class-of-97-wear-sunscreen</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 02:10:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Imee add a quote by Mary Schmich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103606-ladies-and-gentlemen-of-the-class-of-97-wear-sunscreen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ladies and gentlemen of the class of '97:

Wear sunscreen.

If I could offer you only one tip for the future, sunscreen would be it. The long-term benefits of sunscreen have been proved by scientists, whereas the rest of my advice has no basis more reliable than my own meandering experience. I will dispense this advice now.

Enjoy the power and beauty of your youth. Oh, never mind. You will not understand the power and beauty of your youth until they've faded. But trust me, in 20 years, you'll look back at photos of yourself and recall in a way you can't grasp now how much possibility lay before you and how fabulous you really looked. You are not as fat as you imagine.

Don't worry about the future. Or worry, but know that worrying is as effective as trying to solve an algebra equation by chewing bubble gum. The real troubles in your life are apt to be things that never crossed your worried mind, the kind that blindside you at 4 p.m. on some idle Tuesday." -- Mary Schmich]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
