<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1092879-allison]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1092879-allison" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2010 06:35:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183096-in-the-political-jargon-of-those-days-the-word-intellectual</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2010 06:35:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183096-in-the-political-jargon-of-those-days-the-word-intellectual]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the political jargon of those days, the word &quot;intellectual&quot; was an insult. It indicated someone who did not understand life and was cut off from the people. All the Communists who were hanged at the time by other Communists were awarded such abuse. Unlike those who had their feet solidly on the ground, they were said to float in the air. So it was fair, in a way, that as punishment the ground was permanently pulled out from under their feet, that they remained suspended a little above the floor." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1716-travel-is-fatal-to-prejudice-bigotry-and-narrow-mindedness-and-many</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 15:05:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1716-travel-is-fatal-to-prejudice-bigotry-and-narrow-mindedness-and-many]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Travel is fatal to prejudice, bigotry, and narrow-mindedness, and many of our people need it sorely on these accounts. Broad, wholesome, charitable views of men and things cannot be acquired by vegetating in one little corner of the earth all one's lifetime." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284727-the-gentle-reader-will-never-never-know-what-a-consummate</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 15:06:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284727-the-gentle-reader-will-never-never-know-what-a-consummate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The gentle reader will never, never know what a consummate ass he can become until he goes abroad. I speak now, of course, in the supposition that the gentle reader has not been abroad, and therefore is not already a consummate ass. If the case be otherwise, I beg his pardon and extend to him the cordial hand of fellowship and call him brother. I shall always delight to meet an ass after my own heart when I have finished my travels." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167055-the-universe-is-very-very-big-it-also-loves-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2010 09:11:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Craig Ferguson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167055-the-universe-is-very-very-big-it-also-loves-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Universe is very, very big.
It also loves a paradox. For example, it has some extremely strict rules.
Rule number one: Nothing lasts forever.
Not you or your family or your house or your planet or the sun. It is an absolute rule. Therefore when someone says that their love will never die, it means that their love is not real, for everything that is real dies. 

Rule number two: Everything lasts forever." -- Craig Ferguson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/380877-well-i-know-she-said-you-ll-pretend-you-were-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 09:02:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/380877-well-i-know-she-said-you-ll-pretend-you-were-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, I know,&quot; she said. &quot;You'll pretend you were men instead of babies, and you'll be played in the movies by Frank Sinatra and John Wayne or some of those other glamorous, war-loving, dirty old men. And war will look just wonderful, so we'll have a lot more of them. And they'll be fought by babies like the babies upstairs.&quot;
So then I understood. It was war that made her so angry. She didn't want her babies or anybody else's babies killed in wars. And she thought wars were partly encouraged by books and movies.

So I held up my right hand and I made her a promise: &quot;Mary,&quot; I said, &quot;I don't think this book of mine will ever be finished. I must have written five thousand pages by now, and thrown them all away. If I ever do finish it, though, I give you my word of honor: there won't be a part for Frank Sinatra or John Wayne.
&quot;I tell you what,&quot; I said, &quot;I'll call it 'The Children's Crusade.'&quot;
She was my friend after that." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406211-the-hardest-bones-containing-the-richest-marrow-can-be-conquered</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2011 10:23:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406211-the-hardest-bones-containing-the-richest-marrow-can-be-conquered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The hardest bones, containing the richest marrow, can be conquered only by a united crushing of all the teeth of all dogs. That of course is only a figure of speech and exaggerated; if all teeth were but ready they would not need even to bite, the bones would crack themselves and the marrow would be freely accessible to the feeblest of dogs. If I remain faithful to this metaphor, then the goal of my aims, my questions, my inquiries, appears monstrous, it is true. For I want to compel all dogs thus to assemble together, I want the bones to crack open under the pressure of their collective preparedness, and then I want to dismiss them to the ordinary life they love, while all by myself, quite alone, I lap up the marrow. That sounds monstrous, almost as if I wanted to feed on the marrow, not merely of bone, but of the whole canine race itself. But it is only a metaphor. The marrow that I am discussing here is no food; on the contrary, it is a poison." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48434-for-there-is-nothing-heavier-than-compassion-not-even-one-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2011 15:55:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48434-for-there-is-nothing-heavier-than-compassion-not-even-one-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["for there is nothing heavier than compassion. Not even one's own pain weighs so heavy as the pain one feels with someone, for someone, a pain intensified by the imagination and prolonged by a hundred echoes." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
