<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1092366-dana-jeri-maier]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1092366-dana-jeri-maier" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 13:54:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134421-never-fall-in-love-with-an-idea-they-re-whores-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 13:54:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Chip Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134421-never-fall-in-love-with-an-idea-they-re-whores-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never fall in love with an idea. They're whores: if the one you're with isn't doing the job, there's always, always, always another." -- Chip Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57542-you-were-ambitious---for-your-life-what-it-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 10:36:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Lionel Shriver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57542-you-were-ambitious---for-your-life-what-it-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You were ambitious - for your life, what it was like when you woke up in the morning, and not for some attainment. Like most people who did not answer a particular calling from an early age, you placed work beside yourself; any occupation would fill up your day but not your heart. I liked that about you. I liked it enormously." -- Lionel Shriver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29973-it-seems-to-me-now-that-the-plain-state-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 10:46:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29973-it-seems-to-me-now-that-the-plain-state-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seems to me now that the plain state of being human is dramatic enough for anyone; you don't need to be a heroin addict or a performance poet to experience extremity. You just have to love someone." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75531-please-stop-patronizing-those-who-are-reading-a-book--</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 10:47:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75531-please-stop-patronizing-those-who-are-reading-a-book--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Please stop patronizing those who are reading a book - The Da Vinci Code, maybe- because they are enjoying it.  For a start, none of us know what kind of an effort this represents for the individual reader.  It could be his or her first full-length adult novel; it might be the book that finally reveals the purpose and joy of reading to someone who has hitherto been mystified by the attraction books exert on others.  And anyway, reading for enjoyment is what we should all be doing.  I don't mean we should all be reading chick lit or thrillers (although if that's what you want to read, it's fine by me, because here's something no one else will tell you: if you don't read the classics, or the novel that won this year's Booker Prize, then nothing bad will happen to you; more importantly,nothing good will happen to you if you do); I simply mean that turning pages should not be like walking through thick mud.  The whole purpose of books is that we read them, and if you find you can't, it might not be your inadequacy that's to blame.  &quot;Good&quot; books can be pretty awful sometimes." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9091-love-it-turns-out-is-as-undemocratic-as-money-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 10:49:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9091-love-it-turns-out-is-as-undemocratic-as-money-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love, it turns out, is as undemocratic as money, so it accumulates around people who have plenty of it already: the sane, the healthy, the lovable." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9330-i-d-stay-there-or-not-and-i-d-eat-or-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 10:51:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9330-i-d-stay-there-or-not-and-i-d-eat-or-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd stay there, or not, and I'd eat, or not, and I'd drink, or not, and go home, or not, and what I did or didn't do wouldn't matter to anyone at all.  And I walked for most of the day.  Do people get sad on holiday sometimes?  I can imagine they do, having all that time to think." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144726-maybe-the-best-thing-to-do-with-favorite-books-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 10:51:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144726-maybe-the-best-thing-to-do-with-favorite-books-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe the best thing to do with favorite books is to leave them be: to achieve such exalted position means that they entered your life at exactly the right time, in precisely the right place, and those conditions can never be recreated." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9316-a-man-who-wants-to-die-feels-angry-and-full</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 13:58:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9316-a-man-who-wants-to-die-feels-angry-and-full]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man who wants to die feels angry and full of life and desperate and bored and exhausted, all at the same time; he wants to fight everyone, and he wants to curl up in a ball and hide in a cupboard somewhere.  He wants to say sorry to everyone, and he wants everyone to know just how badly they've all let him down." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7337-books-are-let-s-face-it-better-than-everything-else-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 14:00:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7337-books-are-let-s-face-it-better-than-everything-else-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are, let's face it, better than everything else. If we played cultural Fantasy Boxing League, and made books go 15 rounds in the ring against the best that any other art form had to offer, then books would win pretty much every time. Go on, try it. “The Magic Flute” v. Middlemarch? Middlemarch in six. “The Last Supper” v. Crime and Punishment? Fyodor on points. See? I mean, I don’t know how scientific this is, but it feels like the novels are walking it. You might get the occasional exception -– “Blonde on Blonde” might mash up The Old Curiosity Shop, say, and I wouldn’t give much for Pale Fire’s chance against Citizen Kane. And every now and again you'd get a shock, because that happens in sport, so Back to the Future III might land a lucky punch on Rabbit, Run; but I'm still backing literature 29 times out of 30." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9331-one-could-argue-that-most-of-the-trouble-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 14:00:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9331-one-could-argue-that-most-of-the-trouble-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One could argue that most of the trouble in the world is caused by introspection." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138694-giving-anyone-anything-takes-courage-since-so-many-presents-backfire</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 12:21:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Lionel Shriver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138694-giving-anyone-anything-takes-courage-since-so-many-presents-backfire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Giving anyone anything takes courage, since so many presents backfire.  A gift conspicuously at odds with your tastes serves only to betray that the benefactor has no earthly clue who you are." -- Lionel Shriver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138693-yet-irina-had-once-tucked-away-she-wasn-t-sure-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 12:25:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Lionel Shriver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138693-yet-irina-had-once-tucked-away-she-wasn-t-sure-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yet Irina had once tucked away, she wasn't sure when or why, that happiness is almost definitionally a condition of which you are not aware at the time.  To inhabit your own contentment is to be wholly present, with no orbiting satellite to take clinical readings of the state of the planet.  Conventionally, you grow conscious of happiness at the very point that it begins to elude you.  When not misused to talk yourself into something - when not a lie - the h-word is a classification applied in retrospect.  It is a bracketing assessment, a label only decisively pasted onto an era once it is over." -- Lionel Shriver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/510300-what-would-i-like-to-get-away-from-complexity-anxiety</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 12:26:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Lionel Shriver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/510300-what-would-i-like-to-get-away-from-complexity-anxiety]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What would I like to get away from? Complexity. Anxiety. A feeling I've had my whole life that at any given time there's something I'm forgetting, some detail or chore, something that I'm supposed to be doing or should have already done. That nagging sensation - I get up with it, I go through the day with it, I go to sleep with it. When I was a kid, I had a habit of coming home from school on Friday afternoons and immediately doing my homework. So I'd wake up on Saturday morning with this wonderful sensation, a clean, open feeling of relief and possibility and calm. There'd be nothing I had to do. Those Saturday mornings, they were a taste of real freedom that I've hardly ever experienced as an adult. I never wake up in Elmsford with the feeling that I've done my homework." -- Lionel Shriver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/534911-he-d-been-unable-to-discern-whether-this-frantic-bustle-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 11:52:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Lionel Shriver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/534911-he-d-been-unable-to-discern-whether-this-frantic-bustle-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He'd been unable to discern whether this frantic bustle of hers was what it claimed to be - an ardent determination to live every remaining day to the fullest - or quite the opposite: an evasion. An equally ardent determination to distract herself, from what only she could know, and thus a complete failure to inhabit her life in the scarcest respect." -- Lionel Shriver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408301-the-only-thing-that-makes-one-an-artist-is-making</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 08:49:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by David Rakoff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408301-the-only-thing-that-makes-one-an-artist-is-making]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only thing that makes one an artist is making art.  And that requires the precise opposite of hanging out; a deeply lonely and unglamorous task of tolerating oneself long enough to push something out." -- David Rakoff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/569519-hanging-out-does-not-make-one-an-artist-a-secondhand</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 20:12:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by David Rakoff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/569519-hanging-out-does-not-make-one-an-artist-a-secondhand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...hanging out does not make one an artist. A secondhand wardrobe does not make one an artist. Neither do a hair-trigger temper, melancholic nature, propensity for tears, hating your parents, nor even HIV - I hate to say it - none of these make one an artist. They can help, but just as being gay does not make one witty (you can suck a mile of cock, as my friend Sarah Thyre puts it, it still won't make you Oscar Wilde, believe me), the only thing that makes one an artist is making art. And that requires the precise opposite of hanging out; a deeply lonely and unglamorous task of tolerating oneself long enough to push something out." -- David Rakoff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/707950-he-was-the-most-astonishing-contradiction-of-components-i-d-ever</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 06:22:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Chip Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/707950-he-was-the-most-astonishing-contradiction-of-components-i-d-ever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was the most astonishing contradiction of components I’d ever encountered. Shy yet fiercely communicative when putting an idea into your head. Vocally astringent regarding his own abilities but not to the point that he couldn’t produce—he was as prolific an artist (yes, an artist, and I never use the term, especially regarding people I like) I’ve ever seen. But I could feel it. Everything he sketched, penciled, inked, made—was a payment, one he could scarcely afford; as if it physically hurt him to put pencil to paper. Yet that only seemed to spur him on, to live far beyond his means. He was unable not to. For Sketch, to draw was to breath, and so the air became lead—silvery in the right light, dark soot in the wrong; heavy, slick and malleable—into shapes he brought together in glorious orchestration, with a child’s eye and a rocket scientist’s precision, all fortified by a furious melancholy, a quiet engine of sourceless shame and humility.

When it came to another’s work, he longed to praise it but then couldn’t resist critiquing it all within an inch of its life, analyzing deficiencies with uncontrollable abandon and laser accuracy. He was sharp as his Radio 914 pen nibs, and as pointed.

And then he’d apologize. Oh, he would apologize: Oh my GOD, forgive me, please don’t hate me, I’m SORRY, don’t listen to me, why am I saying things, what do I know, I don’t know anything, why do you listen to me you should just tell me to shut UP, I’m awful, forgive me, you hate me, don’t you? Tell the truth. Please don’t hate me. Please don’t. Please." -- Chip Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/710095-couples-stray-said-edgar-part-of-the-breaking-in-process-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 01:22:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Lionel Shriver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/710095-couples-stray-said-edgar-part-of-the-breaking-in-process-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Couples stray,” said Edgar. “Part of the breaking-in process.”

“Not breaking in, breaking.” Nicola differed sharply. “You can glue people together again. But then your relationship’s like any other repaired object, with cracks, blobs of epoxy, a little askew. It’s never the same. I can see you haven’t a notion what I’m on about, so you’ll have to take my word for it.”

“Christ, you’re a babe in the woods.” Edgar stopped slicing tomatoes. “You got it ass-backward. A marriage perched like porcelain on the mantelpiece is doomed. Sooner or later grown-ups treat each other like shit. You gotta be able to kick the thing around, less like china than an old shoe—bam, under the bed, or walk it through some puddles. No love’s gonna last it if can’t take abuse." -- Lionel Shriver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/554890-it-was-really-rather-wretched-that-you-couldn-t-will-yourself</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 19:01:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Lionel Shriver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/554890-it-was-really-rather-wretched-that-you-couldn-t-will-yourself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was really rather wretched that you couldn’t will yourself to fall in love, for the very effort can keep falling at bay. Nor could you will yourself to stay that way. Least of all could you will yourself NOT to fall in love, for thus far whatever meager resistance she had put up had only made the compulsion more intense. So you were perpetually tyrannized by a feeling that came and went as it pleased, like a cat with its own pet door. How much more agreeable, if love were something that you stirred up from a reliable recipe, or elected, however perversely, to pour down the drain. Still, there was nothing for it. The popular expression notwithstanding, love was not something you made.  Nor could you dispose of the stuff once manifested because it was inconvenient, or even because it was wicked, and ruining your life, and, by the by, someone else’s." -- Lionel Shriver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/722121-it-s-not-all-it-s-cracked-up-to-be-having-real</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 13:41:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Lionel Shriver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/722121-it-s-not-all-it-s-cracked-up-to-be-having-real]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...it's not all it's cracked up to be, having real emotions. I know that with the most dazzling men there have been times I've been terribly bored and I am sure they've been equally bored with me. Then much of life is indeed boring, and that's nobody's fault....Myself, I've been in the very arms of a beloved and felt nothing, when the only choice was whether to admit I felt nothing or to lie. The hardest thing about loving someone is those moments when you're not. And there are inevitablty such moments; the amount of trust required to get past them is stupendous." -- Lionel Shriver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728459-if-edgar-sounded-overeager-even-rushed-the-race-was-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 21:51:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Lionel Shriver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728459-if-edgar-sounded-overeager-even-rushed-the-race-was-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If Edgar sounded overeager, even rushed, the race was with his own temperament. He placed a premium on savvy. Yet since you could only obtain new information by admitting you didn’t know it already, savvy required an apprenticeship as a naive twit. You had to ask crude, obvious questions…you had to sit still while worldly-wise warhorses…fired withering glances as if you were born yesterday.


Well, Edgar was born yesterday for the moment, although his tolerance for being treated liked a simpleton was in short supply. He’d needed to rattle off a multitude of stupid questions before he embraced his next incarnation as an insider. The trouble was that savvy coated your brain in plastic like a driver’s license: nothing more could get in. Hence the point at which you decided you knew everything was exactly the point at which you became an ignorant dipshit." -- Lionel Shriver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/673423-this-brings-up-yet-another-far-more-important-misconception-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 19:21:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by David Rakoff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/673423-this-brings-up-yet-another-far-more-important-misconception-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This brings up yet another, far more important misconception: that being comically generative and having a sense of humor are one and the same thing. The former is among the least important things in the world, while the latter is among the most. One is a handy social tool, the other an integral component of human survival. It bears repeating a third time: Not being funny doesn't make you a bad person. Not having a sense of humor does." -- David Rakoff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/737594-pregnancy-had-seemed-a-reasonable-excuse-for-letting-her-metal-smithing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 09:57:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Lionel Shriver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/737594-pregnancy-had-seemed-a-reasonable-excuse-for-letting-her-metal-smithing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pregnancy had seemed a reasonable excuse for letting her metal-smithing tools languish, but that accounted for only eighteen months of the last twenty-six years. Motherhood wasn't the real problem, though it took him a long time to figure out what was. She needed resistance, the very quality that metal most demonstrably offered up. Suddenly Glynis had no difficulty to overcome, no hard artisan's life with galleries filching half the too-small price of a mokume brooch that had taken three weeks to forge. No, her husband made a good living, and if she slept late and dawdled the afternoon away reading Lustre, American Craft Magazine and Lapidary Journal, the phone bill would still get paid. For that matter, she needed need itself. She could overcome her anguish about embarking on an object that, once completed, might not meet her exacting standards only if she had no choice. In this sense, his helping had hurt her. By providing the financial cushion that should have facilitated making all the metal whathaveyou she liked, he had ruined her life. Wrapped in a slackening bow, ease was a poisonous present." -- Lionel Shriver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41291-the-sense-of-unhappiness-is-so-much-easier-to-convey</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 19:06:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41291-the-sense-of-unhappiness-is-so-much-easier-to-convey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sense of unhappiness is so much easier to convey than that of happiness. In misery we seem aware of our own existence, even though it may be in the form of a monstrous egotism: this pain of mine is individual, this nerve that winces belongs to me and to no other. But happiness annihilates  us: we lose our identity." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159220-i-had-never-wanted-to-be-one-of-those-girls</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2013 17:32:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Elizabeth McCracken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159220-i-had-never-wanted-to-be-one-of-those-girls]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had never wanted to be one of those girls in love with boys who would not have me. Unrequited love - plain desperate aboveboard boy-chasing - turned you into a salesperson, and what you were selling was something he didn't want, couldn't use, would never miss. Unrequited love was deciding to be useless, and I could never abide uselessness.

Neither could James. He understood. In such situations, you do one of two things - you either walk away and deny yourself, or you do sneaky things to get what you need. You attend weddings, you go for walks. You say, yes. Yes, you're my best friend, too." -- Elizabeth McCracken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/822921-trexler-knew-what-he-wanted-and-what-in-general-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 15:00:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/822921-trexler-knew-what-he-wanted-and-what-in-general-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Trexler knew what he wanted, and what, in general, all men wanted; and he was glad, in a way, that it was both inexpressible and unattainable, and that it wasn't a wing. He was satisfied to remember that it was deep, formless, enduring and impossible of fulfillment, and that it made men sick, and that when you sauntered along Third Avenue and looked through the doorways into the dim saloons, you could sometimes pick out from the unregenerate ranks the ones who had not forgotten, gazing steadily into the bottoms of their glasses on the long chance that they could get another little peek at it. Trexler found himself renewed by the remembrance that what he wanted was at once great and microscopic, and that although it borrowed from the nature of large deeds and of youthful love and of old songs and early intimations, it was not any one of these things, and that it had not been isolated or pinned down, and that a man who attempted to define it in the privacy of a doctor's office would fall flat on his face." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/870193-his-weight-makes-him-a-social-pariah-it-reduces-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 18:28:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Lionel Shriver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/870193-his-weight-makes-him-a-social-pariah-it-reduces-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His weight makes him a social pariah. It reduces the likelihood he’ll remarry. It has grave implications for his health. But it isn’t evil. Just like all that exercise of yours has nothing to do with being good. I know you think it does. It makes you feel good, and feel good about yourself, and feel superior to people who slob around all day. But it’s mostly a waste of time that doesn’t do anything for anybody else but you." -- Lionel Shriver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119935-there-is-one-province-in-which-sooner-or-later-virtually</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 13:54:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by Lionel Shriver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119935-there-is-one-province-in-which-sooner-or-later-virtually]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is one province in which, sooner or later, virtually everyone gets dealt a leading role--hero, heroine, or villain.... Unlike the slight implications of quotidian dilemmas that confront the average citizen in other areas of life ... the stakes in this realm could not be higher. For chances are that at some point along the line you will hold in your hands another person's heart. There is no greater responsibility on the planet. However you contend with this fragile organ, which pounds or seizes in accordance with your caprice, will take your full measure." -- Lionel Shriver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213688-what-passes-for-hip-cynical-transcendence-of-sentiment-is-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 12:29:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213688-what-passes-for-hip-cynical-transcendence-of-sentiment-is-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What passes for hip cynical transcendence of sentiment is really some kind of fear of being really human, since to be really human [...] is probably to be unavoidably sentimental and naïve and goo-prone and generally pathetic." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229234-almost-nothing-important-that-ever-happens-to-you-happens</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 12:29:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana Jeri add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229234-almost-nothing-important-that-ever-happens-to-you-happens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[...] almost nothing important that ever happens to you happens because you engineer it. Destiny has no beeper; destiny always leans trenchcoated out of an alley with some sort of 'psst' that you usually can't even hear because you're in such a rush to or from something important you've tried to engineer. " -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
