<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/109233-mari]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/109233-mari" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 21:03:56 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2447-yes-i-am-a-dreamer-for-a-dreamer-is-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 21:03:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2447-yes-i-am-a-dreamer-for-a-dreamer-is-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yes: I am a dreamer. For a dreamer is one who can only find his way by moonlight, and his punishment is that he sees the dawn before the rest of the world." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12745-our-politics-religion-news-athletics-education-and-commerce-have-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 12:46:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by Neil Postman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12745-our-politics-religion-news-athletics-education-and-commerce-have-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our politics, religion, news, athletics, education and commerce have been transformed into congenial adjuncts of show business, largely without protest or even much popular notice.  The result is that we are a people on the verge of amusing ourselves to death." -- Neil Postman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25-we-are-all-in-the-gutter-but-some-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 12:45:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25-we-are-all-in-the-gutter-but-some-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all in the gutter, but some of us are looking at the stars." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/454-a-cynic-is-a-man-who-knows-the-price-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 12:45:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/454-a-cynic-is-a-man-who-knows-the-price-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A cynic is a man who knows the price of everything, and the value of nothing." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18978-to-be-ignorant-of-what-occurred-before-you-were-born</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 12:46:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18978-to-be-ignorant-of-what-occurred-before-you-were-born]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be ignorant of what occurred before you were born is to remain always a child. For what is the worth of human life, unless it is woven into the life of our ancestors by the records of history?" -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12746-the-power-of-the-ballot-we-need-in-sheer-self-defense</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 14:58:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by W.E.B. Du Bois]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12746-the-power-of-the-ballot-we-need-in-sheer-self-defense]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The power of the ballot we need in sheer self-defense, - else what shall save us from a second slavery?" -- W.E.B. Du Bois]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12754-dad-himself-used-to-tell-a-story-about-one-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 15:07:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by Frank B. Gilbreth Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12754-dad-himself-used-to-tell-a-story-about-one-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dad himself used to tell a story about one time when Mother went off to fill a lecture engagement and left him in charge at home.  When Mother returned, she asked him if everything had run smoothly.
Didn't have any trouble except with that one over there,' he replied.  'But a spanking brought him into line.'
Mother could handle any crisis without losing her composure.
That's not one of ours, dear,' she said.  'He belongs next door." -- Frank B. Gilbreth Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12760-we-greeks-believe-that-a-man-who-takes-no-part</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 15:22:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by Thucydides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12760-we-greeks-believe-that-a-man-who-takes-no-part]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We Greeks believe that a man who takes no part in public affairs is not merely lazy, but good for nothing" -- Thucydides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2608-these-violent-delights-have-violent-ends-and-in-their-triump</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 21:12:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2608-these-violent-delights-have-violent-ends-and-in-their-triump]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These violent delights have violent ends
And in their triump die, like fire and powder
Which, as they kiss, consume" -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174939-i-believe-in-political-equality-but-there-are-two-opposite</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 23:55:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174939-i-believe-in-political-equality-but-there-are-two-opposite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in political equality. But there are two opposite reasons for being a democrat. You may think all men so good that they deserve a share in the government of the commonwealth, and so wise that the commonwealth needs their advice. That is, in my opinion, the false, romantic doctrine of democracy. On the other hand, you may believe fallen men to be so wicked that not one of them can be trusted with any irresponsible power over his fellows.
	That I believe to be the true ground of democracy. I do not believe that God created an egalitarian world. I believe the authority of parent over child, husband over wife, learned over simple to have been as much a part of the original plan as the authority of man over beast. I believe that if we had not fallen...patriarchal monarchy would be the sole lawful government. But since we have learned sin, we have found, as Lord Acton says, that 'all power corrupts, and absolute power corrupts absolutely.' The only remedy has been to take away the powers and substitute a legal fiction of equality. The authority of father and husband has been rightly abolished on the legal plane, not because this authority is in itself bad (on the contrary, it is, I hold, divine in origin), but because fathers and husbands are bad. Theocracy has been rightly abolished not because it is bad that learned priests should govern ignorant laymen, but because priests are wicked men like the rest of us. Even the authority of man over beast has had to be interfered with because it is constantly abused." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456296-she-turned-and-at-her-turning-came-a-fragrant-air</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:03:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456296-she-turned-and-at-her-turning-came-a-fragrant-air]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She turned, and at her turning came a fragrant air
Of godhead, and her robe grew long; ambrosial hair
Flashed, and a rosy brightness on her neck, and all
The goddess in her going was revealed. His call
Followed his mother vanishing. &quot;Unkind! Thou too?
And why so oft deceive me under shapes untrue,
Suffering me not to take thee by the hand nor hear
Thy voice unfeigned and answer in thy listening ear?" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456300-i-suppose-even-dictators-have-their-chummy-moments-when-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:14:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456300-i-suppose-even-dictators-have-their-chummy-moments-when-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I suppose even Dictators have their chummy moments, when they put their feet up and relax with the boys, but it was plain from the outset that if Roderick Spode had a sunnier side, he had not come with any idea of exhibiting it now. His manner was curt. One sensed the absence of the bonhomous note.
...
Here he laid a hand on my shoulder, and I can't remember when I have experienced anything more unpleasant. Apart from what Jeeves would have called the symbolism of the action, he had a grip like the bite of a horse.
&quot;Did you say 'Oh yes?'&quot; he asked.
&quot;Oh no,&quot; I assured him." -- P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170584-there-are-moments-jeeves-when-one-asks-oneself-do-trousers</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:15:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170584-there-are-moments-jeeves-when-one-asks-oneself-do-trousers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are moments, Jeeves, when one asks oneself, 'Do trousers matter?'&quot;
&quot;The mood will pass, sir." -- P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456303-to-day-all-our-novels-and-newspapers-will-be-found-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:21:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456303-to-day-all-our-novels-and-newspapers-will-be-found-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To-day all our novels and newspapers will be found to be swarming with numberless allusions to the popular character called a Cave-Man. He seems to be quite familiar to us, not only as a public character but as a private character. His psychology is seriously taken into account in psychological fiction and psychological medicine. So far as I can understand, his chief occupation in life was knocking his wife about, or treating women in general with what is, I believe, known in the world of the film as 'rough stuff.' I have never happeend to come upon the evidence for this idea; and I do not know on what primitive diaries or prehistoric divorce-reports it is founded. Nor, as I have explained elsewhere, have I ever been able to see the probability of it, even considered a priori. We are always told without any explanation or authority that primitive man waved a club and knocked the woman down before he carried her off. But on every animal analogy, it would seem an almost morbid modesty and reluctance, on the part of the lady, always to insist on being knocked down before consenting to be carried off. And I repeat that I can never comprehend why, when the male was so very rude, the female should have been so very refined. The cave-man may have been a brute, but there is no reason why he should have been more brutal than the brutes. And the loves of the giraffes and the river romances of the hippopotami are affected without any of this preliminary fracas or shindy." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48128-the-glory-of-christianity-is-to-conquer-by-forgiveness</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:23:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by William Blake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48128-the-glory-of-christianity-is-to-conquer-by-forgiveness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The glory of Christianity is to conquer by forgiveness." -- William Blake]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33698-m-y-religious-belief-teaches-me-to-feel-as-safe-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:25:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by Stonewall Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33698-m-y-religious-belief-teaches-me-to-feel-as-safe-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[M]y religious belief teaches me to feel as safe in battle as in bed. God has fixed the time for my death. I do not concern myself about that, but to be always ready, no matter when it may overtake me. That is the way all men should live, and then all would be equally brave." -- Stonewall Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/946-no-man-who-worships-education-has-got-the-best-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:25:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/946-no-man-who-worships-education-has-got-the-best-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No man who worships education has got the best out of education... Without a gentle contempt for education no man's education is complete." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456304-to-your-eyes-a-thousand-years-are-like-yesterday-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:33:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by Psalm 89]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456304-to-your-eyes-a-thousand-years-are-like-yesterday-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To Your eyes a thousand years are like yesterday come and gone, no more than a watch in the night.

You sweep men away like a dream, like grass which springs up in the morning.

In the morning it springs up and flowers, by evening it withers and fades.

So we are destroyed in Your anger, struck with terror in Your fury.

Our guilt lies open before You; our secrets in the light of Your face.

All our days pass away in Your anger. Our life is over like a sigh.

Our span is seventy years or eighty for those who are strong. And most of these are emptiness and pain, they pass swiftly and we are gone." -- Psalm 89]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25839-i-discovered-that-my-obsession-for-having-each-thing-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:38:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by Gabriel Garcia Marquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25839-i-discovered-that-my-obsession-for-having-each-thing-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I discovered that my obsession for having each thing in the right place, each subject at the right time, each word in the right style, was not the well-deserved reward of an ordered mind but just the opposite: a complete system of pretense invented by me to hide the disorder of my nature. I discovered that I am not disciplined out of virtue but as a reaction to my negligence, that I appear generous in order to conceal my meanness, that I pass myself off as prudent because I am evil-minded, that I am conciliatory in order not to succumb to my repressed rage, that I am punctual only to hide how little I care about other people’s time. I learned, in short, that love is not a condition of the spirit but a sign of the zodiac." -- Gabriel Garcia Marquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440790-esterina-i-vent-anni-ti-minacciano-grigiorosea-nube-che-a-poco</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:40:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by Eugenio Montale]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440790-esterina-i-vent-anni-ti-minacciano-grigiorosea-nube-che-a-poco]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Esterina, i vent’anni ti minacciano,
grigiorosea nube
che a poco a poco in sé ti chiude.
Ciò intendi e non paventi.
Sommersa ti vedremo
nella fumea che il vento
lacera o addensa, violento.
Poi dal fiotto di cenere uscirai
adusta più che mai,
proteso a un’avventura più lontana 
l’intento viso che assembra
l’arciera Diana.
Salgono i venti autunni,
t’avviluppano andate primavere;
ecco per te rintocca
un presagio nell’elisie sfere. 
Un suono non ti renda
qual d’incrinata brocca
percossa!; io prego sia
per te concerto ineffabile
di sonagliere.
La dubbia dimane non t’impaura.
Leggiadra ti distendi 
sullo scoglio lucente di sale 
e al sole bruci le membra.
Ricordi la lucertola
ferma sul masso brullo;
te insidia giovinezza,
quella il lacciòlo d’erba del fanciullo.
L’acqua’ è la forza che ti tempra, 
nell’acqua ti ritrovi e ti rinnovi: 
noi ti pensiamo come un’alga, un ciottolo
come un’equorea creatura
che la salsedine non intacca
ma torna al lito più pura.
Hai ben ragione tu!
Non turbare
di ubbie il sorridente presente.
La tua gaiezza impegna già il futuro
ed un crollar di spalle
dirocca i fortilizî
del tuo domani oscuro.
T’alzi e t’avanzi sul ponticello
esiguo, sopra il gorgo che stride:
il tuo profilo s’incide
contro uno sfondo di perla.
Esiti a sommo del tremulo asse,
poi ridi, e come spiccata da un vento
t’abbatti fra le braccia
del tuo divino amico che t’afferra. 
Ti guardiamo noi, della razza 
di chi rimane a terra" -- Eugenio Montale]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381-to-die-would-be-an-awfully-big-adventure</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:41:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381-to-die-would-be-an-awfully-big-adventure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To die would be an awfully big adventure." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48568-god-gave-us-memory-so-that-we-might-have-roses</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:42:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48568-god-gave-us-memory-so-that-we-might-have-roses]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God gave us memory so that we might have roses in December." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4627-if-you-have-it-love-you-don-t-need-to-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:43:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4627-if-you-have-it-love-you-don-t-need-to-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you have it [love], you don't need to have anything else, and if you don't have it, it doesn't matter much what else you have." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42861-stars-are-beautiful-but-they-must-not-take-an-active</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:43:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42861-stars-are-beautiful-but-they-must-not-take-an-active]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stars are beautiful, but they must not take an active part in anything, they must just look on forever. It is a punishment put on them for something they did so long ago that no star now knows what it was." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2452-i-think-god-in-creating-man-somewhat-overestimated-his-ability</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:44:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2452-i-think-god-in-creating-man-somewhat-overestimated-his-ability]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think God, in creating man, somewhat overestimated his ability." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1247-who-being-loved-is-poor</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:46:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1247-who-being-loved-is-poor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who, being loved, is poor?" -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14392-if-you-want-to-tell-people-the-truth-make-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:46:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14392-if-you-want-to-tell-people-the-truth-make-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to tell people the truth, make them laugh, otherwise they'll kill you." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3067-to-lose-one-parent-may-be-regarded-as-a-misfortune</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:47:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3067-to-lose-one-parent-may-be-regarded-as-a-misfortune]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To lose one parent may be regarded as a misfortune; to lose both looks like carelessness." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456919-you-say-you-are-a-poet-of-law-i-saw</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 12:20:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456919-you-say-you-are-a-poet-of-law-i-saw]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You say you are a poet of law; I saw you are a contradiction in terms. I only wonder there were not comets and earthquakes on the night you appeared in this garden" -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456932-an-artist-is-identical-with-an-anarchist-he-cried-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 12:39:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mari add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456932-an-artist-is-identical-with-an-anarchist-he-cried-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An artist is identical with an anarchist,' he cried. 'You might transpose the words anywhere. An anarchist is an artist. The man who throws a bomb is an artist, because he prefers a great moment to everything. He sees how much more valuable is one burst of blazing light, one peal of perfect thunder, than the mere common bodies of a few shapeless policemen. An artist disregards all governments, abolishes all conventions. The poet delights in disorder only. If it were not so, the most poetical thing in the world would be the Underground Railway.'
'So it is,' said Mr. Syme.
'Nonsense!' said Gregory, who was very rational when any one else attempted paradox." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
