<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1093398-samantha]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1093398-samantha" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 12:52:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460006-to-burn-with-desire-and-keep-quiet-about-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 12:52:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Federico García Lorca]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460006-to-burn-with-desire-and-keep-quiet-about-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To burn with desire and keep quiet about it is the greatest punishment we can bring on ourselves." -- Federico García Lorca]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377704-down-with-tyranny-bramble-cried-aristocracy-autocracy-monocracy-other-ocracy</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 11:53:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Heather Dixon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377704-down-with-tyranny-bramble-cried-aristocracy-autocracy-monocracy-other-ocracy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Down with tyranny!' Bramble cried. 'Aristocracy! Autocracy! Monocracy! Other ocracy things! You are outnumbered, sir! &lt;i&gt;Surrender&lt;/i&gt;!" -- Heather Dixon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315932-once-a-little-boy-sent-me-a-charming-card-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 07:33:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Maurice Sendak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315932-once-a-little-boy-sent-me-a-charming-card-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once a little boy sent me a charming card with a little drawing on it. I loved it. I answer all my children’s letters — sometimes very hastily — but this one I lingered over. I sent him a card and I drew a picture of a Wild Thing on it. I wrote, “Dear Jim: I loved your card.” Then I got a letter back from his mother and she said, “Jim loved your card so much he ate it.” That to me was one of the highest compliments I’ve ever received. He didn’t care that it was an original Maurice Sendak drawing or anything. He saw it, he loved it, he ate it." -- Maurice Sendak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49273-one-glance-at-a-book-and-you-hear-the-voice</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 10:01:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49273-one-glance-at-a-book-and-you-hear-the-voice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One glance at a book and you hear the voice of another person, perhaps someone dead for 1,000 years. To read is to voyage through time." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81428-d-on-t-ever-apologize-to-an-author-for-buying-something-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 10:01:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81428-d-on-t-ever-apologize-to-an-author-for-buying-something-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[D]on't ever apologize to an author for buying something in paperback, or taking it out from a library (that's what they're there for. Use your library). Don't apologize to this author for buying books second hand, or getting them from bookcrossing or borrowing a friend's copy. What's important to me is that people read the books and enjoy them, and that, at some point in there, the book was bought by someone. And that people who like things, tell other people. The most important thing is that people read... " -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 10:02:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 10:02:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May your coming year be filled with magic and dreams and good madness. I hope you read some fine books and kiss someone who thinks you're wonderful, and don't forget to make some art -- write or draw or build or sing or live as only you can. And I hope, somewhere in the next year, you surprise yourself." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 10:04:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/699895-a-peasant-that-reads-is-a-prince-in-waiting</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 07:47:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Walter Mosley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/699895-a-peasant-that-reads-is-a-prince-in-waiting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A peasant that reads is a prince in waiting." -- Walter Mosley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132670-i-hope-you-will-have-a-wonderful-year-that-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2013 12:16:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132670-i-hope-you-will-have-a-wonderful-year-that-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hope you will have a wonderful year, that you'll dream dangerously and outrageously, that you'll make something that didn't exist before you made it, that you will be loved and that you will be liked, and that you will have people to love and to like in return. And, most importantly (because I think there should be more kindness and more wisdom in the world right now), that you will, when you need to be, be wise, and that you will always be kind." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15200-war-is-what-happens-when-language-fails</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 18:55:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15200-war-is-what-happens-when-language-fails]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["War is what happens when language fails." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7552-don-t-let-the-bastards-grind-you-down</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 18:56:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7552-don-t-let-the-bastards-grind-you-down]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't let the bastards grind you down." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188039-men-are-afraid-that-women-will-laugh-at-them-women</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 18:57:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188039-men-are-afraid-that-women-will-laugh-at-them-women]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men are afraid that women will laugh at them. Women are afraid that men will kill them." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105196-how-could-i-be-sleeping-with-this-particular-man-surely</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 18:58:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105196-how-could-i-be-sleeping-with-this-particular-man-surely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How could I be sleeping with this particular man.... Surely only true love could justify my lack of taste." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13088-and-she-finds-it-difficult-to-believe-that-a-person-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 18:58:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13088-and-she-finds-it-difficult-to-believe-that-a-person-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And she finds it difficult to believe—that a person would love her even when she isn't trying. Trying to figure out what other people need, trying to be worthy." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207355-that-is-such-crap-how-dare-you-be-so-fraudulently</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 17:23:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Helen Fielding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207355-that-is-such-crap-how-dare-you-be-so-fraudulently]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That is such crap. How dare you be so fraudulently flirtatious, cowardly and dysfunctional? I am not interested in emotional fuckwittage. Goodbye." -- Helen Fielding]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
