<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1093785-dayle-kennedy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1093785-dayle-kennedy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 12:32:33 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44274-people-speak-sometimes-about-the-bestial-cruelty-of-man-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 12:32:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky  ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44274-people-speak-sometimes-about-the-bestial-cruelty-of-man-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People speak sometimes about the &quot;bestial&quot; cruelty of man, but that is terribly unjust and offensive to beasts, no animal could ever be so cruel as a man, so artfully, so artistically cruel." -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky  ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181804-existentialism-isn-t-so-atheistic-that-it-wears-itself-out-showing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 18:40:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181804-existentialism-isn-t-so-atheistic-that-it-wears-itself-out-showing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Existentialism isn't so atheistic that it wears itself out showing that God doesn't exist. Rather, it declares that even if God did exist, that would change nothing." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117869-when-reason-fails-the-devil-helps</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 18:40:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117869-when-reason-fails-the-devil-helps]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When reason fails, the devil helps!" -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176384-i-think-the-devil-doesn-t-exist-but-man-has-created</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 18:41:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176384-i-think-the-devil-doesn-t-exist-but-man-has-created]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think the devil doesn't exist, but man has created him, he has created him in his own image and likeness." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140105-i-am-alone-i-thought-and-they-are-everybody</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 18:44:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140105-i-am-alone-i-thought-and-they-are-everybody]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am alone, I thought, and they are everybody." -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80810-you-are-told-a-lot-about-your-education-but-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 18:44:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Dostoyevsky Fyodor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80810-you-are-told-a-lot-about-your-education-but-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are told a lot about your education, but some beautiful, sacred memory, preserved since childhood, is perhaps the best education of all. If a man carries many such memories into life with him, he is saved for the rest of his days. And even if only one good memory is left in our hearts, it may also be the instrument of our salvation one day." -- Dostoyevsky Fyodor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71299-the-more-stupid-one-is-the-closer-one-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 18:47:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71299-the-more-stupid-one-is-the-closer-one-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The more stupid one is, the closer one is to reality.  The more stupid one is, the clearer one is.  Stupidity is brief and artless, while intelligence squirms and hides itself.  Intelligence is unprincipled, but stupidity is honest and straightforward." -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7244-in-a-morbid-condition-dreams-are-often-distinguished-by-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 18:47:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7244-in-a-morbid-condition-dreams-are-often-distinguished-by-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a morbid condition, dreams are often distinguished by their remarkably graphic, vivid, and extremely lifelike quality. The resulting picture is sometimes monstrous, but the setting and the whole process of the presentation sometimes happen to be so probable, and with details so subtle, unexpected, yet artistically consistent with the whole fullness of the picture, that even the dreamer himself would be unable to invent them in reality, though he were as much an artist as Pushkin or Turgenev. Such dreams, morbid dreams, are always long remembered and produce a strong impression on the disturbed and already excited organism of the person.Raskolnikov had a terrible dream." -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7124-what-is-to-be-done-with-the-millions-of-facts</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 18:48:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7124-what-is-to-be-done-with-the-millions-of-facts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is to be done with the millions of facts that bear witness that men, consciously, that is fully understanding their real interests, have left them in the background and have rushed headlong on another path, to meet peril and danger, compelled to this course by nobody and by nothing, but, as it were, simply disliking the beaten track, and have obstinately, wilfully, struck out another difficult, absurd way, seeking it almost in the darkness. So, I suppose, this obstinacy and perversity were pleasanter to them than any advantage...

The fact is, gentlemen, it seems there must really exist something that is dearer to almost every man than his greatest advantages, or (not to be illogical) there is a most advantageous advantage (the very one omitted of which we spoke just now) which is more important and more advantageous than all other advantages, for the sake of which a man if necessary is ready to act in opposition to all laws; that is, in opposition to reason, honour, peace, prosperity -- in fact, in opposition to all those excellent and useful things if only he can attain that fundamental, most advantageous advantage which is dearer to him than all. &quot;Yes, but it's advantage all the same,&quot; you will retort. But excuse me, I'll make the point clear, and it is not a case of playing upon words. What matters is, that this advantage is remarkable from the very fact that it breaks down all our classifications, and continually shatters every system constructed by lovers of mankind for the benefit of mankind. In fact, it upsets everything...

One's own free unfettered choice, one's own caprice, however wild it may be, one's own fancy worked up at times to frenzy -- is that very &quot;most advantageous advantage&quot; which we have overlooked, which comes under no classification and against which all systems and theories are continually being shattered to atoms. And how do these wiseacres know that man wants a normal, a virtuous choice? What has made them conceive that man must want a rationally advantageous choice? What man wants is simply independent choice, whatever that independence may cost and wherever it may lead. And choice, of course, the devil only knows what choice.

Of course, this very stupid thing, this caprice of ours, may be in reality, gentlemen, more advantageous for us than anything else on earth, especially in certain cases… for in any circumstances it preserves for us what is most precious and most important -- that is, our personality, our individuality. Some, you see, maintain that this really is the most precious thing for mankind; choice can, of course, if it chooses, be in agreement with reason… It is profitable and sometimes even praiseworthy. But very often, and even most often, choice is utterly and stubbornly opposed to reason ... and ... and ... do you know that that, too, is profitable, sometimes even praiseworthy?

I believe in it, I answer for it, for the whole work of man really seems to consist in nothing but proving to himself every minute that he is a man and not a piano-key! …And this being so, can one help being tempted to rejoice that it has not yet come off, and that desire still depends on something we don't know?

You will scream at me (that is, if you condescend to do so) that no one is touching my free will, that all they are concerned with is that my will should of itself, of its own free will, coincide with my own normal interests, with the laws of nature and arithmetic. Good heavens, gentlemen, what sort of free will is left when we come to tabulation and arithmetic, when it will all be a case of twice two make four? Twice two makes four without my will. As if free will meant that!" -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140106-i-utter-what-you-would-not-dare-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:02:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140106-i-utter-what-you-would-not-dare-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I utter what you would not dare think" -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62939-love-life-more-than-the-meaning-of-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:08:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62939-love-life-more-than-the-meaning-of-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love life more than the meaning of it?" -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5615-is-it-not-possible-to-eat-me-without-insisting-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:08:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5615-is-it-not-possible-to-eat-me-without-insisting-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is it not possible to eat me without insisting that I sing praises of my devourer?" -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31837-to-go-wrong-in-one-s-own-way-is-better-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:09:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31837-to-go-wrong-in-one-s-own-way-is-better-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To go wrong in one's own way is better then to go right in someone else's." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132598-in-most-cases-people-even-wicked-people-are-far-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:09:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132598-in-most-cases-people-even-wicked-people-are-far-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In most cases, people, even wicked people, are far more naive and simple-hearted than one generally assumes.  And so are we." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279569-it-is-amazing-what-one-ray-of-sunshine-can-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:09:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Dostoyevsky, Fyodor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279569-it-is-amazing-what-one-ray-of-sunshine-can-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is amazing what one ray of sunshine can do for a man!" -- Dostoyevsky, Fyodor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23875-some-sleepers-have-intelligent-faces-even-in-sleep-while-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:09:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23875-some-sleepers-have-intelligent-faces-even-in-sleep-while-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some sleepers have intelligent faces even in sleep, while other faces, even intelligent ones, become very stupid in sleep and therefore ridiculous. I don't know what makes that happen; I only want to say that a laughing man, like a sleeping one, most often knows nothing about his face. A great many people don't know how to laugh at all. However, there's nothing to know here: it's a gift, and it can't be fabricated. It can only be fabricated by re-educating oneself, developing oneself for the better, and overcoming the bad instincts of one's character; then the laughter of such a person might quite possibly change for the better. A man can give himself away completely by his laughter, so that you suddenly learn all of his innermost secrets. Even indisputably intelligent laughter is sometimes repulsive. Laughter calls first of all for sincerity, and where does one find sincerity? Laughter calls for lack of spite, but people most often laugh spitefully. Sincere and unspiteful laughter is mirth. A man's mirth is a feature that gives away the whole man, from head to foot. Someone's character won't be cracked for a long time, then the man bursts out laughing somehow quite sincerely, and his whole character suddenly opens up as if on the flat of your hand. Only a man of the loftiest and happiest development knows how to be mirthful infectiously, that is, irresistibly and goodheartedly. I'm not speaking of his mental development, but of his character, of the whole man. And so, if you want to discern a man and know his soul, you must look, not at how he keeps silent, or how he speaks, or how he weeps, or even how he is stirred by the noblest ideas, but you had better look at him when he laughs. If a man has a good laugh, it means he's a good man. Note at the same time all the nuances: for instance, a man's laughter must in no case seem stupid to you, however merry and simplehearted it may be. The moment you notice the slightest trace of stupidity in someone's laughter, it undoubtedly means that the man is of limited intelligence, though he may do nothing but pour out ideas. Or if his laughter isn't stupid, but the man himself, when he laughs, for some reason suddenly seems ridiculous to you, even just slightly—know, then, that the man has no real sense of dignity, not fully in any case. Or finally, if his laughter is infectious, but for some reason still seems banal to you, know, then, that the man's nature is on the banal side as well, and all the noble and lofty that you noticed in him before is either deliberately affected or unconsciously borrowed, and later on the man is certain to change for the worse, to take up what's 'useful' and throw his noble ideas away without regret, as the errors and infatuations of youth." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9972-you-are-not-entitled-to-your-opinion-you-are-entitled</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:17:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Harlan Ellison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9972-you-are-not-entitled-to-your-opinion-you-are-entitled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are not entitled to your opinion. You are entitled to your &lt;i&gt;informed&lt;/i&gt; opinion. No one is entitled to be ignorant." -- Harlan Ellison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102395-if-you-make-people-think-they-re-thinking-they-ll-love-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:17:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Harlan Ellison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102395-if-you-make-people-think-they-re-thinking-they-ll-love-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you make people think they're thinking, they'll love you; but if you really make them think, they'll hate you." -- Harlan Ellison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7245-the-only-thing-worth-writing-about-is-people-people-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:17:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Harlan Ellison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7245-the-only-thing-worth-writing-about-is-people-people-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only thing worth writing about is people. People. Human beings. Men and women whose individuality must be created, line by line, insight by insight. If you do not do it, the story is a failure. [...] There is no nobler chore in the universe than holding up the mirror of reality and turning it slightly, so we have a new and different perception of the commonplace, the everyday, the 'normal', the obvious. People are reflected in the glass. The fantasy situation into which you thrust them is the mirror itself. And what we are shown should illuminate and alter our perception of the world around us. Failing that, you have failed totally." -- Harlan Ellison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51303-the-world-is-turning-into-a-cesspool-of-imbeciles</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:17:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Harlan Ellison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51303-the-world-is-turning-into-a-cesspool-of-imbeciles]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is turning into a cesspool of imbeciles." -- Harlan Ellison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25888-k-is-for-kenghis-khan-he-was-a-very-nice</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:18:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Harlan Ellison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25888-k-is-for-kenghis-khan-he-was-a-very-nice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["K is for &quot;Kenghis Khan&quot;; He was a very nice person. History has no record of him. There is a moral in that, somewhere." -- Harlan Ellison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219911-the-ability-to-dream-is-all-i-have-to-give</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:18:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Harlan Ellison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219911-the-ability-to-dream-is-all-i-have-to-give]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The ability to dream is all I have to give. That is my responsibility; that is my burden. And even I grow tired." -- Harlan Ellison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139434-the-prince-says-that-the-world-will-be-saved-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 05:14:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139434-the-prince-says-that-the-world-will-be-saved-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The prince says that the world will be saved by beauty! And I maintain that the reason he has such playful ideas is that he is in love. " -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127210-i-did-not-bow-down-to-you-i-bowed-down</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 05:14:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127210-i-did-not-bow-down-to-you-i-bowed-down]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I did not bow down to you, I bowed down to all the suffering of humanity." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16238-some-people-never-go-crazy-what-truly-horrible-lives-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 05:15:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16238-some-people-never-go-crazy-what-truly-horrible-lives-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people never go crazy. What truly horrible lives they must lead." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11871-that-s-the-problem-with-drinking-i-thought-as-i-poured</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 05:15:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11871-that-s-the-problem-with-drinking-i-thought-as-i-poured]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's the problem with drinking, I thought, as I poured myself a drink. If something bad happens you drink in an attempt to forget; if something good happens you drink in order to celebrate; and if nothing happens you drink to make something happen." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39207-if-you-re-going-to-try-go-all-the-way-otherwise</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 05:15:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39207-if-you-re-going-to-try-go-all-the-way-otherwise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're going to try, go all the way. Otherwise, don't even start. This could mean losing girlfriends, wives, relatives and maybe even your mind. It could mean not eating for three or four days. It could mean freezing on a park bench. It could mean jail. It could mean derision. It could mean mockery--isolation. Isolation is the gift. All the others are a test of your endurance, of how much you really want to do it. And, you'll do it, despite rejection and the worst odds. And it will be better than anything else you can imagine. If you're going to try, go all the way. There is no other feeling like that. You will be alone with the gods, and the nights will flame with fire. You will ride life straight to perfect laughter. It's the only good fight there is." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14996-my-ambition-is-handicapped-by-laziness</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 05:15:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14996-my-ambition-is-handicapped-by-laziness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My ambition is handicapped by laziness" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64329-we-re-all-going-to-die-all-of-us-what-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 05:15:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64329-we-re-all-going-to-die-all-of-us-what-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're all going to die, all of us, what a circus! That alone should make us love each other but it doesn't. We are terrorized and flattened by trivialities, we are eaten up by nothing." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41127-there-are-worse-things-than-being-alone-but-it-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 05:15:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dayle add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41127-there-are-worse-things-than-being-alone-but-it-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["there are worse things
than being alone
but it often takes
decades to realize this
and most often when you do
it's too late
and there's nothing worse
than too late" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
