<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1095573-ashlee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1095573-ashlee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 06:24:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46208-if-you-are-not-yelling-at-your-kids-you-are-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 06:24:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by Reese Witherspoon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46208-if-you-are-not-yelling-at-your-kids-you-are-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are not yelling at your kids,you are not spending enough time with them." -- Reese Witherspoon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 20:10:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She is too fond of books, and it has turned her brain." -- Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14109-faith-is-not-the-belief-that-god-will-do-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 05:34:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by Max Lucado]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14109-faith-is-not-the-belief-that-god-will-do-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Faith is not the belief that God will do what you want. It is the belief that God will do what is right." -- Max Lucado]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48832-is-it-kind-is-it-true-is-it-necessary</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 07:08:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by Amy Carmicheal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48832-is-it-kind-is-it-true-is-it-necessary]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is it kind? Is it true? Is it necessary?" -- Amy Carmicheal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 07:11:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312-i-can-t-think-about-that-right-now-if-i-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 08:33:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312-i-can-t-think-about-that-right-now-if-i-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can't think about that right now. If I do, I'll go crazy. I'll think about that tomorrow." -- Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59757-some-people-without-brains-do-an-awful-lot-of-talking</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2008 07:59:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by Frank Baum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59757-some-people-without-brains-do-an-awful-lot-of-talking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people without brains do an awful lot of talking, don't you think?" -- Frank Baum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374231-i-only-hope-that-one-day-i-can-frighten-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 12:08:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374231-i-only-hope-that-one-day-i-can-frighten-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I only hope that one day I can frighten my daughter this much. Right now, she's not scared of my husband or me at all. I think it's a problem. I was a freshman home from college the first time my dad said, &quot;You're going  out at ten p.m.? I don't think so,&quot; and I just laughed and said, &quot;It's fine.&quot; I feel like my daughter will be doing that to me by age six.

How can I give her what Don Fey gave me? The gift of anxiety. The fear of getting in trouble. The knowledge that while you are loved, you are not above the law. The Worldwide Parental Anxiety System is failing if this many of us have made sex tapes." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371653-first-lord-no-tattoos-may-neither-chinese-symbol-for-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 11:35:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371653-first-lord-no-tattoos-may-neither-chinese-symbol-for-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First, Lord: No tattoos. May neither Chinese symbol for truth nor Winnie-the-Pooh holding the FSU logo stain her tender haunches.

May she be Beautiful but not Damaged, for it’s the Damage that draws the creepy soccer coach’s eye, not the Beauty.

When the Crystal Meth is offered, May she remember the parents who cut her grapes in half And stick with Beer.

Guide her, protect her

When crossing the street, stepping onto boats, swimming in the ocean, swimming in pools, walking near pools, standing on the subway platform, crossing 86th Street, stepping off of boats, using mall restrooms, getting on and off escalators, driving on country roads while arguing, leaning on large windows, walking in parking lots, riding Ferris wheels, roller-coasters, log flumes, or anything called “Hell Drop,” “Tower of Torture,” or “The Death Spiral Rock ‘N Zero G Roll featuring Aerosmith,” and standing on any kind of balcony ever, anywhere, at any age.

Lead her away from Acting but not all the way to Finance. Something where she can make her own hours but still feel intellectually fulfilled and get outside sometimes And not have to wear high heels.

What would that be, Lord? Architecture? Midwifery? Golf course design? I’m asking You, because if I knew, I’d be doing it, Youdammit.

May she play the Drums to the fiery rhythm of her Own Heart with the sinewy strength of her Own Arms, so she need Not Lie With Drummers.

Grant her a Rough Patch from twelve to seventeen. Let her draw horses and be interested in Barbies for much too long, For childhood is short – a Tiger Flower blooming Magenta for one day – And adulthood is long and dry-humping in cars will wait.

O Lord, break the Internet forever, That she may be spared the misspelled invective of her peers And the online marketing campaign for Rape Hostel V: Girls Just Wanna Get Stabbed.

And when she one day turns on me and calls me a Bitch in front of Hollister, Give me the strength, Lord, to yank her directly into a cab in front of her friends, For I will not have that Shit. I will not have it.

And should she choose to be a Mother one day, be my eyes, Lord, that I may see her, lying on a blanket on the floor at 4:50 A.M., all-at-once exhausted, bored, and in love with the little creature whose poop is leaking up its back.

“My mother did this for me once,” she will realize as she cleans feces off her baby’s neck. “My mother did this for me.” And the delayed gratitude will wash over her as it does each generation and she will make a Mental Note to call me. And she will forget. But I’ll know, because I peeped it with Your God eyes." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174533-never-allow-someone-to-be-your-priority-while-allowing-yourself</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 09:19:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174533-never-allow-someone-to-be-your-priority-while-allowing-yourself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never allow someone to be your priority while allowing yourself to be their option." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173410-was-it-hard-i-ask-letting-go-not-as-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 09:20:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by Lisa Schroeder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173410-was-it-hard-i-ask-letting-go-not-as-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Was it hard?&quot; I ask.
Letting go?&quot;

Not as hard as holding on to something that wasn't real." -- Lisa Schroeder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66562-no-reflection-was-to-be-allowed-now-not-one-glance</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 09:29:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66562-no-reflection-was-to-be-allowed-now-not-one-glance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No reflection was to be allowed now, not one glance was to be cast back; not even one forward. Not one thought was to be given either to the past or the future. The first was a page so heavenly sweet, so deadly sad, that to read one line of it would dissolve my courage and break down my energy. The last was an awful blank, something like then world when the deluge was gone by." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
