<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1095232-konstantina-meggi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1095232-konstantina-meggi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 14:42:23 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1946-tis-better-to-have-loved-and-lost-than-never-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 14:42:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1946-tis-better-to-have-loved-and-lost-than-never-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tis better to have loved and lost
Than never to have loved at all." -- Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 14:43:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6130-a-woman-should-have-enough-money-within-her-control</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 14:47:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Pamela Redmond Satran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6130-a-woman-should-have-enough-money-within-her-control]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  enough money within her control to move out
  and rent a place of her own even if she never wants
  to or needs to...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  something perfect to wear if the employer or date of her
  dreams wants to see her in an hour...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ...
  a youth she's content to leave behind....
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a past juicy enough that she's looking forward to
  retelling it in her old age....
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE .....
  a set of screwdrivers, a cordless drill, and a black
  lace bra...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  one friend who always makes her laugh... and one who
  lets her cry...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a good piece of furniture not previously owned by anyone
  else in her family...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  eight matching plates, wine glasses with stems, and a
  recipe for a meal that will make her guests feel honored...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a feeling of control over her destiny...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  how to fall in love without losing herself..
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  HOW TO QUIT A JOB,
  BREAK UP WITH A LOVER,
  AND CONFRONT A FRIEND WITHOUT RUINING THE FRIENDSHIP...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  when to try harder... and WHEN TO WALK AWAY...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  that she can't change the length of her calves,
  the width of her hips, or the nature of her parents..
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  that her childhood may not have been perfect...but it's over...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  what she would and wouldn't do for love or more...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  how to live alone... even if she doesn't like it...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  whom she can trust,
  whom she can't,
  and why she shouldn't
  take it personally...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  where to go...
  be it to her best friend's kitchen table...
  or a charming inn in the woods...
  when her soul needs soothing...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  what she can and can't accomplish in a day...
  a month...and a year..." -- Pamela Redmond Satran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 14:49:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24138-love-is-patient-love-is-kind-it-does-not-envy</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 14:49:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24138-love-is-patient-love-is-kind-it-does-not-envy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is patient, love is kind. It does not envy, it does not boast, it is not proud. It is not rude, it is not self-seeking, it is not easily angered, it keeps no record of wrongs. Love does not delight in evil but rejoices with the truth. It always protects, always trusts, always hopes, always perseveres." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17533-i-carry-your-heart-with-me-i-carry-it-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 14:53:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by E.E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17533-i-carry-your-heart-with-me-i-carry-it-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I carry your heart with me (I carry it in my heart)I am never without it (anywhere
I go you go,my dear; and whatever is done by only me is your doing,my darling)
I fear no fate (for you are my fate,my sweet)I want no world (for beautiful you are my world,my true)
and it's you are whatever a moon has always meant and whatever a sun will always sing is you

here is the deepest secret nobody knows
(here is the root of the root and the bud of the bud and the sky of the sky of a tree called life; which grows
higher than the soul can hope or mind can hide)
and this is the wonder that's keeping the stars apart

I carry your heart (I carry it in my heart)" -- E.E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37491-love-is-needing-someone-love-is-putting-up-with-someone-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 14:56:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37491-love-is-needing-someone-love-is-putting-up-with-someone-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is needing someone. Love is putting up with someone's bad qualities because they somehow complete you." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29865-just-when-you-think-it-can-t-get-any-worse-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 14:58:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29865-just-when-you-think-it-can-t-get-any-worse-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just when you think it can't get any worse, it can. And just when you think it can't get any better, it can." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 15:06:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Bob Moorehead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The paradox of our time in history is that we have taller buildings but 
shorter tempers, wider Freeways, but narrower viewpoints.  We spend more, 
but have less, we buy more, but enjoy less. We have bigger houses and 
smaller families, more conveniences, but less time.  We have more degrees 
but less sense, more knowledge, but less judgment, more experts, yet more 
problems, more medicine, but less wellness.

We drink too much, smoke too much, spend too recklessly, laugh too little, 
drive too fast, get too angry, stay up too late, get up too tired, read too 
little, watch TV too much, and pray too seldom.  We have multiplied our 
possessions, but reduced our values.  We talk too much, love too seldom, and 
hate too often.

We've learned how to make a living, but not a life. We've added years to 
life not life to years.  We've been all the way to the moon and back, but 
have trouble crossing the street to meet a new neighbor.  We conquered outer 
space but not inner space.  We've done larger things, but not better things.

We've cleaned up the air, but polluted the soul. We've conquered the atom, 
but not our prejudice.  We write more, but learn less.  We plan more, but 
accomplish less.  We've learned to rush, but not to wait.  We build more 
computers to hold more information, to produce more copies than ever, but we 
communicate less and less.

These are the times of fast foods and slow digestion, big men and small 
character, steep profits and shallow relationships.

These are the days of two incomes but more divorce, fancier houses, but 
broken homes.  These are days of quick trips, disposable diapers, throwaway 
morality, one night stands, overweight bodies, and pills that do everything 
from cheer, to quiet, to kill.  It is a time when there is much in the 
showroom window and nothing in the stockroom.  A time when technology can 
bring this letter to you, and a time when you can choose either to share 
this insight, or to just hit delete...

Remember, to spend some time with your loved ones, because they are not 
going to be around forever.  Remember, say a kind word to someone who looks 
up to you in awe, because that little person soon will grow up and leave 
your side.

Remember, to give a warm hug to the one next to you, because that is the 
only treasure you can give with your heart and it doesn't cost a cent.

Remember, to say, &quot;I love you&quot; to your partner and your loved ones, but most 
of all mean it.  A kiss and an embrace will mend hurt when it comes from 
deep inside of you.

Remember to hold hands and cherish the moment for someday that person might 
not be there again.  Give time to love, give time to speak! And give time to 
share the precious thoughts in your mind." -- Bob Moorehead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14286-time-is-too-slow-for-those-who-wait-too-swift</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 15:09:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Henry van Dyke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14286-time-is-too-slow-for-those-who-wait-too-swift]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time is
     Too Slow for those who Wait,
     Too Swift for those who Fear,
     Too Long for those who Grieve,
     Too Short for those who Rejoice;
         But for those who Love,
             Time is not." -- Henry van Dyke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4749-you-can-only-become-truly-accomplished-at-something-you-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 15:12:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4749-you-can-only-become-truly-accomplished-at-something-you-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can only become truly accomplished at something you love. Don’t make money your goal. Instead pursue the things you love doing and then do them so well that people can’t take their eyes off of you." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14190-love-has-nothing-to-do-with-what-you-are-expecting</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2008 13:00:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Katharine Hepburn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14190-love-has-nothing-to-do-with-what-you-are-expecting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love has nothing to do with what you are expecting to get - only with what you are expecting to give - which is everything" -- Katharine Hepburn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49792-to-the-world-you-may-be-one-person-but-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 16:54:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Bill Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49792-to-the-world-you-may-be-one-person-but-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To the world you may be one person  but to one person you may be the world." -- Bill Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4964-love-is-that-condition-in-which-the-happiness-of-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 14:47:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4964-love-is-that-condition-in-which-the-happiness-of-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is that condition in which the happiness of another person is essential to your own." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2658-happiness-is-when-what-you-think-what-you-say-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 04:13:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2658-happiness-is-when-what-you-think-what-you-say-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is when what you think, what you say, and what you do are in harmony." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4808-success-is-getting-what-you-want-happiness-is-wanting-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 04:14:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by W. P. Kinsella]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4808-success-is-getting-what-you-want-happiness-is-wanting-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Success is getting what you want, happiness is wanting what you get" -- W. P. Kinsella]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43294-the-grand-essentials-to-happiness-in-this-life-are-something</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 04:19:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by George Washington Burnap]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43294-the-grand-essentials-to-happiness-in-this-life-are-something]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The grand essentials to happiness in this life are something to do, something to love, and something to hope for." -- George Washington Burnap]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27995-happiness-is-good-health-and-a-bad-memory</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 04:28:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Ingrid Bergman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27995-happiness-is-good-health-and-a-bad-memory]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is good health and a bad memory." -- Ingrid Bergman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150453-we-either-make-ourselves-miserable-or-we-make-ourselves-strong</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 10:28:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Carlos Castaneda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150453-we-either-make-ourselves-miserable-or-we-make-ourselves-strong]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We either make ourselves miserable, or we make ourselves strong. The amount of work is the same." -- Carlos Castaneda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 12:41:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We accept the love we think we deserve." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89885-he-was-my-north-my-south-my-east-and-west</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 10:36:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by W. H. Auden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89885-he-was-my-north-my-south-my-east-and-west]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was my North, my South, my East and West,
My working week and my Sunday rest,
My noon, my midnight, my talk, my song;
I thought that love would last forever: I was wrong." -- W. H. Auden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/701142-part-of-me-knows-one-more-day-won-t-do-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 11:26:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[konstantina add a quote by Gayle Forman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/701142-part-of-me-knows-one-more-day-won-t-do-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Part of me knows one more day won't do anything except postpone the heartbreak. But another part of me believes differently. We are born in one day. We die in one day. We can change in one day. And we can fall in love in one day. Anything can happen in just one day." -- Gayle Forman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
