<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1095906-helen-hwang]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1095906-helen-hwang" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 12:20:13 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 12:20:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helen add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that everything happens for a reason. People change so that you can learn to let go, things go wrong so that you appreciate them when they're right, you believe lies so you eventually learn to trust no one but yourself, and sometimes good things fall apart so better things can fall together." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6384-imperfection-is-beauty-madness-is-genius-and-it-s-better-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 12:21:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helen add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6384-imperfection-is-beauty-madness-is-genius-and-it-s-better-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imperfection is beauty, madness is genius and it's better to be absolutely ridiculous than absolutely boring." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270950-this-life-is-what-you-make-it-no-matter-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 12:24:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Helen add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270950-this-life-is-what-you-make-it-no-matter-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This life is what you make it. No matter what, you're going to mess up sometimes, it's a universal truth. But the good part is you get to decide how you're going to mess it up. Girls will be your friends - they'll act like it anyway. But just remember, some come, some go. The ones that stay with you through everything - they're your true best friends. Don't let go of them. Also remember, sisters make the best friends in the world. As for lovers, well, they'll come and go too. And baby, I hate to say it, most of them - actually pretty much all of them are going to break your heart, but you can't give up because if you give up, you'll never find your soulmate. You'll never find that half who makes you whole and that goes for everything. Just because you fail once, doesn't mean you're gonna fail at everything. Keep trying, hold on, and always, always, always believe in yourself, because if you don't, then who will, sweetie? So keep your head high, keep your chin up, and most importantly, keep smiling, because life's a beautiful thing and there's so much to smile about." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
