<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1096934-bruno]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/1096934-bruno" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 20:32:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22089-to-get-a-better-idea-try-this-focus-on-these</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 20:32:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22089-to-get-a-better-idea-try-this-focus-on-these]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To get a better idea try this: focus on these words, and whatever you do don’t let your eyes wander past the perimeter of this page. Now imagine just beyond your peripheral vision, maybe behind you, maybe to the side of you, maybe even in front of you, but right where you can’t see it, something is quietly closing in on you, so quiet in fact that you can only hear it as silence. Find those pockets without sound. That’s where it is. Right at this moment. But don’t look. Keep your eyes here. Now take a deep breath. Go ahead take and even deeper one. Only this time as you start to exhale try to imagine how fast it will happen, how hard it’s gonna hit you, how many times it will stab your jugular with it’s teeth or are they nails?, don’t worry, that particular detail doesn’t matter, because before you have time to even process that you should be moving, you should be running, you should at the very least be flinging up your arms – you sure as hell should be getting rid of this book – you won’t have time to even scream.&lt;br&gt;
Don’t look.&lt;br&gt;
I didn’t." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2-i-must-not-fear-fear-is-the-mind-killer-fear-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 20:36:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Frank Herbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2-i-must-not-fear-fear-is-the-mind-killer-fear-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I must not fear. Fear is the mind-killer. Fear is the little-death that brings total obliteration. I will face my fear. I will permit it to pass over me and through me. And when it has gone past I will turn the inner eye to see its path. Where the fear has gone there will be nothing. Only I will remain." -- Frank Herbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 20:40:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 20:41:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things need not have happened to be true. Tales and dreams are the shadow-truths that will endure when mere facts are dust and ashes, and forgot." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5251-sometimes-you-wake-up-sometimes-the-fall-kills-you-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2008 18:42:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5251-sometimes-you-wake-up-sometimes-the-fall-kills-you-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes you wake up. Sometimes the fall kills you. And sometimes, when you fall, you fly." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22088-this-is-not-for-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2008 20:15:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22088-this-is-not-for-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is not for you." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 19:07:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fairy tales are more than true: not because they tell us that dragons exist, but because they tell us that dragons can be beaten." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8716-and-in-that-moment-i-swear-we-were-infinite</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 17:57:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8716-and-in-that-moment-i-swear-we-were-infinite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And in that moment, I swear we were infinite." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8526-memories-warm-you-up-from-the-inside-but-they-also</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 17:32:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8526-memories-warm-you-up-from-the-inside-but-they-also]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Memories warm you up from the inside. But they also tear you apart." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217419-if-you-re-brave-enough-to-try-you-might-be-able</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 19:40:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by China Miéville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217419-if-you-re-brave-enough-to-try-you-might-be-able]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're brave enough to try, you might be able to catch a train from UnLondon to Parisn't, or No York, or Helsunki, or Lost Angeles, or Sans Francisco, or Hong Gone, or Romeless." -- China Miéville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50677-who-has-never-killed-an-hour-not-casually-or-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 16:03:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50677-who-has-never-killed-an-hour-not-casually-or-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who has never killed an hour? Not casually or without thought, but carefully: a premeditated murder of minutes. The violence comes from a combination of giving up, not caring, and a resignation that getting past it is all you can hope to accomplish. So you kill the hour. You do not work, you do not read, you do not daydream. If you sleep it is not because you need to sleep. And when at last it is over, there is no evidence: no weapon, no blood, and no body. The only clue might be the shadows beneath your eyes or a terribly thin line near the corner of your mouth indicating something has been suffered, that in the privacy of your life you have lost something and the loss is too empty to share." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138477-passion-has-little-to-do-with-euphoria-and-everything-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 16:08:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138477-passion-has-little-to-do-with-euphoria-and-everything-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Passion has little to do with euphoria and everything to do with patience. It is not about feeling good. It is about endurance. Like patience, passion comes from the same Latin root: pati. It does not mean to flow with exuberance. It means to suffer." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1344-only-the-phoenix-rises-and-does-not-descend-and-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 16:15:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1344-only-the-phoenix-rises-and-does-not-descend-and-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only the phoenix rises and does not descend. And everything changes. And nothing is truly lost." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148296-you-don-t-have-to-stay-anywhere-forever</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 16:24:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148296-you-don-t-have-to-stay-anywhere-forever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't have to stay anywhere forever." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66881-the-only-thing-known-to-go-faster-than-ordinary-light</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2011 06:29:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66881-the-only-thing-known-to-go-faster-than-ordinary-light]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only thing known to go faster than ordinary light is monarchy, according to the philosopher Ly Tin Wheedle. He reasoned like this: you can't have more than one king, and tradition demands that there is no gap between kings, so when a king dies the succession must therefore pass to the heir &lt;i&gt;instantaneously&lt;/i&gt;. Presumably, he said, there must be some elementary particles -- kingons, or possibly queons -- that do this job, but of course succession sometimes fails if, in mid-flight, they strike an anti-particle, or republicon. His ambitious plans to use his discovery to send messages, involving the careful torturing of a small king in order to modulate the signal, were never fully expanded because, at that point, the bar closed." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/450367-there-he-was-the-infant-titus-his-eyes-were-open</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 10:10:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Mervyn Peake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/450367-there-he-was-the-infant-titus-his-eyes-were-open]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There he was. The infant Titus. His eyes were open but he was quite still. The puckered-up face of the newly-born child, old as the world, wise as the roots of trees. Sin was there and goodness, love, pity and horror, and even beauty for his eyes were pure violet. Earth's passions, earth's griefs, earth's incongruous, ridiculous humours - dormant, yet visible in the wry pippin of a face." -- Mervyn Peake]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287691-you-tell-them-what-a-happy-ending-consists-of-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2011 06:38:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Scarlett Thomas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287691-you-tell-them-what-a-happy-ending-consists-of-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You tell them what a happy ending consists of, which is always individual success. You tell them that nothing irrational exists in this world, which is a lie. You tell them that conflict only exists only to be neatly resolved, and that everyone who is poor wants to be rich, and everyone who is ill wants to get better, and everyone who gets involved in crime comes to a bad end, and that love should be pure. You tell them that despite all this they are special, that the world revolves around them..." -- Scarlett Thomas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/495016-the-earth-is-literally-a-mirror-of-thoughts-objects-themselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 16:57:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Saul Bellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/495016-the-earth-is-literally-a-mirror-of-thoughts-objects-themselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The earth is literally a mirror of thoughts. Objects themselves are embodied thoughts. Death is the dark backing that a mirror needs if we are to see anything." -- Saul Bellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/347732-my-thought-is-me-that-s-why-i-can-t-stop-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 17:01:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Jean-Paul Sartre]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/347732-my-thought-is-me-that-s-why-i-can-t-stop-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My thought is me: that's why I can't stop. I exist because I think… and I can't stop myself from thinking. At this very moment - it's frightful - if I exist, it is because I am horrified at existing. I am the one who pulls myself from the nothingness to which I aspire." -- Jean-Paul Sartre]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485841-you-don-t-get-to-choose-if-you-get-hurt-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2012 13:44:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485841-you-don-t-get-to-choose-if-you-get-hurt-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't get to choose if you get hurt in this world...but you do have some say in who hurts you. I like my choices." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485844-some-infinities-are-bigger-than-other-infinities</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2012 13:45:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485844-some-infinities-are-bigger-than-other-infinities]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some infinities are bigger than other infinities." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/453749-that-s-what-the-world-is-after-all-an-endless</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 05:49:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/453749-that-s-what-the-world-is-after-all-an-endless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's what the world is , after all: an endless battle of contrasting memories." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508582-the-two-of-them-on-top-of-the-freezing-slide</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 05:53:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508582-the-two-of-them-on-top-of-the-freezing-slide]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The two of them on top of the freezing slide, wordlessly holding hands. Once again they were a ten-year-old boy and girl. A lonely boy, and a lonely girl. A classroom, just after school let out, at the beginning of winter. They had neither the power nor the knowledge to know what they should offer to each other, what they should be seeking. They had never, ever, been truly loved, or truly loved someone else. They had never held anyone, never been held. They had not idea, either, where this action would take them. What they entered then was a doorless room. They couldn't get out, nor could anyone else come in. The two of them didn't know it at the time, but this was the only truly complete place in the entire world. Totally isolated, yet the one place not tainted with loneliness." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265648-there-is-neither-source-nor-end-for-all-things-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 11:48:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265648-there-is-neither-source-nor-end-for-all-things-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is neither source nor end, for all things are in the Center of Time.  As all the stars may be reflected in a round raindrop falling in the night: so too do all the stars reflect the raindrop.  There is neither darkness nor death, for all things are, in the Light of the Moment, and their end and their beginning are one." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60922-light-is-the-left-hand-of-darkness-and-darkness-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 18:46:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60922-light-is-the-left-hand-of-darkness-and-darkness-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Light is the left hand of darkness
and darkness the right hand of light.
Two are one, life and death, lying
together like lovers in kemmer,
like hands joined together,
like the end and the way." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279916-we-think-we-understand-a-song-s-lyrics-but-what-makes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 09:36:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Carlos Ruiz Zafón]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279916-we-think-we-understand-a-song-s-lyrics-but-what-makes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We think we understand a song's lyrics but what makes us believe in them, or not, is the music" -- Carlos Ruiz Zafón]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173756-the-only-way-you-can-truly-get-to-know-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 08:41:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Carlos Ruiz Zafón]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173756-the-only-way-you-can-truly-get-to-know-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only way you can truly get to know an author is through the trail of ink he leaves behind him.  The person you think you see is only an empty character: truth is always hidden in fiction." -- Carlos Ruiz Zafón]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/529803-life-is-a-gift-bestowed-without-anyone-asking-for-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 17:24:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Julian Barnes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/529803-life-is-a-gift-bestowed-without-anyone-asking-for-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...life is a gift bestowed without anyone asking for it; that the thinking person has a philosophical duty to examine both the nature of life and the conditions it comes with; and that if this person decides to renounce the gift no one asks for, it is the moral and human duty to act on the consequences of that decision." -- Julian Barnes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460624-history-is-that-certainty-produced-at-the-point-where-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 17:26:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Julian Barnes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460624-history-is-that-certainty-produced-at-the-point-where-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["History is that certainty produced at the point where the imperfections of memory meet the inadequacies of documentation." -- Julian Barnes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494064-i-remember-a-period-in-late-adolescence-when-my-mind</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 17:28:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bruno add a quote by Julian Barnes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494064-i-remember-a-period-in-late-adolescence-when-my-mind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I remember a period in late adolescence when my mind would make itself drunk with images of adventurousness. This is how it will be when I grow up. I shall go there, do this, discover that, love her, and then her and her and her. I shall live as people in novels live and have lived. Which ones I was not sure, only that passion and danger, ecstasy and despair (but then more ecstasy) would be in attendance. However...who said that thing about &quot;the littleness of life that art exaggerates&quot;? There was a moment in my late twenties when I admitted that my adventurousness had long since petered out. I would never do those things adolescence had dreamt about. Instead, I mowed my lawn, I took holidays, I had my life.

But time...how time first grounds us and then confounds us. We thought we were being mature when we were only being safe. We imagined we were being responsible but we were only being cowardly. What we called realism turned out to be a way of avoiding things rather than facing them. Time...give us enough time and our best-supported decisions will seem wobbly, our certainties whimsical." -- Julian Barnes]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
