<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/110752-careuhhline]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/110752-careuhhline" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2008 18:23:53 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124599-any-combination-of-a-250-pound-mexican-and-lsd-25-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2008 18:23:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124599-any-combination-of-a-250-pound-mexican-and-lsd-25-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any combination of a 250-pound Mexican and LSD-25 is a potentially terminal menace for anything it can reach" -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149902-there-is-nothing-lonelier-than-adventure</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 19:15:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Aleida Guevara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149902-there-is-nothing-lonelier-than-adventure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing lonelier than adventure." -- Aleida Guevara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149907-the-word-that-most-perfectly-describes-the-city-of-cuzco</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 19:18:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149907-the-word-that-most-perfectly-describes-the-city-of-cuzco]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The word that most perfectly describes the city of Cuzco is evocative.  Intangible dust of another era settles on its streets, rising like the disturbed sediment of a muddy lake when you touch its bottom." -- Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149909-this-is-the-cuzco-asking-you-to-pull-on-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 19:20:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149909-this-is-the-cuzco-asking-you-to-pull-on-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is the Cuzco asking you to pull on your armor and, mounted on the ample back of a powerful horse, cleave a path through the defenseless flesh of a naked Indian flock whose human wall collapses and disappears beneath the four hooves of the galloping beast." -- Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149913-and-yet-every-so-often-the-heart-of-america-shuddering</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 19:23:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149913-and-yet-every-so-often-the-heart-of-america-shuddering]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And yet every so often, the heart of America, shuddering with indignation, sends a nervous spasm through the gentle back of the Andes, and tumultuous shock waves assault the surface of the land.  Three times the cuppola of proud Santo Domingo has collapsed from on high to the rhythm of broken bones and its worn walls have opened and fallen too.  But the foundations they rest on are unmoved, the great blocks of the Temple of the Sun exhibit their gray stone indifferently; however colossal the disaster befalling its oppressor, not one of its huge rocks shifts from its place." -- Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149919-the-spectacular-landscape-circling-the-fortress-supplies-an-essential-backdrop</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 19:28:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149919-the-spectacular-landscape-circling-the-fortress-supplies-an-essential-backdrop]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The spectacular landscape circling the fortress supplies an essential backdrop, inspiring dreamers to wander its ruins for the sake of it; North American tourists, bound down by their practical world view, are able to place those members of the disintegrating tribes they may have seen in their travels among these once-living walls, unaware of the moral distance separating them, since only the semi-indigenous spirit of the South American can grasp the subtle differences." -- Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149921-wrapped-in-a-police-blanket-i-watched-the-rain-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 19:29:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149921-wrapped-in-a-police-blanket-i-watched-the-rain-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wrapped in a police blanket, I watched the rain and smoked one black cigarette after another..." -- Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149922-its-tall-chimneys-throw-up-black-smoke-impregnating-everything-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 19:31:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149922-its-tall-chimneys-throw-up-black-smoke-impregnating-everything-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Its tall chimneys throw up black smoke, impregnating everything with soot, and the miners' faces as they traveled the streets were also imbued with that ancient melancholy of smoke, unifying everything with its grayish monotones, a perfect coupling with the gray mountain days." -- Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149926-the-stars-drew-light-across-the-night-sky-in-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 19:35:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149926-the-stars-drew-light-across-the-night-sky-in-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The stars drew light across the night sky in that little mountain village, and the silence and the cold made the darkness vanish away. It was - I don't know how to explain it - as if everything solid melted away into the ether, eliminating all individualtiy and absorbing us, rigid, into the immense darkness. Not a single cloud to lend perspective to the space blocked any portion of the starry sky." -- Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149931-i-also-know---and-this-won-t-alter-the-course</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 19:42:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149931-i-also-know---and-this-won-t-alter-the-course]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...I also know - and this won't alter the course of history or your personal view of me - that you will die with a clenched fist and a tense jaw, the epitome of hatred and struggle, because you are not a symbol (some inanimate example) but a genuine member of the society to be destroyed; the spirit of the beehive speaks through your mouth and motivates your actions. You are as useful as I am, but you are not aware of how useful your contribution is to the society that sacrifices you." -- Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149947-i-knew-that-when-the-great-guiding-spirit-cleaves-humanity</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 20:46:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149947-i-knew-that-when-the-great-guiding-spirit-cleaves-humanity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I knew that when the great guiding spirit cleaves humanity into two antagonistic halves, I would be with the people. I know this, I see it printed in the night sky that I, eclectic dissembler of doctrine and psychoanalyst of dogma, howling like one possessed, will assault the barricades or the trenches , will take my bloodstained weapon, and consumed with fury, slaughter any enemy who falls into my hands." -- Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149948-and-then-many-things-became-very-clear-we-learned-perfectly</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 20:48:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149948-and-then-many-things-became-very-clear-we-learned-perfectly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And then many things became very clear... we learned perfectly that the life of a single human being is worth millions of times more than all the property of the richest man on earth." -- Ernesto Che Guevara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494254-mcs-don-t-just-rhyme-sounds-they-rhyme-ideas</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 09:45:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Adam Bradley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494254-mcs-don-t-just-rhyme-sounds-they-rhyme-ideas]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["MCs don't just rhyme sounds, they rhyme ideas." -- Adam Bradley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/505848-hip-hop-is-a-beautiful-culture-it-s-inspirational-because-it-s-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 01:23:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Mos Def]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/505848-hip-hop-is-a-beautiful-culture-it-s-inspirational-because-it-s-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hip-hop is a beautiful culture.  It's inspirational, because it's a culture of survivors.  You can create beauty out of nothingness." -- Mos Def]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112715-we-are-busy-with-the-luxury-of-things-their-number</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2012 23:39:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Farid al-Din Attar (عطار)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112715-we-are-busy-with-the-luxury-of-things-their-number]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are busy with the luxury of things.
Their number and multiple faces bring
To us confusion we call knowledge. Say:
God created the world, pinned night to day,
Made mountains to weigh it down, seas
To wash its face, living creatures with pleas
(The ancestors of prayers) seeking a place
In this mystery that floats in endless space.
God set the earth on the back of a bull,
The bull on a fish dancing on a spool
Of silver light so fine it is like air;
That in turn rests on nothing there
But nothing that nothing can share.
All things are but masks at God's beck and call,
They are symbols that instruct us that God is all." -- Farid al-Din Attar (عطار)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/482814-set-your-life-on-fire-seek-those-who-fan-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 10:13:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/482814-set-your-life-on-fire-seek-those-who-fan-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Set your life on fire. Seek those who fan your flames" -- Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/409707-time-to-leave-now-get-out-of-this-room-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 12:46:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Stefan Zweig]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/409707-time-to-leave-now-get-out-of-this-room-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time to leave now, get out of this room, go somewhere, anywhere; sharpen this feeling of happiness and freedom, stretch your limbs, fill your eyes, be awake, wider awake, vividly awake in every sense and every pore." -- Stefan Zweig]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133492-trying-to-build-my-dreams-with-what-i-have-now</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 22:53:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Aaron Cometbus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133492-trying-to-build-my-dreams-with-what-i-have-now]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Trying to build my dreams with what I have now, it's like building a forty-five story house with thirty-four bricks. (DoubleDuce.)" -- Aaron Cometbus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/735609-you-can-tell-when-iraqis-are-getting-upset-because-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 00:52:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/735609-you-can-tell-when-iraqis-are-getting-upset-because-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can tell when Iraqis are getting upset because, like Italians we start talking with our hands." -- Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/735610-perhaps-this-one-summed-it-up-some-say-they-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 00:58:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/735610-perhaps-this-one-summed-it-up-some-say-they-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps this one summed it up: 'Some say they are trying to stop the shooting, a lot say they are having a party shotting him. most are just watching. That. my friend. is America. Nuff said." -- Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/735613-i-m-not-sure-exactly-where-i-stand-in-this-generational</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 01:10:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/735613-i-m-not-sure-exactly-where-i-stand-in-this-generational]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not sure exactly where I stand in this generational continuum.  I'm rebellious, but not against tradition--I'm very respectful of tradition.  I'm rebellious against stagnant tradition, and authoritarian control used to keep that tradition in place.  If push comes to shove I will always place myself on the side of the new generation, because if a culture can't keep renewing itself, it will eventually die." -- Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/735614-in-any-culture-the-dispossessed-and-powerless-willl-turn-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 01:16:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/735614-in-any-culture-the-dispossessed-and-powerless-willl-turn-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In any culture the dispossessed and powerless willl turn to religion and legend, because what else do they have to believe in?  They need these stories of heroism and superhuman saviors to give them hope." -- Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739951-my-honors-thesis-project-was-my-first-interactive-exhibit-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 11:38:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739951-my-honors-thesis-project-was-my-first-interactive-exhibit-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My honors thesis project was my first interactive exhibit, in which two facing chairs were activated by a motion sensor when the viewer walked by.  One was a cofortable armchair of plush red velvet, with a dildo sticking out of a hole in the seat.  When activated, the dildo moved up and down and a strobe light pulsed.  The facing chair was hard and uncomfortable, with spikes protruding from the seat, and when the viewer walked by it a dog would bark.  The juxtaposition of the two chairs was meant to represent how forces of repression censor the desire for liberation.

In that same exhibition, I showed a handmade box in the shape of a cross, decorated with a beautiful painting of the Holy Trinity.  The viewer was encouraged to open the box, where they would find a dildo wrapped in the American flag and nailed to a cross-- this was meant to symbolize the hypocrisy and repression that is hidden under the attractive facade of organized religion.  The dildo was surrounded by pages from the Bible, which were themselves surrounded by images of the sickness and starvation caused by the embargo in Iraq, a comment on the effects of imposing one culture and religion on another." -- Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739956-the-boar-held-a-vcr-reote-control-and-cackled-maliciously</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 11:56:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739956-the-boar-held-a-vcr-reote-control-and-cackled-maliciously]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The boar held a VCR reote control and cackled maliciously as he watched a video of U.S. politicians grinning with their one-time budy Saddam--Dick Cheney, Gulf War-era Secretary of State James Baker, Rev. Jesse Jackson, Bob Dole, George H.W. Bush, to the tune of &quot;Taking Care of Business.&quot;  And then the viewers saw themselves in a mirror emblazoned with the words &quot;You are a witness." -- Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739961-more-than-100-000-soldiers-will-soon-return-home-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 12:08:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739961-more-than-100-000-soldiers-will-soon-return-home-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["More than 100,000 soldiers will soon return home with the post-traumatic stress I know so well, not to mention the mysterious effects of deplted uranium...and the ripples of resentment and animosity this war has sent throughout the world will inevitably wash up on U.S. shores.

As I write this, mainstream political dialogue is still focused on the crazy idea that we can somehow still &quot;win&quot; the war in Iraq.  For someone like me, a citizen of both countries, what outcome would constitute a victory?  When you're talking about war, about so many thousands dead, so many families shattered on both sides, how can anyone claim victory?" -- Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739963-a-young-artist-s-career-is-a-matter-of-claiming-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 12:10:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739963-a-young-artist-s-career-is-a-matter-of-claiming-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A young artist's career is a matter of claiming a place for oneself, of saying, &quot;I am here.&quot;  Having gone through that phase, a more mature artist can concentrate on truly developing talent and vision." -- Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739966-it-made-no-sense-but-i-always-wanted-to-create</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 12:11:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739966-it-made-no-sense-but-i-always-wanted-to-create]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It made no sense, but I always wanted to create a home, even in the most unlikely places." -- Wafaa Bilal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/388521-if-you-retain-nothing-else-always-remember-the-most-important</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 17:52:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/388521-if-you-retain-nothing-else-always-remember-the-most-important]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you retain nothing else, always remember the most important rule of beauty, which is: who cares?" -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20941-sex-is-kicking-death-in-the-ass-while-singing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 19:03:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20941-sex-is-kicking-death-in-the-ass-while-singing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sex is kicking death in the ass while singing." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541810-find-what-you-love-and-let-it-kill-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 19:04:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Careuhhline add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541810-find-what-you-love-and-let-it-kill-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Find what you love and let it kill you." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
