<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/111194-lisa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/111194-lisa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 03:44:59 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398353-our-father-who-art-in-nature-who-has-given-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 03:44:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398353-our-father-who-art-in-nature-who-has-given-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our Father who art in nature, who has given the gift of survival to the coyote, the common brown rat, the English sparrow, the house fly and the moth, must have a great and overwhelming love for no-goods and blots-on-the-town and bums, and Mack and the boys. Virtues and graces and laziness and zest. Our Father who art in nature." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32928-the-world-is-mud-luscious-and-puddle-wonderful</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 00:47:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by e. e. cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32928-the-world-is-mud-luscious-and-puddle-wonderful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is mud-luscious and puddle-wonderful." -- e. e. cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3828-cannery-row-s-inhabitants-are-as-the-man-once-said-whores</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 14:54:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3828-cannery-row-s-inhabitants-are-as-the-man-once-said-whores]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Cannery Row's] inhabitants are, as the man once said, 'whores, pimps, gamblers, and sons of bitches,' by which he meant everybody. Had the man looked through another peephole he might have said, 'saints and angels and martyrs and holy men,' and he would have meant the same thing." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63849-i-thank-you-god-for-this-most-amazing-day-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 19:00:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by e.e. cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63849-i-thank-you-god-for-this-most-amazing-day-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I thank you God for this most amazing day, for the leaping greenly spirits of trees, and for the blue dream of sky and for everything which is natural, which is infinite, which is yes." -- e.e. cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 18:58:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what you shall do; Love the earth and sun and the animals, despise riches, give alms to every one that asks, stand up for the stupid and crazy, devote your income and labor to others, hate tyrants, argue not concerning God, have patience and indulgence toward the people, take off your hat to nothing known or unknown or to any man or number of men, go freely with powerful uneducated persons and with the young and with the mothers of families, read these leaves in the open air every season of every year of your life, re-examine all you have been told at school or church or in any book, dismiss whatever insults your own soul, and your very flesh shall be a great poem and have the richest fluency not only in its words but in the silent lines of its lips and face and between the lashes of your eyes and in every motion and joint of your body." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2822-you-ve-seen-the-sun-flatten-and-take-strange-shapes-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 18:58:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2822-you-ve-seen-the-sun-flatten-and-take-strange-shapes-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've seen the sun flatten and take strange shapes just before it sinks in the ocean. Do you have to tell yourself every time that it's an illusion caused by atmospheric dust and light distorted by the sea, or do you simply enjoy the beauty of it?" -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/351374-it-was-the-shadow-of-some-one-who-had-gone</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 00:46:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Charles Dickens ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/351374-it-was-the-shadow-of-some-one-who-had-gone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was the shadow of Some one who had gone by long before: of Some one who had gone on far away quite out of reach, never, never to come back. It was bright to look at; and when the tiny woman showed it to the Princess, she was proud of it with all her heart, as a great, great, treasure. When the Princess had considered it a little while, she said to the tiny woman, And you keep watch over this, every day? And she cast down her eyes, and whispered, Yes. Then the Princess said, Remind me why. To which the other replied, that no one so good and so kind had ever passed that way, and that was why in the beginning. She said, too, that nobody missed it, that nobody was the worse for it, that Some one had gone on to those who were expecting him-- 

'Some one was a man then?' interposed Maggy. 

Little Dorrit timidly said yes, she believed so; and resumed:

'-- Had gone on to those who were expecting him, and that this remembrance 
was stolen or kept back from nobody. The Princess made answer, Ah! But when the cottager died it would be discovered there. The tiny woman told her No; when that time came, it would sink quietly into her own grave, and would never be found." -- Charles Dickens ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54860-it-is-better-to-sit-in-appreciative-contemplation-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 18:58:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54860-it-is-better-to-sit-in-appreciative-contemplation-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to sit in appreciative contemplation of a world in which beauty is eternally supported on a foundation of ugliness: cut out the support, and beauty will sink from sight." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42145-the-best-remedy-for-those-who-are-afraid-lonely-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 00:47:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42145-the-best-remedy-for-those-who-are-afraid-lonely-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best remedy for those who are afraid, lonely or unhappy is to go outside, somewhere where they can be quite alone with the heavens, nature and God.  Because only then does one feel  that all is as it should be and that God wishes to see people happy, amidst the simple beauty of nature.  As longs as this exists, and it certainly always will, I know that then there will always be comfort for every sorrow, whatever the circumstances may be.  And I firmly believe that nature brings solace in all troubles." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7337-books-are-let-s-face-it-better-than-everything-else-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 00:46:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7337-books-are-let-s-face-it-better-than-everything-else-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are, let's face it, better than everything else. If we played cultural Fantasy Boxing League, and made books go 15 rounds in the ring against the best that any other art form had to offer, then books would win pretty much every time. Go on, try it. “The Magic Flute” v. Middlemarch? Middlemarch in six. “The Last Supper” v. Crime and Punishment? Fyodor on points. See? I mean, I don’t know how scientific this is, but it feels like the novels are walking it. You might get the occasional exception -– “Blonde on Blonde” might mash up The Old Curiosity Shop, say, and I wouldn’t give much for Pale Fire’s chance against Citizen Kane. And every now and again you'd get a shock, because that happens in sport, so Back to the Future III might land a lucky punch on Rabbit, Run; but I'm still backing literature 29 times out of 30." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186921-on-the-black-earth-on-which-the-ice-plants-bloomed</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 18:59:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186921-on-the-black-earth-on-which-the-ice-plants-bloomed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the black earth on which the ice plants bloomed, hundreds of black stink bugs crawled.  And many of them stuck their tails up in the air.  &quot;Look at all them stink bugs,&quot; Hazel remarked, grateful to the bugs for being there.
     &quot;They're interesting,&quot; said Doc.
     &quot;Well, what they got their asses up in the air for?&quot;
     Doc rolled up his wool socks and put them in the rubber boots and from his pocket he brought out dry socks and a pair of thin moccasins.  &quot;I don't know why,&quot; he said.  &quot;I looked them up recently--they're very common animals and one of the commonest things they do is put their tails up in the air.  And in all the books there isn't one mention of the fact that they put their tails up in the air or why.&quot;
     Hazel turned one of the stink bugs over with the toe of his wet tennis shoe and the shining black beetle strove madly with floundering legs to get upright again.  &quot;Well, why do you think they do it?&quot;
     &quot;I think they're praying,&quot; said Doc.
     &quot;What!&quot; Hazel was shocked.
     &quot;The remarkable thing,&quot; said Doc, &quot;isn't that they put their tails up in the air--the really incredibly remarkable thing is that we find it remarkable.  We can only use ourselves as yardsticks.  If we did something as inexplicable and strange we'd probably be praying--so maybe they're praying.&quot;
     &quot;Let's get the hell out of here,&quot; said Hazel." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57409-one-of-the-strange-things-about-living-in-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 18:58:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57409-one-of-the-strange-things-about-living-in-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the strange things about living in the world is that it is only now and then one is quite sure one is going to live forever and ever and ever. One knows it sometimes when one gets up at the tender solemn dawn-time and goes out and stands out and throws one's head far back and looks up and up and watches the pale sky slowly changing and flushing and marvelous unknown things happening until the East almost makes one cry out and one's heart stands still at the strange unchanging majesty of the rising of the sun--which has been happening every morning for thousands and thousands and thousands of years. One knows it then for a moment or so. And one knows it sometimes when one stands by oneself in a wood at sunset and the mysterious deep gold stillness slanting through and under the branches seems to be saying slowly again and again something one cannot quite hear, however much one tries. Then sometimes the immense quiet of the dark blue at night with the millions of stars waiting and watching makes one sure; and sometimes a sound of far-off music makes it true; and sometimes a look in someone's eyes." -- Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245735-when-everyone-drowns-and-i-m-the-only-one-to-escape</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 18:58:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Nikos Kazantzakis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245735-when-everyone-drowns-and-i-m-the-only-one-to-escape]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When everyone drowns and I'm the only one to escape, God is protecting me. When everyone else is saved and I'm the only one to drown, God is protecting me then too." -- Nikos Kazantzakis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 19:06:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12444-i-believe-in-everything-until-it-s-disproved-so-i-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 19:06:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12444-i-believe-in-everything-until-it-s-disproved-so-i-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in everything until it's disproved. So I believe in fairies, the myths, dragons. It all exists, even if it's in your mind. Who's to say that dreams and nightmares aren't as real as the here and now?" -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4889-to-be-nobody-but-yourself-in-a-world-which-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 19:13:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by e.e. cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4889-to-be-nobody-but-yourself-in-a-world-which-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be nobody but 
yourself in a world 
which is doing its best day and night to make you like 
everybody else means to fight the hardest battle 
which any human being can fight and never stop fighting." -- e.e. cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127555-i-am-the-sum-total-of-everything-that-went-before</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 19:10:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127555-i-am-the-sum-total-of-everything-that-went-before]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the sum total of everything that went before me, of all I have been seen done, of everything done-to-me. I am everyone everything whose being-in-the-world affected was affected by mine. I am anything that happens after I'm gone which would not have happened if I had not come." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1922-resist-much-obey-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 19:15:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1922-resist-much-obey-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Resist much, obey little." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229910-out-of-obscurity-i-came-to-obscurity-i-can-easily</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 19:16:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229910-out-of-obscurity-i-came-to-obscurity-i-can-easily]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Out of obscurity I came, to obscurity I can easily return.  " -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11540-you-get-a-little-moody-sometimes-but-i-think-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 18:58:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11540-you-get-a-little-moody-sometimes-but-i-think-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You get a little moody sometimes but I think that's because you like to read. People that like to read are always a little fucked up." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/991-until-i-feared-i-would-lose-it-i-never-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 19:18:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/991-until-i-feared-i-would-lose-it-i-never-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until I feared I would lose it, I never loved to read. One does not love breathing." -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22107-i-soon-discovered-that-one-doesn-t-simply-read-crime-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 19:21:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Alberto Manguel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22107-i-soon-discovered-that-one-doesn-t-simply-read-crime-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I soon discovered that one doesn't simply read &lt;i&gt;Crime and Punishment&lt;/i&gt; or &lt;i&gt;A Tree Grows in Brooklyn&lt;/i&gt;. One reads a certain edition, a specific copy, recognizable by the roughness or the smoothness of its paper, by its scent, by a slight tear on page 72 and a coffee ring on the right-hand corner of the back cover. " -- Alberto Manguel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7570-if-you-have-a-garden-and-a-library-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 18:58:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7570-if-you-have-a-garden-and-a-library-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you have a garden and a library, you have everything you need." -- Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 17:03:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hello babies. Welcome to Earth. It's hot in the summer and cold in the winter. It's round and wet and crowded. On the outside, babies, you've got a hundred years here. There's only one rule that I know of, babies-&quot;God damn it, you've got to be kind." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/515-i-am-so-far-from-being-a-pessimist-on-the-contrary</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2013 01:32:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Eugene O'Neill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/515-i-am-so-far-from-being-a-pessimist-on-the-contrary]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am so far from being a pessimist...on the contrary, in spite of my scars, I am tickled to death at life." -- Eugene O'Neill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267448-i-read-a-book-one-day-and-my-whole-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 01:09:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Orhan Pamuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267448-i-read-a-book-one-day-and-my-whole-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read a book one day and my whole life was changed." -- Orhan Pamuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41233-what-matters-most-is-how-well-you-walk-through-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 00:25:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Charles Bukowski ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41233-what-matters-most-is-how-well-you-walk-through-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["what matters most is how well you walk through the fire" -- Charles Bukowski ]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
