<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/111436-kim]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/111436-kim" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 07:15:10 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32858-an-artist-s-only-concern-is-to-shoot-for-some-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 07:15:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32858-an-artist-s-only-concern-is-to-shoot-for-some-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An artist's only concern is to shoot for some kind of perfection, and on his own terms, not anyone else's." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37505-it-s-everybody-i-mean-everything-everybody-does-is-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 07:15:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37505-it-s-everybody-i-mean-everything-everybody-does-is-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's everybody, I mean. Everything everybody does is so — I don't know — not wrong, or even mean, or even stupid necessarily. But just so tiny and meaningless and — sad-making. And the worst part is, if you go bohemian or something crazy like that, you're conforming just as much only in a different way." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18881-i-m-a-kind-of-paranoiac-in-reverse-i-suspect-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 10:20:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18881-i-m-a-kind-of-paranoiac-in-reverse-i-suspect-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm a kind of paranoiac in reverse. I suspect people of plotting to make me happy." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21900-franny-has-the-measles-for-one-thing-incidentally-did-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 12:27:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21900-franny-has-the-measles-for-one-thing-incidentally-did-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Franny has the measles, for one thing. Incidentally, did you hear her last week? She went on at beautiful length about how she used to fly all around the apartment when she was four and no one was home. The new announcer is worse than Grant - if possible, even worse than Sullivan in the old days. He said she surely dreamt that she was able to fly. The baby stood her ground like an angel. She said she knew she was able to fly because when she came down she always had dust on her fingers from touching the light bulbs." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/307434-we-search-for-patterns-you-see-only-to-find-where</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 02:01:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/307434-we-search-for-patterns-you-see-only-to-find-where]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We search for patterns, you see, only to find where the patterns break. And it’s there, in that fissure, that we pitch our tents and wait." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8574-what-a-terrible-mistake-to-let-go-of-something-wonderful</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2011 06:28:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Miranda July]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8574-what-a-terrible-mistake-to-let-go-of-something-wonderful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a terrible mistake to let go of something wonderful for something real." -- Miranda July]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/288270-when-you-can-see-the-beauty-of-a-tree-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2011 05:25:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Miranda July]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/288270-when-you-can-see-the-beauty-of-a-tree-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you can see the beauty of a tree, then you will know what love is." -- Miranda July]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364058-we-often-forget-that-we-are-nature-nature-is-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 10:20:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Andy Goldsworthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364058-we-often-forget-that-we-are-nature-nature-is-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We often forget that WE ARE NATURE. Nature is not something separate from us. So when we say that we have lost our connection to nature, we’ve lost our connection to ourselves." -- Andy Goldsworthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289634-people-as-a-rule-do-mean-much-more-than-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 02:13:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Glenway Wescott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289634-people-as-a-rule-do-mean-much-more-than-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People as a rule do mean much more than they understand." -- Glenway Wescott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498578-that-is-what-literature-offers-a-language-powerful-enough-to-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 07:34:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498578-that-is-what-literature-offers-a-language-powerful-enough-to-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That is what literature offers—a language powerful enough to say how it is. It isn't a hiding place. It is a finding place." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498579-the-more-i-read-the-more-i-felt-connected-across</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 07:35:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498579-the-more-i-read-the-more-i-felt-connected-across]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The more I read, the more I felt connected across time to other lives and deeper sympathies. I felt less isolated. I wasn’t floating on my little raft in the present; there were bridges that led over to solid ground. Yes, the past is another country, but one that we can visit, and once there we can bring back the things we need.
    Literature is common ground. It is ground not managed wholly by commercial interests, nor can it be strip-mined like popular culture—exploit the new thing then move on.
    There’s a lot of talk about the tame world versus the wild world. It is not only a wild nature that we need as human beings; it is the untamed open space of our imaginations.
    Reading is where the wild things are." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152711-it-would-be-a-thousand-pities-if-women-wrote-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 05:00:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152711-it-would-be-a-thousand-pities-if-women-wrote-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It would be a thousand pities if women wrote like men, or lived like men, or looked like men, for if two sexes are quite inadequate, considering the vastness and variety of the world, how should we manage with one only?  Ought not education to bring out and fortify the differences rather than the similarities?" -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/507432-one-holds-every-phrase-every-scene-to-the-light-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 05:00:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/507432-one-holds-every-phrase-every-scene-to-the-light-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One holds every phrase, every scene to the light as one reads - for Nature seems, very oddly, to have provided us with an inner light by which to judge of the novelist’s integrity or disintegrity. Or perhaps it is rather that Nature, in her most irrational mood, has traced in invisible ink on the walls of the mind a premonition which these great artists confirm; a sketch which only needs to be held to the fire of genius to become visible. When one so exposes it and sees it come to life one exclaims in rapture, But this is what I have always felt and known and desired! And one boils over with excitement, and, shutting the book even with a kind of reverence as if it were something very precious, a stand-by to return to as long as one lives, one puts it back on the shelf […]." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331224-we-are-in-the-realm-not-of-logic-but-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 02:50:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Joseph O'Neill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331224-we-are-in-the-realm-not-of-logic-but-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are in the realm not of logic but of wistfulness, and I must maintain that wistfulness is a respectable, serious condition. How, otherwise, to account for much of one's life?" -- Joseph O'Neill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221129-she-worries-over-the-way-her-love-for-me-comes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 00:49:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221129-she-worries-over-the-way-her-love-for-me-comes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She worries over the way her love for me comes and goes, appears and disappears.  She doubts its reality simply because it isn't as steadily pleasurable as a kitten.  God knows it is sad.  The human voice conspires to desecrate everything on earth." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105553-however-contradictory-the-coroner-s-report-whether-he-pronounces-consumption</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 00:50:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105553-however-contradictory-the-coroner-s-report-whether-he-pronounces-consumption]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["However contradictory the coroner's report — whether he pronounces Consumption or Loneliness or Suicide to be the cause of death — isn't it plain how the true artist-seer actually dies? I say that the true artist-seer, the heavenly fool who can and does produce beauty, is mainly dazzled to death by his own scruples, the blinding shapes and colors of his own sacred human conscience." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/653563-the-thing-about-trees-is-that-they-know-what-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 04:35:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Ali Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/653563-the-thing-about-trees-is-that-they-know-what-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The thing about trees is that they know what to do. When a leaf loses its colour, it's not because its time is up and it's dying, it's because the tree is taking back into itself the nutrients the leaf's been holding in reserve for it, out there on the twig, and why leaves change colour in autumn is because the tree is preparing for winter, it's filling itself with its own stored health so it can withstand the season. Then, clever tree, it literally pushes the used leaf off with the growth that's coming behind it. But because that growth has to protect itself through winter too, the tree fills the little wound in its branch or twig where the leaf was with a protective corky stuff which seals it against cold and bacteria.
 
Otherwise every leaf lost would be an open wound on a tree and a single tree would be covered in thousands of little wounds.
 
Clever trees." -- Ali Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156247-be-clearly-aware-of-the-stars-and-infinity-on-high</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 08:39:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Vincent Van Gogh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156247-be-clearly-aware-of-the-stars-and-infinity-on-high]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be clearly aware of the stars and infinity on high. Then life seems almost enchanted after all." -- Vincent Van Gogh]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
