<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/112549-jennie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/112549-jennie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 11:21:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145129-a-woman-at-one-of-mother-s-parties-once-said-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 11:21:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Rachel Ferguson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145129-a-woman-at-one-of-mother-s-parties-once-said-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A woman at one of mother's parties once said to me, &quot;Do you like reading?&quot; which smote us all to silence, for how could one tell her that books are like having a bath or sleeping, or eating bread - absolute necessities which one never thinks of in terms of appreciation. And we all sat waiting for her to say that she had so little time for reading, before ruling her right out for ever and ever." -- Rachel Ferguson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269490-the-questions-i-would-have-liked-to-ask-people-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 19:44:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Françoise Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269490-the-questions-i-would-have-liked-to-ask-people-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The questions I would have liked to ask people were: ‘Are you in love? What are you reading?" -- Françoise Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137568-when-i-was-all-set-to-go-when-i-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 15:14:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137568-when-i-was-all-set-to-go-when-i-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was all set to go, when I had my bags and all, I stood for a while next to the stairs and took a last look down the goddam corridor. I was sort of crying. I don't know why. I put my red hunting hat on, and turned the peak around to the back, the way I liked it, and then I yelled at the top of my goddam voice, &quot;Sleep tight, ya morons!&quot; I'll bet I woke up every bastard on the whole floor. Then I got the hell out. Some stupid guy had thrown peanut shells all over the stairs, and I damn near broke my crazy neck." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317286-she-had-taken-to-wondering-lately-during-these-swift-counted-years</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 14:36:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Shirley Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317286-she-had-taken-to-wondering-lately-during-these-swift-counted-years]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had taken to wondering lately, during these swift-counted years, what had been done with all those wasted summer days; how could she have spent them so wantonly?  I am foolish, she told herself early every summer, I am very foolish; I am grown up now and know the values of things.  Nothing is ever really wasted, she believed sensibly, even one's childhood, and then each year, one summer morning, the warm wind would come down the city street where she walked and she would be touched with the little cold thought: I have let more time go by." -- Shirley Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384465-hopes-were-wallflowers-hopes-hugged-the-perimeter-of-a-dance</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 18:54:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Karen Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384465-hopes-were-wallflowers-hopes-hugged-the-perimeter-of-a-dance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hopes were wallflowers.  Hopes hugged the perimeter of a dance floor in your brain, tugging at their party lace, all perfume and hems and doomed expectation. They fanned their dance cards, these guests that pressed against the walls of your heart." -- Karen Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/426803-a-single-note-held-in-an-amber-suspension-of-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 19:03:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Karen Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/426803-a-single-note-held-in-an-amber-suspension-of-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A single note, held in an amber suspension of time, like a charcoal drawing of Icarus falling. It was sad and fierce all at once, alive with a lonely purity. It went on and on, until my own lungs were burning.
“What bird are you calling?” I asked finally, when I couldn’t stand it any longer.
The Bird Man stopped whistling. He grinned, so that I could see all his pebbly teeth.

“You." -- Karen Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/477187-don-t-be-so-anxious-about-it-she-laughed-i-m-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 11:30:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/477187-don-t-be-so-anxious-about-it-she-laughed-i-m-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't be so anxious about it,' she laughed. 'I'm not used to being loved. I wouldn't know what to do; I never got the trick of it.' She looked down at him, shy and fatigued. 'So here we are. I told you years ago that I had the makings of Cinderella.'
He took her hand; she drew it back instinctively and then replaced it in his. 'Beg your pardon. Not even used to being touched. But I'm not afraid of you, if you stay quiet and don't move suddenly." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403550-wendy-wendy-when-you-are-sleeping-in-your-silly-bed</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 11:30:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403550-wendy-wendy-when-you-are-sleeping-in-your-silly-bed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wendy, Wendy, when you are sleeping in your silly bed you might be flying about with me saying funny things to the stars." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102603-and-finally-i-twist-my-heart-round-again-so-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 11:30:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102603-and-finally-i-twist-my-heart-round-again-so-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And finally I twist my heart round again, so that the bad is on the outside and the good is on the inside, and keep on trying to find a way of becoming what I would so like to be, and could be, if there weren't any other people living in the world." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491903-two-small-figures-were-beating-against-the-rock-the-girl</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 11:50:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491903-two-small-figures-were-beating-against-the-rock-the-girl]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two small figures were beating against the rock; the girl had fainted and lay on the the boy's arm. With a last effort Peter pulled her up the rock and then lay down beside her. Even as he also fainted he saw that the water was raising, He knew that they would soon be drowned, but he could do no more.
As they lay side by side a mermaid caught Wendy by the feet, and began pulling her softly into the water. Peter feeling her slip from him, woke with a start, and was just in time to draw her back. But he had to tell her the truth.
&quot;We are on the rock, Wendy,&quot; he said, &quot;but it is growing smaller. Soon the water will be over it.&quot;
She did not understand even now.
&quot;We must go,&quot; she said, almost brightly.
&quot;Yes,&quot; he answered faintly.
&quot;Shall we swim or fly, Peter?&quot;
He had to tell her.
&quot;Do you think you could swim or fly as far as the island, Wendy, without my help?&quot;
She had to admit she was too tired.
He moaned.
&quot;What is it?&quot; she asked, anxious about him at once.
&quot;I can't help you, Wendy. Hook wounded me. I can neither fly nor swim.&quot;
&quot;Do you mean we shall both be downed?&quot;
&quot;Look how the water is raising.&quot;
They put their hands over their eyes to shut out the sight. They thought they would soon be no more. As they sat thus something brushed against Peter as light as a kiss, and stayed there, as if to say timidly, &quot;Can I be of any us?&quot; It was the tail of a kite, which Michael had made some days before. It had torn itself out of his hand and floated away.
&quot;Michael's kite,&quot; Peter said without interest, but the next moment he had seized the tail, and was pulling the kite towards him.
&quot;It lifted Michael off the ground,&quot; he cried; &quot;why should it not carry you?&quot;
&quot;Both of us!&quot;
&quot;It can't left two; Michael and Curly tried.&quot;
&quot;Let us draw lots,&quot; Wendy said bravely.
&quot;And you a lady; never.&quot; Already he had tied the tail round her. She clung to him; she refused to go without him; but with a &quot;Good-bye, Wendy.&quot; he pushed her from the rock; and in a few minutes she was borne out of his sight. Peter was alone on the lagoon.
The rock was very small now; soon it would be submerged. Pale rays of light tiptoed across the waters; and by and by there was to be heard a sound at once the most musical and the most melancholy in the world: the mermaids calling to the moon." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31430-but-we-are-alone-darling-child-terribly-isolated-each-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 14:41:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Truman Capote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31430-but-we-are-alone-darling-child-terribly-isolated-each-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But we are alone, darling child, terribly, isolated each from the other; so fierce is the world's ridicule we cannot speak or show our tenderness; for us, death is stronger than life, it pulls like a wind through the dark, all our cries burlesqued in joyless laughter; and with the garbage of loneliness stuffed down us until our guts burst bleeding green, we go screaming round the world, dying in our rented rooms, nightmare hotels, eternal homes of the transient heart." -- Truman Capote]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470428-what-we-want-most-is-only-to-be-held-and-told-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 15:48:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Truman Capote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470428-what-we-want-most-is-only-to-be-held-and-told-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What we want most is only to be held…and told…that everything (everything is a funny thing, is baby milk and Papa’s eyes, is roaring logs on a cold morning, is hoot-owls and the boy who makes you cry after school, is Mama’s long hair, is being afraid, and twisted faces on the bedroom wall)…everything is going to be all right." -- Truman Capote]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/695074-i-know-she-ll-hate-him-she-likes-to-be-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 13:56:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Mervyn Peake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/695074-i-know-she-ll-hate-him-she-likes-to-be-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know she’ll hate him. She likes to be the only one, you know. She likes to dream that she’s queen and that when the rest are dead there’ll be no one who can order her to do anything. She said, dear, that she’d burn down the whole place, burn down Goremenghast when she was ruler and she’d live on her own, and I said she was wicked, and she said that everyone was- everyone and everything except rivers, clouds, and some rabbits. She makes me frightened sometimes." -- Mervyn Peake]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265272-there-seemed-to-be-some-heavenly-support-beneath-his-shoulder</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 16:37:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Zelda Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265272-there-seemed-to-be-some-heavenly-support-beneath-his-shoulder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There seemed to be some heavenly support beneath his shoulder blades that lifted his feet from the ground in ecstatic suspension, as if he secretly enjoyed the ability to fly but was walking as a compromise to convention." -- Zelda Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/452241-but-this-time-i-m-not-to-blame-i-want-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 13:56:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/452241-but-this-time-i-m-not-to-blame-i-want-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But this time I'm not to blame; I want you to believe that. I simply slipped into those violets. No, I want to be really truthful. I am a little to blame. The sky, you know, was gold, and the ground all blue, and for a moment he looked like some one in a book." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/695082-everything-went-black-in-the-shocking-folds-of-his-embrace</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 13:58:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Angela Carter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/695082-everything-went-black-in-the-shocking-folds-of-his-embrace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything went black in the shocking folds of his embrace. She was very startled and near to sobbing.
'Caw, caw,' echoed his raincoat.
'Don't be frightened,' he said. 'It is only poor Finn, who will do you no harm.'
She recovered herself a little, though she was still trembling. She could see her own face reflected in little in the black pupils of his subaqueous eyes. She still looked the same. She saluted herself. He was only a little taller than she and their eyes were almost level. Remotely, she wished him three inches taller. Or four. She felt the warm breath from his wild beast's mouth softly, against her cheek. She did not move. Stiff, wooden, and unresponsive, she stood in his arms and watched herself in his eyes. It was a comfort to see herself as she thought she looked.
'Oh, get it over with, get it over with,' she urged furiously under her breath.
He was grinning like Pan in a wood. He kissed her, closing his eyes so that she could not see herself any more. His lips were wet and rough, cracked. It might have been anybody, kissing her, and besides, she did not know him well, if at all. She wondered why he was doing this, putting his mouth on her own undesiring one, softly moving his body against her. What was the need? She felt a long way away from him, and superior, also." -- Angela Carter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134660-i-am-half-sick-of-shadows-said-the-lady-of-shalott</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2013 10:43:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134660-i-am-half-sick-of-shadows-said-the-lady-of-shalott]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am half-sick of shadows,' said The Lady of Shalott." -- Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/701071-if-i-was-bound-for-hell-let-it-be-hell</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 20:17:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Jean Rhys]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/701071-if-i-was-bound-for-hell-let-it-be-hell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I was bound for hell, let it be hell. No more false heavens. No more damned magic." -- Jean Rhys]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/475884-i-ve-been-so-ridiculous-all-my-life-that-a-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 18:52:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Jean Rhys]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/475884-i-ve-been-so-ridiculous-all-my-life-that-a-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been so ridiculous all my life that a little bit more or a little bit less hardly matters now." -- Jean Rhys]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/436381-after-all-this-what-happened-what-happened-was-that-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 18:52:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Jean Rhys]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/436381-after-all-this-what-happened-what-happened-was-that-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After all this, what happened? 
What happened was that, as soon as I had the slightest chance of a place to hide in, I crept into it and hid. 
Well, sometimes it's a fine day isn't it? Sometimes the skies are blue. Sometimes the air is light, easy to breathe. 
And there is always tomorrow..." -- Jean Rhys]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11034-risk-anything-care-no-more-for-the-opinion-of-others</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 00:21:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11034-risk-anything-care-no-more-for-the-opinion-of-others]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Risk anything! Care no more for the opinion of others ... Do the hardest thing on earth for you. Act for yourself. Face the truth.&quot;

(Journal entry, 14 October 1922)" -- Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249748-but-the-hearts-of-small-children-are-delicate-organs-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 10:12:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Carson McCullers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249748-but-the-hearts-of-small-children-are-delicate-organs-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the hearts of small children are delicate organs. A cruel beginning in this world can twist them into curious shapes. The heart of a hurt child can shrink so that forever afterward it is hard and pitted as the seed of a peach. Or again, the heart of such a child may fester and swell until it is a misery to carry within the body, easily chafed and hurt by the most ordinary things." -- Carson McCullers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171904-something-in-her-brain-that-still-remained-calm-told-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 18:15:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Jean Rhys]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171904-something-in-her-brain-that-still-remained-calm-told-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Something in her brain that still remained calm told her that she was doing a very foolish thing indeed." -- Jean Rhys]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42841-she-had-lived-her-early-years-as-though-she-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 13:16:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Marguerite Duras]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42841-she-had-lived-her-early-years-as-though-she-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had lived her early years as though she were waiting for something she might, but never did, become." -- Marguerite Duras]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/735007-what-a-fool-you-must-be-said-my-head-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 10:33:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Anne bronte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/735007-what-a-fool-you-must-be-said-my-head-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a fool you must be,&quot; said my head to my heart, or my sterner to my softer self." -- Anne bronte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180794-of-course-she-had-some-pathetic-illusions-about-herself-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2013 10:39:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Jean Rhys]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180794-of-course-she-had-some-pathetic-illusions-about-herself-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of course she had some pathetic illusions about herself or she would not be able to go on living." -- Jean Rhys]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/504674-i-think-i-want-to-be-in-love-with-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 13:05:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Angela Carter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/504674-i-think-i-want-to-be-in-love-with-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think I want to be in love with you but I don't know how." -- Angela Carter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129161-i-only-want-to-live-in-peace-and-plant-potatoes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 08:55:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Tove Jansson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129161-i-only-want-to-live-in-peace-and-plant-potatoes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I ONLY WANT TO LIVE IN PEACE AND PLANT POTATOES AND DREAM!" -- Tove Jansson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216230-if-he-loved-with-all-the-powers-of-his-puny</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2013 23:57:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216230-if-he-loved-with-all-the-powers-of-his-puny]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If he loved with all the powers of his puny being, he couldn't love as much in eighty years as I could in a day." -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54451-the-thing-that-irks-me-most-is-this-shattered-prison</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 00:00:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennie  add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54451-the-thing-that-irks-me-most-is-this-shattered-prison]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The thing that irks me most is this shattered prison, after all. I'm tired, tired of being enclosed here. I'm wearying to escape into that glorious world, and to be always there: not seeing it dimly through tears, and yearning for it through the walls of an aching heart, but really with it, and in it." -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
