<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/113551-anjali]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/113551-anjali" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 06:58:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123746-i-no-longer-drink-nearly-as-much-as-i-used</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 06:58:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anjali add a quote by Sarah Vowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123746-i-no-longer-drink-nearly-as-much-as-i-used]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I no longer drink nearly as much as I used to but, still, my motto is Sine coffea nihil sum. Without coffee, I'm nothing." -- Sarah Vowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115802-being-a-nerd-which-is-to-say-going-too-far</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 06:58:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anjali add a quote by Sarah Vowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115802-being-a-nerd-which-is-to-say-going-too-far]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being a nerd, which is to say going too far and caring too much about a subject, is the best way to make friends I know.  For me, the spark that turns an acquaintance into a friend has usually been kindled by some shared enthusiasm . . . At fifteen, I couldn't say two words about the weather or how I was doing, but I could come up with a paragraph or two about the album &lt;i&gt;Charlie Parker with Strings.&lt;/i&gt;  In high school, I made the first real friends I ever had because one of them came up to me at lunch and started talking about the Cure." -- Sarah Vowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79254-our-homes-do-not-have-to-offer-us-permanent-occupancy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 07:55:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anjali add a quote by Alain De Botton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79254-our-homes-do-not-have-to-offer-us-permanent-occupancy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our homes do not have to offer us permanent occupancy or store our clothes to merit the name. To speak of home in relation to a building is simply to recognise its harmony with our own prized internal song. Home can be an airport or a library, a garden or a motorway diner." -- Alain De Botton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29024-because-children-grow-up-we-think-a-child-s-purpose-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 12:42:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anjali add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29024-because-children-grow-up-we-think-a-child-s-purpose-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because children grow up, we think a child's purpose is to grow up. But a child's purpose is to be a child. Nature doesn't disdain what lives only for a day. It pours the whole of itself into the each moment. We don't value the lily less for not being made of flint and built to last. Life's bounty is in its flow, later is too late. Where is the song when it's been sung? The dance when it's been danced? It's only we humans who want to own the future, too. We persuade ourselves that the universe is modestly employed in unfolding our destination. We note the haphazard chaos of history by the day, by the hour, but there is something wrong with the picture. Where is the unity, the meaning, of nature's highest creation? Surely those millions of little streams of accident and wilfulness have their correction in the vast underground river which, without a doubt, is carrying us to the place where we're expected! But there is no such place, that's why it's called utopia. The death of a child has no more meaning than the death of armies, of nations. Was the child happy while he lived? That is a proper question, the only question. If we can't arrange our own happiness, it's a conceit beyond vulgarity to arrange the happiness of those who come after us." -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26969-we-re-actors-we-re-the-opposite-of-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 12:43:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anjali add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26969-we-re-actors-we-re-the-opposite-of-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're actors — we're the opposite of people!" -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14119-i-shall-have-poetry-in-my-life-and-adventure-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 12:43:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anjali add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14119-i-shall-have-poetry-in-my-life-and-adventure-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I shall have poetry in my life.  And adventure. And love, love, love, above all.  Love as there has never been in a play.  Unbiddable, ungovernable, like a riot in the heart and nothing to be done, come ruin or rapture." -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
