<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/113683-rob]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/113683-rob" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:34:10 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19334-it-s-not-god-that-i-don-t-accept-alyosha-only-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:34:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19334-it-s-not-god-that-i-don-t-accept-alyosha-only-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s not God that I don’t accept, Alyosha, only I most respectfully return him the ticket." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19364-it-was-as-if-that-great-rush-of-anger-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 11:14:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19364-it-was-as-if-that-great-rush-of-anger-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was as if that great rush of anger had washed me clean, emptied me of hope, and, gazing up at the dark sky spangled with its signs and stars, for the first time, the first, I laid my heart open to the benign indifference of the universe.
To feel it so like myself, indeed, so brotherly, made me realize that I'd been happy, and that I was happy still. For all to be accomplished, for me to feel less lonely, all that remained to hope was that on the day of my execution there should be a huge crowd of spectators and that they should greet me with howls of execration." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33042-maybe-i-d-never-see-him-again-maybe-he-d-gone-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 14:08:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33042-maybe-i-d-never-see-him-again-maybe-he-d-gone-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe I'd never see him again... maybe he'd gone for good... swallowed up, body and soul, in the kind of stories you hear about... Ah, it's an awful thing... and being young doesn't help any... when you notice for the first time... the way you lose people as you go along ... the buddies you'll never see again... never again... when you notice that they've disappeared like dreams... that it's all over... finished... that you too will get lost someday... a long way off but inevitably... in the awful torrent of things and people... of the days and shapes... that pass... that never stop..." -- Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44629-somebody-might-have-come-along-that-way-who-would-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 12:54:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Thomas Hardy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44629-somebody-might-have-come-along-that-way-who-would-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Somebody might have come along that way who would have asked him his trouble, and might have cheered him by saying that his notions were further advanced than those of his grammarian. But nobody did come, because nobody does; and under the crushing recognition of his gigantic error Jude continued to wish himself out of the world." -- Thomas Hardy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45309-i-know-a-rock-in-a-highland-s-ravine-on-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 11:54:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Mikhail Lermontov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45309-i-know-a-rock-in-a-highland-s-ravine-on-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know a rock in a highland's ravine,
On which only eagles might ever be seen,
But a black wooden cross o'er a precipice reigns,
It rots and it ages from tempests and rains.

And many years have gone without any hints,
From times when it was seen from faraway hills.
And its every arm is raised up to the sky,
As if catching clouds or going to fly.

Oh, if I were able to rise there and stay,
Then how I'd cry there and how I'd pray;
And then I would throw off real life's chains
And live as a brother of tempests and rains!" -- Mikhail Lermontov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51465-days-and-nights-passed-over-this-despair-of-flesh-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 13:56:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51465-days-and-nights-passed-over-this-despair-of-flesh-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Days and nights passed over this despair of flesh, but one morning he awoke, looked (with calm now) at the blurred things that lay about him, and felt, inexplicably, the way one might feel upon recognizing a melody or a voice, that all this had happened to him before and that he had faced it with fear but also with joy and hopefulness and curiosity. Then he descended into his memory, which seemed to him endless, and managed to draw up from that vertigo the lost remembrance that gleamed like a coin in the rain - perhaps because he had never really looked at it except (perhaps) in a dream." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73763-i-ve-lived-to-bury-my-desires-and-see-my-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 09:14:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Aleksandr Sergeevich Pushkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73763-i-ve-lived-to-bury-my-desires-and-see-my-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've lived to bury my desires
and see my dreams corrode with rust
now all that's left are fruitless fires
that burn my empty heart to dust.

Struck by the clouds of cruel fate
My crown of Summer bloom is sere
Alone and sad, I watch and wait
And wonder if the end is near.

As conquered by the last cold air
When Winter whistles in the wind
Alone upon a branch that's bare
A trembling leaf is left behind." -- Aleksandr Sergeevich Pushkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98120-the-worst-part-is-wondering-how-you-ll-find-the-strength</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 13:57:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Louis-Ferdinand Celine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98120-the-worst-part-is-wondering-how-you-ll-find-the-strength]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worst part is wondering how you’ll find the strength tomorrow
to go on doing what you did today and have been doing for much
too long, where you’ll find the strength for all that stupid running around, those projects that come to nothing, those attempts to escape from crushing necessity, which always founder and serve only to convince you one more time that destiny is implacable, that every night will find you down and out, crushed by the dread of more and more sordid and insecure tomorrows. And maybe it’s treacherous old age coming on, threatening the worst. Not much music left inside us for life to dance to. Our youth has gone to the ends of the earth to die in the silence of the truth. And where, I ask you, can a man escape to, when he hasn’t enough madness left inside him? The truth is an endless death agony. The truth is death. You have to choose: death or lies. I’ve never been able to kill myself." -- Louis-Ferdinand Celine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98315-why-how-can-you-ask-such-a-question-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 08:13:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Pierre-Joseph Proudhon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98315-why-how-can-you-ask-such-a-question-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why, how can you ask such a question? You are a republican.&quot;
A republican! Yes; but that word specifies nothing. Res publica; that is, the public thing. Now, whoever is interested in public affairs -- no matter under what form of government -- may call himself a republican. Even kings are republicans.&quot;
Well! You are a democrat?&quot;
No.&quot;
What! &quot;you would have a monarchy?&quot;
No.&quot;
 A Constitutionalist?&quot;
God forbid.&quot;
Then you are an aristocrat?&quot;
Not at all!&quot;
You want a mixed form of government?&quot;
Even less.&quot;
Then what are you?&quot;
I am an anarchist.&quot;


Oh! I understand you; you speak satirically. This is a hit at the government.&quot;


By no means. I have just given you my serious and well-considered profession of faith. Although a firm friend of order, I am (in the full force of the term) an anarchist. Listen to me." -- Pierre-Joseph Proudhon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98547-seeing-him-brought-in-has-i-think-saved-me-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 21:14:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Gene Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98547-seeing-him-brought-in-has-i-think-saved-me-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Seeing him brought in, has, I think, saved me from losing my mind; for that I do not thank him-sanity, after all is only reason applied to human affairs, and when this reason, applied over years, has resulted in disaster, destruction, despair, misery, starvation, and rot, the mind is correct to abandon it. This decision to discard reason, I see now, is not the last but the first reasonable act; and this insanity we are taught to fear consists in nothing but responding naturally and instinctively rather than with the culturally acquired, mannered thing called reason; an insane man talks nonsense because like a bird or a cat he is too sensible to talk sense." -- Gene Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98550-philosophy-teaches-how-man-thinks-he-thinks-but-drinking-shows</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 21:16:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Rene Daumal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98550-philosophy-teaches-how-man-thinks-he-thinks-but-drinking-shows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Philosophy teaches how man thinks he thinks; but drinking shows how he really thinks." -- Rene Daumal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98553-i-suffered-no-pain-my-hunger-had-taken-the-edge</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 21:48:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Knut Hamsun]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98553-i-suffered-no-pain-my-hunger-had-taken-the-edge]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I suffered no pain, my hunger had taken the edge off; instead I felt pleasantly empty, untouched by everything around me and happy to be unseen by all. I put my legs up  on the bench and leaned back, the best way to feel the true well-being of seclusion. There wasn't a cloud in my mind, nor did I feel any discomfort, and I hadn't a single unfulfilled desire or craving as far as my thought could reach. I lay with open eyes in a state of utter absence from myself and felt deliciously out of it." -- Knut Hamsun]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98554-nothing-is-worse-and-more-hurtful-than-a-happiness-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 22:03:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Ivan S. Turgenev]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98554-nothing-is-worse-and-more-hurtful-than-a-happiness-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing is worse and more hurtful than a happiness that comes too late. It can give no pleasure, yet it deprives you of that most precious of rights - the right to swear and curse at your fate!" -- Ivan S. Turgenev]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98555-to-kill-for-murder-is-a-punishment-incomparably-worse-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 22:09:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98555-to-kill-for-murder-is-a-punishment-incomparably-worse-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To kill for murder is a punishment incomparably worse than the crime itself. Murder by legal sentence is immeasurably more terrible than murder by brigands. Anyone murdered by brigands, whose throat is cut at night in a wood, or something of that sort, must surely hope to escape till the very last minute. There have been instances when a man has still hoped for escape, running or begging for mercy after his throat was cut. But in the other case all that last hope, which makes dying ten times as easy, is taken away for certain. There is the sentence, and the whole awful torture lies in the fact that there is certainly no escape, and there is no torture in the world more terrible." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100595-whoever-will-be-free-must-make-himself-free-freedom-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 17:21:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Max Stirner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100595-whoever-will-be-free-must-make-himself-free-freedom-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whoever will be free must make himself free. Freedom is no fairy gift to fall into a man's lap. What is freedom? To have the will to be responsible for one's self." -- Max Stirner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110181-i-love-you-sons-of-bitches-you-re-all-i-read</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2008 12:42:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110181-i-love-you-sons-of-bitches-you-re-all-i-read]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you sons of bitches. You’re all I read any more. You're the only ones who’ll talk all about the really terrific changes going on, the only ones crazy enough to know that life is a space voyage, and not a short one, either, but one that’ll last for billions of years. You’re the only ones with guts enough to really care about the future, who really notice what machines do to us, what wars do to us, what cities do to us, what big, simple ideas do to us, what tremendous misunderstanding, mistakes, accidents, catastrophes do to us. You're the only ones zany enough to agonize over time and distance without limit, over mysteries that will never die, over the fact that we are right now determining whether the space voyage for the next billion years or so is going to be Heaven or Hell." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110925-here-there-comes-a-practical-question-which-has-often-troubled</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2008 20:53:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110925-here-there-comes-a-practical-question-which-has-often-troubled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here there comes a practical question which has often troubled me. Whenever I go into a foreign country or a prison or any similar place they always ask me what is my religion.

I never know whether I should say &quot;Agnostic&quot; or whether I should say &quot;Atheist&quot;. It is a very difficult question and I daresay that some of you have been troubled by it. As a philosopher, if I were speaking to a purely philosophic audience I should say that I ought to describe myself as an Agnostic, because I do not think that there is a conclusive argument by which one prove that there is not a God.

On the other hand, if I am to convey the right impression to the ordinary man in the street I think I ought to say that I am an Atheist, because when I say that I cannot prove that there is not a God, I ought to add equally that I cannot prove that there are not the Homeric gods.

None of us would seriously consider the possibility that all the gods of homer really exist, and yet if you were to set to work to give a logical demonstration that Zeus, Hera, Poseidon, and the rest of them did not exist you would find it an awful job. You could not get such proof.

Therefore, in regard to the Olympic gods, speaking to a purely philosophical audience, I would say that I am an Agnostic. But speaking popularly, I think that all of us would say in regard to those gods that we were Atheists. In regard to the Christian God, I should, I think, take exactly the same line. " -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22595-it-s-not-what-you-don-t-know-that-kills-you-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 12:29:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22595-it-s-not-what-you-don-t-know-that-kills-you-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not what you don't know that kills you, it's what you know for sure that ain't true." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187173-but-the-truth-he-knows-is-otherwise-his-pleasure-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 20:07:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187173-but-the-truth-he-knows-is-otherwise-his-pleasure-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the truth, he knows, is otherwise. His pleasure in living has been snuffed out. Like a leaf on a stream, like a puffball on a breeze, he has begun to float towards his end. He sees it quite clearly, and it fills him with (the word will not go away) despair. The blood of life is leaving his body and despair is taking its place, despair that is like a gas, odourless, tasteless, without nourishment. You breathe it in, your limbs relax, you cease to care, even at the moment when the steel touches your throat." -- J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72442-sometimes-he-would-advise-me-to-read-poetry-and-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 10:39:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Peter Kropotkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72442-sometimes-he-would-advise-me-to-read-poetry-and-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes he would advise me to read poetry, and would send me in his letters quantities of verses and whole poems, which he wrote from memory. 'Read poetry,' he wrote: 'poetry makes men better.' How often, in my later life, I realized the truth of this remark of his! Read poetry: it makes men better." -- Peter Kropotkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
