<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/113872-elizabeth]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/113872-elizabeth" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 14:03:11 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11230-one-should-as-a-rule-respect-public-opinion-in-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 14:03:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11230-one-should-as-a-rule-respect-public-opinion-in-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One should as a rule respect public opinion in so far as is necessary to avoid starvation and to keep out of prison, but anything that goes beyond this is voluntary submission to an unnecessary tyranny, and is likely to interfere with happiness in all kinds of ways." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106117-perhaps-the-reason-we-are-unable-to-love-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 14:11:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106117-perhaps-the-reason-we-are-unable-to-love-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps the reason we are unable to love is that we yearn to be loved, that is, we demand something (love) from our partner instead of delivering ourselves up to him demand-free and asking for nothing but his company." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39065-the-body-is-not-a-thing-it-is-a-situation</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:13:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39065-the-body-is-not-a-thing-it-is-a-situation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The body is not a thing, it is a situation: it is our grasp on the world and our sketch of our project" -- Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65027-so-he-was-deserted-the-whole-world-was-clamouring-kill</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 13:39:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65027-so-he-was-deserted-the-whole-world-was-clamouring-kill]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So he was deserted. The whole world was clamouring: Kill yourself, kill yourself, for our sakes. But why should he kill himself for their sakes? Food was pleasant; the sun hot; and this killing oneself, how does one set about it, with a table knife, uglily, with floods of blood, - by sucking a gaspipe? He was too weak; he could scarcely raise his hand. Besides, now that he was quite alone, condemned, deserted, as those who are about to die are alone, there was a luxury in it, an isolation full of sublimity; a freedom which the attached can never know." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1860-one-cannot-think-well-love-well-sleep-well-if-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 13:37:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1860-one-cannot-think-well-love-well-sleep-well-if-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One cannot think well, love well, sleep well, if one has not dined well." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382399-no-one-would-take-me-just-as-i-was-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:16:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382399-no-one-would-take-me-just-as-i-was-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one would take me just as I was, no one loved me; I shall love myself enough, I thought, to make up for this abandonment by everyone. Formerly, I had been quite satisfied with myself, but I had taken very little trouble to increase my self-knowledge; from now on, I would stand outside myself, watch over and observe myself; in my diary I had long conversations with myself. I was entering a world whose newness stunned me. I learned to distinguish between distress and melancholy, lack of emotion and serenity; I learned to recognize the hesitations of the heart, and its ecstasies, the splendor of great renunciations, and the subterranean murmurings of hope. I entered into exalted trances, as on those evenings when I used to gaze upon the sky full of moving clouds behind the distant blue of the hills; I was both the landscape and its beholder: I existed only through myself, and for myself… My path was clearly marked: I had to perfect, enrich and express myself in a work of art that would help others to live." -- Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446217-to-be-oneself-simply-oneself-is-so-amazing-and-utterly</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:18:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446217-to-be-oneself-simply-oneself-is-so-amazing-and-utterly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be oneself, simply oneself, is so amazing and utterly unique an experience that it's hard to convince oneself so singular a thing happens to everybody." -- Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369018-what-disturbs-and-depresses-young-people-is-the-hunt-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 14:27:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369018-what-disturbs-and-depresses-young-people-is-the-hunt-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What disturbs and depresses young people is the hunt for happiness on the firm assumption that it must be met with in life. From this arises constantly deluded hope and so also dissatisfaction. Deceptive images of a vague happiness hover before us in our dreams, and we search in vain for their original. Much would have been gained if, through timely advice and instruction, young people could have had eradicated from their minds the erroneous notion that the world has a great deal to offer them." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152389-peril-loneliness-an-uncertain-future-are-not-oppressive-evils-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 13:32:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152389-peril-loneliness-an-uncertain-future-are-not-oppressive-evils-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Peril, loneliness, an uncertain future, are not oppressive evils, so long as the frame is healthy and the faculties are employed; so long, especially, as Liberty lends us her wings, and Hope guides us by her star." -- Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31495-one-of-the-symptoms-of-an-approaching-nervous-breakdown-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 14:03:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31495-one-of-the-symptoms-of-an-approaching-nervous-breakdown-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the symptoms of an approaching nervous breakdown is the belief that one’s work is terribly important." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27860-life-is-so-constructed-that-an-event-does-not-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 13:31:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27860-life-is-so-constructed-that-an-event-does-not-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is so constructed that an event does not, cannot, will not, match the expectation." -- Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/332225-but-solitude-is-sadness-yes-it-is-sadness-life-however</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 13:32:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/332225-but-solitude-is-sadness-yes-it-is-sadness-life-however]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But solitude is sadness.'

'Yes; it is sadness. Life, however, has worse than that. Deeper than melancholy lies heart-break." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6050-the-fundamental-cause-of-the-trouble-is-that-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 14:02:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6050-the-fundamental-cause-of-the-trouble-is-that-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The  fundamental cause of the trouble is that in the modern world the stupid are cocksure while the intelligent are full of doubt." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17856-i-do-not-pretend-to-be-able-to-prove-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 14:02:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Bertrand Russell ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17856-i-do-not-pretend-to-be-able-to-prove-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not pretend to be able to prove that there is no God. I equally cannot prove that Satan is a fiction. The Christian god may exist; so may the gods of Olympus, or of ancient Egypt, or of Babylon. But no one of these hypotheses is more probable than any other: they lie outside the region of even probable knowledge, and therefore there is no reason to consider any of them." -- Bertrand Russell ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/842623-there-are-two-kinds-of-pity-one-the-weak-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 13:27:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Stefan Zweig]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/842623-there-are-two-kinds-of-pity-one-the-weak-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two kinds of pity. One, the weak and sentimental kind, which is really no more than the heart's impatience to be rid as quickly as possible of the painful emotion aroused by the sight of another's unhappiness, that pity which is not compassion, but only an instinctive desire to fortify one's own soul agains the sufferings of another; and the other, the only one at counts, the unsentimental but creative kind, which knows what it is about and is determined to hold out, in patience and forbearance, to the very limit of its strength and even beyond." -- Stefan Zweig]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/797667-is-that-the-summit-of-earthly-happiness-the-end-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 14:13:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/797667-is-that-the-summit-of-earthly-happiness-the-end-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is that the summit of earthly happiness, the end of life - to love? I don't think it is. It may be the extreme of mortal misery, it may be sheer waste of time, and fruitless torture of feeling." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584427-into-the-hands-of-common-sense-i-confided-the-matter</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 14:13:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584427-into-the-hands-of-common-sense-i-confided-the-matter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Into the hands of common sense I confided the matter. Common sense, however, was as chilled and bewildered as all my other faculties, and it was only under the spur of an inexorable necessity that she spasmodically executed her trust." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300781-self-consciousness-is-not-knowledge-but-a-story-one-tells-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:16:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300781-self-consciousness-is-not-knowledge-but-a-story-one-tells-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Self-consciousness is not knowledge but a story one tells about oneself." -- Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180590-love-is-by-definition-an-unmerited-gift-being-loved-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 14:09:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180590-love-is-by-definition-an-unmerited-gift-being-loved-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is by definition an unmerited gift; being loved without meriting it is the very proof of real love.  If a woman tells me: I love you because you're intelligent, because you're decent, because you buy me gifts, because you don't chase women, because you do the dishes, then I'm disappointed; such love seems a rather self-interested business.  How much finer it is to hear: I'm crazy about you even though you're neither intelligent nor decent, even though you're a liar, an egotist, a bastard." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81498-the-goals-we-pursue-are-always-veiled-a-girl-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 14:12:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81498-the-goals-we-pursue-are-always-veiled-a-girl-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The goals we pursue are always veiled. A girl who longs for marriage longs for something she knows nothing about. The boy who hankers after fame has no idea what fame is. The thing that gives our every move its meaning is always totally unknown to us." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17940-living-is-being-happy-seeing-hearing-touching-drinking-eating-urinating</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 14:12:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17940-living-is-being-happy-seeing-hearing-touching-drinking-eating-urinating]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Living is being happy: seeing, hearing, touching, drinking, eating, urinating, defecating, diving into the water and gazing at the sky, laughing and crying." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374845-we-want-to-believe-young-students-try-to-believe-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 14:23:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374845-we-want-to-believe-young-students-try-to-believe-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We &lt;em&gt;want&lt;/em&gt; to believe. Young students try to believe in older authors, constituents try to believe in their congressmen, countries try to believe in their statesmen, but they &lt;em&gt;can't&lt;/em&gt;. Too many voices, too much scattered, illogical, ill-considered criticism. It's worse in the case of newspapers. Any rich, unprogressive old party with that particularly grasping, acquisitive form of mentality known as financial genius can own a paper that is the intellectual meat and drink of thousands of tired, hurried men, men too involved in the business of modern living to swallow anything but predigested food. For two cents the voter buys his politics, prejudices and philosophy. A year later there is a new political ring or a change in the paper's ownership, consequence: more confusion, more contradiction, a sudden inrush of new ideas, their tempering, their distillation, the reaction against them -" -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318818-it-is-difficult-to-find-happiness-within-oneself-but-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 14:26:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318818-it-is-difficult-to-find-happiness-within-oneself-but-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is difficult to find happiness within oneself, but it is impossible to find it anywhere else." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2195-compassion-is-the-basis-of-morality</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 14:26:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2195-compassion-is-the-basis-of-morality]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Compassion is the basis of morality." -- Arthur Schopenhauer ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255277-the-art-of-not-reading-is-a-very-important-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 14:27:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255277-the-art-of-not-reading-is-a-very-important-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The art of &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; reading is a very important one. It consists in not taking an interest in whatever may be engaging the attention of the general public at any particular time. When some political or ecclesiastical pamphlet, or novel, or poem is making a great commotion, you should remember that he who writes for fools always finds a large public. A precondition for reading good books is not reading bad ones: for life is short." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245710-i-have-not-yet-spoken-my-last-word-about-women</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 14:28:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245710-i-have-not-yet-spoken-my-last-word-about-women]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have not yet spoken my last word about women. I believe that if a woman succeeds in withdrawing from the mass, or rather raising herself from above the mass, she grows ceaselessly and more than a man." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219626-what-a-person-is-for-himself-what-abides-with-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 14:30:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219626-what-a-person-is-for-himself-what-abides-with-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a person is for himself, what abides with him in his loneliness and isolation, and what no one can give or take away from him, this is obviously more essential for him than everything that he possesses or what he may be in the eyes of others..." -- Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416716-a-man-finds-himself-to-his-great-astonishment-suddenly-existing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 14:30:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416716-a-man-finds-himself-to-his-great-astonishment-suddenly-existing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man finds himself, to his great astonishment, suddenly existing, after thousands and thousands of years of non-existence: he lives for a little while; and then, again, comes an equally long period when he must exist no more. The heart rebels against this, and feels that it cannot be true." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122359-life-is-full-of-troubles-and-vexations-that-one-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 14:31:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122359-life-is-full-of-troubles-and-vexations-that-one-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is full of troubles and vexations, that one must either rise above it by means of corrected thoughts, or leave it." -- Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369021-how-very-paltry-and-limited-the-normal-human-intellect-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 14:32:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369021-how-very-paltry-and-limited-the-normal-human-intellect-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How very paltry and limited the normal human intellect is, and how little lucidity there is in the human consciousness, may be judged from the fact that, despite the ephemeral brevity of human life, the uncertainty of our existence and the countless enigmas which press upon us from all sides, everyone does not continually and ceaselessly philosophize, but that only the rarest of exceptions do." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
