<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/113807-emilie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/113807-emilie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 15:51:47 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 15:51:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to write the book that wants to be written. And if the book will be too difficult for grown-ups, then you write it for children." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/676-how-wonderful-it-is-that-nobody-need-wait-a-single</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 20:35:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/676-how-wonderful-it-is-that-nobody-need-wait-a-single]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How wonderful it is that nobody need wait a single moment before starting to improve the world." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 17:38:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 17:39:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 17:39:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things need not have happened to be true. Tales and dreams are the shadow-truths that will endure when mere facts are dust and ashes, and forgot." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11285-god-does-not-play-dice-with-the-universe-he-plays</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 17:39:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11285-god-does-not-play-dice-with-the-universe-he-plays]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God does not play dice with the universe; He plays an ineffable game of His own devising, which might be compared, from the perspective of any of the other players [i.e. everybody], to being involved in an obscure and complex variant of poker in a pitch-dark room, with blank cards, for infinite stakes, with a Dealer who won't tell you the rules, and who &lt;i&gt;smiles all the time&lt;/i&gt;." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13169-one-describes-a-tale-best-by-telling-the-tale-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 17:43:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13169-one-describes-a-tale-best-by-telling-the-tale-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One describes a tale best by telling the tale. You see? The way one describes a story, to oneself or to the world, is by telling the story. It is a balancing act and it is a dream. The more accurate the map, the more it resembles the territory. The most accurate map possible would be the territory, and thus would be perfectly accurate and perfectly useless. 
The tale is the map that is the territory.
You must remember this." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413047-everybody-has-a-secret-world-inside-of-them-i-mean</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 17:52:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413047-everybody-has-a-secret-world-inside-of-them-i-mean]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody has a secret world inside of them. I mean everybody. All of the people in the whole world, I mean everybody — no matter how dull and boring they are on the outside. Inside them they've all got unimaginable, magnificent, wonderful, stupid, amazing worlds... Not just one world. Hundreds of them. Thousands, maybe." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39535-each-person-who-ever-was-or-is-or-will-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 17:54:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39535-each-person-who-ever-was-or-is-or-will-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each person who ever was or is or will be has a song. It isn't a song that anybody else wrote. It has its own melody, it has its own words. Very few people get to sing their song. Most of us fear that we cannot do it justice with our voices, or that our words are too foolish or too honest, or too odd. So people live their song instead." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36842-he-stared-up-at-the-stars-and-it-seemed-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 17:56:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36842-he-stared-up-at-the-stars-and-it-seemed-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He stared up at the stars: and it seemed to him then that they were dancers, stately and graceful, performing a dance almost infinite in its complexity. He imagined he could see the very faces of the stars; pale, they were, and smiling gently, as if they had spent so much time above the world, watching the scrambling and the joy and the pain of the people below them, that they could not help being amused every time another little human believed itself the center of its world, as each of us does." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38853-people-believe-thought-shadow-it-s-what-people-do-they-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 17:56:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38853-people-believe-thought-shadow-it-s-what-people-do-they-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People believe, thought Shadow. It's what people do. They believe, and then they do not take responsibility for their beliefs; they conjure things, and do not trust the conjuration. People populate the darkness; with ghost, with gods, with electrons, with tales. People imagine, and people believe; and it is that rock solid belief, that makes things happen." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46677-i-would-like-to-see-anyone-prophet-king-or-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 17:56:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46677-i-would-like-to-see-anyone-prophet-king-or-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would like to see anyone, prophet, king or God, convince a thousand cats to do the same thing at the same time." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/987-there-are-only-two-ways-to-live-your-life-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:01:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/987-there-are-only-two-ways-to-live-your-life-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are only two ways to live your life. One is as though nothing is a miracle. The other is as though everything is a miracle." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:01:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:01:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the world were merely seductive, that would be easy. If it were merely challenging, that would be no problem. But I arise in the morning torn between a desire to improve the world and a desire to enjoy the world. This makes it hard to plan the day." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:01:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2634-give-a-man-a-fire-and-he-s-warm-for-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:01:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2634-give-a-man-a-fire-and-he-s-warm-for-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Give a man a fire and he's warm for a day, but set fire to him and he's warm for the rest of his life." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406-all-god-does-is-watch-us-and-kill-us-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:01:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406-all-god-does-is-watch-us-and-kill-us-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All God does is watch us and kill us when we get boring. We must never, ever be boring." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:01:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't see things as they are, we see them as we are." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5785-the-fear-of-death-follows-from-the-fear-of-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:02:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5785-the-fear-of-death-follows-from-the-fear-of-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fear of death follows from the fear of life. A man who lives fully is prepared to die at any time." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49-it-s-never-too-late---in-fiction-or-in-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:02:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Nancy Thayer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49-it-s-never-too-late---in-fiction-or-in-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's never too late - in fiction or in life - to revise." -- Nancy Thayer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1132-deserves-it-i-daresay-he-does-many-that-live-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:02:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1132-deserves-it-i-daresay-he-does-many-that-live-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Deserves it! I daresay he does. Many that live deserve death. And some that die deserve life. Can you give it to them? Then do not be too eager to deal out death in judgement. For even the very wise cannot see all ends." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2633-it-is-said-that-your-life-flashes-before-your-eyes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:02:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2633-it-is-said-that-your-life-flashes-before-your-eyes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is said that your life flashes before your eyes just before you die. That is true, it's called Life." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1420-i-wanted-a-perfect-ending-now-i-ve-learned-the-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:02:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Gilda Radner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1420-i-wanted-a-perfect-ending-now-i-ve-learned-the-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted a perfect ending. Now I've learned, the hard way, that some poems don't rhyme, and some stories don't have a clear beginning, middle, and end. Life is about not knowing, having to change, taking the moment and making the best of it, without knowing what's going to happen next.
Delicious Ambiguity." -- Gilda Radner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2396-people-aren-t-either-wicked-or-noble-they-re-like-chef-s-salads</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:03:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2396-people-aren-t-either-wicked-or-noble-they-re-like-chef-s-salads]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People aren't either wicked or noble. They're like chef's salads, with good things and bad things chopped and mixed together in a vinaigrette of confusion and conflict." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2476-to-morrow-and-to-morrow-and-to-morrow-creeps-in-this-petty-pace</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:03:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2476-to-morrow-and-to-morrow-and-to-morrow-creeps-in-this-petty-pace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To-morrow, and to-morrow, and to-morrow,
Creeps in this petty pace from day to day,
To the last syllable of recorded time;
And all our yesterdays have lighted fools
The way to dusty death. Out, out, brief candle!
Life's but a walking shadow, a poor player,
That struts and frets his hour upon the stage,
And then is heard no more. It is a tale
Told by an idiot, full of sound and fury,
Signifying nothing." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2201-there-is-more-treasure-in-books-than-in-all-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:04:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Walt Disney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2201-there-is-more-treasure-in-books-than-in-all-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is more treasure in books than in all the pirates' loot on Treasure Island and best of all, you can enjoy these riches every day of your life." -- Walt Disney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6267-and-by-the-way-everything-in-life-is-writable-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:05:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6267-and-by-the-way-everything-in-life-is-writable-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And by the way, everything in life is writable about if you have the outgoing guts to do it, and the imagination to improvise. The worst enemy to creativity is self-doubt." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:05:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I can hear my bones straining under the weight of all the lives I'm not living." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/801-my-alma-mater-was-books-a-good-library-i-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 18:12:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emilie add a quote by Malcolm X]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/801-my-alma-mater-was-books-a-good-library-i-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My alma mater was books, a good library.... I could spend the rest of my life reading, just satisfying my curiosity." -- Malcolm X]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
