<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/115677-justin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/115677-justin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 22:11:05 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31110-for-everyone-here-in-ohio-and-across-america-who-s-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 22:11:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Justin add a quote by Hillary Rodham Clinton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31110-for-everyone-here-in-ohio-and-across-america-who-s-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For everyone here in Ohio and across America who's been ever been counted out but refused to be knocked out, for everyone who has stumbled but stood right back up, and for everyone who works hard and never gives up -- this one is for you." -- Hillary Rodham Clinton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34430-see-the-man-they-are-fitting-into-the-bottom-slot</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 15:43:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Justin add a quote by Helen Zenna Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34430-see-the-man-they-are-fitting-into-the-bottom-slot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["See the man they are fitting into the bottom slot. He is coughing badly. No, not pneumonia. Not tuberculosis. Nothing so picturesque. Gently, gently, stretcher-bearers… he is about done. He is coughing up clots of pinky-green filth. Only his lungs, Mother and Mrs. Evans-Mawington. He is coughing well to-night. That is gas. You’ve heard of gas. Haven’t you? It burns and shrivels the lungs to… to the mess you see on the ambulance floor there. He’s about the age of Bertie, Mother. Not unlike Bertie, either, with his gentle brown eyes and fair curly hair. Bertie would look up pleading like that in between coughing up his lungs… The son you have so generously given to the War. Cough, cough, little fair-haired boy. Perhaps somewhere your mother is thinking of you… boasting of the life she has so nobly given… the life you thought was your own, but which is hers to squander as she thinks fit. ‘My boy is not a slacker, thank God.’ Cough away, little boy, cough away. What does it matter, providing your mother doesn’t have to face the shame of her son’s cowardice?" -- Helen Zenna Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
