<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/116331-carl]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/116331-carl" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 20:05:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/827-among-those-whom-i-like-or-admire-i-can-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 20:05:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by W. H. Auden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/827-among-those-whom-i-like-or-admire-i-can-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Among those whom I like or admire, I can find no common denominator, but among those whom I love, I can; all of them make me laugh." -- W. H. Auden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107627-christmas-and-easter-can-be-subjects-for-poetry-but-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 20:07:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by W.H. Auden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107627-christmas-and-easter-can-be-subjects-for-poetry-but-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Christmas and Easter can be subjects for poetry, but Good Friday, like Auschwitz, cannot. The reality is so horrible it is not surprising that people should have found it a stumbling block to faith." -- W.H. Auden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107628-the-critical-opinions-of-a-writer-should-always-be-taken</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 20:07:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by W.H. Auden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107628-the-critical-opinions-of-a-writer-should-always-be-taken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The critical opinions of a writer should always be taken with a large grain of salt. For the most part, they are manifestations of his debate with himself as to what he should do next and what he should avoid." -- W.H. Auden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115160-it-is-necessary-to-find-one-s-own-way-in-new</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2008 19:34:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by Maeve Brennan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115160-it-is-necessary-to-find-one-s-own-way-in-new]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is necessary to find one's own way in New York.  New York City is not hospitable.  She is very big and she has no heart.  She is not charming.  She is not sympathetic.  She is rushed and noisy and unkempt, a hard, ambitious, irresolute place, not very lively, and never gay.  When she glitters she is very, very bright, and when she does not glitter she is dirty.  New York does nothing for those of us who are inclined to love her except implant in our hearts a homesickness that baffles us until we go away from her, and then we realize why we are restless.  At home or away, we are homesick for New York not because New York used to be better and not because she used to be worse but because the city holds us and we don't know why." -- Maeve Brennan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11858-perhaps-everybody-has-a-garden-of-eden-i-don-t-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2008 19:46:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11858-perhaps-everybody-has-a-garden-of-eden-i-don-t-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps everybody has a garden of Eden, I don't know; but they have scarcely seen their garden before they see the flaming sword.  Then, perhaps, life only offers the choice of remembering the garden or forgetting it.  Either, or: it takes strength to remember, it takes another kind of strength to forget, it takes a hero to do both.  People who remember court madness through pain, the pain of the perpetually recurring death of their innocence; people who forget court another kind of madness, the madness of the denial of pain and the hatred of innocence; and the world is mostly divided between madmen who remember and madmen who forget.  Heroes are rare." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103556-i-fall-upon-the-thorns-of-life-i-bleed-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2008 07:36:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by Saul Bellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103556-i-fall-upon-the-thorns-of-life-i-bleed-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I fall upon the thorns of life, I bleed. And then? I fall upon the thorns of life, I bleed. And what next? I get laid, I take a short holiday, but very soon after I fall upon those same thorns with gratification in pain, or suffering in joy - who knows what the mixture is! What good, what lasting good is there in me? Is there nothing else between birth and death but what I can get out of this perversity - only a favorable balance of disorderly emotions? No freedom? Only impulses? And what about all the good I have in my heart - does it mean anything? Is it simply a joke? A false hope that makes a man feel the illusion of worth? And so he goes on with his struggles. But this good is no phony. I know it isn't. I swear it." -- Saul Bellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145417-but-i-awoke-at-three-feeling-terribly-sad-and-feeling</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 22:03:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by John Cheever]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145417-but-i-awoke-at-three-feeling-terribly-sad-and-feeling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I awoke at three, feeling terribly sad, and feeling rebelliously that I didn't want to study sadness, madness, melancholy, and despair. I wanted to study triumphs, the rediscoveries of love, all that I know in the world to be decent, radiant, and clear. Then the word &quot;love&quot;, the impulse to love, welled up in me somewhere above my middle. Love seemed to flow from me in all directions, abundant as water--love for Cora, love for Flora, love for all my friends and neighbors, love for Penumbra. This tremendous flow of vitality could not be contained within its spelling, and I seemed to seize a laundry marker and write &quot;luve&quot; on the wall. I wrote &quot;luve&quot; on the staircase, &quot;luve&quot; on the pantry, &quot;luve&quot; on the oven, the washing machine, and the coffeepot, and when Cora came down in the morning (I would be nowhere around) everywhere she looked she would read &quot;luve&quot;, &quot;luve&quot;, &quot;luve.&quot; Then I saw a green meadow and a sparkling stream. On the ridge there were thatched-roof cottages and a square church tower, so I knew it must be England. I climbed up from the meadow to the streets of the village, looking for the cottage where Cora and Flora would be waiting for me. There seemed to have been some mistake. No one knew their names. I asked at the post office, but the answer here was the same. Then it occurred to me that they would be at the manor house. How stupid I had been! I left the village and walked up a sloping lawn to a Georgian house, where a butler let me in. The squire was entertaining. There were twenty-five or thirty people in the hall, drinking sherry. I took a glass from a tray and looked through the gathering for Flora and my wife, but they were not there. Then I thanked my host and walked down the broad lawn, back to the meadow and the sparkling brook, where I lay on the grass and fell into a sweet sleep." -- John Cheever]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19699-clarissa-had-a-theory-in-those-days---they-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 22:04:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19699-clarissa-had-a-theory-in-those-days---they-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Clarissa had a theory in those days - they had heaps of theories, always theories, as young people have. It was to explain the feeling they had of dissatisfaction; not knowing people; not being known. For how could they know each other? You met every day; then not for six months, or years. It was unsatisfactory, they agreed, how little one knew people. But she said, sitting on the bus going up Shaftesbury Avenue, she felt herself everywhere; not 'here, here, here'; and she tapped the back of the seat; but everywhere. She waved her hand, going up Shaftesbury Avenue. She was all that. So that to know her, or any one, one must seek out the people who completed them; even the places. Odd affinities she had with people she had never spoke to, some women in the street, some man behind a counter - even trees, or barns. It ended in a transcendental theory which, with her horror of death, allowed her to believe, or say that she believed (for all her scepticism), that since our apparitions, the part of us which appears, are so momentary compared with the other, the unseen part of us, which spreads wide, the unseen might survive, be recovered somehow attached to this person or that, or even haunting certain places, after death. Perhaps - perhaps." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152593-on-the-a-train-there-were-no-seats-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2009 19:10:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by Maeve Brennan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152593-on-the-a-train-there-were-no-seats-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["ON THE A TRAIN

There were no seats to be had on the A train last night, but I had a good grip on the pole at the end of one of the seats and I was reading the beauty column of the Journal-American, which the man next to me was holding up in front of him. All of a sudden I felt a tap on my arm, and I looked down and there was a man beginning to stand up from the seat where he was sitting. &quot;Would you like to sit down?&quot; he said. Well, I said the first thing that came into my head, I was so surprised and pleased to be offered a seat in the subway. &quot;Oh, thank you very much,&quot; I said, &quot;but I am getting out at the next station.&quot; He sat back and that was that, but I felt all set up and I thought what a nice man he must be and I wondered what his wife was like and I thought how lucky she was to have such a polite husband, and then all of a sudden I realized that I wasn't getting out at the next station at all but the one after that, and I felt perfectly terrible. I decided to get out at the next station anyway, but then I thought, If I get out at the next station and wait around for the next train I'll miss my bus and they only go every hour and that will be silly. So I decided to brazen it out as best I could, and when the train was slowing up at the next station I stared at the man until I caught his eye and then I said, &quot;I just remembered this isn't my station after all.&quot; Then I thought he would think I was asking him to stand up and give me his seat, so I said, &quot;But I still don't want to sit down, because I'm getting off at the next station.&quot; I showed him by my expression that I thought it was all rather funny, and he smiled, more or less, and nodded, and lifted his hat and put it back on his head again and looked away. He was one of those small, rather glum or sad men who always look off into the distance after they have finished what they are saying, when they speak. I felt quite proud of my strong-mindedness at not getting off the train and missing my bus simply because of the fear of a little embarrassment, but just as the train was shutting its doors I peered out and there it was, 168th Street. &quot;Oh dear!&quot; I said. &quot;That was my station and now I have missed the bus!&quot; I was fit to be fled, and I had spoken quite loudly, and I felt extremely foolish, and I looked down, and the man who had offered me his seat was partly looking at me, and I said, &quot;Now, isn't that silly? That was my station. A Hundred and Sixty-eighth Street is where I'm supposed to get off.&quot; I couldn't help laughing, it was all so awful, and he looked away, and the train fidgeted along to the next station, and I got off as quickly as I possibly could and tore over to the downtown platform and got a local to 168th, but of course I had missed my bus by a minute, or maybe two minutes. I felt very much at a loose end wandering around 168th Street, and I finally went into a rudely appointed but friendly bar and had a martini, warm but very soothing, which cost me only fifty cents. While I was sipping it, trying to make it last to exactly the moment that would get me a good place in the bus queue without having to stand too long in the cold, I wondered what I should have done about that man in the subway. After all, if I had taken his seat I probably would have got out at 168th Street, which would have meant that I would hardly have been sitting down before I would have been getting up again, and that would have seemed odd. And rather grasping of me. And he wouldn't have got his seat back, because some other grasping person would have slipped into it ahead of him when I got up. He seemed a retiring sort of man, not pushy at all. I hesitate to think of how he must have regretted offering me his seat. Sometimes it is very hard to know the right thing to do." -- Maeve Brennan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164277-having-a-coke-with-you-is-even-more-fun-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2009 15:06:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by Frank O'Hara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164277-having-a-coke-with-you-is-even-more-fun-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Having a Coke with You

is even more fun than going to San Sebastian, Irún, Hendaye, Biarritz, Bayonne
or being sick to my stomach on the Travesera de Gracia in Barcelona
partly because in your orange shirt you look like a better happier St. Sebastian
partly because of my love for you, partly because of your love for yoghurt
partly because of the fluorescent orange tulips around the birches
partly because of the secrecy our smiles take on before people and statuary
it is hard to believe when I’m with you that there can be anything as still
as solemn as unpleasantly definitive as statuary when right in front of it
in the warm New York 4 o’clock light we are drifting back and forth
between each other like a tree breathing through its spectacles

and the portrait show seems to have no faces in it at all, just paint
you suddenly wonder why in the world anyone ever did them

I look
at you and I would rather look at you than all the portraits in the world
except possibly for the Polish Rider occasionally and anyway it’s in the Frick
which thank heavens you haven’t gone to yet so we can go together the first time
and the fact that you move so beautifully more or less takes care of Futurism
just as at home I never think of the Nude Descending a Staircase or
at a rehearsal a single drawing of Leonardo or Michelangelo that used to wow me
and what good does all the research of the Impressionists do them
when they never got the right person to stand near the tree when the sun sank
or for that matter Marino Marini when he didn’t pick the rider as carefully
as the horse

it seems they were all cheated of some marvelous experience
which is not going to go wasted on me which is why I am telling you about it" -- Frank O'Hara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222592-artistic-growth-is-more-than-it-is-anything-else-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 22:25:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by Willa Cather ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222592-artistic-growth-is-more-than-it-is-anything-else-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Artistic growth is, more than it is anything else, a refining of the sense of truthfulness. The stupid believe that to be truthful is easy; only the artist, the great artist, knows how difficult it is." -- Willa Cather ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222597-many-a-night-that-summer-she-left-dr-archie-s-office</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 22:40:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by Willa Cather]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222597-many-a-night-that-summer-she-left-dr-archie-s-office]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many a night that summer she left Dr. Archie's office with a desire to run and run about those quiet streets until she wore out her shoes, or wore out the streets themselves; when her chest ached and it seemed as if her heart were spreading all over the desert. When she went home, it was not to go to sleep. She used to drag her mattress beside her low window and lie awake for a long while, vibrating with excitement, as a machine vibrates from speed. Life rushed in upon her through that window -- or so it seemed. In reality, of course, life rushes from within, not from without. There is no work of art so big or so beautiful that it was not once all contained in some youthful body, like this one which lay on the floor in the moonlight, pulsing with ardor and anticipation. It was on such nights that Thea Kronborg learned the thing that old Dumas meant when he told the Romanticists that to make a drama he needed but one passion and four walls." -- Willa Cather]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98909-we-mortals-men-and-women-devour-many-a-disappointment-between</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 19:40:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98909-we-mortals-men-and-women-devour-many-a-disappointment-between]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We mortals, men and women, devour many a disappointment between breakfast and dinner-time; keep back the tears and look a little pale about the lips, and in answer to inquiries say, &quot;Oh, nothing!&quot; Pride helps; and pride is not a bad thing when it only urges us to hide our hurts— not to hurt others." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98908-signs-are-small-measurable-things-but-interpretations-are-illimitable-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 19:41:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98908-signs-are-small-measurable-things-but-interpretations-are-illimitable-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Signs are small measurable things, but interpretations are illimitable, and in girls of sweet, ardent nature, every sign is apt to conjure up wonder,  hope, belief, vast as a sky, and colored by a thimbleful of matter in the shape of knowledge....wrong reasoning sometimes lands poor mortals in right conclusions: starting a long way off the true point, and proceeding by loops and zigzags, we now and then arrive just where we ought to be.  Just because Miss Brooke was hasty in her trust, it is not therefore clear that Mr. Casaubon was unworthy of it." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9581-the-clergy-are-practically-the-most-irresponsible-of-all-talkers</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 19:42:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9581-the-clergy-are-practically-the-most-irresponsible-of-all-talkers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The clergy are, practically, the most irresponsible of all talkers.

[&lt;i&gt;&quot;Evangelical Teaching: Dr. Cumming,&quot; The Westminster Review, 1885.&lt;/i&gt;]" -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94174-when-a-man-has-seen-the-woman-whom-he-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 19:43:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94174-when-a-man-has-seen-the-woman-whom-he-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a man has seen the woman whom he would have chosen if he had intended to marry speedily, his remaining a bachelor will usually depend on her resolution rather than on his." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134704-that-element-of-tragedy-which-lies-in-the-very-fact</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 19:46:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134704-that-element-of-tragedy-which-lies-in-the-very-fact]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That element of tragedy which lies in the very fact of frequency, has not yet wrought itself into the coarse emotion of mankind; and perhaps our frames could hardly bear much of it. If we had a keen vision and feeling of all ordinary human life, it would be like hearing the grass grow and the squirrel’s heart beat, and we should die of that roar which lies on the other side of silence. As it is, the quickest of us walk about well wadded with stupidity." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239553-our-sense-of-duty-must-often-wait-for-some-work</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 09:56:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239553-our-sense-of-duty-must-often-wait-for-some-work]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our sense of duty must often wait for some work which shall take the place of dilettanteism and make us feel that the quality of our action is not a matter of indifference." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156557-duty-has-a-trick-of-behaving-unexpectedly----something-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 09:57:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156557-duty-has-a-trick-of-behaving-unexpectedly----something-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Duty has a trick of behaving unexpectedly -- something like a heavy friend whom we have amiably asked to visit us, and who breaks his leg within our gates." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239554-but-how-little-we-know-what-would-make-paradise-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 10:00:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239554-but-how-little-we-know-what-would-make-paradise-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But how little we know what would make paradise for our neighbors.  We judge from our own desires, and our neighbors themselves are not always open enough even to throw out a hint of theirs." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239555-for-the-egoism-which-enters-into-our-theories-does-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 10:03:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239555-for-the-egoism-which-enters-into-our-theories-does-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the egoism which enters into our theories does not affect their sincerity; rather, the more our egoism is satisfied, the more robust is our belief." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310394-he-turned-from-the-sight-of-human-ignorance-and-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 07:47:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310394-he-turned-from-the-sight-of-human-ignorance-and-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He turned from the sight of human ignorance and human fate and the sea eating the ground we stand on, which, had he been able to contemplate it fixedly might have led to something; and found consolation in trifles so slight compared with the august theme just now before him that he was disposed to slur that comfort over, to deprecate it, as if to be caught happy in a world of misery was for an honest man the most despicable of crimes." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312931-there-s-nothing-that-makes-you-so-aware-of-the-improvisation</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 14:57:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by Carson McCullers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312931-there-s-nothing-that-makes-you-so-aware-of-the-improvisation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's nothing that makes you so aware of the improvisation of human existence as a song unfinished. Or an old address book." -- Carson McCullers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6029-in-every-important-way-we-are-such-secrets-from-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 14:02:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6029-in-every-important-way-we-are-such-secrets-from-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In every important way we are such secrets from one another, and I do believe that there is a separate language in each of us, also a separate aesthetics and a separate jurisprudence. Every single one of us is a little civilization built on the ruins of any number of preceding civilizations, but with our own variant notions of what is beautiful and what is acceptable - which, I hasten to add, we generally do not satisfy and by which we struggle to live. We take fortuitous resemblances among us to be actual likeness, because those around us have also fallen heir to the same customs, trade in the same coin, acknowledge, more or less, the same notions of decency and sanity. But all that really just allows us to coexist with the inviolable, intraversable, and utterly vast spaces between us." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14502-disbelief-is-more-resistant-than-faith-because-it-is-sustained</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 13:04:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14502-disbelief-is-more-resistant-than-faith-because-it-is-sustained]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Disbelief is more resistant than faith because it is sustained by the senses." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13902-and-i-knew-that-it-was-better-to-live-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 05:53:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by Ralph Ellison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13902-and-i-knew-that-it-was-better-to-live-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I knew that it was better to live out one's absurdity than to die for that of others." -- Ralph Ellison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382640-and-the-mind-that-has-conceived-a-plan-of-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 06:03:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by Ralph Ellison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382640-and-the-mind-that-has-conceived-a-plan-of-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the mind that has conceived a plan of living must never lose sight of the chaos against which that pattern was conceived. That goes for societies as well as for individuals." -- Ralph Ellison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53777-even-in-the-most-insignificant-details-of-our-daily-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 15:57:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53777-even-in-the-most-insignificant-details-of-our-daily-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even in the most insignificant details of our daily life, none of us can be said to constitute a material whole, which is identical for everyone, and need only be turned up like a page in an account-book or the record of a will; our social personality is created by the thoughts of other people." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/486266-and-so-it-is-with-our-own-past-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 16:04:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/486266-and-so-it-is-with-our-own-past-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And so it is with our own past. It is a labour in vain to attempt to recapture it: all the efforts of our intellect must prove futile. The past is hidden somewhere outside the realm, beyond the reach of intellect, in some material object (in the sensation which that material object will give us) of which we have no inkling. And it depends on chance whether or not we come upon this object before we ourselves must die." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/486267-but-none-of-the-feeling-which-the-joys-or-misfortunes</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 16:14:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/486267-but-none-of-the-feeling-which-the-joys-or-misfortunes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But none of the feeling which the joys or misfortunes of a real person arouse in us can be awakened except through a mental picture of those joys or misfortunes; and the ingenuity of the first novelist lay in his understanding that, as the image was the one essential element in the complicated structure of our emotions, so that simplification of it which consisted in the suppression, pure and simple, of real people would be a decided improvement. A real person, profoundly as we may sympathise with him, is in a great measure perceptible only through our senses, that is to say, remains opaque, presents a dead weight which our sensibilities have not the strength to lift. If some misfortune comes to him, it is only in one small section of the complete idea we have of him that we are capable of feeling any emotion; indeed it is only in one small section of the complete idea he has of himself that he is capable of feeling any emotion either. The novelist's happy discovery was to think of substituting for those opaque sections, impenetrable to the human soul, their equivalent in immaterial sections, things, that is, which one's soul can assimilate. After which it matters not that the actions, the feelings of this new order of creatures appear to us in the guise of truth, since we have made them our own, since it is in ourselves that they are happening." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
