<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/116982-everett]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/116982-everett" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 10:53:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156775-despina-can-be-reached-in-two-ways-by-ship-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 10:53:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Everett add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156775-despina-can-be-reached-in-two-ways-by-ship-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Despina can be reached in two ways: by ship or by camel. The city displays one face to the traveler arriving overland and a different one to him who arrives by sea.

When the camel driver sees, at the horizon of the tableland, the pinnacles of the skyscrapers come into view, the radar antennae, the white and red wind-socks flapping, the chimneys belching smoke, he thinks of a ship; he knows it is a city, but he thinks of it as a vessel that will take him away from the desert, a windjammer about to cast off, with the breeze already swelling the sails, not yet unfurled, or a steamboat with its boiler vibrating in the iron keel; and he thinks of all the ports, the foreign merchandise the cranes unload on the docks, the taverns where crews of different flags break bottles over one another’s heads, the lighted, ground-floor windows, each with a woman combing her hair.

In the coastline’s haze, the sailor discerns the form of a camel’s withers, an embroidered saddle with glittering fringe between two spotted humps, advancing and swaying; he knows it is a city, but he thinks of it as a camel from whose pack hang wine-skins and bags of candied fruit, date wine, tobacco leaves, and already he sees himself at the head of a long caravan taking him away from the desert of the sea, toward oases of fresh water in the palm trees’ jagged shade, toward palaces of thick, whitewashed walls, tiled courts where girls are dancing barefoot, moving their arms, half-hidden by their veils, and half-revealed.

Each city receives its form from the desert it opposes; and so the camel driver and the sailor see Despina, a border city between two deserts." -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156779-we-will-go-out-into-the-world-and-plant-gardens</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 10:56:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Everett add a quote by Kim Stanley Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156779-we-will-go-out-into-the-world-and-plant-gardens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We will go out into the world and plant gardens and orchards to the horizons, we will build roads through the mountains and across the deserts, and terrace the mountains and irrigate the deserts until there will be garden everywhere, and plenty for all, and there will be no more empires or kingdoms, no more caliphs, sultans, emirs, khans, or zamindars, no more kings or queens or princes, no more quadis or mullahs or ulema, no more slavery and no more usury, no more property and no more taxes, no more rich and no more poor, no killing or maiming or torture or execution, no more jailers and no more prisoners, no more generals, soldiers, armies or navies, no more patriarchy, no more caste, no more hunger, no more suffering than what life brings us for being born and having to die, and then we will see for the first time what kind of creatures we really are." -- Kim Stanley Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156780-i-think-of-the-postmodern-attitude-as-that-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 10:59:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Everett add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156780-i-think-of-the-postmodern-attitude-as-that-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think of the postmodern attitude as that of a man who loves a very cultivated woman and knows that he cannot say to her &quot;I love you madly&quot;, because he knows that she knows (and that she knows he knows) that these words have already been written by [author:Barbara Cartland|10320]. Still there is a solution. He can say &quot;As Barbara Cartland would put it, I love you madly&quot;. At this point, having avoided false innocence, having said clearly it is no longer possible to talk innocently, he will nevertheless say what he wanted to say to the woman: that he loves her in an age of lost innocence." -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
