<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/117607-danielle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/117607-danielle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:36:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19884-be-yourself-everyone-else-is-already-taken</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:36:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19884-be-yourself-everyone-else-is-already-taken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be yourself; everyone else is already taken." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:37:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54-don-t-walk-behind-me-i-may-not-lead-don-t-walk</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:37:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54-don-t-walk-behind-me-i-may-not-lead-don-t-walk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't walk behind me; I may not lead. Don't walk in front of me; I may not follow. Just walk beside me and be my friend." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:37:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204561-we-re-all-a-little-weird-and-life-is-a-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:38:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204561-we-re-all-a-little-weird-and-life-is-a-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We’re all a little weird. And life is a little weird. And when we find someone whose weirdness is compatible with ours, we join up with them and fall into mutually satisfying weirdness—and call it love—true love." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1519-i-believe-that-imagination-is-stronger-than-knowledge-that-myth</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:38:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1519-i-believe-that-imagination-is-stronger-than-knowledge-that-myth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that imagination is stronger than knowledge. That myth is more potent than history. That dreams are more powerful than facts. That hope always triumphs over experience. That laughter is the only cure for grief. And I believe that love is stronger than death." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246075-these-are-the-things-i-learned-in-kindergarten-1-share</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:38:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246075-these-are-the-things-i-learned-in-kindergarten-1-share]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These are the things I learned (in Kindergarten):

1. Share everything.
2. Play fair.
3. Don't hit people.
4. Put thngs back where you found them.
5. CLEAN UP YOUR OWN MESS.
6. Don't take things that aren't yours.
7. Say you're SORRY when you HURT somebody.
8. Wash your hands before you eat.
9. Flush.
10. Warm cookies and cold milk are good for you.
11. Live a balanced life - learn some and drink some and draw some and paint some and sing and dance and play and work everyday some.
12.  Take a nap every afternoon.
13. When you go out into the world, watch out for traffic, hold hands, and stick together.
14.  Be aware of wonder. Remember the little seed in the Stryrofoam cup: The roots go down and the plant goes up and nobody really knows how or why, but we are all like that.
15. Goldfish and hamster and white mice and even the little seed in the Styrofoam cup - they all die.  So do we.
16. And then remember the Dick-and-Jane books and the first workd you learned - the biggest word of all - LOOK." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5074-the-grass-is-not-in-fact-always-greener-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:39:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5074-the-grass-is-not-in-fact-always-greener-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The grass is not, in fact, always greener on the other side of the fence. No, not at all. Fences have nothing to do with it. The grass is greenest where it is watered. When crossing over fences, carry water with you and tend the grass wherever you may be." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54295-the-heart-will-turn-to-a-prune-if-love-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:40:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54295-the-heart-will-turn-to-a-prune-if-love-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The heart will turn to a prune if love is always by the numbers.  How will you know if someone really loves you if they only meet your expectations and not your needs?" -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118047-if-i-don-t-have-time-to-live-my-life-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:40:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118047-if-i-don-t-have-time-to-live-my-life-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I don't have time to live my life well the first time, when am I going to find the time to go back and live it over?" -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127130-we-can-do-no-great-things-only-small-things-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:40:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127130-we-can-do-no-great-things-only-small-things-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can do no great things; only small things with great love.(mother Teresa)" -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127124-speed-and-efficiency-do-not-always-increase-the-quality-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:42:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127124-speed-and-efficiency-do-not-always-increase-the-quality-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Speed and efficiency do not always increase the quality of life." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273360-then-he-read-the-words-of-the-scroll-slowly-first</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:42:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273360-then-he-read-the-words-of-the-scroll-slowly-first]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then he read the words of the scroll slowly, first in Japanese and then carefully translated into English:

'There is really nothing you must be. 
And there is nothing you must do.
There is really nothing you must have.
And there is nothing you must know.
There is really nothing you must become.
However. It helps to understand 
   that fire burns, and when it rains, 
   the earth gets wet. . . .'

   'Whatever, there are consequences. Nobody is exempt,' said the master." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230302-i-often-say-that-i-don-t-worry-about-the-meaning</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:42:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230302-i-often-say-that-i-don-t-worry-about-the-meaning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I often say that I don't worry about the meaning &lt;i&gt;of&lt;/i&gt; life--I can't handle that big stuff. What concerns me is the meaning &lt;i&gt;in&lt;/i&gt; life--day by day, hour by hour, while I'm doing whatever it is that I do. What counts is not what I do, but how I think about myself while I'm doing it." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310131-making-a-living-and-having-a-life-are-not-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:42:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310131-making-a-living-and-having-a-life-are-not-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Making a living and having a life are not the same thing.  Making a living and making a life that's worthwhile are not the same thing.  Living the good life and living a good life are not the same thing.  A job title doesn't even come close to answering the question. &quot;What do you do?&quot;." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20261-one-of-the-very-few-reasons-i-had-any-respect</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:43:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20261-one-of-the-very-few-reasons-i-had-any-respect]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the very few reasons I had any respect for my mother when I was thirteen was because she would reach into the sink with her bare hands - bare hands - and pick up that lethal gunk and drop it into the garbage.  To top that, I saw her reach into the wet garbage bag and fish around in there looking for a lost teaspoon.  Bare hands - a kind of mad courage." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402888-if-you-want-an-interesting-party-sometime-combine-a-few</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:45:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402888-if-you-want-an-interesting-party-sometime-combine-a-few]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want an interesting party sometime combine a few cocktails and a box of crayons." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/412265-i-ve-always-thought-anyone-can-make-money-making-a-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:46:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/412265-i-ve-always-thought-anyone-can-make-money-making-a-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've always thought anyone can make money. Making a life worth living, that's the real test." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:48:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opposite of love is not hate, it's indifference. The opposite of art is not ugliness, it's indifference. The opposite of faith is not heresy, it's indifference. And the opposite of life is not death, it's indifference." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14304-it-is-better-to-be-hated-for-what-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:48:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Andre Gide]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14304-it-is-better-to-be-hated-for-what-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to be hated for what you are than to be loved for what you are not." -- Andre Gide]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:49:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2279-being-deeply-loved-by-someone-gives-you-strength-while-loving</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:49:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Lao Tzu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2279-being-deeply-loved-by-someone-gives-you-strength-while-loving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being deeply loved by someone gives you strength, while loving someone deeply gives you courage." -- Lao Tzu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4964-love-is-that-condition-in-which-the-happiness-of-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:49:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4964-love-is-that-condition-in-which-the-happiness-of-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is that condition in which the happiness of another person is essential to your own." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3616-i-am-nothing-special-of-this-i-am-sure-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:50:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3616-i-am-nothing-special-of-this-i-am-sure-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am nothing special, of this I am sure. I am a common man with common thoughts and I've led a common life. There are no monuments dedicated to me and my name will soon be forgotten, but I've loved another with all my heart and soul, and to me, this has always been enough.." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:52:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13374-you-don-t-love-someone-because-they-re-perfect-you-love-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:52:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13374-you-don-t-love-someone-because-they-re-perfect-you-love-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't love someone because they're perfect, you love them in spite of the fact that they're not." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
