<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/118469-susan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/118469-susan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 08:05:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46196-be-brave-enough-to-live-creatively-the-creative-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 08:05:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Alan Alda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46196-be-brave-enough-to-live-creatively-the-creative-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be brave enough to live creatively. The creative is the place where no one else has ever been. You have to leave the city of your comfort and go into the wilderness of your intuition. You cannot get there by bus, only by hard work, risking and by not quite knowing what you are doing. What you will discover will be wonderful: Yourself." -- Alan Alda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/695574-on-the-job-people-feel-skillful-and-challenged-and-therefore</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2013 08:38:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/695574-on-the-job-people-feel-skillful-and-challenged-and-therefore]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the job people feel skillful and challenged, and therefore feel more happy, strong, creative, and satisfied. In their free time people feel that there is generally not much to do and their skills are not being used, and therefore they tend to feel more sad, weak, dull, and dissatisfied. Yet they would like to work less and spend more time in leisure.

What does this contradictory pattern mean? There are several possible explanations, but one conclusion seems inevitable: when it comes to work, people do not heed the evidence of their senses. They disregard the quality of immediate experience, and base their motivation instead on the strongly rooted cultural stereotype of what work is supposed to be like. They think of it as an imposition, a constraint, an infringement of their freedom, and therefore something to be avoided as much as possible." -- Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
