<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/118731-jessica]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/118731-jessica" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:25:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2582-a-literary-academic-can-no-more-pass-a-bookstore-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:25:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Amanda Cross]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2582-a-literary-academic-can-no-more-pass-a-bookstore-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A literary academic can no more pass a bookstore than an alcoholic can pass a bar." -- Amanda Cross]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1858-for-most-of-history-anonymous-was-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:26:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1858-for-most-of-history-anonymous-was-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For most of history, Anonymous was a woman." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17828-what-is-freedom-of-expression-without-the-freedom-to-offend</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:29:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17828-what-is-freedom-of-expression-without-the-freedom-to-offend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is freedom of expression?  Without the freedom to offend, it ceases to exist." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13945-a-poet-s-work-to-name-the-unnamable</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:29:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13945-a-poet-s-work-to-name-the-unnamable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A poet's work . . . to name the unnamable, to point at frauds, to take sides, start arguments, shape the world and stop it from going to sleep." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43084-whenever-someone-who-knows-you-disappears-you-lose-one-version</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:29:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43084-whenever-someone-who-knows-you-disappears-you-lose-one-version]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever someone who knows you disappears, you lose one version of yourself. Yourself as you were seen, as you were judged to be. Lover or enemy, mother or friend, those who know us construct us, and their several knowings slant the different facets of our characters like diamond-cutter's tools. Each such loss is a step leading to the grave, where all versions blend and end." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:30:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:31:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May your coming year be filled with magic and dreams and good madness. I hope you read some fine books and kiss someone who thinks you're wonderful, and don't forget to make some art -- write or draw or build or sing or live as only you can. And I hope, somewhere in the next year, you surprise yourself." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17827-free-societies-are-societies-in-motion-and-with-motion-comes-tension</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 12:11:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Salman Rushdie ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17827-free-societies-are-societies-in-motion-and-with-motion-comes-tension]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Free societies...are societies in motion, and with motion comes tension, dissent, friction.  Free people strike sparks, and those sparks are the best evidence of freedom's existence." -- Salman Rushdie ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11427-we-are-described-into-corners-and-then-we-must-describe</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 12:12:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11427-we-are-described-into-corners-and-then-we-must-describe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are described into corners, and then we must describe ourselves out of corners." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118594-faith-without-doubt-is-addiction</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 12:12:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118594-faith-without-doubt-is-addiction]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["faith without doubt is addiction" -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54001-they-are-the-we-of-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 12:14:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Carson McCullers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54001-they-are-the-we-of-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They are the we of me." -- Carson McCullers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81708-listen-f-jasmine-said-what-i-ve-been-trying-to-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 12:26:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Carson McCullers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81708-listen-f-jasmine-said-what-i-ve-been-trying-to-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen,” F. Jasmine said. “What I’ve been trying to say is this. Doesn’t it strike you as strange that I am I, and you are you? I am F. Jasmine Addams. And you are Berenice Sadie Brown. And we can look at each other, and touch each other, and stay together year in and year out in the same room. Yet always I am I, and you are you. And I can’t ever be anything else but me, and you can ever be anything else but you. Have you ever thought of that? And does it seem to you strange? " -- Carson McCullers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245965-people-don-t-do-right-because-of-the-fear-of-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 12:30:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Dorothy Allison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245965-people-don-t-do-right-because-of-the-fear-of-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People don't do right because of the fear of God or love of him. You do the right thing because the world doesn't make sense if you don't.&quot; (145)" -- Dorothy Allison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 15:01:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8425-i-have-hated-words-and-i-have-loved-them-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 22:36:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8425-i-have-hated-words-and-i-have-loved-them-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have hated words and I have loved them, and I hope I have made them right." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58751-i-wanted-to-tell-the-book-thief-many-things-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 22:36:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58751-i-wanted-to-tell-the-book-thief-many-things-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted to tell the book thief many things, about beauty and brutality.  But what could I tell her about those things that she didn't already know?  I wanted to explain that I am constantly overestimating and underestimating the human race-that rarely do I ever simply estimate it.  I wanted to ask her how the same thing could be so ugly and so glorious, and its words and stories so damning and brilliant." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79868-he-was-the-crazy-one-who-had-painted-himself-black</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 22:37:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79868-he-was-the-crazy-one-who-had-painted-himself-black]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was the crazy one who had painted himself black and defeated the world.

She was the book thief without the words.

Trust me, though, the words were on their way, and when they arrived, Liesel would hold them in her hands like the clouds, and she would wring them out like rain." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138526-a-small-but-noteworthy-note-i-ve-seen-so-many-young</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 22:37:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138526-a-small-but-noteworthy-note-i-ve-seen-so-many-young]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A small but noteworthy note. I've seen so many young men over the years who think they're running at other young men. They are not. They are running at me." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94709-his-soul-sat-up-it-met-me-those-kinds-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 22:38:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94709-his-soul-sat-up-it-met-me-those-kinds-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His soul sat up. It met me. Those kinds of souls always do - the best ones. The ones who rise up and say &quot;I know who you are and I am ready. Not that I want to go, of course, but I will come.&quot; Those souls are always light because more of them have been put out. More of them have already found their way to other places." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123779-the-consequence-of-this-is-that-i-m-always-finding-humans</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 22:38:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123779-the-consequence-of-this-is-that-i-m-always-finding-humans]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The consequence of this is that I'm always finding humans at their best and worst. I see their ugly and their beauty, and I wonder how the same thing can be both. (Death)" -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117222-somewhere-far-down-there-was-an-itch-in-his-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 22:38:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117222-somewhere-far-down-there-was-an-itch-in-his-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Somewhere, far down, there was an itch in his heart, but he made it a point not to scratch it.  He was afraid of what might come leaking out." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118224-people-observe-the-colors-of-a-day-only-at-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 22:39:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Marcus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118224-people-observe-the-colors-of-a-day-only-at-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People observe the colors of a day only at its beginnings and ends, but to me it's quite clear that a day merges through a multitude of shades and intonations with each passing moment. A single hour can consist of thousands of different colors. Waxy yellows, cloud-spot blues. Murky darkness. In my line of work, I make it a point to notice them." -- Marcus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120131-of-course-i-m-being-rude-i-m-spoiling-the-ending-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 22:40:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120131-of-course-i-m-being-rude-i-m-spoiling-the-ending-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of course, I'm being rude. I'm spoiling the ending, not only of the entire book, but of this particular piece of it. I have given you two events in advance, because I don't have much interest in building mystery. Mystery bores me. It chores me. I know what happens and so do you. It's the machinations that wheel us there that aggravate, perplex, interest, and astound me. There are many things to think of. There is much story." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225816-he-does-something-to-me-that-boy-every-time-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 22:40:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225816-he-does-something-to-me-that-boy-every-time-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He does something to me, that boy. Every time. It’s his only detriment. He steps on my heart. He makes me cry." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102251-the-words-why-did-they-have-to-exist-without-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 22:41:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102251-the-words-why-did-they-have-to-exist-without-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The words. Why did they have to exist? Without them, there wouldn't be any of this." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167892-i-like-that-every-page-in-every-book-can-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 22:41:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167892-i-like-that-every-page-in-every-book-can-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like that every page in every book can have a gem on it. It's probably what I love most about writing--that words can be used in a way that's like a child playing in a sandpit, rearranging things, swapping them around. They're the best moments in a day of writing -- when an image appears that you didn't know would be there when you started work in the morning." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151354-i-can-promise-you-that-the-world-is-a-factory</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 22:44:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151354-i-can-promise-you-that-the-world-is-a-factory]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can promise you that the world is a factory.  The sun stirs it, the humans rule it.  And I remain.  I carry them away.- spoken by death" -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
