<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/121939-jd]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/121939-jd" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:40:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225239-only-the-man-who-has-had-to-face-despair-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:40:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JD add a quote by Thomas Merton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225239-only-the-man-who-has-had-to-face-despair-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only the man who has had to face despair is really convinced that he needs mercy. Those who do not want mercy never seek it. It is better to find God on the threshold of despair than to risk our lives in a complacency that has never felt the need of forgiveness. A life that is without problems may literally be more hopeless than one that always verges on despair." -- Thomas Merton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125183-to-consume-the-eucharist-is-an-act-of-anticonsumption-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:40:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JD add a quote by William T. Cavanaugh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125183-to-consume-the-eucharist-is-an-act-of-anticonsumption-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To consume the Eucharist is an act of anticonsumption, for here to consume is to be consumed, to be taken up into participation in something larger than the self, yet in a way in which the identity of the self is paradoxically secured." -- William T. Cavanaugh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121489-everything-in-this-life-passes-away-only-god-remains</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:40:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JD add a quote by Seraphim Rose]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121489-everything-in-this-life-passes-away-only-god-remains]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything in this life passes away — only God remains, only He is worth struggling towards. We have a choice: to follow the way of this world, of the society that surrounds us, and thereby find ourselves outside of God; or to choose the way of life, to choose God Who calls us and for Whom our heart is searching." -- Seraphim Rose]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104233-we-made-bad-use-of-immortality-and-so-ended-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2008 16:32:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JD add a quote by Augustine of Hippo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104233-we-made-bad-use-of-immortality-and-so-ended-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We made bad use of immortality, and so ended up dying; Christ made good use of mortality, so that we might end up living." -- Augustine of Hippo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110067-god-became-man-so-that-man-might-become-a-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 21:35:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JD add a quote by Saint Athanasius the Great]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110067-god-became-man-so-that-man-might-become-a-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God became man so that man might become a god." -- Saint Athanasius the Great]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58652-let-no-one-bewail-his-poverty-for-the-universal-kingdom</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2009 13:20:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JD add a quote by St. John Chrysostom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58652-let-no-one-bewail-his-poverty-for-the-universal-kingdom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let no one bewail his poverty,
For the universal Kingdom has been revealed.
Let no one weep for his iniquities,
For pardon has shown forth from the grave.
Let no one fear death,
For the Saviour's death has set us free.
He that was held prisoner of it has annihilated it.

By descending into Hell, He made Hell captive.
He embittered it when it tasted of His flesh.
And Isaiah, foretelling this, did cry:
Hell, said he, was embittered
When it encountered Thee in the lower regions.

It was embittered, for it was abolished.
It was embittered, for it was mocked.
It was embittered, for it was slain.
It was embittered, for it was overthrown.
It was embittered, for it was fettered in chains.
It took a body, and met God face to face.
It took earth, and encountered Heaven.
It took that which was seen, and fell upon the unseen.

O Death, where is thy sting?
O Hell, where is thy victory? " -- St. John Chrysostom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83530-cheap-grace-is-the-grace-we-bestow-on-ourselves-cheap</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 14:08:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JD add a quote by Dietrich Bonhoeffer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83530-cheap-grace-is-the-grace-we-bestow-on-ourselves-cheap]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cheap grace is the grace we bestow on ourselves. Cheap grace is the preaching of forgiveness without requiring repentance, baptism without church discipline, Communion without confession...Cheap grace is grace without discipleship, grace without the cross, grace without Jesus Christ, living and incarnate." -- Dietrich Bonhoeffer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103513-nothing-in-theosis-is-the-product-of-human-nature-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:40:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JD add a quote by St. Maximus The Confessor, Letter 22]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103513-nothing-in-theosis-is-the-product-of-human-nature-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing in theosis is the product of human nature for nature cannot comprehend God. It is only the mercy of God that has the capacity to endow theosis unto the existing... In theosis man (the image of God) becomes likened to God, he rejoices in all the plenitude that does not belong to him by nature, because the grace of the Spirit triumphs within him, and because God acts in him." -- St. Maximus The Confessor, Letter 22]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78936-tradition-is-the-living-faith-of-the-dead-traditionalism-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 10:33:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JD add a quote by Jaroslav Pelikan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78936-tradition-is-the-living-faith-of-the-dead-traditionalism-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tradition is the living faith of the dead, traditionalism is the dead faith of the living. And, I suppose I should add, it is traditionalism that gives tradition such a bad name." -- Jaroslav Pelikan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137336-we-no-longer-dare-to-believe-in-beauty-and-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 08:29:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JD add a quote by Hans Urs von Balthasar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137336-we-no-longer-dare-to-believe-in-beauty-and-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We no longer dare to believe in beauty and we make of it a mere appearance in order the more easily to dispose of it. Our situation today shows that beauty demands for itself at least as much courage and decision as do truth and goodness, and she will not allow herself to be separated and banned from her two sisters without taking them along with herself in an act of mysterious vengeance. We can be sure that whoever sneers at her name as if she were the ornament of a bourgeois past -- whether he admits it or not -- can no longer pray and soon will no longer be able to love." -- Hans Urs von Balthasar]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
