<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/122409-lindsay]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/122409-lindsay" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 18:32:32 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142707-we-are-all-alone-born-alone-die-alone-and---</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 18:32:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142707-we-are-all-alone-born-alone-die-alone-and---]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all alone, born alone, die alone, and -- in spite of True Romance magazines -- we shall all someday look back on our lives and see that, in spite of our company, we were alone the whole way. I do not say lonely -- at least, not all the time -- but essentially, and finally, alone. This is what makes your self-respect so important, and I don't see how you can respect yourself if you must look in the hearts and minds of others for your happiness." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142709-the-office-was-large-with-many-women-and-men-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 18:35:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Andre Dubus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142709-the-office-was-large-with-many-women-and-men-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The office was large, with many women and men at desks, and she learned their names, and presented to them an amiability she assumed upon entering the building. Often she felt that her smiles, and her feigned interest in people's anecdotes about commuting and complaints about colds, were an implicit and draining part of her job. A decade later she would know that spending time with people and being unable either to speak from her heart or to listen with it was an imperceptible bleeding of her spirit." -- Andre Dubus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142710-course-they-wouldn-t-have-all-the-details-like-whether-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 18:36:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Miriam Toews]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142710-course-they-wouldn-t-have-all-the-details-like-whether-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Course they wouldn't have all the details, like whether or not they played in squares of sunlight on their walls, if they wore spiders on their hats, if they ate hamburger every other day, if they had ever made love in a yellow canola field tenderly or passionately or awkwardly. If they preferred dresses or pants, if they shaved their legs or didn't, or if they preferred red peppers to green. Stuff was happening. Even in Half-a-Life. Little things, but it all added up to something big. To our lives. It was happening all along. These were our lives. This was it. My mom was hanging on to the lives, the recorded lives, of these women. We might escape, but what if we didn't? What if we lived in Half-a-Life all our lives, poor, lonely, proud, happy? If we did, we did. These were our lives. If we couldn't escape them, we'd have to live them." -- Miriam Toews]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142712-it-s-funny-to-think-that-anson-and-i-were-here</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 18:37:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Helen Humphreys]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142712-it-s-funny-to-think-that-anson-and-i-were-here]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's funny to think that Anson and I were here, in this same place, together all that time ago, and now here we are again. It makes me feel good, makes me feel that perhaps everything doesn't just disappear, that some things are circling back, taking the long way, but circling back towards me." -- Helen Humphreys]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142713-there-are-words-in-my-life-that-i-wish-i-d</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 18:38:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Helen Humphreys]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142713-there-are-words-in-my-life-that-i-wish-i-d]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are words in my life that I wish I'd never said. I wish I'd never told my wife that I loved her, because then I had to line up all my actions with those words. I had to always act like that was true. And those three words, I love you, should never be used if you don't mean them. My lying has meant I will never get to use them on anyone else. I went against my own truth, my own heart, and there is really no coming back from that." -- Helen Humphreys]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142715-it-takes-so-little-so-infinitely-little-for-a-person</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 18:39:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142715-it-takes-so-little-so-infinitely-little-for-a-person]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It takes so little, so infinitely little, for a person to cross the border beyond which everything loses meaning: love, convictions, faith, history. Human life -- and herein lies its secret -- takes place in the immediate proximity of that border, even in direct contact with it; it is not miles away, but a fraction of an inch." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124647-you-see-we-cannot-draw-lines-and-compartments-and-refuse</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 18:41:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Rohinton Mistry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124647-you-see-we-cannot-draw-lines-and-compartments-and-refuse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You see, we cannot draw lines and compartments and refuse to budge beyond them. Sometimes you have to use your failures as stepping-stones to success. You have to maintain a fine balance between hope and despair.' He paused, considering what he had just said. 'Yes', he repeated. 'In the end, it's all a question of balance." -- Rohinton Mistry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142721-sidda-was-tired-of-being-vigilant-alert-sharp-she-longed</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 18:42:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Rebecca Wells]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142721-sidda-was-tired-of-being-vigilant-alert-sharp-she-longed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sidda was tired of being vigilant, alert, sharp. She longed for porch friendship, for the sticky, hot sensation of familiar female legs thrown over hers in companionship. She pined for the girlness of it all, the unplanned, improvisational laziness. She wanted to soak the words &quot;time management&quot; out of her lexicon. She wanted to hand over, to yield, to let herself float down into the uncharted beautiful fertile musky swamp of life, where creativity and eroticism and deep intelligence dwell." -- Rebecca Wells]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142724-where-i-m-going-anything-may-happen-nothing-may-happen-maybe</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 18:44:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Margaret Laurence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142724-where-i-m-going-anything-may-happen-nothing-may-happen-maybe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where I'm going, anything may happen. Nothing may happen. Maybe I will marry a middle-aged widower, or a longshoreman, or a cattle-hoof-trimmer, or a barrister or a thief. And have my children in time. Or maybe not. Most of the chances are against it. But not, I think, quite all. What will happen? What will happen. It may be that my children will always be temporary, never to be held. But so are everyone's.

I may become, in time, slightly more eccentric all the time. I may begin to wear outlandish hats, feathered and sequinned and rosetted, and dangling necklaces made from coy and tiny seashells which I've gathered myself along the beach and painted coral-pink with nail polish. And all the kids will laugh, and I'll laugh, too, in time. I will be light and straight as any feather. The wind will bear me, and I will drift and settle, and drift and settle. Anything may happen, where I'm going." -- Margaret Laurence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60836-so-we-shall-let-the-reader-answer-this-question-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 18:47:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60836-so-we-shall-let-the-reader-answer-this-question-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So we shall let the reader answer this question for himself: who is the happier man, he who has braved the storm of life and lived or he who has stayed securely on shore and merely existed?" -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 09:43:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be yourself in a world that is constantly trying to make you something else is the greatest accomplishment." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143949-it-seems-to-me-that-canadian-sensibility-has-been-profoundly</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 21:51:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Northrop Frye]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143949-it-seems-to-me-that-canadian-sensibility-has-been-profoundly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seems to me that Canadian sensibility has been profoundly disturbed, not so much by our famous problem of identity, important as that is, as by a series of paradoxes in what confronts that identity.  It is less perplexed by the question &quot;Who am I?&quot; than by some such riddle as &quot;Where is here?" -- Northrop Frye]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143950-what-a-lost-person-needs-is-a-map-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 21:55:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143950-what-a-lost-person-needs-is-a-map-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a lost person needs is a map of the territory, with his own position marked on it so he can see where he is in relation to everything else.  Literature is not only a mirror; it is also a map, a geography of the mind.  Our literature is one such map, if we can learn to read it as our literature, as the product of who and where we have been.  We need such a map desperately, we need to know about here, because here is where we live.  For the members of a country or a culture, shared knowledge of their place, their here, is not a luxury but a necessity.  Without that knowledge we will not survive." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143951-my-interest-in-this-pack-of-failures-betrays-my-character</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 21:58:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Leonard Cohen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143951-my-interest-in-this-pack-of-failures-betrays-my-character]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My interest in this pack of failures betrays my character." -- Leonard Cohen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25403-and-the-curt-truth-is-that-in-a-deep-secret</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 22:52:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Carson McCullers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25403-and-the-curt-truth-is-that-in-a-deep-secret]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the curt truth is that, in a deep secret way, the state of being loved is intolerable to many." -- Carson McCullers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29664-i-m-the-most-terrific-liar-you-ever-saw-in-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 23:02:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29664-i-m-the-most-terrific-liar-you-ever-saw-in-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm the most terrific liar you ever saw in your life. It's awful. If I'm on my way to the store to buy a magazine, even, and somebody asks me where I'm going, I'm liable to say I'm going to the opera. It's terrible." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80120-and-i-have-one-of-those-very-loud-stupid-laughs</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 23:02:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80120-and-i-have-one-of-those-very-loud-stupid-laughs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I have one of those very loud, stupid laughs. I mean if I ever sat behind myself in a movie or something, I'd probably lean over and tell myself to please shut up." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9157-they-re-certainly-entitled-to-think-that-and-they-re-entitled-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2009 21:12:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9157-they-re-certainly-entitled-to-think-that-and-they-re-entitled-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They're certainly entitled to think that, and they're entitled to full respect for their opinions... but before I can live with other folks I've got to live with myself.  The one thing that doesn't abide by majority rule is a person's conscience." -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142650-so-if-this-were-indeed-my-final-hour-these-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 12:58:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Margaret Laurence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142650-so-if-this-were-indeed-my-final-hour-these-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So, if this were indeed my Final Hour, these would be my words to you. I would not claim to pass on any secret of life, for there is none, or any wisdom except the passionate plea of caring ... Try to feel, in your heart's core, the reality of others. This is the most painful thing in the world, probably, and the most necessary. In times of personal adversity, know that you are not alone. Know that although in the eternal scheme of things you are small, you are also unique and irreplaceable, as are all of your fellow humans everywhere in the world. Know that your commitment is above all to life itself." -- Margaret Laurence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51063-i-wonder-which-is-preferable-to-walk-around-all-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 20:56:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51063-i-wonder-which-is-preferable-to-walk-around-all-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wonder which is preferable, to walk around all your life swollen up with your own secrets until you burst from the pressure of them, or to have them sucked out of you, every paragraph, every sentence, every word of them, so at the end you're depleted of all that was once as precious to you as hoarded gold, as close to you as your skin - everything that was of the deepest importance to you, everything that made you cringe and wish to conceal, everything that belonged to you alone - and must spend the rest of your days like an empty sack flapping in the wind, an empty sack branded with a bright fluorescent label so that everyone will know what sort of secrets used to be inside you?" -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23728-canadians-are-fond-of-a-good-disaster-especially-if-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 20:57:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23728-canadians-are-fond-of-a-good-disaster-especially-if-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Canadians are fond of a good disaster, especially if it has ice, water, or snow in it. You thought the national flag was about a leaf, didn't you? Look harder. It's where someone got axed in the snow." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249591-ruby-said-there-were-many-songs-that-you-could-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 21:16:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Charles Frazier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249591-ruby-said-there-were-many-songs-that-you-could-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ruby said there were many songs that you could not say anybody in particular had made by himself. A song went around from fiddler to fiddler and each one added something and took something away so that in time the song became a different thing from what it had been, barely recognizable in either tune or lyric. But you could not say the song had been improved, for as was true of all human effort, there was never advancement. Everything added meant something lost, and about as often as not the thing lost was preferable to the thing gained, so that over time we'd be lucky if we just broke even. Any thought otherwise was empty pride." -- Charles Frazier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/337515-love-was-the-hardest-thing-don-t-let-anyone-ever-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 20:59:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Kate Atkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/337515-love-was-the-hardest-thing-don-t-let-anyone-ever-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love was the hardest thing.  Don't let anyone ever tell you different." -- Kate Atkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148344-the-other-day-i-found-her-passport-in-her-drawer</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 21:11:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Miriam Toews]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148344-the-other-day-i-found-her-passport-in-her-drawer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The other day I found her passport in her drawer when I was putting away my dad's laundered handkerchiefs. I wish I hadn't. For the purpose of my story, she should have it with her. I sat on my dad's bed and flipped through page after empty page. No stamps. No exotic locales. No travel-worn smudges or creases. Just the ID information and my mother's black-and-white photo which if it were used in a psychology textbook on the meaning of facial expressions would be labelled: Obscenely, heartbreakingly hopeful." -- Miriam Toews]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/537548-i-wish-i-were-a-girl-again-half-savage-and-hardy</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 14:26:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/537548-i-wish-i-were-a-girl-again-half-savage-and-hardy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish I were a girl again, half-savage and hardy, and free." -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
