<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/122484-leigh]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/122484-leigh" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 20:13:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334254-i-used-to-sleep-with-my-books-in-piles-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 20:13:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leigh add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334254-i-used-to-sleep-with-my-books-in-piles-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I used to sleep with my books in piles all over my bed and sometimes they were the only thing keeping me warm and always the only thing keeping me alive. Books are the best and worst defense." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361051-it-s-where-we-re-nearest-to-our-humanness-useless-knowledge-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 20:15:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leigh add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361051-it-s-where-we-re-nearest-to-our-humanness-useless-knowledge-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's where we're nearest to our humanness.  Useless knowledge for its own sake.  Useful knowledge is good, too, but it's for the faint-hearted, an elaboration of the real thing, which is only to shine some light, it doesn't matter where on what, it's the light itself, against the darkness, it's what's left of God's purpose when you take away God." -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11780-the-best-moments-in-reading-are-when-you-come-across</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 20:15:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leigh add a quote by Alan Bennett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11780-the-best-moments-in-reading-are-when-you-come-across]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best moments in reading are when you come across something - a thought, a feeling, a way of looking at things - which you had thought special and particular to you. And now, here it is, set down by someone else, a person you have never met, someone even who is long dead. And it is as if a hand has come out, and taken yours" -- Alan Bennett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8078-henry-leave-me-out-of-it-they-don-t-count-maybe</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 20:15:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leigh add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8078-henry-leave-me-out-of-it-they-don-t-count-maybe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["HENRY:
Leave me out of it.  They don’t count.  Maybe Brodie got a raw deal, maybe he didn’t.  I don’t know.  It doesn’t count.  He’s a lout with language.  I can’t help somebody who thinks, or thinks he thinks, that editing a newspaper is censorship, or that throwing bricks is a demonstration while building tower blocks is social violence, or that unpalatable statement is provocation while disrupting the speaker is the exercise of free speech…Words don’t deserve that kind of malarkey.  They’re innocent, neutral, precise, standing for this, describing that, meaning the other, so if you look after them you can build bridges across incomprehension and chaos.  But when they get their corners knocked off, they’re no good any more, and Brodie knocks their corners off.  I don’t think writers are sacred, but words are.  They deserve respect.  If you get the right ones in the right order, you can nudge the world a little or make a poem which children will speak for you when you’re dead.
Act II, Scene 5, HENRY and ANNIE" -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25673-i-think-it-may-truly-said-that-if-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 20:16:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leigh add a quote by Charles McCabe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25673-i-think-it-may-truly-said-that-if-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think it may truly said that if you are tired of San Francisco, you are tired of life." -- Charles McCabe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213648-san-francisco-is-the-place-where-most-people-were-last</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 20:16:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leigh add a quote by Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213648-san-francisco-is-the-place-where-most-people-were-last]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["San Francisco is the place where most people were last seen" -- Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25300-belize-hell-or-heaven-roy-indicates-heaven-through-a-glance</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 20:16:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leigh add a quote by Tony Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25300-belize-hell-or-heaven-roy-indicates-heaven-through-a-glance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Belize: Hell or heaven? 

[Roy indicates &quot;Heaven&quot; through a glance]

Belize: Like San Francisco.

Roy Cohn: A city. Good. I was worried... it'd be a garden. I hate that shit.

Belize: Mmmm. Big city. Overgrown with weeds, but flowering weeds. On every corner a wrecking crew and something new and crooked going up catty corner to that. Windows missing in every edifice like broken teeth, fierce gusts of gritty wind, and a gray high sky full of ravens.

Roy Cohn: Isaiah.

Belize: Prophet birds, Roy. Piles of trash, but lapidary like rubies and obsidian, and diamond-colored cowspit streamers in the wind. And voting booths.

Roy Cohn: And a dragon atop a golden horde.

Belize: And everyone in Balencia gowns with red corsages, and big dance palaces full of music and lights and racial impurity and gender confusion. And all the deities are creole, mulatto, brown as the mouths of rivers. Race, taste and history finally overcome. And you ain't there.

Roy Cohn: And Heaven?

Belize: That was Heaven, Roy." -- Tony Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116915-we-shed-as-we-pick-up-like-travellers-who-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 20:11:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leigh add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116915-we-shed-as-we-pick-up-like-travellers-who-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We shed as we pick up, like travellers who must carry everything in their arms, and what we let fall will be picked up by those behind. The procession is very long and life is very short. We die on the march. But there is nothing outside the march so nothing can be lost to it. The missing plays of Sophocles will turn up piece by piece, or be written again in another language. Ancient cures for diseases will reveal themselves once more. Mathematical discoveries glimpsed and lost to view will have their time again. You do not suppose, my lady, that if all of Archimedes had been hiding in the great library of Alexandria, we would be at a loss for a corkscrew?" -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372627-comparing-what-we-re-looking-for-misses-the-point-it-s-wanting</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 20:12:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leigh add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372627-comparing-what-we-re-looking-for-misses-the-point-it-s-wanting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Comparing what we're looking for misses the point. It's wanting to know that makes us matter. Otherwise we're going out the way we came in. That's why you can't believe in the afterlife, Valentine. Believe in the after, by all means, but not the life. Believe in God, the soul, the spirit, the infinite, believe in angels if you like, but not in the great celestial get-together for an exchange of views. If the answers are in the back of the book I can wait, but what a drag. Better to struggle on knowing that failure is final." -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2838-a-writer-is-someone-for-whom-writing-is-more-difficult</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 18:58:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leigh add a quote by Thomas Mann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2838-a-writer-is-someone-for-whom-writing-is-more-difficult]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A writer is someone for whom writing is more difficult than it is for other people." -- Thomas Mann]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
