<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/123081-david-gross]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/123081-david-gross" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 16:40:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213677-charles-ii-once-invited-the-members-of-the-royal-society</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 16:40:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Alasdair MacIntyre]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213677-charles-ii-once-invited-the-members-of-the-royal-society]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Charles II once invited the members of the Royal Society to explain to him why a dead fish weighs more than the same fish alive; a number of subtle explanations were offered to him. He then pointed out that it does not." -- Alasdair MacIntyre]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43278-the-self-is-a-relation-which-relates-itself-to-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2008 11:07:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43278-the-self-is-a-relation-which-relates-itself-to-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The self is a relation which relates itself to its own self, or it is that in the relation that the relation relates itself to its own self; the self is not the relation but that the relation relates itself to its own self." -- Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54574-it-is-a-proof-of-the-divergence-of-the-tendencies</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 08:29:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Edmund Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54574-it-is-a-proof-of-the-divergence-of-the-tendencies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a proof of the divergence of the tendencies of the socialist and the bourgeois pictures of history—and from now on there will be two distinct historical cultures running side by side without ever really fusing—that people who have been brought up on the conventional version of history and know all about the Robespierrist Terror during the Great French Revolution, should find it an unfamiliar fact that the Terror of the government of Thiers executed, imprisoned or exiled more people—the number has been estimated at a hundred thousand—in that one week of the suppression of the [Paris] Commune [of 1871] than the revolutionary Terror of Robespierre had done in three years." -- Edmund Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83548-the-sceptical-attack-on-free-will-philosophy-s-concept-of-libertarian</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 14:43:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Thomas Pink]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83548-the-sceptical-attack-on-free-will-philosophy-s-concept-of-libertarian]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sceptical attack [on free will philosophy’s concept of libertarian freedom] amounts simply to a dogmatic determination to describe the world only in terms that already exclude freedom as a distinctive feature of human life. The sceptic assumes that the world can contain no power other than causation; and that any event that is not causally determined by prior events must just be random. But if we insist on describing the world only in these terms, then of course it may well appear that libertarian freedom is not possible and cannot exist. But by what right do we so exclude such freedom from the very outset?" -- Thomas Pink]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83550-in-short-to-overstate-the-point-only-slightly-because-people-don-t-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 14:47:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Kwame Anthony Appiah]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83550-in-short-to-overstate-the-point-only-slightly-because-people-don-t-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In short—to overstate the point only slightly—because people don’t really know why they do what they do, they give explanations of their own behavior that are about as reliable as anyone else’s, and in many circumstances actually less so." -- Kwame Anthony Appiah]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84480-money-and-honour-have-no-attraction-for-them-good-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 10:37:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Socrates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84480-money-and-honour-have-no-attraction-for-them-good-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…money and honour have no attraction for them; good men do not wish to be openly demanding payment for governing and so to get the name of hirelings, nor by secretly helping themselves out of the public revenues to get the name of thieves. And not being ambitious they do not care about honour. Wherefore necessity must be laid upon them, and they must be induced to serve from the fear of punishment. And this, as I imagine, is the reason why the forwardness to take office, instead of waiting to be compelled, has been deemed dishonourable. Now the worst part of the punishment is that he who refuses to rule is liable to be ruled by one who is worse than himself. And the fear of this, as I conceive, induces the good to take office, not because they would, but because they cannot help — not under the idea that they are going to have any benefit or enjoyment themselves, but as a necessity, and because they are not able to commit the task of ruling to any one who is better than themselves, or indeed as good. For there is reason to think that if a city were composed entirely of good men, then to avoid office would be as much an object of contention as to obtain office is at present…" -- Socrates]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84487-since-the-branch-of-philosophy-on-which-we-are-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 10:40:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Aristotle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84487-since-the-branch-of-philosophy-on-which-we-are-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Since the branch of philosophy on which we are at present engaged differs from the others in not being a subject of merely intellectual interest — I mean we are not concerned to know what goodness essentially is, but how we are to become good men, for this alone gives the study its practical value — we must apply our minds to the solution of the problems of conduct. " -- Aristotle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109392-out-of-the-city-s-eighty-five-thousand-streets-there-are-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2008 14:30:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Lida]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109392-out-of-the-city-s-eighty-five-thousand-streets-there-are-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…out of the city’s eighty-five thousand streets, there are about eight hundred fifty called Juárez, seven hundred fifty named Hidalgo, and seven hundred known as Morelos.  Two hundred are called 16 de Septiembre, while a hundred more are called 16 de Septiembre Avenue, Alley, Mews, or Extension…" -- David Lida]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38264-there-are-certain-queer-times-and-occasions-in-this-strange</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 16:57:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38264-there-are-certain-queer-times-and-occasions-in-this-strange]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are certain queer times and occasions in this strange mixed affair we call life when a man takes this whole universe for a vast practical joke, though the wit thereof he but dimly discerns, and more than suspects that the joke is at nobody's expense but his own." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181816-revolutionary-movements-do-not-spread-by-contamination-but-by-resonance</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 22:40:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by The Invisible Committee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181816-revolutionary-movements-do-not-spread-by-contamination-but-by-resonance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Revolutionary movements do not spread by contamination but by &lt;i&gt;resonance&lt;/i&gt;. Something that is constituted here resonates with the shock wave emitted by something constituted over there.&amp;hellip; An insurrection is not like a plague or a forest fire &amp;mdash; a linear process which spreads from place to place after an initial spark. It rather takes the shape of a music, whose focal points, though dispersed in time and space, succeed in imposing the rhythms of their own vibrations, always taking on more density." -- The Invisible Committee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203142-what-do-believers-in-the-absolute-mean-by-saving-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 16:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by William James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203142-what-do-believers-in-the-absolute-mean-by-saving-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What do believers in the Absolute mean by saving that their belief affords them comfort? They mean that since in the Absolute finite evil is ‘overruled’ already, we may, therefore, whenever we wish, treat the temporal as if it were potentially the eternal, be sure that we can trust its outcome, and, without sin, dismiss our fear and drop the worry of our finite responsibility. In short, they mean that we have a right ever and anon to take a moral holiday, to let the world wag in its own way, feeling that its issues are in better hands than ours and are none of our business." -- William James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275194-having-perfected-his-arrangements-he-would-get-my-pipe-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 22:29:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275194-having-perfected-his-arrangements-he-would-get-my-pipe-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Having perfected his arrangements, he would get my pipe, and, lighting it, would hand it to me. Often he was obliged to strike a light for the occasion, and as the mode he adopted was entirely different from what I had ever seen or heard of before I will describe it.

A straight, dry, and partly decayed stick of the Hibiscus, about six feet in length, and half as many inches in diameter, with a small, bit of wood not more than a foot long, and scarcely an inch wide, is as invariably to be met with in every house in Typee as a box of lucifer matches in the corner of a kitchen cupboard at home.

The islander, placing the larger stick obliquely against some object, with one end elevated at an angle of forty-five degrees, mounts astride of it like an urchin about to gallop off upon a cane, and then grasping the smaller one firmly in both hands, he rubs its pointed end slowly up and down the extent of a few inches on the principal stick, until at last he makes a narrow groove in the wood, with an abrupt termination at the point furthest from him, where all the dusty particles which the friction creates are accumulated in a little heap.

At first Kory-Kory goes to work quite leisurely, but gradually quickens his pace, and waxing warm in the employment, drives the stick furiously along the smoking channel, plying his hands to and fro with amazing rapidity, the perspiration starting from every pore. As he approaches the climax of his effort, he pants and gasps for breath, and his eyes almost start from their sockets with the violence of his exertions. This is the critical stage of the operation; all his previous labours are vain if he cannot sustain the rapidity of the movement until the reluctant spark is produced. Suddenly he stops, becoming perfectly motionless. His hands still retain their hold of the smaller stick, which is pressed convulsively against the further end of the channel among the fine powder there accumulated, as if he had just pierced through and through some little viper that was wriggling and struggling to escape from his clutches. The next moment a delicate wreath of smoke curls spirally into the air, the heap of dusty particles glows with fire, and Kory-Kory, almost breathless, dismounts from his steed." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/294195-the-majority-of-men-do-not-think-in-order-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2010 16:39:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/294195-the-majority-of-men-do-not-think-in-order-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…the majority of men do not think in order to know the truth, but in order to assure themselves that the life which they lead, and which is agreeable and habitual to them, is the one which coincides with the truth." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/307652-from-time-to-time-i-meet-people-who-live-among</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 16:43:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/307652-from-time-to-time-i-meet-people-who-live-among]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From time to time I meet people who live among riches I cannot even imagine. I still have to make an effort to realize that others can feel envious of such wealth. A long time ago, I once lived a whole week luxuriating in all the goods of this world: we slept without a roof, on a beach, I lived on fruit, and spent half my days alone in the water. I learned something then that has always made me react to the signs of comfort or of a well-appointed house with irony, impatience, and sometimes anger. Although I live without worrying about tomorrow now, and therefore count myself among the privileged, I don't know how to own things. What I do have, which always comes to me without my asking for it, I can't seem to keep. Less from extravagance, I think, than from another kind of parsimony: I cling like a miser to the freedom that disappears as soon as there is an excess of things." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/307837-the-most-loathsome-materialism-is-not-the-kind-people-usually</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 10:25:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/307837-the-most-loathsome-materialism-is-not-the-kind-people-usually]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most loathsome materialism is not the kind people usually think of, but the sort that attempts to let dead ideas pass for living realities, diverting into sterile myths the stubborn and lucid attention we give to what we have within us that must forever die." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309080-for-the-greeks-values-existed-a-priori-and-marked-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2010 12:38:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309080-for-the-greeks-values-existed-a-priori-and-marked-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the Greeks, values existed a priori and marked out the exact limits of every action. Modern philosophy places its values at the completion of action. They are not, but they become, and we shall know them completely only at the end of history. When they disappear, limits vanish as well, and since ideas differ as to what these values will be, since there is no struggle which, unhindered by these same values, does not extend indefinitely, we are now witnessing the Messianic forces confronting one another, their clamors merging in the shock of empires. Excess is a fire, according to Heraclitus. The fire is gaining ground; Nietzsche has been overtaken. It is no longer with hammer blows but with cannon shots that Europe philosophizes." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316395-suppose-a-problem-in-psychology-was-set-what-can-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2010 16:52:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316395-suppose-a-problem-in-psychology-was-set-what-can-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suppose a problem in psychology was set: What can be done to persuade the men of our time — Christians, humanitarians or, simply, kindhearted people — into committing the most abominable crimes with no feeling of guilt? There could be only one way: to do precisely what is being done now, namely, to make them governors, inspectors, officers, policemen, and so forth; which means, first, that they must be convinced of the existence of a kind of organization called ‘government service,’ allowing men to be treated like inanimate objects and banning thereby all human brotherly relations with them; and secondly, that the people entering this ‘government service’ must be so unified that the responsibility for their dealings with men would never fall on any one of them individually." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317610-looking-at-her-one-was-for-some-reason-always-reminded</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2010 19:39:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Anton Pavlovich Chekhov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317610-looking-at-her-one-was-for-some-reason-always-reminded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...looking at her, one was for some reason always reminded that she had already sewn herself a shroud for the hour of death, and that the same storage chest which held the shroud also concealed her lottery tickets." -- Anton Pavlovich Chekhov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/389358-the-genuflection-toward-fairness-is-a-familiar-newsroom-piety-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 14:37:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/389358-the-genuflection-toward-fairness-is-a-familiar-newsroom-piety-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The genuflection toward 'fairness' is a familiar newsroom piety, in practice the excuse for a good deal of autopilot reporting and lazy thinking but in theory a benign ideal. In Washington, however, a community in which the management of news has become the single overriding preoccupation of the core industry, what 'fairness' has often come to mean is a scrupulous passivity, an agreement to cover the story not as it is occurring but as it is presented, which is to say as it is manufactured." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401970-are-you-in-earnest-resolved-never-to-barter-your-liberty</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 13:00:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Adam Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401970-are-you-in-earnest-resolved-never-to-barter-your-liberty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Are you in earnest resolved never to barter your liberty for the lordly servitude of a court, but to live free, fearless, and independent? There seems to be one way to continue in that virtuous resolution; and perhaps but one. Never enter the place from whence so few have been able to return; never come within the circle of ambition; nor ever bring yourself into comparison with those masters of the earth who have already engrossed the attention of half mankind before you." -- Adam Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402127-the-attitude-of-resistance-is-one-of-weakness-inasmuch-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 20:28:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402127-the-attitude-of-resistance-is-one-of-weakness-inasmuch-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The attitude of resistance is one of weakness inasmuch as it only faces an enemy. It has its back to all that is truly attractive." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/409605-it-was-as-though-our-love-were-a-small-creature</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 20:34:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/409605-it-was-as-though-our-love-were-a-small-creature]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was as though our love were a small creature caught in a trap and bleeding to death: I had to shut my eyes and wring its neck." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/418789-where-lies-the-power-there-let-the-blame-lie-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 21:48:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/418789-where-lies-the-power-there-let-the-blame-lie-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where lies the power, there let the blame lie too.&quot;
Nay, power is relative; you cannot fright
The coming pest with border fortresses,
Or catch your carp with subtle argument.
All force is twain in one:  cause is not cause
Unless effect be there; and action's self
Must needs contain a passive.  So command
Exists but with obedience." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246124-i-have-no-particular-love-for-the-idealized-worker-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2011 22:51:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246124-i-have-no-particular-love-for-the-idealized-worker-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have no particular love for the idealized “worker” as he appears in the bourgeois Communist’s mind, but when I see an actual flesh-and-blood worker in conflict with his natural enemy, the policeman, I do not have to ask myself which side I am on." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625351-the-characteristic-feature-of-all-ethics-is-to-consider-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 21:09:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625351-the-characteristic-feature-of-all-ethics-is-to-consider-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The characteristic feature of all ethics is to consider human life as a game that can be won or lost and to teach man the means of winning." -- Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625352-to-will-oneself-moral-and-to-will-oneself-free-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 21:10:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625352-to-will-oneself-moral-and-to-will-oneself-free-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To will oneself moral and to will oneself free are one and the same decision." -- Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26741-say-what-you-will-about-the-sweet-miracle-of-unquestioning</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 20:55:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26741-say-what-you-will-about-the-sweet-miracle-of-unquestioning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Say what you will about the sweet miracle of unquestioning faith, I consider a capacity for it terrifying and absolutely vile." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630936-what-can-any-one-person-do-he-said-each-person</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 21:35:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630936-what-can-any-one-person-do-he-said-each-person]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What can any one person do?' he said.
'Each person does a little something,' I said, 'and there you are." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/633341-there-is-far-too-much-croaking-among-young-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 21:09:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Samuel Smiles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/633341-there-is-far-too-much-croaking-among-young-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is far too much croaking among young men." -- Samuel Smiles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/653235-to-censure-my-own-faults-in-some-other-person-seems</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 22:04:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Michel de Montaigne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/653235-to-censure-my-own-faults-in-some-other-person-seems]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To censure my own faults in some other person seems to me no more incongruous than to censure, as I often do, another's in myself. They must be denounced everywhere, and be allowed no place of sanctuary." -- Michel de Montaigne]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
