<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/123487-michelle-v]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/123487-michelle-v" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 13:21:09 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116915-we-shed-as-we-pick-up-like-travellers-who-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 13:21:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116915-we-shed-as-we-pick-up-like-travellers-who-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We shed as we pick up, like travellers who must carry everything in their arms, and what we let fall will be picked up by those behind. The procession is very long and life is very short. We die on the march. But there is nothing outside the march so nothing can be lost to it. The missing plays of Sophocles will turn up piece by piece, or be written again in another language. Ancient cures for diseases will reveal themselves once more. Mathematical discoveries glimpsed and lost to view will have their time again. You do not suppose, my lady, that if all of Archimedes had been hiding in the great library of Alexandria, we would be at a loss for a corkscrew?" -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728197-let-s-say-i-will-rip-your-life-apart-me-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 14:22:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728197-let-s-say-i-will-rip-your-life-apart-me-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let's say I will rip your life apart. Me and my banker friends. 
How can he explain that to him? The world is not run from where he thinks. Not from border fortresses, not even from Whitehall. The world is run from Antwerp, from Florence, from places he has never imagined; from Lisbon, from where the ships with sails of silk drift west and are burned up in the sun. Not from the castle walls, but from counting houses, not be the call of the bugle, but by the click of the abacus, not by the grate and click of the mechanism of the gun but by the scrape of the pen on the page of the promissory note that pays for the gun and the gunsmith and the powder and shot." -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78990-all-stories-are-about-wolves-all-worth-repeating-that-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2013 09:17:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78990-all-stories-are-about-wolves-all-worth-repeating-that-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All stories are about wolves. All worth repeating, that is. Anything else is sentimental drivel.

All of them?

Sure, he says. Think about it. There's escaping from the wolves, fighting the wolves, capturing the wolves, taming the wolves. Being thrown to the wolves, or throwing others to the wolves so the wolves will eat them instead of you. Running with the wolf pack. Turning into a wolf. Best of all, turning into the head wolf. No other decent stories exist." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/603194-the-war-had-made-a-man-of-him-it-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2012 11:12:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Ford Madox Ford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/603194-the-war-had-made-a-man-of-him-it-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The war had made a man of him! It had coarsened him and hardened him. There was no other way to look at it. It had made him reach a point at which he would no longer stand unbearable things." -- Ford Madox Ford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/640782-i-will-not-die-for-a-long-time-joseph-tugged</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 11:18:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Christopher Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/640782-i-will-not-die-for-a-long-time-joseph-tugged]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will not die for a long time.&quot; Joseph tugged at his gray beard. &quot;My beard goes white, but there's a lot of life in me yet.&quot;
&quot;Don't be so sure, Abba,&quot; Joshua said.
Joseph dropped the bowl he was working on and stared into his hands. &quot;Run away and play, you two,&quot; he said, his voice little more than a whisper.
Joshua stood and walked away. I wanted to throw my arms around the old man, for I had never seen a grown man afraid before and it frightened me too. &quot;Can I help?&quot; I said, pointing to the half-finished bowl that lay in Joseph's lap.
&quot;You go with Joshua. He needs a friend to teach him to be human. Then I can teach him to be a man." -- Christopher Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221968-you-re-in-a-car-with-a-beautiful-boy-and-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 08:21:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by richard siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221968-you-re-in-a-car-with-a-beautiful-boy-and-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You’re in a car with a beautiful boy, and he won’t tell you that he loves you, but he loves you. And you feel like you’ve done something terrible, like robbed a liquor store, or swallowed pills, or shoveled yourself a grave in the dirt, and you’re tired. You’re in a car with a beautiful boy, and you’re trying not to tell him that you love him, and you’re trying to choke down the feeling, and you’re trembling, but he reaches over and he touches you, like a prayer for which no words exist, and you feel your heart taking root in your body, like you’ve discovered something you didn’t even have a name for." -- richard siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/712122-t-he-heart-is-like-any-other-organ-you-can-weigh</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 14:13:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/712122-t-he-heart-is-like-any-other-organ-you-can-weigh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[T]he heart is like any other organ, you can weigh it on a scale." -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/505216-the-trouble-with-england-he-thinks-is-that-it-s-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 14:15:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/505216-the-trouble-with-england-he-thinks-is-that-it-s-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble with England, he thinks, is that it's so poor in gesture. We shall have to develop a hand signal for ‘Back off, our prince is fucking this man's daughter.’ He is surprised that the Italians have not done it. Though perhaps they have, and he just never caught on." -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728194-he-turns-to-the-painting-i-fear-mark-was-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 14:19:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728194-he-turns-to-the-painting-i-fear-mark-was-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He turns to the painting. &quot;I fear Mark was right.&quot;
&quot;Who is Mark?&quot;
&quot;A silly little boy who runs after George Boleyn. I once heard him say I looked like a murderer.&quot;
Gregory says, &quot;Did you not know?" -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/769416-the-entire-history-of-human-desire-takes-about-seventy-minutes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 12:22:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Richard Siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/769416-the-entire-history-of-human-desire-takes-about-seventy-minutes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The entire history of human desire takes about seventy minutes to tell. Unfortunately, we don’t have that kind of time." -- Richard Siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508928-there-s-nothing-hard-about-it-but-i-get-praised-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2013 16:50:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Dorothy Baker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508928-there-s-nothing-hard-about-it-but-i-get-praised-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's nothing hard about it. But I get praised for the hardest of things I do, and I do some of the hardest of things. Things like waking up in the morning and going to sleep at night, all alone except for when I'm with someone; and it's getting harder and harder." -- Dorothy Baker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584441-men-always-say-that-as-the-defining-compliment-don-t-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 07:18:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584441-men-always-say-that-as-the-defining-compliment-don-t-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men always say that as the defining compliment, don’t they? She’s a cool girl. Being the Cool Girl means I am a hot, brilliant, funny woman who adores football, poker, dirty jokes, and burping, who plays video games, drinks cheap beer, loves threesomes and anal sex, and jams hot dogs and hamburgers into her mouth like she’s hosting the world’s biggest culinary gang bang while somehow maintaining a size 2, because Cool Girls are above all hot. Hot and understanding. Cool Girls never get angry; they only smile in a chagrined, loving manner and let their men do whatever they want. Go ahead, shit on me, I don’t mind, I’m the Cool Girl.

Men actually think this girl exists. Maybe they’re fooled because so many women are willing to pretend to be this girl. For a long time Cool Girl offended me. I used to see men – friends, coworkers, strangers – giddy over these awful pretender women, and I’d want to sit these men down and calmly say: You are not dating a woman, you are dating a woman who has watched too many movies written by socially awkward men who’d like to believe that this kind of woman exists and might kiss them. I’d want to grab the poor guy by his lapels or messenger bag and say: The bitch doesn’t really love chili dogs that much – no one loves chili dogs that much! And the Cool Girls are even more pathetic: They’re not even pretending to be the woman they want to be, they’re pretending to be the woman a man wants them to be. Oh, and if you’re not a Cool Girl, I beg you not to believe that your man doesn’t want the Cool Girl. It may be a slightly different version – maybe he’s a vegetarian, so Cool Girl loves seitan and is great with dogs; or maybe he’s a hipster artist, so Cool Girl is a tattooed, bespectacled nerd who loves comics. There are variations to the window dressing, but believe me, he wants Cool Girl, who is basically the girl who likes every fucking thing he likes and doesn’t ever complain. (How do you know you’re not Cool Girl? Because he says things like: “I like strong women.” If he says that to you, he will at some point fuck someone else. Because “I like strong women” is code for “I hate strong women.”)" -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277021-tell-me-about-the-dream-where-we-pull-the-bodies</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 16:16:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Richard Siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277021-tell-me-about-the-dream-where-we-pull-the-bodies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tell me about the dream where we pull the bodies out of the lake
                                                                                and dress them in warm clothes again.
          How it was late, and no one could sleep, the horses running
until they forget that they are horses.
                    It’s not like a tree where the roots have to end somewhere,
          it’s more like a song on a policeman’s radio,
                              how we rolled up the carpet so we could dance, and the days
were bright red, and every time we kissed there was another apple
                                                                                                                        to slice into pieces.
Look at the light through the windowpane. That means it’s noon, that means
          we're inconsolable.
                                                            Tell me how all this, and love too, will ruin us.
These, our bodies, possessed by light.
                                                                                          Tell me we’ll never get used to it." -- Richard Siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132361-oh-will-she-said-what-can-we-do-whatever-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 20:52:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132361-oh-will-she-said-what-can-we-do-whatever-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh, Will,&quot; she said, &quot;What can we do? Whatever can we do? I want to live with you forever. I want to kiss you and lie down with you and wake up with you every day of my life till I die, years and years and years away. I don't want a memory, just a memory...&quot;

&quot;No,&quot; he said. &quot;Memory's a poor thing to have. It's your own real hair and mouth and arms and eyes and hands I want. I didn't know I could ever love anything so much. Oh, Lyra, I wish this night would never end! If only we could stay here like this, and the world could stop turning, and everyone else could fall into a sleep...&quot;

&quot;Everyone except us! And you and I could live here forever and just love each other.&quot;

&quot;I will love you forever; whatever happens. Till I die and after I die, and when I find my way out of the land of the dead, I'll drift about forever, all my atoms, till I find you again...&quot;

&quot;I'll be looking for you, Will, every moment, every single moment. And when we do find each other again, we'll cling together so tight that nothing and no one'll ever tear us apart. Every atom of me and every atom of you...We'll live in birds and flowers and dragonflies and pin trees and in clouds and in those little specks of light you see floating in sunbeams...And when they use our atoms to make new lives, they won't just be able to take one, they'll have to take two, one of you and one of me, we'll be joined so tight...&quot;

They lay side by side, hand in hand, looking at the sky." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470-it-is-a-far-far-better-thing-that-i-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2012 11:49:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470-it-is-a-far-far-better-thing-that-i-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a far, far better thing that I do, than I have ever done; it is a far, far better rest that I go to than I have ever known." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/944278-i-think-you-re-doing-better-than-you-were-the-last</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 06:59:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/944278-i-think-you-re-doing-better-than-you-were-the-last]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think you're doing better than you were the last time we saw you. You're growing a new heart, for a start." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271815-i-knew-you-read-the-symposium-in-the-vac-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 07:03:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by E. M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271815-i-knew-you-read-the-symposium-in-the-vac-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I knew you read the &lt;i&gt;Symposium&lt;/i&gt; in the vac,&quot; he said in a low voice.
Maurice felt uneasy.
&quot;Then you understand - without me saying more - &quot;
&quot;How do you mean?&quot;
Durham could not wait. People were all around them, but with eyes that had gone intensely blue he whispered, &quot;I love you." -- E. M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
