<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/124217-sean]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/124217-sean" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2012 08:31:08 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/571309-as-he-finally-sheds-his-body-s-suit--------finds-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2012 08:31:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sean add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/571309-as-he-finally-sheds-his-body-s-suit--------finds-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...as he finally sheds his body's suit, ------ finds his gut and throat again and newly whole, clean and unimpeded, free, catapulted home over fans and the Convexity's glass palisades at desperate speeds, soaring north, sounding a bell-clear and nearly maternal alarmed call-to-arms in all the world's well-known tongues." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158499-without-turning-the-pharmacist-answered-that-he-liked-books-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 07:30:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sean add a quote by Roberto Bolano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158499-without-turning-the-pharmacist-answered-that-he-liked-books-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without turning, the pharmacist answered that he liked books like The Metamorphosis, Bartleby, A Simple Heart, A Christmas Carol.  And then he said that he was reading Capote's Breakfast at Tiffany's. Leaving aside the fact that A Simple Heart and A Christmas Carol were stories, not books, there was something revelatory about the taste of this bookish young pharmacist, who ... clearly and inarguably preferred minor works to major ones.  He chose The Metamorphosis over The Trial, he chose Bartleby over Moby Dick, he chose A Simple Heart over Bouvard and Pecouchet, and A Christmas Carol over A Tale of Two Cities or The Pickwick Papers. What a sad paradox, thought Amalfitano.  Now even bookish pharmacists are afraid to take on the great, imperfect, torrential works, books that blaze a path into the unknown.  They choose the perfect exercises of the great masters.  Or what amounts to the same thing: they want to watch the great masters spar, but they have no interest in real combat, when the great masters struggle against that something, that something that terrifies us all, that something that cows us and spurs us on, amid blood and mortal wounds and stench." -- Roberto Bolano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/509187-i-don-t-have-to-tell-you-things-are-bad-everybody</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 19:27:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sean add a quote by Paddy Chayefsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/509187-i-don-t-have-to-tell-you-things-are-bad-everybody]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't have to tell you things are bad. Everybody knows things are bad. It's a depression. Everybody's out of work or scared of losing their job. The dollar buys a nickel's worth, banks are going bust, shopkeepers keep a gun under the counter. Punks are running wild in the street and there's nobody anywhere who seems to know what to do, and there's no end to it. We know the air is unfit to breathe and our food is unfit to eat, and we sit watching our TV's while some local newscaster tells us that today we had fifteen homicides and sixty-three violent crimes, as if that's the way it's supposed to be. We know things are bad - worse than bad. They're crazy. It's like everything everywhere is going crazy, so we don't go out anymore. We sit in the house, and slowly the world we are living in is getting smaller, and all we say is, 'Please, at least leave us alone in our living rooms. Let me have my toaster and my TV and my steel-belted radials and I won't say anything. Just leave us alone.' Well, I'm not gonna leave you alone. I want you to get mad! I don't want you to protest. I don't want you to riot - I don't want you to write to your congressman because I wouldn't know what to tell you to write. I don't know what to do about the depression and the inflation and the Russians and the crime in the street. All I know is that first you've got to get mad. You've got to say, 'I'm a HUMAN BEING, God damn it! My life has VALUE!' So I want you to get up now. I want all of you to get up out of your chairs. I want you to get up right now and go to the window. Open it, and stick your head out, and yell, 'I'M AS MAD AS HELL, AND I'M NOT GOING TO TAKE THIS ANYMORE!' I want you to get up right now, sit up, go to your windows, open them and stick your head out and yell - 'I'm as mad as hell and I'm not going to take this anymore!' Things have got to change. But first, you've gotta get mad!... You've got to say, 'I'm as mad as hell, and I'm not going to take this anymore!' Then we'll figure out what to do about the depression and the inflation and the oil crisis. But first get up out of your chairs, open the window, stick your head out, and yell, and say it: &quot;I'M AS MAD AS HELL, AND I'M NOT GOING TO TAKE THIS ANYMORE!" -- Paddy Chayefsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111182-i-believe-in-aristocracy-though----if-that-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:19:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sean add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111182-i-believe-in-aristocracy-though----if-that-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in aristocracy, though -- if that is the right word, and if a democrat may use it.  Not an aristocracy of power, based upon rank and influence, but an aristocracy of the sensitive, the considerate and the plucky.  Its members are to be found in all nations and classes, and all through the ages, and there is a secreat understanding between them when they meet.  They represent the true human tradition, the one permanent victory of our queer race over cruelty and chaos.  Thousands of them perish in obscurity, a few are great names.  They are sensitive for others as well as themselves, they are considerate without being fussy, their pluck is not swankiness but power to endure, and they can take a joke." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
