<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/124879-beth]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/124879-beth" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 15:52:20 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128910-i-ve-never-written-a-book-except-my-first-without-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 15:52:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Julian Barnes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128910-i-ve-never-written-a-book-except-my-first-without-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've never written a book, except my first, without at some point considering that I might die before it was completed. This is all part of the superstition, the folklore, the mania of the business, the fetishistic fuss.....Dying in the middle of a wo(rd), or three-fifths of the way through a nov(el). My friend the nov(el)ist Brian Moore used to fear this as well, though for an extra reason: &quot;Because some bastard will come along and finish it for you.&quot; Here is a novelist's would-you-rather. Would you rather die in the middle of a book, and have some bastard finish it for you, or leave behind a work in progress that not a single bastard in the whole world was remotely interested in finishing?" -- Julian Barnes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2900-oh-but-he-was-a-tight-fisted-hand-at-the-grindstone</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 16:15:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2900-oh-but-he-was-a-tight-fisted-hand-at-the-grindstone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh! But he was a tight-fisted hand at the grindstone, Scrooge! a squeezing, wrenching, grasping, scraping, clutching, covetous, old sinner! Hard and sharp as flint, from which no steel had ever struck out generous fire; secret, and self-contained, and solitary as an oyster." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/656903-one-of-the-many-things-i-love-about-bound-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 20:27:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Will Schwalbe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/656903-one-of-the-many-things-i-love-about-bound-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the many things I love about bound books is their sheer physicality. Electronic books live out of sight and out of mind. But printed books have body, presence. ... I often seek electronic books, but they never come after me. They may make me feel, but I can't feel them. They are all soul with no flesh, no texture, and no weight." -- Will Schwalbe]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
