<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/124877-georgiana]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/124877-georgiana" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2009 16:50:19 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149304-we-don-t-understand-that-life-is-heaven-for-we-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2009 16:50:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Georgiana add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149304-we-don-t-understand-that-life-is-heaven-for-we-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't understand that life is heaven, for we have only to understand that and it will at once be fulfilled in all its beauty, we shall embrace each other and weep." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149342-may-understood-people-and-she-let-them-be-whatever-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2009 23:08:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Georgiana add a quote by Cynthia Rylant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149342-may-understood-people-and-she-let-them-be-whatever-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[May] understood people and she let them be whatever way they needed to be. She had faith in every single person she ever met, and this never failed her, for nobody ever disappointed May.  Seems people knew she saw the very best of them, and they'd turn that side to her to give her a better look." -- Cynthia Rylant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480603-the-complaint-was-the-answer-to-have-heard-myself-making</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 11:39:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Georgiana add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480603-the-complaint-was-the-answer-to-have-heard-myself-making]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The complaint was the answer.  To have heard myself making it was to be answered.  Lightly men talk of saying what they mean.  Often when he was teaching me to write in Greek the Fox would say, 'Child, to say the very thing you really mean, the whole of it, nothing more or less or other than what you really mean; that's the whole art and joy of words.'

A glib saying.  When the time comes to you at which you will be forced at last to utter the speech which has lain at the center of your soul for years which you have, all that time, idiot-like, been saying over and over, you'll not talk about the joy of words. I saw well why the gods do not speak to us openly, nor let us answer.  Till that word can be dug out of us, why should they hear the babble that we think we mean?  How can they meet us face to face till we have faces?" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
