<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/124946-ambo]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/124946-ambo" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 23:53:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35446-what-about-little-microphones-what-if-everyone-swallowed-them-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 23:53:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ambo add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35446-what-about-little-microphones-what-if-everyone-swallowed-them-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What about little microphones? What if everyone swallowed them, and they played the sounds of our hearts through little speakers, which could be in the pouches of our overalls? When you skateboarded down the street at night you could hear everyone's heartbeat, and they could hear yours, sort of like sonar. One weird thing is, I wonder if everyone's hearts would start to beat at the same time, like how women who live together have their menstrual periods at the same time, which I know about, but don't really want to know about. That would be so weird, except that the place in the hospital where babies are born would sound like a crystal chandelier in a houseboat, because the babies wouldn't have had time to match up their heartbeats yet. And at the finish line at the end of the New York City Marathon it would sound like war." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83017-i-like-to-see-people-reunited-i-like-to-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 23:56:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ambo add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83017-i-like-to-see-people-reunited-i-like-to-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like to see people reunited, I like to see people run to each other, I like the kissing and the crying, I like the impatience, the stories that the mouth can't tell fast enough, the ears that aren't big enough, the eyes that can't take in all of the change, I like the hugging, the bringing together, the end of missing someone." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33121-i-took-the-world-into-me-rearranged-it-and-sent</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 23:56:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ambo add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33121-i-took-the-world-into-me-rearranged-it-and-sent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I took the world into me, rearranged it, and sent it back out as a question: &quot;Do you like me?" -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7411-i-started-inventing-things-and-then-i-couldn-t-stop-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 00:01:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ambo add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7411-i-started-inventing-things-and-then-i-couldn-t-stop-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I started inventing things, and then I couldn't stop, like beavers, which I know about. People think they cut down trees so they can build dams, but in reality it's because their teeth never stop growing, and if they didn't constantly file them down by cutting through all of those trees, their teeth would start to grow into their own faces, which would kill them. That's how my brain was." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243558-i-have-found-it-very-important-in-my-own-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2012 20:07:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ambo add a quote by Henri Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243558-i-have-found-it-very-important-in-my-own-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have found it very important in my own life to try to let go of my wishes and instead to live in hope.  I am finding that when I choose to let go of my sometimes petty and superficial wishes and trust that my life is precious and meaningful in the eyes of God something really new, something beyond my own expectations begins to happen for me. (Finding My Way Home)" -- Henri Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220542-i-kept-running-around-it-in-large-or-small-circles</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2012 20:10:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ambo add a quote by Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220542-i-kept-running-around-it-in-large-or-small-circles]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I kept running around it in large or small circles, always looking for someone or something able to convince me of my Belovedness.

Self-rejection is the greatest enemy of the spiritual life because it contradicts the sacred voice that calls us the &quot;Beloved&quot;.  Being the Beloved expresses the core truth of our existence." -- Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195757-i-wish-grace-and-healing-were-more-abracadabra-kind-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 17:51:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ambo add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195757-i-wish-grace-and-healing-were-more-abracadabra-kind-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish grace and healing were more abracadabra kind of things. Also, that delicate silver bells would ring to announce grace's arrival. But no, it's clog and slog and scootch, on the floor, in the silence, in the dark." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
