<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/125043-carrie-sleme]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/125043-carrie-sleme" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 12:14:43 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382930-they-turn-nature-into-an-achievement-course-a-series-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 12:14:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by David Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382930-they-turn-nature-into-an-achievement-course-a-series-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They turn nature into an achievement course, a series of ordeals and obstacles they can conquer. They go into nature to behave unnaturally. In nature animals flee cold and seek warmth and comfort. But Bobo naturalists flee comfort and seek cold and deprivation." -- David Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266381-everybody-is-comparing-the-oil-spill-to-hurricane-katrina-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 12:14:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by David Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266381-everybody-is-comparing-the-oil-spill-to-hurricane-katrina-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody is comparing the oil spill to Hurricane Katrina, but the real parallel could be the Iranian hostage crisis. In the late 1970s, the hostage crisis became a symbol of America's inability to take decisive action in the face of pervasive problems. In the same way, the uncontrolled oil plume could become the objective correlative of the country's inability to govern itself." -- David Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385880-we-are-primarily-the-products-of-thinking-that-happens-below</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 21:50:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by David Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385880-we-are-primarily-the-products-of-thinking-that-happens-below]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are primarily the products of thinking that happens below the level of awareness." -- David Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399722-learning-was-a-by-product-of-her-search-for-pleasure</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 21:50:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by David Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399722-learning-was-a-by-product-of-her-search-for-pleasure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Learning was a by-product of her search for pleasure" -- David Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 21:52:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The really important kind of freedom involves attention, and awareness, and discipline, and effort, and being able truly to care about other people and to sacrifice for them, over and over, in myriad petty little unsexy ways, every day." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237311-if-you-worship-money-and-things-if-they-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 21:52:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237311-if-you-worship-money-and-things-if-they-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you worship money and things — if they are where you tap real meaning in life — then you will never have enough. Never feel you have enough. It’s the truth. Worship your own body and beauty and sexual allure and you will always feel ugly, and when time and age start showing, you will die a million deaths before they finally plant you. On one level, we all know this stuff already — it’s been codified as myths, proverbs, clichés, bromides, epigrams, parables: the skeleton of every great story. The trick is keeping the truth up-front in daily consciousness. Worship power — you will feel weak and afraid, and you will need ever more power over others to keep the fear at bay. Worship your intellect, being seen as smart — you will end up feeling stupid, a fraud, always on the verge of being found out. And so on." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392771-learning-how-to-think-really-means-learning-how-to-exercise</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 21:53:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392771-learning-how-to-think-really-means-learning-how-to-exercise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Learning how to think&quot; really means learning how to exercise some control over how and what you think.
It means being conscious and aware enough to choose what you pay attention to and to choose how you construct meaning from experience.
Because if you cannot or will not exercise this kind of choice in adult life, you will be totally hosed." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/379173-most-enjoyable-activities-are-not-natural-they-demand-an-effort</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 21:55:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/379173-most-enjoyable-activities-are-not-natural-they-demand-an-effort]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most enjoyable activities are not natural; they demand an effort that initially one is reluctant to make. But once the interaction starts to provide feedback to the person's skills, it usually begins to be intrinsically rewarding." -- Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/660992-few-things-are-sadder-than-encountering-a-person-who-knows</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 21:55:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/660992-few-things-are-sadder-than-encountering-a-person-who-knows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Few things are sadder than encountering a person who knows exactly what he should do, yet cannot muster enough energy to do it. &quot;He who desires but acts not,&quot; wrote Blake with his accustomed vigor, &quot;Breeds pestilence." -- Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/439996-who-are-we-to-say-getting-incested-or-abused-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 21:57:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/439996-who-are-we-to-say-getting-incested-or-abused-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who are we to say getting incested or abused or violated or any of those things can’t have their positive aspects in the long run? … You have to be careful of taking a knee-jerk attitude. Having a knee-jerk attitude to anything is a mistake, especially in the case of women, where it adds up to this very limited and condescending thing of saying they’re fragile, breakable things that can be destroyed easily. Everybody gets hurt and violated and broken sometimes. Why are women so special? Not that anybody ought to be raped or abused, nobody’s saying that, but that’s what is going on. What about afterwards? All I’m saying is there are certain cases where it can enlarge you or make you more of a complete human being, like Viktor Frankl. Think about the Holocaust. Was the Holocaust a good thing? No way. Does anybody think it was good that it happened? No, of course not. But did you read Viktor Frankl? Viktor Frankl’s Man’s Search for Meaning? It’s a great, great book, but it comes out of his experience. It’s about his experience in the human dark side. Now think about it, if there was no Holocaust, there’d be no Man’s Search for Meaning… . Think about it. Think about being degraded and brought within an inch of your life, for example. No one’s gonna say the sick bastards who did it shouldn’t be put in jail, but let’s put two things into perspective here. One is, afterwards she knows something about herself that she never knew before. What she knows is that the most totally terrible terrifying thing that she could ever have imagined happening to her has now happened, and she survived. She’s still here, and now she knows something. I mean she really, really knows. Look, totally terrible things happen… . Existence in life breaks people in all kinds of awful fucking ways all the time, trust me I know. I’ve been there. And this is the big difference, you and me here, cause this isn’t about politics or feminism or whatever, for you this is just ideas, you’ve never been there. I’m not saying nothing bad has ever happened to you, you’re not bad looking, I’m sure there’s been some sort of degradation or whatever come your way in life, but I’m talking Viktor Frankl’s Man’s Search for Meaning type violation and terror and suffering here. The real dark side. I can tell from just looking at you, you never. You wouldn’t even wear what you’re wearing, trust me.
 What if I told you it was my own sister that was raped? What if I told you a little story about a sixteen-year-old girl who went to the wrong party with the wrong guy and four of his buddies that ended up doing to her just about everything four guys could do to you in terms of violation? But if you could ask her if she could go into her head and forget it or like erase the tape of it happening in her memory, what do you think she’d say? Are you so sure what she’d say? What if she said that even after that totally negative as what happened was, at least now she understood it was possible. People can. Can see you as a thing. That people can see you as a thing, do you know what that means? Because if you really can see someone as a thing you can do anything to him. What would it be like to be able to be like that? You see, you think you can imagine it but you can’t. But she can. And now she knows something. I mean she really, really knows.
 This is what you wanted to hear, you wanted to hear about four drunk guys who knee-jerk you in the balls and make you bend over that you didn’t even know, that you never saw before, that you never did anything to, that don’t even know your name, they don’t even know your name to find out you have to choose to have a fucking name, you have no fucking idea, and what if I said that happened to ME? Would that make a difference?" -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620930-there-s-been-time-this-whole-time-you-can-t-kill-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 22:00:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620930-there-s-been-time-this-whole-time-you-can-t-kill-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There’s been time this whole time. You can’t kill time with your heart. Everything takes time." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83017-i-like-to-see-people-reunited-i-like-to-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 22:06:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83017-i-like-to-see-people-reunited-i-like-to-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like to see people reunited, I like to see people run to each other, I like the kissing and the crying, I like the impatience, the stories that the mouth can't tell fast enough, the ears that aren't big enough, the eyes that can't take in all of the change, I like the hugging, the bringing together, the end of missing someone." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105921-i-feel-too-much-that-s-what-s-going-on-do-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 22:07:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105921-i-feel-too-much-that-s-what-s-going-on-do-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I feel too much.  That's what's going on.'  'Do you think one can feel too much?  Or just feel in the wrong ways?'  'My insides don't match up with my outsides.'  'Do anyone's insides and outsides match up?'  'I don't know.  I'm only me.'  'Maybe that's what a person's personality is: the difference between the inside and outside.'  'But it's worse for me.'  'I wonder if everyone thinks it's worse for him.'  'Probably.  But it really is worse for me." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/575922-art-is-not-as-the-metaphysicians-say-the-manifestation-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 13:53:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/575922-art-is-not-as-the-metaphysicians-say-the-manifestation-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Art is not, as the metaphysicians say, the manifestation of some mysterious idea of beauty or God; it is not, as the aesthetical physiologists say, a game in which man lets off his excess of stored-up energy; it is not the expression of man's emotions by external signs; it is not the production of pleasing objects; and, above all, it is not pleasure; but it is a means of union among men, joining them together in the same feelings, and indispensable for the life and progress toward well-being of individuals and of humanity." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/538103-to-talk-about-paintings-is-not-only-difficult-but-perhaps</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 14:33:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Gerhard Richter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/538103-to-talk-about-paintings-is-not-only-difficult-but-perhaps]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To talk about paintings is not only difficult but perhaps pointless too. You can only express in words what words are capable of expressing-- what language can communicate. Painting has nothing to do with that." -- Gerhard Richter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406564-when-it-first-emerged-twitter-was-widely-derided-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 14:32:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Steven Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406564-when-it-first-emerged-twitter-was-widely-derided-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When it first emerged, Twitter was widely derided as a frivolous distraction that was mostly good for telling your friends what you had for breakfast. Now it is being used to organize and share news about the Iranian political protests, to provide customer support for large corporations, to share interesting news items, and a thousand other applications that did not occur to the founders when they dreamed up the service in 2006. This is not just a case of cultural exaptation: people finding a new use for a tool designed to do something else. In Twitter's case, the users have been redesigning the tool itself. The convention of replying to another user with the @ symbol was spontaneously invented by the Twitter user base. Early Twitter users ported over a convention from the IRC messaging platform and began grouping a topic or event by the &quot;hash-tag&quot; as in &quot;#30Rock&quot; or &quot;inauguration.&quot; The ability to search a live stream of tweets - which is likely to prove crucial to Twitter's ultimate business model, thanks to its advertising potential - was developed by another start-up altogether. Thanks to these innovations, following a live feed of tweets about an event - political debates or Lost episodes - has become a central part of the Twitter experience. But for the first year of Twitter's existence, that mode of interaction would have been technically impossible using Twitter. It's like inventing a toaster oven and then looking around a year later and discovering that all your customers have, on their own, figured out a way to turn it into a microwave." -- Steven Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367265-the-patterns-are-simple-but-followed-together-they-make-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 14:34:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Steven Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367265-the-patterns-are-simple-but-followed-together-they-make-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The patterns are simple, but followed together, they make for a whole that is wiser than the sum of its parts.  Go for a walk; cultivate hunches; write everything down, but keep your folders messy; embrace serendipity; make generative mistakes; take on multiple hobbies; frequent coffeehouses and other liquid networks; follow the links; let others build on your ideas; borrow, recycle; reinvent.  Build a tangled bank." -- Steven Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/388161-chance-favors-the-connected-mind</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 14:37:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Steven Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/388161-chance-favors-the-connected-mind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chance favors the connected mind." -- Steven Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169959-justice-to-be-ever-ready-to-admit-that-another-person</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2013 21:58:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Simone Weil]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169959-justice-to-be-ever-ready-to-admit-that-another-person]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Justice. To be ever ready to admit that another person is something quite different from what we read when he is there (or when we think about him). Or rather, to read in him that he is certainly something different, perhaps something completely different from what we read in him.
Every being cries out silently to be read differently." -- Simone Weil]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/705505-the-man-who-has-known-pure-joy-if-only-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2013 22:01:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Simone Weil]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/705505-the-man-who-has-known-pure-joy-if-only-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who has known pure joy, if only for a moment ... is the only man for whom affliction is something devastating. At the same time he is the only man who has not deserved the punishment. But, after all, for him it is no punishment; it is God holding his hand and pressing rather hard. For, if he remains constant, what he will discover buried deep under the sound of his own lamentations is the pearl of the silence of God." -- Simone Weil]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/672746-compassion-constitutes-a-radical-form-of-criticism-for-it-announces</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2013 10:02:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Walter Brueggemann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/672746-compassion-constitutes-a-radical-form-of-criticism-for-it-announces]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Compassion constitutes a radical form of criticism, for it announces that the hurt is to be taken seriously, that the hurt is not to be accepted as normal and natural but is an abnormal and unacceptable condition for humanness." -- Walter Brueggemann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/615469-the-christian-leader-of-the-future-is-called-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 18:11:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/615469-the-christian-leader-of-the-future-is-called-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Christian leader of the future is called to be completely irrelevant and to stand in this world with nothing to offer but his or her own vulnerable self." -- Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/648303-who-knows-what-i-want-to-do-who-knows-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 15:40:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/648303-who-knows-what-i-want-to-do-who-knows-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who knows what I want to do? Who knows what anyone wants to do? How can you be sure about something like that? Isn't it all a question of brain chemistry, signals going back and forth, electrical energy in the cortex? How do you know whether something is really what you want to do or just some kind of nerve impulse in the brain? Some minor little activity takes place somewhere in this unimportant place in one of the brain hemispheres and suddenly I want to go to Montana or I don't want to go to Montana. How do I know I really want to go and it isn't just some neurons firing or something? Maybe it's just an accidental flash in the medulla and suddenly there I am in Montana and I find out I really didn't want to go there in the first place. I can't control what happens in my brain, so how can I be sure what I want to do ten seconds from now, much less Montana next summer? It's all this activity in the brain and you don't know what's you as a person and what's some neuron that just happens to fire or just happens to misfire." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541239-we-drove-22-miles-into-the-country-around-farmington-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 15:43:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541239-we-drove-22-miles-into-the-country-around-farmington-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We drove 22 miles into the country around Farmington.  There were meadows and apple orchards.  White fences trailed through the rolling fields.  Soon the sign started appearing.  THE MOST PHOTOGRAPHED BARN IN AMERICA.  We counted five signs before we reached the site.  There were 40 cars and a tour bus in the makeshift lot.  We walked along a cowpath to the slightly elevated spot set aside for viewing and photographing.  All the people had cameras; some had tripods, telephoto lenses, filter kits.  A man in a booth sold postcards and slides -- pictures of the barn taken from the elevated spot.  We stood near a grove of trees and watched the photographers.  Murray maintained a prolonged silence, occasionally scrawling some notes in a little book. 

&quot;No one sees the barn,&quot; he said finally. 

A long silence followed. 

&quot;Once you've seen the signs about the barn, it becomes impossible to see the barn.&quot;

He fell silent once more.  People with cameras left the elevated site, replaced by others.

We're not here to capture an image, we're here to maintain one. Every photograph reinforces the aura.  Can you feel it, Jack? An accumulation of nameless energies.&quot; 

There was an extended silence.  The man in the booth sold postcards and slides. 

&quot;Being here is a kind of spiritual surrender.  We see only what the others see.  The thousands who were here in the past, those who will come in the future.  We've agreed to be part of a collective perception.  It literally colors our vision.  A religious experience in a way, like all tourism.&quot; 

Another silence ensued. 

&quot;They are taking pictures of taking pictures,&quot; he said." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214230-and-he-wishes-in-the-cold-quiet-of-his-archer-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 19:11:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214230-and-he-wishes-in-the-cold-quiet-of-his-archer-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And he wishes, in the cold quiet of his archer's heart, that he himself could feel the intensity of their reconciliations as strongly as he feels that of their battles." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
