<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/125300-beth]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/125300-beth" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 20:54:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410837-yet-i-m-sure-there-s-something-more-to-be-read-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 20:54:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by André Gide]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410837-yet-i-m-sure-there-s-something-more-to-be-read-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yet I'm sure there's something more to be read in a man. People dare not -- they dare not turn the page. The laws of mimicry -- I call them the laws of fear. People are afraid to find themselves alone, and don't find themselves at all. I hate this moral agoraphobia -- it's the worst kind of cowardice. You can't create something without being alone. But who's trying to create here? What seems different in yourself: that's the one rare thing you possess, the one thing which gives each of us his worth; and that's just what we try to suppress. We imitate. And we claim to love life." -- André Gide]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170602-nothing-is-ever-perfect-it-is-what-you-make-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2009 07:59:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Emily Giffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170602-nothing-is-ever-perfect-it-is-what-you-make-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing is ever perfect. It is what you make of it." -- Emily Giffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170622-his-words-are-like-the-sound-of-a-needle-dragging</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2009 08:54:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Emily Giffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170622-his-words-are-like-the-sound-of-a-needle-dragging]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His words are like the sound of a needle dragging across a record. A sinking, sickening feeling washes over me. This is why you should never, ever get your hopes up. This is why you should see the glass as half empty. So, when the whole things spills, you aren't as devastated." -- Emily Giffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410834-i-cannot-apply-myself-to-the-distinctions-and-the-reservations</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 20:50:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Andre Gide]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410834-i-cannot-apply-myself-to-the-distinctions-and-the-reservations]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot apply myself to the distinctions and the reservations they insist on making -- I exist only as a whole man. I lay claim to nothing but my own nature, and the pleasure I take in an action is my clue to its propriety." -- Andre Gide]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170660-songs-and-smells-will-bring-you-back-to-a-moment</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 20:50:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Emily Giffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170660-songs-and-smells-will-bring-you-back-to-a-moment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Songs and smells will bring you back to a moment in time more than anything else. It's amazing how much can be conjured with a few notes of a song or a solitary whiff of a room. A song you didn't even pay attention to at the time, a place that you didn't even know had a particular smell. I wonder what will someday bring back Dex and our few months together. Maybe the sound of Dido's voice. Maybe the scent of the Aveda shampoo I've been using all summer." -- Emily Giffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170664-but-i-have-learned-that-you-make-your-own-happiness</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 20:50:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Emily Giffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170664-but-i-have-learned-that-you-make-your-own-happiness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I have learned that you make your own happiness, that part of going for what you want means losing something else. And when the stakes are high, the losses can be that much greater." -- Emily Giffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170975-anxiety-was-not-an-emotion-i-could-ever-remember-feeling</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 20:50:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Emily Giffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170975-anxiety-was-not-an-emotion-i-could-ever-remember-feeling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anxiety was not an emotion I could ever remember feeling when I went out in New York, and I wondered why tonight felt so different. Maybe it was because I no longer had a boyfriend or fiance. I suddenly recognized that there was safety in having someone, as well as a lack of pressure to shine. Ironically, this had cultivated a certain free-spiritedness that had, in turn, allowed me to be the life of the party and hoard the affection of additional men....But that had all changed. I didn't have a boyfriend, a perfect figure, or alcohol-induced outrageousness to fall back on." -- Emily Giffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170994-love-and-friendship-they-are-what-make-us-who-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 20:50:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Emily Giffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170994-love-and-friendship-they-are-what-make-us-who-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love and friendship. They are what make us who we are, and what can change us, if we let them." -- Emily Giffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410838-if-there-s-one-thing-i-detest-it-s-a-man-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 20:55:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Andre Gide]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410838-if-there-s-one-thing-i-detest-it-s-a-man-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there's one thing I detest it's a man of principles." -- Andre Gide]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629045-third-there-is-the-new-york-of-the-person-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 20:08:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629045-third-there-is-the-new-york-of-the-person-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Third, there is the New York of the person who was born somewhere else and came to New York in quest of something. Of these three trembling cities the greatest is the last--the city of final destination, the city that is a goal. It is this third city that accounts for New York's high-strung disposition, its poetical deportment, its dedication to the arts, and its incomparable achievements. Commuters give the city its tidal restlessness; natives give it solidity and continuity; but the settlers give it passion." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629048-a-poem-compresses-much-in-a-small-space-and-adds</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 20:11:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629048-a-poem-compresses-much-in-a-small-space-and-adds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A poem compresses much in a small space and adds music, thus heightening its meaning. The city is like poetry: it compresses all life, all races and breeds, into a small island and adds music and the accompaniment of internal engines. The island of Manhattan is without any doubt the greatest human concentrate on earth, the poem whose magic is comprehensible to millions of permanent residents but whose full meaning will always remain elusive." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512610-i-began-to-like-new-york-the-racy-adventurous-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2013 20:32:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512610-i-began-to-like-new-york-the-racy-adventurous-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I began to like New York, the racy, adventurous feel of it at night, and the satisfaction that the constant flicker of men and women and machines gives to the restless eye." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
