<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/125642-dan-weaver]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/125642-dan-weaver" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 09:16:12 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65109-my-life-is-a-rather-grim-one-one-day-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 09:16:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by John Kennedy Toole]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65109-my-life-is-a-rather-grim-one-one-day-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My life is a rather grim one. One day I shall perhaps describe it to you in great detail." -- John Kennedy Toole]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233667-between-notes-he-had-contemplated-means-of-destroying-myrna-minkoff</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 09:18:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by John Kennedy Toole]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233667-between-notes-he-had-contemplated-means-of-destroying-myrna-minkoff]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Between notes, he had contemplated means of destroying Myrna Minkoff but had reached no satisfactory conclusion. His most promising scheme had involved getting a book on munitions from the library, constructing a bomb, and mailing it in plain paper to Myrna. Then he remembered that his library card had been revoked." -- John Kennedy Toole]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31911-mornings-out-in-the-garden-she-would-at-times-read</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 12:05:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by Joy Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31911-mornings-out-in-the-garden-she-would-at-times-read]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mornings, out in the garden, she would, at times, read aloud from one of her many overdue library books. Dew as radiant as angel spit glittered on the petals of Jack's roses. Jack was quite the gardener. Miriam thought she knew why her particularly favored roses. The inside of a rose does not at all correspond with its exterior beauty. If one tears off all the petals of the corolla, all that remains is a sordid-looking tuft. Roses would be right up Jack's alley, all right.

&quot;Here's something for you, Jack,&quot; Miriam said. You'll appreciate this. Beckett describes tears as 'liquified brain.'

&quot;God, Miriam,&quot; Jack said. &quot;Why are you sharing that with me? Look at this day, it's a beautiful day! Stop pumping out the cesspit! Leave the cesspit alone!" -- Joy Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256777-from-the-line-watching-three-things-are-striking-a-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 06:18:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256777-from-the-line-watching-three-things-are-striking-a-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From the line, watching, three things are striking: (a) what on TV is a brisk crack is here a whooming roar that apparently is what a shotgun really sounds like; (b) trapshooting looks comparatively easy, because now the stocky older guy who's replaced the trim bearded guy at the rail is also blowing these little fluorescent plates away one after the other, so that a steady rain of lumpy orange crud is falling into the Nadir's wake; (c) a clay pigeon, when shot, undergoes a frighteningly familiar-looking midflight peripeteia -- erupting material, changing vector, and plummeting seaward in a corkscrewy way that all eerily recalls footage of the 1986 Challenger disaster.

All the shooters who precede me seem to fire with a kind of casual scorn, and all get eight out of ten or above. But it turns out that, of these six guys, three have military-combat backgrounds, another two are L. L. Bean-model-type brothers who spend weeks every year hunting various fast-flying species with their &quot;Papa&quot; in southern Canada, and the last has got not only his own earmuffs, plus his own shotgun in a special crushed-velvet-lined case, but also his own trapshooting range in his backyard (31) in North Carolina. When it's finally my turn, the earmuffs they give me have somebody else's ear-oil on them and don't fit my head very well. The gun itself is shockingly heavy and stinks of what I'm told is cordite, small pubic spirals of which are still exiting the barrel from the Korea-vet who preceded me and is tied for first with 10/10. The two brothers are the only entrants even near my age; both got scores of 9/10 and are now appraising me coolly from identical prep-school-slouch positions against the starboard rail. The Greek NCOs seem extremely bored. I am handed the heavy gun and told to &quot;be bracing a hip&quot; against the aft rail and then to place the stock of the weapon against, no, not the shoulder of my hold-the-gun arm but the shoulder of my pull-the-trigger arm. (My initial error in this latter regard results in a severely distorted aim that makes the Greek by the catapult do a rather neat drop-and-roll.) 

Let's not spend a lot of time drawing this whole incident out. Let me simply say that, yes, my own trapshooting score was noticeably lower than the other entrants' scores, then simply make a few disinterested observations for the benefit of any novice contemplating trapshooting from a 7NC Megaship, and then we'll move on: (1) A certain level of displayed ineptitude with a firearm will cause everyone who knows anything about firearms to converge on you all at the same time with cautions and advice and handy tips. (2) A lot of the advice in (1) boils down to exhortations to &quot;lead&quot; the launched pigeon, but nobody explains whether this means that the gun's barrel should move across the sky with the pigeon or should instead sort of lie in static ambush along some point in the pigeon's projected path. (3) Whatever a &quot;hair trigger&quot; is, a shotgun does not have one. (4) If you've never fired a gun before, the urge to close your eyes at the precise moment of concussion is, for all practical purposes, irresistible. (5) The well-known &quot;kick&quot; of a fired shotgun is no misnomer; it knocks you back several steps with your arms pinwheeling wildly for balance, which when you're holding a still-loaded gun results in mass screaming and ducking and then on the next shot a conspicuous thinning of the crowd in the 9-Aft gallery above. Finally, (6), know that an unshot discus's movement against the vast lapis lazuli dome of the open ocean's sky is sun-like -- i.e., orange and parabolic and right-to-left -- and that its disappearance into the sea is edge-first and splashless and sad." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
