<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/125896-shane]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/125896-shane" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 08:50:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/597940-now-i-see-in-that-laughter-a-good-deal-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 08:50:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Frederick Exley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/597940-now-i-see-in-that-laughter-a-good-deal-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now I see in that laughter a good deal of desperation and sadness. About to leave the haven of our separate universities and be thrown out onto the brutal free-spinning of the world, as we walked arm in arm through the snow, we carried with us, if only unconsciously, the knowledge that it would be our last holiday together; and we drank and laughed and sneered with the resolute sadness of men who knew that tomorrow we'd be trying to free our own mortgaged Buicks from our own snowlocked drives. That is what most of us ended up doing. I didn't; but I don't question that my friends were right and I wrong, that they were happy and I not, that theirs was the hard and mine the easy way. What always saddened me on confronting them was the surety that had I been foolish enough to bring up &quot;old times,&quot; none would have allowed himself a memory of sticking his finger into the vaporous and flaky air and shouting, &quot;Shovel, you f*cking dummies!&quot; A self-destructively romantic man, I accepted our jeering defiance as a pact; forever." -- Frederick Exley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/588984-at-twelve-o-clock-when-aureli-ano-jos-had-bled-to-death</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 08:50:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Gabriel Garcí­a Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/588984-at-twelve-o-clock-when-aureli-ano-jos-had-bled-to-death]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At twelve o’clock, when Aureli-ano, José had bled to death and Carmelita Montiel found that the cards showing her future were blank, more than four hundred men had filed past the theater and discharged their revolvers into the abandoned body of Captain Aquiles Ricardo. A patrol had to use a wheelbarrow to carry the body, which was heavy with lead and fell apart like a water-soaked loaf of bread." -- Gabriel Garcí­a Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/588977-then-i-heard-footsteps-on-a-stairs-and-in-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 08:50:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/588977-then-i-heard-footsteps-on-a-stairs-and-in-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then I heard footsteps on a stairs, and in a moment the thickish figure of a woman blocked out the light from the office door. She was in the middle thirties, and faintly stout, but she carried her surplus flesh sensuously as some women can. Her face, above a spotted dress of dark blue crepe-de-chine, contained no facet or gleam of beauty, but there was an immediately perceptible vitality about her as if the nerves of her body were continually smouldering. She smiled slowly and, walking through her husband as if he were a ghost, shook hands with Tom, looking him flush in the eye. Then she wet her lips, and without turning around spoke to her husband in a soft, coarse voice: “Get some chairs, why don‟t you, so somebody can sit down." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/588990-i-darted-like-a-minnow-through-passers-by-in-a-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 08:50:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/588990-i-darted-like-a-minnow-through-passers-by-in-a-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I darted like a minnow through passers-by, in a most ungraceful fashion, constantly giving way to generals. officers of the Horse Guards and the Hussars, and fine ladies; at those moments I felt a spasmodic pain in my heart and hot flushes down my spine at the thought of the wretched inadequacy of my costume and the mean vulgarity of my small figure darting about." -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/588999-a-true-war-story-is-never-moral-it-does-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 08:50:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Tim O'Brien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/588999-a-true-war-story-is-never-moral-it-does-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A true war story is never moral. It does not instruct, nor encourage virtue, nor suggest models of proper human behavior, nor restrain men from doing the things they have always done. If a story seems moral, do not believe it. If at the end of a war story you feel uplifted, or if you feel that some small bit of rectitude has been salvaged from the larger waste, then you have been made a victim of a very old and terrible lie. There is no rectitude whatsoever. There is no virtue. As a first rule of thumb, therefore, you can tell a true war story by its absolute and uncompromising allegiance to obscenity and evil. Listen to Rat Kiley. Cooze, he says. He does not say bitch. He certainly does not say woman, or girl. He says cooze. Then he spits and stares. He’s nineteen years old — it’s too much for him — so he looks at you with those big sad gentle killer eyes and says cooze, because his friend is dead, and because it’s so incredibly sad and true: she never wrote back.

You can tell a true war story if it embarrasses you. If you don’t care for obscenity, you don’t care for the truth; if you don’t care for the truth, watch how you vote. Send guys to war, they come home talking dirty. Listen to Rat: “Jesus Christ, man, I write this beautiful fuckin’ letter, I slave over it, and what happens? The dumb cooze never writes back." -- Tim O'Brien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/589002-there-was-of-course-nowhere-better-in-the-world-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 08:50:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/589002-there-was-of-course-nowhere-better-in-the-world-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was, of course, nowhere better in the world to be than New York City. This fact was the foundation of her family's satisfaction with itself, the platform from which all else could be ridiculed, the collateral of adult sophistication that bought them the right to behave like children." -- Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
