<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/126266-geoff]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/126266-geoff" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 06:51:32 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140046-ascend-beyond-the-sickly-atmosphere-to-a-higher-plane-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 06:51:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Charles Baudelaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140046-ascend-beyond-the-sickly-atmosphere-to-a-higher-plane-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ascend beyond the sickly atmosphere
to a higher plane, and purify yourself
by drinking as if it were ambrosia
the fire that fills and fuels Emptiness.

Free from the futile strivings and the cares
which dim existence to a realm of mist,
happy is he who wings an upward way
on mighty pinions to the fields of light;

whose thoughts like larks spontaneously rise
into the morning sky; whose flight, unchecked,
outreaches life and readily comprehends
the language of flowers and of all mute things." -- Charles Baudelaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162555-over-and-above-the-various-prejudices-i-acknowledge-the-affinities</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 05:23:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Andre Breton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162555-over-and-above-the-various-prejudices-i-acknowledge-the-affinities]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Over and above the various prejudices I acknowledge, the affinities I feel, the attractions I succumb to, the events which occur to me and to me alone- over and above a sum of movements I am conscious of making, of emotions I alone experience- I strive, in relation to other men, to discover the nature, if not the necessity, of my difference from them.  Is it not precisely to the degree I become conscious of this difference that I shall recognize what I alone have been put on this earth to do, what unique message I alone may bear, so that I alone can answer for its fate?" -- Andre Breton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162558-i-am-the-saint-at-prayer-on-the-terrace-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 05:24:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by RIMBAUD]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162558-i-am-the-saint-at-prayer-on-the-terrace-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the saint at prayer on the terrace like the peaceful beasts that graze down to the sea of Palestine.

I am the scholar of the dark armchair.  Branches and rain hurl themselves at the windows of my library.

I am the pedestrian of the highroad by way of the dwarf woods; the roar of the sluices drowns my steps.  I can see for a long time the melancholy wash of the setting sun.

I might well be the child abandoned on the jetty on its way to the high seas, the little farm boy following the lane, its forehead touching the sky.

The paths are rough.  The hillocks are covered with broom.  The air is motionless.  How far away are the birds and the springs!  It can only be the end of the world ahead." -- RIMBAUD]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197942-we-all-have-to-die-a-bit-every-now-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 16:16:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197942-we-all-have-to-die-a-bit-every-now-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all have to die a bit every now and then and usually it's so gradual that we end up more alive than ever.  Infinitely old and infinitely alive." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235263-walkin-through-the-leaves-fallin-from-the-trees-feelin-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 17:08:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Bob Dylan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235263-walkin-through-the-leaves-fallin-from-the-trees-feelin-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Walkin' through the leaves fallin' from the trees, Feelin' like a stranger nobody sees..." -- Bob Dylan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248355-what-is-life-thoughts-and-feelings-arise-with-or-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 16:50:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Percy Bysshe Shelley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248355-what-is-life-thoughts-and-feelings-arise-with-or-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is life?  Thoughts and feelings arise, with or without our will, and we employ words to express them.  We are born, and our birth is unremembered and our infancy remembered but in fragments.  We live on, and in living we lose the apprehension of life.  How vain is it to think that words can penetrate the mystery of our being.  Rightly used they may make evident our ignorance of ourselves, and this is much." -- Percy Bysshe Shelley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156503-anyone-who-cannot-cope-with-life-while-he-is-alive</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2010 16:38:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156503-anyone-who-cannot-cope-with-life-while-he-is-alive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who cannot cope with life while he is alive needs one hand to ward off a little his despair over his fate...but with his other hand he can jot down what he sees among the ruins, for he sees different and more things than the others; after all, he is dead in his own lifetime and the real survivor." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/262764-it-is-this-admirable-this-immortal-instinctive-sense-of-beauty</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 06:15:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Charles Baudelaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/262764-it-is-this-admirable-this-immortal-instinctive-sense-of-beauty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is this admirable, this immortal, instinctive sense of beauty that leads us to look upon the spectacle of this world as a glimpse, a correspondence with heaven.  Our unquenchable thirst for all that lies beyond, and that life reveals, is the liveliest proof of our immortality.  It is both by poetry and through poetry, by music and through music, that the soul dimly descries the splendours beyond the tomb; and when an exquisite poem brings tears to our eyes, those tears are not a proof of overabundant joy:  they bear witness rather to an impatient melancholy, a clamant demand by our nerves, our nature, exiled in imperfection, which would fain enter into immediate possession, while still on this earth, of a revealed paradise." -- Charles Baudelaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265059-it-s-an-abominable-fallacy-that-suffering-makes-for-greater-art</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 02:43:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Joseph Brodsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265059-it-s-an-abominable-fallacy-that-suffering-makes-for-greater-art]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's an abominable fallacy that suffering makes for greater art.  Suffering blinds, deafens, ruins, and often kills.  Osip Mandelstam was a great poet &lt;i&gt;before&lt;/i&gt; the revolution.  So was Anna Akhmatova, so was Marina Tsvetaeva.  They would have become what they became even if none of the historical events that befell Russia in this century had taken place:  because they were &lt;i&gt;gifted&lt;/i&gt;.  Basically, talent doesn't need history." -- Joseph Brodsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2946-the-true-paradises-are-the-paradises-that-we-have-lost</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 10:03:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2946-the-true-paradises-are-the-paradises-that-we-have-lost]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The true paradises are the paradises that we have lost." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300638-devotees-who-say-that-la-recherche-du-temps-perdu</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 20:38:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Clive James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300638-devotees-who-say-that-la-recherche-du-temps-perdu]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Devotees who say that &lt;i&gt;À la recherche du temps perdu&lt;/i&gt; reminds them of a cathedral should be asked which cathedral they mean.  It reminds me of a sandcastle that the tide reached before its obsessed constructor could finish it; but he knew that would happen, or else why build it on a beach?" -- Clive James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155686-a-raznochinets-needs-no-memory-it-is-enough-for-him-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 03:20:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Osip Mandelstam]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155686-a-raznochinets-needs-no-memory-it-is-enough-for-him-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A  raznochinets needs no memory—it is enough for him to tell of the books he has read, and his biography is done." -- Osip Mandelstam]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181294-my-congratulations-to-you-sir-your-manuscript-is-both-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 12:43:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Samuel Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181294-my-congratulations-to-you-sir-your-manuscript-is-both-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My congratulations to you, sir. Your manuscript is both good and original; but the part that is good is not original, and the part that is original is not good. " -- Samuel Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325842-in-the-end-like-the-almighty-himself-we-make-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 17:10:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Joseph Brodsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325842-in-the-end-like-the-almighty-himself-we-make-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the end, like the Almighty Himself, we make everything in our image, for want of a more reliable model; our artifacts tell more about ourselves than our confessions." -- Joseph Brodsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334829-he-whose-sensitive-heart-grasps-the-sufferings-of-petrarch-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 08:14:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by M.N. Muravyov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334829-he-whose-sensitive-heart-grasps-the-sufferings-of-petrarch-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He whose sensitive heart grasps the sufferings of Petrarch and shares the majestic sorrow of Phaedra and Dido, whose soul soars skyward at striking descriptions by Corneille or fantastical scenes from Shakespeare, he who admires Lomonosov, the beauty of a poem, or the composition of a painting, is not capable of founding his own happiness on the misfortunes of others." -- M.N. Muravyov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53773-the-inferno-of-the-living-is-not-something-that-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 08:22:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53773-the-inferno-of-the-living-is-not-something-that-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The inferno of the living is not something that will be; if there is one, it is what is already here, the inferno where we live every day, that we form by being together. There are two ways to escape suffering it. The first is easy for many: accept the inferno and become such a part of it that you can no longer see it. The second is risky and demands constant vigilance and apprehension: seek and learn to recognize who and what, in the midst of inferno, are not inferno, then make them endure, give them space." -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/373833-but-sitting-here-beside-this-girl-as-unknown-to-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 08:39:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/373833-but-sitting-here-beside-this-girl-as-unknown-to-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But sitting here beside this girl as unknown to him now as outer space, waiting for whatever she might say to unfreeze him, now he felt like he could see the edge or outline of what a real vision of hell might be.  It was of two great and terrible armies within himself, opposed and facing each other, silent.  There would be battle but no victor.  Or never a battle- the armies would stay like that, motionless, looking across at each other and seeing therein something so different and alien from themselves that they could not understand, they could not hear each other's speech as even words or read anything from what their faces looked like, frozen like that, opposed and uncomprehending, for all human time.  Two hearted, a hypocrite to yourself either way." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394820-like-all-who-are-impassioned-i-take-blissful-delight-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 17:59:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394820-like-all-who-are-impassioned-i-take-blissful-delight-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like all who are impassioned, I take blissful delight in losing myself, in fully experiencing the thrill of surrender.  And so I often write with no desire to think, in an externalized reverie, letting the words cuddle me like a baby in their arms.  They form sentences with no meaning, flowing softly like water I can feel, a forgetful stream whose ripples mingle and undefine, becoming other, still other ripples, and still again other.  Thus ideas and images, throbbing with expressiveness, pass through me in resounding processions of pale silks on which imagination shimmers like moonlight, dappled and indefinite." -- Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408606-if-one-s-fated-to-be-born-in-caesar-s-empire-let</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 08:01:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Joseph Brodsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408606-if-one-s-fated-to-be-born-in-caesar-s-empire-let]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If one's fated to be born in Caesar's Empire, let him live aloof, provincial, by the seashore..." -- Joseph Brodsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/496-know-what-it-is-to-be-a-child-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 10:08:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Percy Bysshe Shelley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/496-know-what-it-is-to-be-a-child-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Know what it is to be a child? It is to be something very different from the man of today. It is to have a spirit yet streaming from the waters of Baptism; it is to believe in belief; it is to be so little that elves can reach to whisper in your ear; it is to turn pumpkins into coaches, and mice into horses, lowness into loftiness, and nothing into everything, for each child had its fairy godmother in its soul." -- Percy Bysshe Shelley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/421039-all-things-of-the-body-stream-away-like-a-river</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 08:11:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/421039-all-things-of-the-body-stream-away-like-a-river]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All things of the body stream away like a river, all things of the mind are dreams and delusion; life is warfare, and a visit to a strange land; the only lasting fame is oblivion." -- Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492328-i-wanted-to-speak-with-someone-but-found-no-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 08:01:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Robert Walser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492328-i-wanted-to-speak-with-someone-but-found-no-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted to speak with someone, but found no time; sought some fixed point, but found none. In the midst of the unrelenting forward thrust I felt the wish to stand still. The muchness and the motion were too much and too fast. Everyone withdrew from everyone. There was a running, as of something liquefied, a constant going forth, as of evaporation. Everything was schematic, ghostlike, even myself." -- Robert Walser]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/324739-all-our-language-is-composed-of-brief-little-dreams-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 13:30:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Paul Valéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/324739-all-our-language-is-composed-of-brief-little-dreams-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All our language is composed of brief little dreams; and the wonderful thing is that we sometimes make of them strangely accurate and marvelously reasonable thoughts. What should we be without the help of that which does not exist? Very little. And our unoccupied minds would languish if fables, mistaken notions, abstractions, beliefs, and monsters, hypotheses, and the so-called problems of metaphysics did not people with beings and objectless images our natural depths and darkness. Myths are the souls of our actions and our loves. We cannot act without moving towards a phantom. We can love only what we create." -- Paul Valéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/503207-the-lively-is-always-more-contemplative-than-what-is-dead</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 07:43:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Robert Walser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/503207-the-lively-is-always-more-contemplative-than-what-is-dead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The lively is always more contemplative than what is dead and sad." -- Robert Walser]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/504389-i-done-me-best-when-i-was-let-thinking-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 07:48:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/504389-i-done-me-best-when-i-was-let-thinking-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I done me best when I was let.  Thinking always if I go all goes.  A hundred cares, a tithe of troubles and is there one who understands me?  One in a thousand of years of the nights?  All me life I have been lived among them but now they are becoming lothed to me.  And I am lothing their little warm tricks.  And lothing their mean cosy turns.  And all the greedy gushes out through their small souls.  And all the lazy leaks down over their brash bodies.  How small it's all!  And me letting on to meself always.  And lilting on all the time." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/510919-average-reality-begins-to-rot-and-stink-as-soon-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 06:00:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/510919-average-reality-begins-to-rot-and-stink-as-soon-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Average reality begins to rot and stink as soon as the act of individual creation ceases to animate a subjectively perceived texture." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522185-spiders-teeth-are-not-so-long-as-a-torment-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 11:16:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Raymond Queneau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522185-spiders-teeth-are-not-so-long-as-a-torment-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Spiders’ teeth are not so long as a torment that cannot be avowed." -- Raymond Queneau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/478344-to-understand-what-i-am-saying-you-have-to-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 10:08:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Pina Bausch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/478344-to-understand-what-i-am-saying-you-have-to-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To understand what I am saying, you have to believe that dance is something other than technique. We forget where the movements come from. They are born from life. When you create a new work, the point of departure must be contemporary life -- not existing forms of dance." -- Pina Bausch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151178-a-place-belongs-forever-to-whoever-claims-it-hardest-remembers</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 10:41:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151178-a-place-belongs-forever-to-whoever-claims-it-hardest-remembers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A place belongs forever to whoever claims it hardest, remembers it most obsessively, wrenches it from itself, shapes it, renders it, loves it so radically that he remakes it in his own image." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/538749-hold-me-tight-down-on-my-knees-so-i-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 12:38:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoff add a quote by Kim Gordon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/538749-hold-me-tight-down-on-my-knees-so-i-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hold me tight, down on my knees, so I don't go burning 'cross the breeze." -- Kim Gordon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
