<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/126501-jennifer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/126501-jennifer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 22:55:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2450-i-will-not-let-anyone-walk-through-my-mind-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 22:55:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by mahatma gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2450-i-will-not-let-anyone-walk-through-my-mind-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will not let anyone walk through my mind  with their dirty feet." -- mahatma gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36317-why-did-you-do-all-this-for-me-he-asked</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 22:58:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36317-why-did-you-do-all-this-for-me-he-asked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why did you do all this for me?' he asked. 'I don't deserve it. I've never done anything for you.' 'You have been my friend,' replied Charlotte. 'That in itself is a tremendous thing." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23446-this-is-how-it-works-i-love-the-people-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 22:59:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by James Lecesne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23446-this-is-how-it-works-i-love-the-people-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is how it works.  I love the people in my life, and I do for my friends whatever they need me to do for them, again and again, as many times as is necessary.  For example, in your case you always forgot who you are and how much you're loved.  So what I do for you as your friend is remind you who you are and tell you how much I love you.  And this isn't any kind of burden for me, because I love who you are very much.  Every time I remind you, I get to remember with you, which is my pleasure." -- James Lecesne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25269-when-i-say-it-s-you-i-like-i-m-talking-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:01:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Fred Rogers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25269-when-i-say-it-s-you-i-like-i-m-talking-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I say it's you I like, I'm talking about that part of you that knows that life is far more than anything you can ever see or hear or touch. That deep part of you that allows you to stand for those things without which humankind cannot survive. Love that conquers hate, peace that rises triumphant over war, and justice that proves more powerful than greed." -- Fred Rogers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74985-we-ll-be-there-harry-said-ron-what-at-your-aunt</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:01:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74985-we-ll-be-there-harry-said-ron-what-at-your-aunt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We'll be there, Harry,&quot; said Ron
&quot;What?&quot;
&quot;At your Aunt and Uncle's house,&quot; said Ron, &quot;And then we'll go with you wherever you're going.&quot;
&quot;No-&quot; said Harry quickly; he hadn't counted on this, he had meant them to understand that he was undertaking the most dangerous journey alone. 
&quot;You said it once before,&quot; said Hermione quickly, &quot;that there was time to turn back if we wanted to. We've had time, haven't we? We're with you whatever happens." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25310-there-s-not-a-word-yet-for-old-friends-who-ve-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:03:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Jim Henson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25310-there-s-not-a-word-yet-for-old-friends-who-ve-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's not a word yet, for old friends who've just met." -- Jim Henson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66148-if-you-have-two-friends-in-your-lifetime-you-re-lucky</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:03:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by S.E. Hinton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66148-if-you-have-two-friends-in-your-lifetime-you-re-lucky]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you have two friends in your lifetime, you're lucky. If you have one &lt;I&gt;good&lt;/i&gt; friend, you're more than lucky." -- S.E. Hinton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289279-friendship--my-definition--is-built-on-two-things-respect-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:04:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Stieg Larsson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289279-friendship--my-definition--is-built-on-two-things-respect-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship- my definition- is built on two things. Respect and trust. Both elements have to be there. And it has to be mutual. You can have respect for someone, but if you don't have trust, the friendship will crumble." -- Stieg Larsson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112790-we-should-meet-in-another-life-we-should-meet-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:05:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112790-we-should-meet-in-another-life-we-should-meet-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We should meet in another life, we should meet in air, me and you." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22486-i-ve-heard-it-said-that-people-come-into-our-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:25:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Stephen Schwartz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22486-i-ve-heard-it-said-that-people-come-into-our-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've heard it said that people come into our lives for a reason
Bringing something we must learn
And we are led to those who help us most to grow 
If we let them and we help them in return." -- Stephen Schwartz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:26:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:27:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739-when-i-despair-i-remember-that-all-through-history-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:28:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739-when-i-despair-i-remember-that-all-through-history-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I despair, I remember that all through history the way of truth and love have always won. There have been tyrants and murderers, and for a time, they can seem invincible, but in the end, they always fall. Think of it--always." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71213-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-who-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:29:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71213-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-who-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time there was a boy who loved a girl, and her laughter was a question he wanted to spend his whole life answering." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49991-so-i-love-you-because-the-entire-universe-conspired-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:30:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49991-so-i-love-you-because-the-entire-universe-conspired-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So, I love you because the entire universe conspired to help me find you." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12860-every-heart-sings-a-song-incomplete-until-another-heart-whispers</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:30:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Plato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12860-every-heart-sings-a-song-incomplete-until-another-heart-whispers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every heart sings a song, incomplete, until another heart whispers back. Those who wish to sing always find a song. At the touch of a lover, everyone becomes a poet." -- Plato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4566-in-vain-have-i-struggled-it-will-not-do-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:31:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4566-in-vain-have-i-struggled-it-will-not-do-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In vain have I struggled. It will not do. My feelings will not be repressed. You must allow me to tell you how ardently I admire and love you." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182896-i-no-longer-believed-in-the-idea-of-soul-mates</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:32:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Lisa Kleypas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182896-i-no-longer-believed-in-the-idea-of-soul-mates]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I no longer believed in the idea of soul mates, or love at first sight.  But I was beginning to believe that a very few times in your life, if you were lucky, you might meet someone who was exactly right for you.  Not because he was perfect, or because you were, but because your combined flaws were arranged in a way that allowed two separate beings to hinge together." -- Lisa Kleypas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43334-i-love-you-also-means-i-love-you-more-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:32:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43334-i-love-you-also-means-i-love-you-more-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you also means I love you more than anyone loves you, or has loved you, or will love you, and also, I love you in a way that no one loves you, or has loved you, or will love you, and also, I love you in a way that I love no one else, and never have loved anyone else, and never will love anyone else." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84061-it-isn-t-possible-to-love-and-part-you-will-wish</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:33:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84061-it-isn-t-possible-to-love-and-part-you-will-wish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It isn't possible to love and part.  You will wish that it was.  You can transmute love, ignore it, muddle it, but you can never pull it out of you. I know by experience that the poets are right:  love is eternal." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11195-when-we-love-we-always-strive-to-become-better-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:33:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11195-when-we-love-we-always-strive-to-become-better-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we love, we always strive to become better than we are. When we strive to become better than we are, everything around us becomes better too." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75358-it-is-a-curious-thought-but-it-is-only-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:34:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Agatha Christie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75358-it-is-a-curious-thought-but-it-is-only-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a curious thought, but it is only when you see people looking ridiculous that you realize just how much you love them.  " -- Agatha Christie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21075-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-volcanoes-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:34:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21075-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-volcanoes-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a temporary madness, it erupts like volcanoes and then subsides.  And when it subsides, you have to make a decision.  You have to work out whether your roots have so entwined together that it is inconceivable that you should ever part.  Because this is what love is.  Love is not breathlessness, it is not excitement, it is not the promulgation of promises of eternal passion, it is not the desire to mate every second minute of the day, it is not lying awake at night imagining that he is kissing every cranny of your body.  No, don't blush, I am telling you some truths.  That is just being &quot;in love&quot;, which any fool can do.  Love itself is what is left over when being in love has burned away, and this is both an art and a fortunate accident." -- Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189796-promise-yourself-to-be-so-strong-that-nothing-can-disturb</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:35:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Christian D. Larson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189796-promise-yourself-to-be-so-strong-that-nothing-can-disturb]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Promise Yourself

To be so strong that nothing
can disturb your peace of mind.
To talk health, happiness, and prosperity
to every person you meet.

To make all your friends feel
that there is something in them
To look at the sunny side of everything
and make your optimism come true.

To think only the best, to work only for the best,
and to expect only the best.
To be just as enthusiastic about the success of others
as you are about your own.

To forget the mistakes of the past
and press on to the greater achievements of the future.
To wear a cheerful countenance at all times
and give every living creature you meet a smile.

To give so much time to the improvement of yourself
that you have no time to criticize others.
To be too large for worry, too noble for anger, too strong for fear,
and too happy to permit the presence of trouble.

To think well of yourself and to proclaim this fact to the world,
not in loud words but great deeds.
To live in faith that the whole world is on your side
so long as you are true to the best that is in you." -- Christian D. Larson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/779-love-doesn-t-just-sit-there-like-a-stone-it-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:36:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/779-love-doesn-t-just-sit-there-like-a-stone-it-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love doesn't just sit there, like a stone, it has to be made, like bread; remade all the time, made new." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48507-i-crave-your-mouth-your-voice-your-hair-silent-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:37:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48507-i-crave-your-mouth-your-voice-your-hair-silent-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I crave your mouth, your voice, your hair.
Silent and starving, I prowl through the streets. 
Bread does not nourish me, dawn disrupts me, all day 
I hunt for the liquid measure of your steps. 

I hunger for your sleek laugh, 
your hands the color of a savage harvest, 
hunger for the pale stones of your fingernails, 
I want to eat your skin like a whole almond. 

I want to eat the sunbeam flaring in your lovely body, 
the sovereign nose of your arrogant face, 
I want to eat the fleeting shade of your lashes, 

and I pace around hungry, sniffing the twilight, 
hunting for you, for your hot heart, 
Like a puma in the barrens of Quitratue." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9481-if-all-else-perished-and-he-remained-i-should-still</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:38:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Emily Jane Brontë ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9481-if-all-else-perished-and-he-remained-i-should-still]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If all else perished, and he remained, I should still continue to be; and if all else remained, and he were annihilated, the universe would turn to a mighty stranger." -- Emily Jane Brontë ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131148-i-read-once-that-the-ancient-egyptians-had-fifty-words</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:39:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Brian Andreas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131148-i-read-once-that-the-ancient-egyptians-had-fifty-words]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read once that the ancient Egyptians had fifty words for sand &amp; the Eskimos had a hundred words for snow. I wish I had a thousand words for love, but all that comes to mind is the way you move against me while you sleep &amp; there are no words for that." -- Brian Andreas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278926-people-always-fall-in-love-with-the-most-perfect-aspects</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:41:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278926-people-always-fall-in-love-with-the-most-perfect-aspects]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People always fall in love with the most perfect aspects of each other’s personalities.  Who wouldn’t? Anybody can love the most wonderful parts of another person. But that’s not the clever trick.  The really clever trick is this: Can you accept the flaws? Can you look at your partner’s faults honestly and say, ‘I can work around that.  I can make something out of it.’?  Because the good stuff is always going to be there, and it’s always going to pretty and sparkly, but the crap underneath can ruin you." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27611-aim-high-but-do-not-aim-so-high-that-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 23:41:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27611-aim-high-but-do-not-aim-so-high-that-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Aim high, but do not aim so high that you totally miss the target. What really matters is that he will love you, that he will respect you, that he will honor you, that he will be absolutely true to you, that he will give you the freedom of expression and let you fly in the development of your own talents. He is not going to be perfect, but if he is kind and thoughtful, if he knows how to work and earn a living, if he is honest and full of faith, the chances are you will not go wrong, that you will be immensely happy." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
