<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/126747-liz]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/126747-liz" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2011 18:05:59 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265387-go-into-yourself-find-out-the-reason-that-commands-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2011 18:05:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liz add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265387-go-into-yourself-find-out-the-reason-that-commands-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Go into yourself. Find out the reason that commands you to write; see whether it has spread its roots into the very depths of your heart; confess to yourself whether you would have to die if you were forbidden to write. 

This most of all: ask yourself in the most silent hour of your night: must I write? Dig into yourself for a deep answer. And if this answer rings out in assent, if you meet this solemn question with a strong, simple “I must,” then build your life in accordance with this necessity; your whole life, even into its humblest and most indifferent hour, must become a sign and witness to this impulse. Then come close to Nature. Then, as if no one had ever tried before, try to say what you see and feel and love and lose...

...Describe your sorrows and desires, the thoughts that pass through your mind and your belief in some kind of beauty - describe all these with heartfelt, silent, humble sincerity and, when you express yourself, use the Things around you, the images from your dreams, and the objects that you remember. If your everyday life seems poor, don’t blame it; blame yourself; admit to yourself that you are not enough of a poet to call forth its riches; because for the creator there is not poverty and no poor, indifferent place. And even if you found yourself in some prison, whose walls let in none of the world’s sounds – wouldn’t you still have your childhood, that jewel beyond all price, that treasure house of memories? Turn your attentions to it. Try to raise up the sunken feelings of this enormous past; your personality will grow stronger, your solitude will expand and become a place where you can live in the twilight, where the noise of other people passes by, far in the distance. - And if out of this turning-within, out of this immersion in your own world, poems come, then you will not think of asking anyone whether they are good or not. Nor will you try to interest magazines in these works: for you will see them as your dear natural possession, a piece of your life, a voice from it. A work of art is good if it has arisen out of necessity. That is the only way one can judge it." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/441676-even-the-simplest-poem-may-destroy-your-immunity-to-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2011 21:43:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liz add a quote by Elma Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/441676-even-the-simplest-poem-may-destroy-your-immunity-to-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even the simplest poem
May destroy your immunity to human emotions.
All poems must carry a Government warning. Words
Can seriously affect your heart." -- Elma Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145124-where-now-are-the-horse-and-the-rider-where-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 10:55:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liz add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145124-where-now-are-the-horse-and-the-rider-where-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where now are the horse and the rider? Where is the horn that was blowing?
Where is the helm and the hauberk, and the bright hair flowing?
Where is the harp on the harpstring, and the red fire glowing?
Where is the spring and the harvest and the tall corn growing?
They have passed like rain on the mountain, like a wind in the meadow;
The days have gone down in the West behind the hills into shadow.
Who shall gather the smoke of the deadwood burning,
Or behold the flowing years from the Sea returning?" -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308837-dead-your-majesty-dead-my-lords-and-gentlemen-dead-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 05:43:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liz add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308837-dead-your-majesty-dead-my-lords-and-gentlemen-dead-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dead, your Majesty. Dead, my lords and gentlemen. Dead, Right Reverends and Wrong Reverends of every order. Dead, men and women, born with Heavenly compassion in your hearts. And dying thus around us every day." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251283-kindred-spirits-are-not-so-scarce-as-i-used-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 05:00:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liz add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251283-kindred-spirits-are-not-so-scarce-as-i-used-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kindred spirits are not so scarce as I used to think.  It's splendid to find out there are so many of them in the world." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
