<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/127857-oolookitty]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/127857-oolookitty" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2012 15:10:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282921-the-pyjamas-have-cats-on-them-i-am-informed-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2012 15:10:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oolookitty add a quote by Martin Millar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282921-the-pyjamas-have-cats-on-them-i-am-informed-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The pyjamas have cats on them. I am informed that these cats belong to an organisation called Hello Kitty." -- Martin Millar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70555-dear-god-she-prayed-let-me-be-something-every-minute</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 19:15:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oolookitty add a quote by Betty Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70555-dear-god-she-prayed-let-me-be-something-every-minute]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dear God,&quot; she prayed, &quot;let me be something every minute of every hour of my life. Let me be gay; let me be sad. Let me be cold; let me be warm. Let me be hungry...have too much to eat. Let me be ragged or well dressed. Let me be sincere - be deceitful. Let me be truthful; let me be a liar. Let me be honorable and let me sin. Only let me be something every blessed minute. And when I sleep, let me dream all the time so that not one little piece of living is ever lost." -- Betty Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/503032-yeah-there-s-some-unlikely-beasts-in-the-world-and-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 21:30:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oolookitty add a quote by Tim Powers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/503032-yeah-there-s-some-unlikely-beasts-in-the-world-and-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yeah, there's some unlikely beasts in the world, and it's best to stay near the ones that you've bought drinks for." -- Tim Powers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/575499-mama-says-mine-is-a-night-mind</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 21:39:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oolookitty add a quote by Jack Womack]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/575499-mama-says-mine-is-a-night-mind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mama says mine is a night mind." -- Jack Womack]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145129-a-woman-at-one-of-mother-s-parties-once-said-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 23:20:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oolookitty add a quote by Rachel Ferguson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145129-a-woman-at-one-of-mother-s-parties-once-said-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A woman at one of mother's parties once said to me, &quot;Do you like reading?&quot; which smote us all to silence, for how could one tell her that books are like having a bath or sleeping, or eating bread - absolute necessities which one never thinks of in terms of appreciation. And we all sat waiting for her to say that she had so little time for reading, before ruling her right out for ever and ever." -- Rachel Ferguson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183388-i-often-think-that-perhaps-there-is-only-a-limited</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 23:20:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oolookitty add a quote by Rachel Ferguson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183388-i-often-think-that-perhaps-there-is-only-a-limited]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I often think that perhaps there is only a limited amount of memory going about the world, and that when it wants to live again, it steals its nest, like a cuckoo." -- Rachel Ferguson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341581-i-never-knew-what-an-extraordinary-thing-it-could-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 23:20:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oolookitty add a quote by Rachel Ferguson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341581-i-never-knew-what-an-extraordinary-thing-it-could-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I never knew what an extraordinary thing it could be to write a book. In the first place, the characters take the bit between their jaws and canter off with you into places you don't want and never catered for. I had smugly intended my book to be about a family rather like ours, but, lud love you! it's already turned into an account of a barmaid's career in an Edgware Road pub, and I can't squeeze us in &lt;i&gt;anywhere!&lt;/i&gt;

Odd things happen, too. I had called my pub, 'The Three Feathers,' and counted on there being heaps of pubs in Edgware Road, not called that, but looking a bit like my description. Before we left home, I went down Edgware Road to investigate, and found my pub, even down to the old-fashioned phonograph on the table in the upstairs sitting-room. And I thought, &lt;i&gt;'I&lt;/i&gt; built that place." -- Rachel Ferguson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/285743-you-should-never-read-just-for-enjoyment-read-to-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 15:14:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oolookitty add a quote by John Waters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/285743-you-should-never-read-just-for-enjoyment-read-to-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You should never read just for &quot;enjoyment.&quot; Read to make yourself smarter! Less judgmental. More apt to understand your friends' insane behavior, or better yet, your own. Pick &quot;hard books.&quot; Ones you have to concentrate on while reading. And for god's sake, don't let me ever hear you say, &quot;I can't read fiction. I only have time for the truth.&quot; Fiction is the truth, fool! Ever hear of &quot;literature&quot;? That means fiction, too, stupid." -- John Waters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1351-he-moved-like-a-dancer-which-is-not-surprising-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 20:17:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oolookitty add a quote by Mark Helprin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1351-he-moved-like-a-dancer-which-is-not-surprising-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He moved like a dancer, which is not surprising; a horse is a beautiful animal, but it is perhaps most remarkable because it moves as if it always hears music." -- Mark Helprin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/769317-the-trees-around-and-overhead-were-so-thick-that-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 15:47:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oolookitty add a quote by Shirley Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/769317-the-trees-around-and-overhead-were-so-thick-that-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trees around and overhead were so thick that it was always dry inside and on Sunday morning I lay there with Jonas, listening to his stories. All cat stories start with the statement: &quot;My mother, who was the first cat, told me this,&quot; and I lay with my head close to Jonas and listened. There was no change coming, I thought here, only spring; I was wrong to be so frightened. The days would get warmer, and Uncle Julian would sit in the sun, and Constance would laugh when she worked in the garden, and it would always be the same. Jonas went on and on (&quot;And then we sang! And then we sang!&quot;) and the leaves moved overhead and it would always be the same." -- Shirley Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
