<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/131963-james-curcio]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/131963-james-curcio" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 19:13:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417745-the-woman-he-had-loved-most-he-was-thirty-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 19:13:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417745-the-woman-he-had-loved-most-he-was-thirty-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The woman he had loved most (he was thirty at the time) would tell him (he was nearly in despair when he heard it) that she held on to life by a thread. Yes, she did want to live, life gave her great joy, but she also knew that her 'i want to live' was spun from the threads of a spiderweb. It takes so little, so infinitely little, for someone to find himself on the other side of the border, where everything-- love, convictions, faith, history-- no longer has meaning. The whole mystery of human life resides in the fact that it is spent in the immediate proximity of, and even in direct contact with, that border, that it is separated from it not by kilometers but by barely a millimeter." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231840-human-life-occurs-only-once-and-the-reason-we-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 19:23:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231840-human-life-occurs-only-once-and-the-reason-we-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human life occurs only once, and the reason we cannot determine which of our decisions are good and which bad is that in a given situation we can make only one decision; we are not granted a second, third, or fourth life in which to compare various decisions." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197776-the-most-fundamental-aggression-to-ourselves-the-most-fundamental-harm</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 23:35:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197776-the-most-fundamental-aggression-to-ourselves-the-most-fundamental-harm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most fundamental aggression to ourselves, the most fundamental harm we can do to ourselves, is to remain ignorant by not having the courage and the respect to look at ourselves honestly and gently." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148850-rather-than-letting-our-negativity-get-the-better-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 23:36:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148850-rather-than-letting-our-negativity-get-the-better-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Rather than letting our negativity get the better of us, we could acknowledge that right now we feel like a piece of shit and not be squeamish about taking a good look." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142188-tamina-serves-coffee-and-calvados-to-the-customers-there-aren-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 15:51:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142188-tamina-serves-coffee-and-calvados-to-the-customers-there-aren-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tamina serves coffee and calvados to the customers (there aren't all that many, the room being always half empty) and then goes back behind the bar. Almost always there is someone sitting on a barstool, trying to talk to her. Everyone likes Tamina. Because she knows how to listen to people.

But is she really listening? Or is she merely looking at them so attentively, so silently? I don't know, and it's not very important. What matters is that she doesn't interrupt anyone. You know what happens when two people talk. One of them speaks and the other breaks in: &quot;It's absolutely the same with me, I...&quot; and starts talking about himself until the first one manages to slip back in with his own &quot;It's absolutely the same with me, I...&quot;

The phrase &quot;It's absolutely the same with me, I...&quot; seems to be an approving echo, a way of continuing the other's thought, but that is an illusion: in reality it is a brute revolt against a brutal violence, an effort to free our own ear from bondage and to occupy the enemy's ear by force. Because all of man's life among his kind is nothing other than a battle to seize the ear of others. The whole secret of Tamina's popularity is that she has no desire to talk about herself. She submits to the forces occupying her ear, never saying: &quot;It's absolutely the same with me, I..." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183096-in-the-political-jargon-of-those-days-the-word-intellectual</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 15:51:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183096-in-the-political-jargon-of-those-days-the-word-intellectual]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the political jargon of those days, the word &quot;intellectual&quot; was an insult. It indicated someone who did not understand life and was cut off from the people. All the Communists who were hanged at the time by other Communists were awarded such abuse. Unlike those who had their feet solidly on the ground, they were said to float in the air. So it was fair, in a way, that as punishment the ground was permanently pulled out from under their feet, that they remained suspended a little above the floor." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/627078-it-takes-so-little-so-infinitely-little-for-someone-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 15:51:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/627078-it-takes-so-little-so-infinitely-little-for-someone-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It takes so little, so infinitely little, for someone to find himself on the other side of the border, where everything - love, convictions, faith, history - no longer has meaning. The whole mystery of human life resides on the fact that it is spent in the immediate proximity of, and even in direct contact with, that border, that it is separated from it not by kilometers but by barely a millimeter." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/723562-graphomania-a-mania-for-writing-books-inevitably-takes-on-epidemic</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 15:55:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/723562-graphomania-a-mania-for-writing-books-inevitably-takes-on-epidemic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Graphomania  (a mania for writing books) inevitably takes on epidemic proportions when a society develops to the point of creating three basic conditions: -

(1) an elevated level of general well being which allows people to devote themselves to useless activities
(2) a high degree of social atomization and , as a consequence, a general isolation of individuals;
(3) the absence of dramatic social changes in the nation's internal life." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/682149-my-very-existence-my-life-in-the-world-seemed-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 12:43:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/682149-my-very-existence-my-life-in-the-world-seemed-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My very existence, my life in the world, seemed like a hallucination. A strong wind would make me think my body was about to be blown to the end of the earth, to some land I had never seen or heard of, where my mind and body would separate forever. “Hold tight,” I would tell myself, but there was nothing for me to hold on to." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116856-margaret-atwood-the-canadian-novelist-once-asked-a-group-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 23:55:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Molly Ivins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116856-margaret-atwood-the-canadian-novelist-once-asked-a-group-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Margaret Atwood, the Canadian novelist, once asked a group of women at a university why they felt threatened by men. The women said they were afraid of being beaten, raped, or killed by men. She then asked a group of men why they felt threatened by women. They said they were afraid women would laugh at them." -- Molly Ivins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 02:01:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lolita, light of my life, fire of my loins. My sin, my soul. Lo-lee-ta: the tip of the tongue taking a trip of three steps down the palate to tap, at three, on the teeth. Lo. Lee. Ta. She was Lo, plain Lo, in the morning, standing four feet ten in one sock. She was Lola in slacks. She was Dolly at school. She was Dolores on the dotted line. But in my arms she was always Lolita. Did she have a precursor? She did, indeed she did. In point of fact, there might have been no Lolita at all had I not loved, one summer, an initial girl-child. In a princedom by the sea. Oh when? About as many years before Lolita was born as my age was that summer. You can always count on a murderer for a fancy prose style. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, exhibit number one is what the seraphs, the misinformed, simple, noble-winged seraphs, envied. Look at this tangle of thorns." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
