<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/132451-megan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/132451-megan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 14:12:02 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626213-you-give-a-lot-of-great-advice-about-what-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 14:12:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626213-you-give-a-lot-of-great-advice-about-what-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You give a lot of great advice about what to do. Do you have any advice of what not to do?


Don’t do what you know on a gut level to be the wrong thing to do. Don’t stay when you know you should go or go when you know you should stay. Don’t fight when you should hold steady or hold steady when you should fight. Don’t focus on the short-term fun instead of the long-term fall out. Don’t surrender all your joy for an idea you used to have about yourself that isn’t true anymore. Don’t seek joy at all costs. I know it’s hard to know what to do when you have a conflicting set of emotions and desires, but it’s not as hard as we pretend it is. Saying it’s hard is ultimately a justification to do whatever seems like the easiest thing to do—have the affair, stay at that horrible job, end a friendship over a slight, keep loving someone who treats you terribly. I don’t think there’s a single dumbass thing I’ve done in my adult life that I didn’t know was a dumbass thing to do while I was doing it. Even when I justified it to myself—as I did every damn time—the truest part of me knew I was doing the wrong thing. Always. As the years pass, I’m learning how to better trust my gut and not do the wrong thing, but every so often I get a harsh reminder that I’ve still got work to do." -- Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/649853-the-best-thing-you-can-possibly-do-with-your-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 14:13:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/649853-the-best-thing-you-can-possibly-do-with-your-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best thing you can possibly do with your life is to tackle the motherfucking shit out of it." -- Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
