<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/133282-janet]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/133282-janet" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 19:24:34 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2461-don-t-be-too-timid-and-squeamish-about-your-actions-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 19:24:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2461-don-t-be-too-timid-and-squeamish-about-your-actions-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't be too timid and squeamish about your actions. All life is an experiment. The more experiments you make the better." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57182-i-have-said-that-texas-is-a-state-of-mind</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 19:34:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57182-i-have-said-that-texas-is-a-state-of-mind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have said that Texas is a state of mind, but I think it is more than that. It is a mystique closely approximating a religion. And this is true to the extent that people either passionately love Texas or passionately hate it and, as in other religions, few people dare to inspect it for fear of losing their bearings in mystery or paradox. But I think there will be little quarrel with my feeling that Texas is one thing. For all its enormous range of space, climate, and physical appearance, and for all the internal squabbles, contentions, and strivings, Texas has a tight cohesiveness perhaps stronger than any other section of America. Rich, poor, Panhandle, Gulf, city, country, Texas is the obsession, the proper study, and the passionate possession of all Texans." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377744-we-do-not-work-for-men-we-work-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 10:54:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Alan Paton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377744-we-do-not-work-for-men-we-work-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We do not work for men. We work for the land and the people. We do not even work for money." -- Alan Paton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15411-actual-happiness-always-looks-pretty-squalid-in-comparison-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 11:01:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15411-actual-happiness-always-looks-pretty-squalid-in-comparison-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Actual happiness always looks pretty squalid in comparison with the overcompensations for misery. And, of course, stability isn't nearly so spectacular as instability. And being contented has none of the glamour of a good fight against misfortune, none of the picturesqueness of a struggle with temptation, or a fatal overthrow by passion or doubt. Happiness is never grand." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 08:06:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202992-happiness-is-never-really-so-welcome-as-changelessness</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 10:56:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202992-happiness-is-never-really-so-welcome-as-changelessness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["happiness is never really so welcome as changelessness" -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416557-nobody-here-could-ever-talk-about-a-heaven-on-earth</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 10:58:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416557-nobody-here-could-ever-talk-about-a-heaven-on-earth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody here could ever talk about a heaven on earth. Heaven remained rigidly in its proper place on the other side of death, and on this side flourished the injustices, the cruelties, the meanness that elsewhere people so cleverly hushed up. Here you could love human beings nearly as God loved them, knowing the worst: you didn’t love a pose, a pretty dress, a sentiment artfully assumed." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416558-they-had-been-corrupted-by-money-and-he-had-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 10:59:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416558-they-had-been-corrupted-by-money-and-he-had-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They had been corrupted by money, and he had been corrupted by sentiment. Sentiment was the more dangerous, because you couldn’t name its price. A man open to bribes was to be relied upon below a certain figure, but sentiment might uncoil in the heart at a name, a photograph, even a smell remembered." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416559-it-seemed-to-scobie-that-life-was-immeasurably-long-couldn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 10:59:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416559-it-seemed-to-scobie-that-life-was-immeasurably-long-couldn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seemed to Scobie that life was immeasurably long. Couldn’t the test of man have been carried out in fewer years? Couldn’t we have committed our first major sin at seven, have ruined ourselves for love or hate at ten, have clutched at redemption on a fifteen-year-old deathbed?" -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416560-from-eight-thirty-in-the-morning-until-eleven-he-dealt-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 11:00:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416560-from-eight-thirty-in-the-morning-until-eleven-he-dealt-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From eight-thirty in the morning until eleven he dealt with a case of petty larceny; there were six witnesses to examine, and he didn’t believe a word that any of them said. In European cases there are words one believes and words one distrusts: it is possible to draw a speculative line between the truth and the lies; at least the cui bono principle to some extent operates, and it is usually safe to assume, if the accusation is theft and there is no question of insurance, that something has at least been stolen. But here one could make no such assumption; one could draw no lines. He had known police officers who nerves broke down in the effort to separate a single grain of incontestable truth; they ended, some of them, by striking a witness, they were pilloried in the local Creole papers and were invalided home or transferred. It woke in some men a virulent hatred of a black skin, but Scobie had long ago, during his fifteen years, passed through the dangerous stages; now lost in the tangle of lies he felt an extraordinary affection for these people who paralysed an alien form of justice by so simple a method." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416561-when-he-was-young-he-had-thought-love-had-something</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 11:01:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416561-when-he-was-young-he-had-thought-love-had-something]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When he was young, he had thought love had something to do with understanding, but with age he knew that no human being understood another. Love was the wish to understand, and presently with constant failure the wish died, and love died too perhaps or changed into this painful affection, loyalty, pity…" -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422013-each-one-of-us-of-course-the-controller-meditatively-continued</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 11:05:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422013-each-one-of-us-of-course-the-controller-meditatively-continued]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each one of us, of course,&quot; the Controller meditatively continued, &quot;goes through life inside a bottle. But if we happen to be Alphas, our bottles are, relatively speaking enormous." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
