<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/133269-barbra]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/133269-barbra" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 15:36:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17177-those-who-believe-in-telekinetics-raise-my-hand</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 15:36:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[baRbRa add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17177-those-who-believe-in-telekinetics-raise-my-hand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who believe in telekinetics, raise my hand." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4739-i-often-recall-these-words-when-i-am-writing-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 15:39:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[baRbRa add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4739-i-often-recall-these-words-when-i-am-writing-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I often recall these words when I am writing, and I think to myself, “It’s true. There aren’t any new words. Our job is to give new meanings and special overtones to absolutely ordinary words.” I find the thought reassuring. It means that vast, unknown stretches still lie before us, fertile territories just waiting for us to cultivate them." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30910-everyone-looks-retarded-once-you-set-your-mind-to-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 15:41:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[baRbRa add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30910-everyone-looks-retarded-once-you-set-your-mind-to-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone looks retarded once you set your mind to it." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53259-among-other-things-you-ll-find-that-you-re-not-the-first</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 15:44:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[baRbRa add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53259-among-other-things-you-ll-find-that-you-re-not-the-first]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Among other things, you'll find that you're not the first person who was ever confused and frightened and even sickened by human behavior. You're by no means alone on that score, you'll be excited and stimulated to know. Many, many men have been just as troubled morally and spiritually as you are right now. Happily, some of them kept records of their troubles. You'll learn from them—if you want to. Just as someday, if you have something to offer, someone will learn something from you. It's a beautiful reciprocal arrangement. And it isn't education. It's history. It's poetry." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13878-whatever-i-do-however-i-find-a-way-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 15:46:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[baRbRa add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13878-whatever-i-do-however-i-find-a-way-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever I do, however I find a way to live, I will tell these stories.  I have spoken to every person I have encountered these last difficult days...I speak to these people, and I speak to you because I cannot help it.  It gives me strength, almost unbelievable strength, to know that you are there.  I covet your eyes, your ears, the collapsible space between us.  How blessed are we to have each other?  I am alive and you are alive and so we must fill the air with our words.  I will fill today, tomorrow, every day until I am taken back to God.  I will tell stories to people who will listen and to people who don't want to listen, to people who seek me out and to those who run.  All the while I will know that you are there.  How can I pretend that you do not exist?  It would be almost as impossible as you pretending that I do not exist." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25680-we-are-the-bright-new-stars-born-of-a-screaming</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 15:47:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[baRbRa add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25680-we-are-the-bright-new-stars-born-of-a-screaming]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are the bright new stars born of a screaming black hole, the nascent suns burst from the darkness, from the grasping void of space that folds and swallows--a darkness that would devour anyone not as strong as we. We are oddities, sideshows, talk show subjects. We capture everyone's imagination." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16831-we-all-die-the-goal-isn-t-to-live-forever-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 15:52:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[baRbRa add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16831-we-all-die-the-goal-isn-t-to-live-forever-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all die. The goal isn't to live forever, the goal is to create something that will." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
