<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/136201-daniel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/136201-daniel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 13:57:03 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1404-if-you-don-t-have-time-to-read-you-don-t-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 13:57:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1404-if-you-don-t-have-time-to-read-you-don-t-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you don't have time to read, you don't have the time (or the tools) to write. Simple as that." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235123-if-you-ve-spent-any-time-trolling-the-blogosphere-you-ve-probably</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 07:17:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235123-if-you-ve-spent-any-time-trolling-the-blogosphere-you-ve-probably]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you've spent any time trolling the blogosphere, you've probably noticed a peculiar literary trend: the pervasive habit of writers inexplicably placing exclamation points at the end of otherwise unremarkable sentences. Sort of like this! This is done to suggest an ironic detachment from the writing of an expository sentence! It's supposed to signify that the writer is self-aware! And this is idiotic. It's the saddest kind of failure. F. Scott Fitzgerald believed inserting exclamation points was the literary equivalent of an author laughing at his own jokes, but that's not the case in the modern age; now, the exclamation point signifies creative confusion. All it illustrates is that even the writer can't tell if what they're creating is supposed to be meaningful, frivolous, or cruel. It's an attempt to insert humor where none exists, on the off chance that a potential reader will only be pleased if they suspect they're being entertained. Of course, the reader isn't really sure, either. They just want to know when they're supposed to pretend to be amused. All those extraneous exclamation points are like little splatters of canned laughter: They represent the &quot;form of funny,&quot; which is more easily understood (and more easily constructed) than authentic funniness. " -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10821-i-knew-that-i-shouldn-t-have-but-i-did-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 13:59:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10821-i-knew-that-i-shouldn-t-have-but-i-did-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I knew that I shouldn’t have, but I did it all the same; and there you have my epitaph, or one of them, because my grave is going to require a monument inscribed on all four sides with rueful mottoes, in small characters, set close together.

" -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5622-as-he-watched-joe-stand-blazing-on-the-fire-escape</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 14:00:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5622-as-he-watched-joe-stand-blazing-on-the-fire-escape]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As he watched Joe stand, blazing, on the fire escape, Sammy felt an ache in his chest that turned out to be, as so often occurs when memory and desire conjoin with a transient effect of weather, the pang of creation.  The desire he felt, watching Joe, was unquestionably physical, but in the sense that Sammy wanted to inhabit the body of his cousin, not possess it.  It was, in part, a longing--common enough among the inventors of heroes--to be someone else; to be more than the result of two hundred regimens and scenarios and self-improvement campaigns that always ran afoul of his perennial inability to locate an actual self to be improved.  Joe Kavalier had an air of competence, of faith in his own abilities, that Sammy, by means of constant effort over the whole of his life, had finally learned only to fake.  " -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 23:55:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by William Nicholson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We read to know we're not alone." -- William Nicholson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19869-los-angeles-give-me-some-of-you-los-angeles-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2008 13:03:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by John Fante]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19869-los-angeles-give-me-some-of-you-los-angeles-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Los Angeles, give me some of you! Los Angeles come to me the way I came to you, my feet over your streets, you pretty town I loved you so much, you sad flower in the sand, you pretty town!" -- John Fante]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41317-you-have-so-many-layers-that-you-can-peel-away</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 12:08:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Craig Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41317-you-have-so-many-layers-that-you-can-peel-away]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have so many layers, that you can peel away a few, and everyone's so shocked or impressed that you're baring your soul, while to you it's nothing, because you know you've twenty more layers to go." -- Craig Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11811-yet-for-all-the-depression-no-one-ever-quit-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 12:09:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Joshua Ferris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11811-yet-for-all-the-depression-no-one-ever-quit-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yet for all the depression no one ever quit.  When someone quit, we couldn't believe it. 'I'm becoming a rafting instructor on the Colorado River,' they said.  'I'm touring college towns with my garage band.'  We were dumbfounded. It was like they were from another planet.  Where had they found the derring-do?  What would they do about car payments?  We got together for going away drinks on their final day and tried to hide our envy while reminding ourselves that we still had the freedom and luxury to shop indiscriminately." -- Joshua Ferris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77670-my-standard-for-verisimilitude-is-simple-and-i-came-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 12:09:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by David Simon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77670-my-standard-for-verisimilitude-is-simple-and-i-came-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My standard for verisimilitude is simple and I came to it when I started to write prose narrative: fuck the average reader. I was always told to write for the average reader in my newspaper life. The average reader, as they meant it, was some suburban white subscriber with two-point-whatever kids and three-point-whatever cars and a dog and a cat and lawn furniture. He knows nothing and he needs everything explained to him right away, so that exposition becomes this incredible, story-killing burden. Fuck him. Fuck him to hell." -- David Simon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2010 12:05:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are bored and disgusted by politics and don't bother to vote, you are in effect voting for the entrenched Establishments of the two major parties, who please rest assured are not dumb, and who are keenly aware that it is in their interests to keep you disgusted and bored and cynical and to give you every possible reason to stay at home doing one-hitters and watching MTV on primary day.  By all means stay home if you want, but don't bullshit yourself that you're not voting.  In reality, there is &lt;i&gt;no such thing as not voting:&lt;/i&gt; you either vote by voting, or you vote by staying home and tacitly doubling the value of some Diehard's vote." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18719-the-truth-will-set-you-free-but-not-until-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2010 12:05:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18719-the-truth-will-set-you-free-but-not-until-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth will set you free. But not until it is finished with you." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100888-because-here-s-something-else-that-s-weird-but-true-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2010 12:06:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by David Foster Wallace  ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100888-because-here-s-something-else-that-s-weird-but-true-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because here's something else that's weird but true: in the day-to day trenches of adult life, there is actually no such thing as atheism. There is no such thing as not worshipping. Everybody worships. The only choice we get is what to worship. And the compelling reason for maybe choosing some sort of god or spiritual-type thing to worship -- be it JC or Allah, be it YHWH or the Wiccan Mother Goddess, or the Four Noble Truths, or some inviolable set of ethical principles -- is that pretty much anything else you worship will eat you alive. If you worship money and things, if they are where you tap real meaning in life, then you will never have enough, never feel you have enough. It's the truth. Worship your body and beauty and sexual allure and you will always feel ugly. And when time and age start showing, you will die a million deaths before they finally grieve you. On one level, we all know this stuff already. It's been codified as myths, proverbs, clichés, epigrams, parables; the skeleton of every great story. The whole trick is keeping the truth up front in daily consciousness." -- David Foster Wallace  ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49274-if-what-s-always-distinguished-bad-writing--flat-characters-a-narrative-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2010 12:07:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49274-if-what-s-always-distinguished-bad-writing--flat-characters-a-narrative-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If what's always distinguished bad writing--flat characters, a narrative world that's clichéd and not recognizably human, etc.--is also a description of today's world, then bad writing becomes an ingenious mimesis of a bad world. If readers simply believe the world is stupid and shallow and mean, then [Bret] Ellis can write a mean shallow stupid novel that becomes a mordant deadpan commentary on the badness of everything. Look man, we'd probably most of us agree that these are dark times, and stupid ones, but do we need fiction that does nothing but dramatize how dark and stupid everything is? In dark times, the definition of good art would seem to be art that locates and applies CPR to those elements of what's human and magical that still live and glow despite the times' darkness. Really good fiction could have as dark a worldview as it wished, but it'd find a way both to depict this world and to illuminate the possibilities for being alive and human in it.

Postmodern irony and cynicism's become an end in itself, a measure of hip sophistication and literary savvy. Few artists dare to try to talk about ways of working toward redeeming what's wrong, because they'll look sentimental and naive to all the weary ironists. Irony's gone from liberating to enslaving. There's some great essay somewhere that has a line about irony being the song of the prisoner who's come to love his cage… The postmodern founders' patricidal work was great, but patricide produces orphans, and no amount of revelry can make up for the fact that writers my age have been literary orphans throughout our formative years.

We enter a spiritual puberty where we snap to the fact that the great transcendent horror is loneliness, excluded encagement in the self. Once we’ve hit this age, we will now give or take anything, wear any mask, to fit, be part-of, not be Alone, we young. The U.S. arts are our guide to inclusion. A how-to. We are shown how to fashion masks of ennui and jaded irony at a young age where the face is fictile enough to assume the shape of whatever it wears. And then it’s stuck there, the weary cynicism that saves us from gooey sentiment and unsophisticated naïveté. Sentiment equals naïveté on this continent.

You burn with hunger for food that does not exist.

A U. S. of modern A. where the State is not a team or a code, but a sort of sloppy intersection of desires and fears, where the only public consensus a boy must surrender to is the acknowledged primacy of straight-line pursuing this flat and short-sighted idea of personal happiness." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49956-the-true-magic-of-this-broken-world-lay-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2010 14:21:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49956-the-true-magic-of-this-broken-world-lay-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The true magic of this broken world lay in the ability of the things it contained to vanish, to become so thoroughly lost, that they might never have existed in the first place." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154364-in-the-immemorial-style-of-young-men-under-pressure-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2010 14:21:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154364-in-the-immemorial-style-of-young-men-under-pressure-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the immemorial style of young men under pressure, they decided to lie down for a while and waste time." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48911-entertainment-is-a-sacred-pursuit-when-done-well-when-done</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2010 14:22:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48911-entertainment-is-a-sacred-pursuit-when-done-well-when-done]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Entertainment is a sacred pursuit when done well. When done well, it raises the quality of human life." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 12:10:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6493-a-children-s-story-that-can-only-be-enjoyed-by-children</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 12:11:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6493-a-children-s-story-that-can-only-be-enjoyed-by-children]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A children's story that can only be enjoyed by children is not a good children's story in the slightest." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26457-i-can-t-imagine-a-man-really-enjoying-a-book-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 12:12:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26457-i-can-t-imagine-a-man-really-enjoying-a-book-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can't imagine a man really enjoying a book and reading it only once." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10152-reality-in-fact-is-usually-something-you-could-not-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 12:13:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10152-reality-in-fact-is-usually-something-you-could-not-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reality, in fact, is usually something you could not have guessed. That is one of the reasons I believe Christianity. It is a religion you could not have guessed. If it offered us just the kind of universe we had always expected, I should feel we were making it up. But, in fact, it is not the sort of thing anyone would have made up. It has just that queer twist about it that real things have. So let us leave behind all these boys' philosophies--these over simple answers. The problem is not simple and the answer is not going to be simple either." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70507-i-don-t-know-yet-what-i-am-capable-of-doing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 09:05:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Thomas Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70507-i-don-t-know-yet-what-i-am-capable-of-doing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know yet what I am capable of doing, but, by God, I have genius -- I know it too well to blush behind it. " -- Thomas Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/702-it-would-seem-that-our-lord-finds-our-desires-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 12:48:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/702-it-would-seem-that-our-lord-finds-our-desires-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It would seem that Our Lord finds our desires not too strong, but too weak. We are half-hearted creatures, fooling about with drink and sex and ambition when infinite joy is offered us, like an ignorant child who wants to go on making mud pies in a slum because he cannot imagine what is meant by the offer of a holiday at the sea. We are far too easily pleased." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6231-even-in-literature-and-art-no-man-who-bothers-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 12:49:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6231-even-in-literature-and-art-no-man-who-bothers-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even in literature and art, no man who bothers about originality will ever be original: whereas if you simply try to tell the truth (without caring twopence how often it has been told before) you will, nine times out of ten, become original without ever having noticed it." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15139-i-am-a-product-of-endless-books-my-father-bought</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 12:50:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15139-i-am-a-product-of-endless-books-my-father-bought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am a product [...of] endless books. My father bought all the books he read and never got rid of any of them. There were books in the study, books in the drawing room, books in the cloakroom, books (two deep) in the great bookcase on the landing, books in a bedroom, books piled as high as my shoulder in the cistern attic, books of all kinds reflecting every transient stage of my parents' interest, books readable and unreadable, books suitable for a child and books most emphatically not. Nothing was forbidden me. In the seemingly endless rainy afternoons I took volume after volume from the shelves. I had always the same certainty of finding a book that was new to me as a man who walks into a field has of finding a new blade of grass." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165276-but-the-truth-is-it-s-hard-for-me-to-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 21:50:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165276-but-the-truth-is-it-s-hard-for-me-to-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the truth is it’s hard for me to know what I really think about any of the stuff I’ve written. It’s always tempting to sit back and make finger-steeples and invent impressive sounding theoretical justifications for what one does, but in my case most of it’d be horseshit. As time passes I get less and less nuts about anything I’ve published, and it gets harder to know for sure when its antagonistic elements are in there because they serve a useful purpose and when their just covert manifestations of this &quot;look-at-me-please-love-me-I-hate you&quot; syndrome I still sometimes catch myself falling into. Anyway, but what I think I meant by &quot;antagonize&quot; or &quot;aggravate&quot; has to do with the stuff in the TV essay about the younger writer trying to struggle against the cultural hegemony of TV. One thing TV does is help us deny that we’re lonely. With televised images, we can have the facsimile of a relationship without the work of a real relationship. It’s an anesthesia of &quot;form.&quot; The interesting thing is why we’re so desperate for this anesthetic against loneliness. You don’t have to think very hard to realize that our dread of both relationships and loneliness, both of which are like sub-dreads of our dread of being trapped inside a self (a psychic self, not just a physical self), has to do with angst about death, the recognition that I’m going to die, and die very much alone, and the rest of the world is going to go merrily on without me. I’m not sure I could give you a steeple-fingered theoretical justification, but I strongly suspect a big part of real art fiction’s job is to aggravate this sense of entrapment and loneliness and death in people, to move people to countenance it, since any possible human redemption requires us first to face what’s dreadful, what we want to deny." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717867-my-conception-of-a-novel-is-that-it-ought-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 07:33:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717867-my-conception-of-a-novel-is-that-it-ought-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My conception of a novel is that it ought to be a personal struggle, a direct and total engagement with the author's story of his or her own life. This conception, again, I take from Kafka, who, although he was never transformed into an insect, and although he never had a piece of food (an apple from his family's table!) lodged in his flesh and rotting there, devoted his whole life as a writer to describing his personal struggle with his family, with women, with moral law, with his Jewish heritage, with his Unconscious, with his sense of guilt, and with the modern world. Kafka's work, which grows out of the nighttime dreamworld in Kafka's brain, is *more* autobiographical than any realistic retelling of his daytime experiences at the office or with his family or with a prostitute could have been. What is fiction, after all, if not a kind of purposeful dreaming? The writer works to create a dream that is vivid and has meaning, so that the reader can then vividly dream it and experience meaning. And work like Kafka's, which seems to proceed directly from dream, is therefore an exceptionally pure form of autobiography. There's an important paradox here that I would like to stress: the greater the autobiographical content of a fiction writer's work, the *smaller* its superficial resemblance to the writer's actual life. The deeper the writer digs for meaning, the more the random particulars of the writer's life become *impediments* to deliberate dreaming." -- Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/836093-for-strange-as-it-may-sound-to-many-people-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 13:14:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Daniel Mendelsohn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/836093-for-strange-as-it-may-sound-to-many-people-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For (strange as it may sound to many people, who tend to think of critics as being motivated by the lower emotions: envy, disdain, contempt even) critics are, above all, people who are in love with beautiful things, and who worry that those things will get broken. What motivates so many of us to write in the first place is, to begin with, a great passion for a subject (Tennessee Williams, Balanchine, jazz, the twentieth-century novel, whatever) that we find beautiful; and, then, a kind of corresponding anxiety about the fragility of that beauty." -- Daniel Mendelsohn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105019-memory-can-make-a-thing-seem-to-have-been-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2013 05:49:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105019-memory-can-make-a-thing-seem-to-have-been-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Memory can make a thing seem to have been much more than it was." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186681-i-wish-i-could-leave-you-certain-of-the-images</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2013 05:49:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186681-i-wish-i-could-leave-you-certain-of-the-images]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish I could leave you certain of the images in my mind, because they are so beautiful that I hate to think they will be extinguished when I am.  Well, but again, this life has its own mortal loveliness.  And memory is not strictly mortal in its nature, either.  It is a strange thing, after all, to be able to return to a moment, when it can hardly be said to have any reality at all, even in its passing.  A moment is such a slight thing.  I mean, that its abiding is a most gracious reprieve." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
