<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/136324-jennifer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/136324-jennifer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 01:33:24 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225597-i-don-t-do-what-i-m-doing-to-fight-terror</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 01:33:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Greg Mortenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225597-i-don-t-do-what-i-m-doing-to-fight-terror]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't do what I'm doing to fight terror. ... I do it because I care about kids.  Fighting terror is maybe seventh or eighth on my list of priorities.  But working over there, I've learned a few things.  I've learned that terror doesn't happen because some group of people somewhere like Pakistan or Afghanistan simply decide to hate us.  It happens because children aren't being offered a bright enough future that they have a reason to choose life over death." -- Greg Mortenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364630-if-as-some-savants-of-consciousness-suggest-we-are-actually</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 21:08:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Phil Lesh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364630-if-as-some-savants-of-consciousness-suggest-we-are-actually]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If, as some savants of consciousness suggest, we are actually agreeing to create, from moment to moment, everything we perceive as real, then it stands to reason that we're also responsible for keeping it going in some harmonious manner." -- Phil Lesh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65564-true-friends-are-always-together-in-spirit-anne-shirley</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 21:06:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65564-true-friends-are-always-together-in-spirit-anne-shirley]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["True friends are always together in spirit. (Anne Shirley)" -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270243-i-ve-wondered-why-it-took-us-so-long-to-catch</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 01:36:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Robert Pirsig]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270243-i-ve-wondered-why-it-took-us-so-long-to-catch]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've wondered why it took us so long to catch on. We saw it, and yet we didn't see it. Or rather we were trained not to see it. Conned perhaps into thinking that the real action was metropolitan and all this was just boring hinterland. It was a puzzling thing. The truth knocks on the door and you say, &quot;Go away. I'm looking for the truth.&quot; And so it goes away. Puzzling." -- Robert Pirsig]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32222-you-see-you-closed-your-eyes-that-was-the-difference</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 21:08:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32222-you-see-you-closed-your-eyes-that-was-the-difference]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You see, you closed your eyes. That was the difference. Sometimes you cannot believe what you see, you have to believe what you feel. And if you are ever going to have other people trust you, you must feel that you can trust them, too--even when you’re in the dark. Even when you’re falling." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234944-meditation-begins-now-right-here-it-can-t-begin-someplace-else</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 21:09:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Steve Hagen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234944-meditation-begins-now-right-here-it-can-t-begin-someplace-else]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Meditation begins &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt;, right &lt;i&gt;here&lt;/i&gt;.  It can't begin someplace else or at some other time.  To paraphrase the great Zen master Dogen, &quot;If you want to practice awareness, then practice awareness without delay.&quot;  If you wish to know a mind that is tranquil and clear, sane and peaceful, you must take it up &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt;.  If you wish to free yourself from the frantic television mind that runs our lives, begin with the intention to be present &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt;.

Nobody can bring awareness to your life but you.

Meditation is not a self-help program--a way to better ourselves so we can get what we want.  Nor is it a way to relax before jumping back into busyness.  It's not something to do once in awhile, either, whenever you happen to feel like it.

Instead, meditation is a practice that saturates your life and in time can be brought into every activity.  It is the transformation of mind from bondage to freedom.

In practicing meditation, we go nowhere other than right here where we now stand, where we now sit, where we now live and breathe.  In meditation we return to where we already are--this shifting, changing ever-present &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt;.

If you wish to take up meditation, it must be &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt; or never." -- Steve Hagen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364632-i-d-always-admired-writers-i-d-always-loved-words-on-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 21:14:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Rosie O'Donnell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364632-i-d-always-admired-writers-i-d-always-loved-words-on-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd always admired writers.  I'd always loved words on a page.  Somehow, words seemed to bypass image and get straight to the heart of things.  Somehow, words seemed big enough to contain pain, and sentences could pull broken bits together." -- Rosie O'Donnell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73541-give-up-defining-yourself---to-yourself-or-to-others</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 21:16:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73541-give-up-defining-yourself---to-yourself-or-to-others]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Give up defining yourself - to yourself or to others. You won't die. You will come to life. And don't be concerned with how others define you. When they define you, they are limiting themselves, so it's their problem. Whenever you interact with people, don't be there primarily as a function or a role, but as the field of conscious Presence. You can only lose something that you have, but you cannot lose something that you are." -- Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177916-the-problem-is-whether-we-are-determined-to-go-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 21:16:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177916-the-problem-is-whether-we-are-determined-to-go-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem is whether we are determined to go in the direction of compassion or not. If we are, then can we reduce the suffering to a minimum? If I lose my direction, I have to look for the North Star, and I go to the north. That does not mean I expect to arrive at the North Star. I just want to go in that direction." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364641-the-only-source-of-peace-is-from-within-when-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 00:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Lewis Yablonsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364641-the-only-source-of-peace-is-from-within-when-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only source of peace is FROM WITHIN.  When one is confronted with the lie about justice, it seems to stimulate a sense of great frustration.  Frustration is just being disappointed because something didn't fulfill the image you laid on them in your head.  And so people shake their fists, and they say, 'we shall overcome,' and 'let there be justice and equality!,' and 'it's all THEIR fault OUT THERE and if THEY will only change then everything will be cool!'  It's never gonna work that way, that view will only compound the sense of frustration!  Because anything, man, which gets people outside of themselves for identity is just reinforcing the whole cycle.  (Gridley)" -- Lewis Yablonsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80729-drum-sound-rises-on-the-air-its-throb-my-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 21:18:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80729-drum-sound-rises-on-the-air-its-throb-my-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Drum sound rises on the air, its throb, my heart. 

A voice inside the beat says, &quot;I know you're tired, but come. This is the way." -- Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21253-a-path-is-only-a-path-and-there-is-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 21:18:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Carlos Castaneda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21253-a-path-is-only-a-path-and-there-is-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A path is only a path, and there is no affront, to oneself or to others, in dropping it if that is what your heart tells you . . . Look at every path closely and deliberately. Try it as many times as you think necessary. Then ask yourself alone, one question . . . Does this path have a heart? If it does, the path is good; if it doesn't it is of no use." -- Carlos Castaneda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245285-you-think-because-you-understand-one-you-must-also-understand</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 21:16:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245285-you-think-because-you-understand-one-you-must-also-understand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think because you understand 'one' you must also understand 'two', because one and one make two. But you must also understand 'and'." -- Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201611-love-calls---everywhere-and-always-we-re-sky-bound-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 21:18:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201611-love-calls---everywhere-and-always-we-re-sky-bound-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love calls - everywhere and always. 
We're sky bound.
Are you coming?" -- Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1342-goodbye-said-the-fox-and-now-here-is-my-secret</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 01:24:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1342-goodbye-said-the-fox-and-now-here-is-my-secret]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Goodbye,&quot; said the fox. &quot;And now here is my secret, a very simple secret: It is only with the heart that one can see rightly; what is essential is invisible to the eye." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30548-when-you-don-t-cover-up-the-world-with-words-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2012 23:45:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30548-when-you-don-t-cover-up-the-world-with-words-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you don't cover up the world with words and labels, a sense of the miraculous returns to your life that was lost a long time ago when humanity, instead of using thought, became possessed by thought." -- Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626901-preventing-war-is-much-better-than-protesting-against-the-war</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 10:19:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626901-preventing-war-is-much-better-than-protesting-against-the-war]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Preventing war is much better than protesting against the war.  Protesting the war is too late." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/633735-in-response-to-my-question-about-how-we-might-rein</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 10:10:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by John Perkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/633735-in-response-to-my-question-about-how-we-might-rein]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In response to my question about how we might rein in the empire, he said, &quot;That's why I'm meeting with you.  Only you in the United States can change it.  Your government created this problem and your people must solve it.  You've got to insist that Washington honor its commitment to democracy, even when deomcratically elected leaders nationalize your corrupting corporations.  You must take control of your corporations and your government.  The people of the United States have a great deal of power.  You need to come to grips with this.  There's no alternative.  We in Brazil have our hands tied.  So do the Venezeulans.  And the Nigerians.  It's up to you." -- John Perkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/641593-stop-being-so-greedy-and-so-selfish-realize-that-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 14:47:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by John Perkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/641593-stop-being-so-greedy-and-so-selfish-realize-that-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stop being so greedy, and so selfish.  Realize that there is more to the world than your big houses and fancy stores.  People are starving and you worry about oil for your cars.  Babies are dying of thirst and you search the fashion pages for the latest styles.  Nations like ours are drowing in poverty, but your people don't even hear our cries for help.  You shut your ears to the voices of those who try to tell you these things.  You label them radicals or Communists.  You must open your hearts to the poor and downtrodden, instead of driving them further into poverty and servitude.  There's not much time left.  If you don't change, you're doomed." -- John Perkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/643994-the-more-shared-past-there-is-in-a-relationship-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 11:49:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/643994-the-more-shared-past-there-is-in-a-relationship-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The more shared past there is in a relationship, the more present you need to be..." -- Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/643995-rather-than-being-your-thoughts-and-emotions-be-the-awareness</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 11:50:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/643995-rather-than-being-your-thoughts-and-emotions-be-the-awareness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Rather than being your thoughts and emotions, be the awareness behind them." -- Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/643996-in-essence-you-are-neither-inferior-nor-superior-to-anyone</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 11:52:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/643996-in-essence-you-are-neither-inferior-nor-superior-to-anyone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In essence, you are neither inferior nor superior to anyone.  True self-esteem and true humility arise out of that realization.  In the eyes of the ego, self-esteem and humility are contradictory.  In truth, they are one and the same." -- Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62315-life-is-the-dancer-and-you-are-the-dance</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 11:53:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62315-life-is-the-dancer-and-you-are-the-dance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is the dancer and you are the dance." -- Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644134-how-i-asked-myself-do-you-convince-men-and-women</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 15:19:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by john perkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644134-how-i-asked-myself-do-you-convince-men-and-women]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How, I asked myself, do you convince men and women who live comfortably to change a system that provides their comforts--even when they know about EHMs and jackals, when they understand that attached to their comforts are terrible price tags?  Where do you find words to empower them to stand up to a force like the corporatocracy?  How do you inspire them to take actions that will bend the corporations to the will of the people?" -- john perkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644137-the-first-question-we-must-address-deals-with-optimism-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 15:26:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by John Perkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644137-the-first-question-we-must-address-deals-with-optimism-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first question we must address deals with optimism, the possibility of achieving our goal.  Are we in a position where we can actually hope to effect change?  Assuming we become convinced that there are reasons for optimism, we move to the next question.  Are we cetain that we want change?  The stories about EHMs, jackals, and suffering around the globe strike raw nerves, but now we demand absolute proof that our grievances justify the efforts change will demand.  Third: Is there a unifying principle that will validate our efforts?  We look to ascertain that we are not merely seeking to impose our moral, religious, or philosophical values on others but instead are intent on creating something of true and lasting universal benefit.  And finally: What can we each do?  You and I personally need to evaluate our talents and passions.  What are our individual options and desires?  How do they fit into the bigger picture?" -- John Perkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644141-pointed-out-that-the-corporation-enjoys-the-same-rights-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 15:33:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by John Perkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644141-pointed-out-that-the-corporation-enjoys-the-same-rights-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...pointed out that the corporation enjoys the same rights as a living person under the Fourteenth Amendment to the Constitution.  This concept was upheld in 1886 by the Supreme Court in 'Santa Clara County v. Southern Pacific Railroad Company' and has been a fact of law ever since.  I emphasized to those executives that the corporation should also be required to accept the same responsibilities as those expected of a person; it too should be a good citizen, an honorable, ethical member of the community.  In the case of international corporations, that community has to be defined as the world." -- John Perkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/649762-there-is-only-one-perpetrator-of-evil-on-the-planet</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 18:15:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/649762-there-is-only-one-perpetrator-of-evil-on-the-planet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is only one perpetrator of evil on the planet: human unconsciousness.  That realization is true forgiveness.  With forgiveness, your victim identity dissolves, and your true power emerges--the power of Presence.  Instead of blaming the darkness, you bring in the light." -- Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/726089-whatever-lessens-suffering-in-yourself-and-others-that-is-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 19:24:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Satish Kumar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/726089-whatever-lessens-suffering-in-yourself-and-others-that-is-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever lessens suffering in yourself and others, that is right.  Whatever increases suffering, that is wrong.  The answer is within you.  When you are free of pride and prejudice, when you are calm and attentive, a light will shine within you.  Through meditation and through being mindful you will find your own knowledge of rightness.  You will be your own light." -- Satish Kumar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/726096-so-it-is-with-the-mind-nandini-allow-it-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 19:35:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Satish Kumar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/726096-so-it-is-with-the-mind-nandini-allow-it-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So it is with the mind, Nandini.  Allow it to be in balance.  Avoid extremes: the middle way is better.  Neither force the mind too hard into concentration nor let it wander aimlessly.  Meditation is to pay attention, to be aware of your breathing, your posture, your feelings, your perceptions, your thoughts, and all that passes through your mind and the mind itself; whatever is going on within you and between you and the universe.  Meditation is not just sitting for an hour here or an hour there; meditation is a way of life.  It is practiced all the time.  There is no separation between meditation and everyday living.  When you have ceased to be bound by the past or by the future, when you are fully present in the here and now, then it is meditation." -- Satish Kumar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/726127-we-must-realize-that-violence-is-not-confined-to-physical</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 19:49:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Satish Kumar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/726127-we-must-realize-that-violence-is-not-confined-to-physical]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must realize that violence is not confined to physical violence.  Fear is violence, caste discrimination is violence, exploitation of others, however subtle, is violence, segregation is violence, thinking ill of others and condemning others are violence.  In order to reduce individual acts of physical violence, we must work to eliminate violence at all levels, mental, verbal, personal, and social, including violence to animals, plants, and all other forms of life." -- Satish Kumar]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
