<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/137972-j-preece]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/137972-j-preece" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 10:50:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83242-then-we-were-at-the-fountain---we-stop-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 10:50:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Knut Hamsun]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83242-then-we-were-at-the-fountain---we-stop-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then we were at the fountain - we stop and look up at the many illuminated windows of number 2.
&quot;This is as far as you can walk me,&quot; she says. &quot;Thanks for taking me home.&quot;
I bowed, not daring to say a word. I doffed my hat and stood bareheaded. I wondered if she would give me her hand.
&quot;Why don't you ask me to walk back with you part of the way?&quot; She says playfully. But she looks down at the tip of her shoe. 
&quot;Gee,&quot; I answer, &quot;if only you would!&quot;
&quot;Sure, but only a little way.&quot;
And we turned around.
I was utterly bewildered, I didn't know which way was up anymore; this person turned all my thinking topsy-turvy. I was enchanted, wonderfully glad; I felt as though I were dying from happiness. She had expressly wanted to go back with me, it wasn't my idea, it was her own wish. I gaze and gaze at her, growing more and more cocky, and she encourages me, drawing me toward her by every word she speaks. I forget for a moment my poverty, my humble self, my whole miserable existence, I feel the blood coursing warmly through my body as in the old days, before I broke down." -- Knut Hamsun]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83478-i-sat-looking-at-her-with-rapt-attention-my-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 10:49:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Knut Hamsun]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83478-i-sat-looking-at-her-with-rapt-attention-my-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I sat looking at her with rapt attention. My heart was thumping, the blood coursing warmly through my veins. What a wonderful pleasure to be sitting in a human dwelling again, hear a clock ticking, and talk with a lively young girl instead of with myself!
Why don't you say something?&quot;
Ah, how sweet you are!&quot; I said. &quot;I'm sitting here getting fascinated by you, at this moment I'm thoroughly fascinated. I can't help it. You are the strangest person that... Sometimes your eyes are so radiant, I've never seen anything like it, they look like flowers. Eh? No, no, maybe not like flowers but... I'm madly in love with you, and it won't do me a bit of good. What's your name? Really, you must tell me what your name is...&quot;
No, what's &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; name? Goodness, I almost forgot again! I was thinking all day yesterday that I must ask you. Well, that is, not &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; day yesterday, I certainly didn't think about you all day yesterday.&quot;
Do you know what I've called you? I have called you Ylajali. How do you like it? Such a gliding sound-&quot;
Ylajali?&quot;
Yes.&quot;
Is it a foreign language?&quot;
Hmm. No, it's not.&quot;
Well, it isn't ugly." -- Knut Hamsun]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83479-she-came-quickly-over-to-me-and-held-out-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 10:56:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Knut Hamsun]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83479-she-came-quickly-over-to-me-and-held-out-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She came quickly over to me and held out her hand. I looked at her full of distrust. Was she doing this freely, with a light heart? Or was she doing it just to get rid of me? She put her arm around my neck, tears in her eyes. I just stood and looked at her. She offered me her mouth but I couldn't believe her, it was bound to be a sacrifice on her part, a means of getting it over with.
She said something, it sounded to me like &quot;I love you anyway!&quot; She said it very softly and indistinctly, I may not have heard it correctly, perhaps she didn't say exactly those words. But she threw herself passionately on my neck, held both arms around my neck a little while, even raised herself on tiptoe to reach well up, and stood thus.
Afraid that she was forcing herself to show me this tenderness, I merely said &quot;How beautiful you are now!&quot;
That was all I said. I stepped back, bumped against the door and walked out backward. She was left standing inside." -- Knut Hamsun]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83785-i-was-drawing-near-to-the-curve-of-the-track</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2008 11:37:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Bohumil Hrabal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83785-i-was-drawing-near-to-the-curve-of-the-track]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was drawing near to the curve of the track; already the twelve hooves of those dead horses were visible in the distance, jutting towards the sky like the columns in the cathedral crypt at Stará Boleslav. I thought of Masha, and of how we met for the first time, when I was still with the track superintendent. He gave us two buckets of red paint and told us to paint the fence round the entire state workshops. Masha began by the railway track, just as I did. We stood facing each other with the tall wire fence between us, at our feet we each had a bucket of cinnabar paint, we each had a brush, and we stippled away with our brushes opposite each other and painted that fence, she from her side and I from mine.

There were four kilometres altogether of this fence; for five months we stood facing each other like this, and there wasn't anything we didn't say to each other, Masha and I, but always there was this fence between us. After we'd painted two kilometres of it, one day I'd done just as high as Masha's mouth with this red colour, and I told her that I loved her, and she, from her side, had painted just up to there, too, and she said that she loved me, too ... and she looked into my eyes, and, as this was in a ditch and among tall goosefoot plants, I put out my lips, and we kissed through the newly painted fence, and when we opened our eyes she had a sort of tiny red fence-pale striped across her mouth, and so had I, and we burst out laughing, and from that moment on we were happy." -- Bohumil Hrabal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83794-i-went-up-the-stairs-of-the-little-hotel-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2008 12:16:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Bohumil Hrabal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83794-i-went-up-the-stairs-of-the-little-hotel-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I went up the stairs of the little hotel, that time in Bystřice by Benešov, and at the turn of the stairs there was a bricklayer at work, in white clothes; he was chiselling channels in the wall to cement in two hooks, on which in a little while he was going to hang a Minimax fire-extinguisher; and this bricklayer was already and old man, but he had such an enormous back that he had to turn round to let me pass by, and then I heard him whistling the waltz from &lt;i&gt;The Count of Luxembourg&lt;/i&gt; as I went into my little room. It was afternoon. I took out two razors, and one of them I scored blade-up into the top of the bathroom stool, and the other I laid beside it, and I, too, began to whistle the waltz from &lt;i&gt;The Count of Luxembourg&lt;/i&gt; while I undressed and turned on the hot-water tap, and then I reflected, and very quietly I opened the door a crack. And the bricklayer was standing there in the corridor on the other side of the door, and it was as if he also had opened the door a crack to have a look at me and see what I was doing, just as I had wanted to have a look at him.

And I slammed the door shut and crept into the bath, I had to let myself down into it gradually, the water was so hot; I gasped with the sting of it as carefully and painfully I sat down. And then I stretched out my wrist, and with my right hand I slashed my left wrist ... and then with all my strength I brought down the wrist of my right hand on the upturned blade I'd grooved into the stool for that purpose. And I plunged both hands into the hot water, and watched the blood flow slowly ouf of me, and the water grew rosy, and yet al the time the pattern of the red blood flowing remained so clearly perceptible, as though someone was drawing out from my wrists a long, feathery red bandage, a film, dancing veil ... and presently I thickened there in the bath, as that red paint thickened when we were painting the fence all round the state workshops, until we had to thin it with turpentine - and my head sagged, and into my mouth flowed pink raspberryade, except that it tasted slightly salty .. and then those concentric circles in blue and violet, trailing feathery fronds like coloured spirals in motion ... and then there was a shadow stooping over me, and my face was brushed lightly by a chin overgrown with stubble. It was that bricklayer in the white clothes. He hoisted me out and landed me like a red fish with delicate red fins sprouting from its wrists. I laid my head on his smock, and I heard the hissing of lime as my wet face slaked it, and that smell was the last thing of which I was conscious. " -- Bohumil Hrabal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83840-she-was-extending-a-hand-that-i-didn-t-know-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2008 14:31:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83840-she-was-extending-a-hand-that-i-didn-t-know-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was extending a hand that I didn't know how to take, so I broke its fingers with my silence, she said, &quot;You don't want to talk to me, do you?&quot; I took my daybook out of my knapsack and found the next blank page, the second to last. &quot;I don't speak,&quot; I wrote. &quot;I'm sorry.&quot; She looked at the piece of paper, then at me, then back at the piece of paper, she covered her eyes with her hands and cried, tears seeped between her fingers, she cried and cried and cried, there weren't any napkins nearby, so I ripped the page from the book - &quot;I don't speak. I'm sorry&quot; - and used it to dry her cheeks, my explanation and apology ran down her face like mascara, she took my pen from me and wrote on the next blank page of my daybook, the final one:

Please marry me

I flipped back and pointed at: &quot;Ha ha ha!&quot; She flipped forward and pointed at: &quot;Please marry me.&quot; I flipped back and pointed at: &quot;Thank you, but I'm about to burst.&quot; She flipped forward and pointed at: &quot;Please marry me.&quot; I flipped back and pointed at: &quot;I'm not sure, but it's late.&quot; She flipped forward and pointed at: &quot;Please marry me&quot;, and this time put her finger on &quot;Please&quot;, as if to hold down the page and end the conversation, or as if she were trying to push through the word, and into what she was trying to say. I thought about life, about my life, the embarrassments, the little coincidences, the shadows of alarm clocks on bedside tables, I thought about my small victories and everything I'd seen destroyed. I'd swum through mink coats on my parents' bed while they hosted downstairs, I'd lost the only person with whom I could have spent my only life, I'd left behind a thousand tonnes of marble from which I could have released sculptures, I could have released myself from the marble of myself, I'd experienced joy, but not nearly enough, could there be enough? The end of suffering does not justify the suffering, and so there is no end to suffering, what a mess I am, I thought, what a fool, how foolish and narrow, how worthless, how pinched and pathetic, how helpless in the universe. None of my pets knows their own name. What kind of person am I? I flipped back, one page at a time:

Help" -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85562-in-these-days-melissa-s-absorbed-and-provoking-gentleness-had-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2008 13:26:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Lawrence Durrell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85562-in-these-days-melissa-s-absorbed-and-provoking-gentleness-had-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In these days Melissa's absorbed and provoking gentleness had all the qualities of a rediscovered youth. Her long uncertain fingers - I used to feel them moving over my face when she thought I slept, as if to memorize the happiness we had shared. In her there was a pliancy, a resilience which was Oriental - a passion to serve. My shabby clothes - the way she picked up a dirty shirt seemed to engulf it with an overflowing solicitude; in the morning I found my razor beautifully cleaned and even the toothpaste laid upon the brush in readiness. Her care for me was a goad, provoking me to give my life some sort of shape and style that might match the simplicity of hers. Of her experiences in love she would never speak, turning from them with a weariness and distaste which suggested that they had been born of necessity rather than desire. She paid me the comlpiment of saying: &quot;For the first time I am not afraid to be light-headed or foolish with a man&quot;." -- Lawrence Durrell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85575-these-are-the-moments-which-are-not-calculable-and-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2008 13:57:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Lawrence Durrell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85575-these-are-the-moments-which-are-not-calculable-and-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These are the moments which are not calculable, and cannot be assessed in words; they live on in the solution of memory, like wonderful creatures, unique of their own kind, dredged up from the floors of some unexplored ocean." -- Lawrence Durrell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85576-goddamn-sometimes-i-only-want-this-feeling-to-stay-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2008 14:01:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85576-goddamn-sometimes-i-only-want-this-feeling-to-stay-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Goddamn sometimes I only want this feeling to stay and last." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85579-between-the-roof-of-the-shed-and-the-big-plant</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2008 14:04:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Mark Haddon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85579-between-the-roof-of-the-shed-and-the-big-plant]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Between the roof of the shed and the big plant that hangs over the fence from the house next door I could see the constellation Orion. People say that Orion is called Orion because Orion was a hunter and the constellation looks like a hunter with a club and a bow and arrow, like this:

But this is really silly because it is just stars, and you could join up the dots in any way you wanted, and you could make it look like a lady with an umbrella who is waving, or the coffeemaker which Mrs. Shears has, which is from Italy, with a handle and steam coming out, or like a dinosaur. 

And there aren't any lines in space, so you could join bits of Orion to bits of Lepus or Taurus or Gemini and say that they were a constellation called the Bunch of Grapes or Jesus or the Bicycle (except that they didn't have bicycles in Roman and Greek times, which was when they called Orion Orion). And anyway, Orion is not a hunter or a coffeemaker or a dinosaur. It is just Betelgeuse and Bellatrix and Alnilam and Rigel and 17 other stars I don't know the names of. And they are nuclear explosions billions of miles away. And that is the truth. 

I stayed awake until 5:47. That was the last time I looked at my watch before I fell asleep. It has a luminous face and lights up if you press a button, so I could read it in the dark. I was cold and I was frightened Father might come out and find me. But I felt safer in the garden because I was hidden. I looked at the sky a lot. I like looking up at the sky in the garden at night. In summer I sometimes come outside at night with my torch and my planisphere, which is two circles of plastic with a pin through the middle. And on the bottom is a map of the sky and on top is an aperture which is an opening shaped in a parabola and you turn it round to see a map of the sky that you can see on that day of the year from the latitude 51.5° north, which is the latitude that Swindon is on, because the largest bit of the sky is always on the other side of the earth. 

And when you look at the sky you know you are looking at stars which are hundreds and thousands of light-years away from you. And some of the stars don't even exist anymore because their light has taken so long to get to us that they are already dead, or they have exploded and collapsed into red dwarfs. And that makes you seem very small, and if you have difficult things in your life it is nice to think that they are what is called negligible, which means that they are so small you don't have to take them into account when you are calculating something. 

I didn't sleep very well because of the cold and because the ground was very bumpy and pointy underneath me and because Toby was scratching in his cage a lot. But when I woke up properly it was dawn and the sky was all orange and blue and purple and I could hear birds singing, which is called the Dawn Chorus. And I stayed where I was for another 2 hours and 32 minutes, and then I heard Father come into the garden and call out, &quot;Christopher...? Christopher...?" -- Mark Haddon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96806-towards-midnight-the-rain-ceased-and-the-clouds-drifted-away</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2008 04:39:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by William Golding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96806-towards-midnight-the-rain-ceased-and-the-clouds-drifted-away]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Towards midnight the rain ceased and the clouds drifted away, so that the sky was scattered once more with the incredible lamps of stars. Then the breeze died too and there was no noise save the drip and tickle of water that ran out of clefts and spilled down, leaf by leaf, to the brown earth of the island. The air was cool, moist, and clear; and presently even the sound of the water was still. The beast lay huddled on the pale beach and the stains spread, inch by inch.

The edge of the lagoon became a streak of phosphorescence which advanced minutely, as the great wave of the tide flowed. The clear water mirrored the clear sky and the angular bright constellations. The line of phosphorescence bulged about the sand grains and little pebbles; it held them each in a dimple of tension, then suddenly accepted them with an inaudible syllable and moved on.

Along the shoreward edge of the shallows the advancing clearness was full of strange, moonbeam-bodied creatures with fiery eyes. Here and there a larger pebble clung to its own air and was covered with a coat of pearls. The tide swelled in over the rain-pitted sand and smoothed everything with a layer of silver. Now it touched the first of the stains that seeped from the broken body and the creatures made a moving patch of light as they gathered at the edge. The water rose further and dressed Simon's coarse hair with brightness. The line of his cheek silvered and the turn of his shoulder became sculptured marble. The strange, attendant creatures, with their fiery eyes and trailing vapours busied themselves round his head. The body lifted a fraction of an inch from the sand and a bubble of air escaped from the mouth with a wet plop. Then it turned gently in the water.

Somewhere over the darkened curve of the world the sun and moon were pulling; and the film of water on the earth planet was held, bulging slightly on one side while the solid core turned. The great wave of the tide moved further along the island and the water lifted. Softly, surrounded by a fringe of inquisitive bright creatures, itself a silver shape beneath the steadfast constellations, Simon's dead body moved out towards the open sea." -- William Golding]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96809-is-that-how-he-sees-it-he-knows-how-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2008 04:55:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Barbara Gowdy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96809-is-that-how-he-sees-it-he-knows-how-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is that how he sees it? He knows how much his death will hurt us, so he must be under the impression that by staying alive he'll eventually hurt us even more. Maybe we should pretend we've stopped caring what he does. Say, &quot;We've given up on you, Abel. You don't matter.&quot; Well, that would gratify him, our failling in line with what he has been telling us for months. How do we get around that? How do we persuade him that he's entitled to cause pain and, what's more, that he has a responsibility to &lt;i&gt;bear&lt;/i&gt; the pain that he causes? 

If only I could say, &quot;You're worthy of your own life,&quot; and make him believe me. Too late. Too late. He seems completely enraptured now by the idea of no longer existing. I think he imagines the space he'll vacate, the actually physical space, and there we'll be, his parents and I, waving our hands around trying to find him, but at least we won't come up against any resistance. There won't be anything to collide with, only air." -- Barbara Gowdy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77670-my-standard-for-verisimilitude-is-simple-and-i-came-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 17:45:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by David Simon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77670-my-standard-for-verisimilitude-is-simple-and-i-came-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My standard for verisimilitude is simple and I came to it when I started to write prose narrative: fuck the average reader. I was always told to write for the average reader in my newspaper life. The average reader, as they meant it, was some suburban white subscriber with two-point-whatever kids and three-point-whatever cars and a dog and a cat and lawn furniture. He knows nothing and he needs everything explained to him right away, so that exposition becomes this incredible, story-killing burden. Fuck him. Fuck him to hell." -- David Simon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121617-a-city-becomes-a-world-when-one-loves-one-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2009 13:42:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Lawrence Durrell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121617-a-city-becomes-a-world-when-one-loves-one-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A city becomes a world when one loves one of its inhabitants." -- Lawrence Durrell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34052-we-are-unusual-and-tragic-and-alive</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2009 13:50:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by dave eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34052-we-are-unusual-and-tragic-and-alive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are unusual and tragic and alive." -- dave eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29533-we-have-advantages-we-have-a-cushion-to-fall-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2009 13:50:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29533-we-have-advantages-we-have-a-cushion-to-fall-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have advantages. We have a cushion to fall back on. This is abundance. A luxury of place and time. Something rare and wonderful. It's almost historically unprecedented. We must do extraordinary things. We have to. It would be absurd not to." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80948-what-the-fuck-does-it-take-to-show-you-motherfuckers</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2009 13:52:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80948-what-the-fuck-does-it-take-to-show-you-motherfuckers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What the fuck does it take to show you motherfuckers, what does it fucking take what do you want how much do you want because I am willing and I'll stand before you and I'll raise my arms and give you my chest and throat and wait, and I've been so old for so long, for you, for you, I want it fast and right through me-- Oh do it, do it motherfuckers, do it do it you fuckers finally, finally, finally." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11943-here-i-am-rock-you-like-a-hurricane</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2009 13:53:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11943-here-i-am-rock-you-like-a-hurricane]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here I am Rock You Like a Hurricane." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39604-every-part-of-my-body-felt-electric-my-chest-ached</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2009 13:53:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39604-every-part-of-my-body-felt-electric-my-chest-ached]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every part of my body felt electric. My chest ached and my head throbbed with the great terrible limitless possibility of the morning, and when it came, the sky was washed white, everything was new, and I hadn't slept at all." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27475-the-way-i-need-you-is-a-loneliness-i-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 17:34:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Carson McCullers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27475-the-way-i-need-you-is-a-loneliness-i-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the way i need you is a loneliness i cannot bear." -- Carson McCullers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10920-i-wanted-the-whole-world-or-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 17:35:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10920-i-wanted-the-whole-world-or-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted the whole world or nothing." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50205-there-is-a-loneliness-in-this-world-so-great-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 17:36:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50205-there-is-a-loneliness-in-this-world-so-great-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["there is a loneliness in this world so great that you can see it in the slow movement of the hands of a clock" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27469-the-shortest-distance-between-two-points-is-often-unbearable</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 17:57:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27469-the-shortest-distance-between-two-points-is-often-unbearable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The shortest distance between two points is often unbearable." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80937-god-i-own-you-like-i-own-the-caves-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 08:28:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80937-god-i-own-you-like-i-own-the-caves-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["GOD: I own you like I own the caves.
THE OCEAN: Not a chance. No comparison.
GOD: I made you. I could tame you.
THE OCEAN: At one time, maybe. But not now.
GOD: I will come to you, freeze you, break you.
THE OCEAN: I will spread myself like wings. I am a billion tiny feathers. You have no idea what's happened to me." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51223-education-is-indoctrination-if-you-re-white---subjugation-if-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 18:14:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51223-education-is-indoctrination-if-you-re-white---subjugation-if-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Education is indoctrination if you're white - subjugation if you're black." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21388-still-though-i-think-if-you-re-not-self-obsessed-you-re-probably</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 16:42:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21388-still-though-i-think-if-you-re-not-self-obsessed-you-re-probably]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Still though, I think if you're not self-obsessed, you're probably boring." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182368-i-have-always-been-accused-of-taking-the-things-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 14:18:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182368-i-have-always-been-accused-of-taking-the-things-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always been accused of taking the things I love - football, of course, but also books and records - much too seriously, and I do feel a kind of anger when I hear a bad record, or when someone is lukewarm about a book that means a lot to me." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106280-i-will-not-wait-to-love-as-best-as-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 14:18:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106280-i-will-not-wait-to-love-as-best-as-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will not wait to love as best as I can. We thought we were young and that there would be time to love well sometime in the future. This is a terrible way to think. It is no way to live, to wait to love." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52076-i-like-the-dark-part-of-the-night-after-midnight</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 14:18:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52076-i-like-the-dark-part-of-the-night-after-midnight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like the dark part of the night, after midnight and before four-thirty, when it's hollow, when ceilings are harder and farther away.  Then I can breathe, and can think while others are sleeping, in a way can stop time, can have it so – this has always been my dream – so that while everyone else is frozen, I can work busily about them, doing whatever it is that needs to be done, like the elves who make the shoes while children sleep." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58143-it-was-miraculous-it-was-almost-no-trick-at-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 13:21:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58143-it-was-miraculous-it-was-almost-no-trick-at-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was miraculous. It was almost no trick at all, he saw, to turn vice into virtue and slander into truth, impotence into abstinence, arrogance into humility, plunder into philanthropy, thievery into honor, blasphemy into wisdom, brutality into patriotism, and sadism into justice. Anybody could do it; it required no brains at all. It merely required no character." -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
