<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/138065-crystal-allen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/138065-crystal-allen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2007 14:58:40 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2007 14:58:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by Groucho Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Outside of a dog, a book is man's best friend. Inside of a dog it's too dark to read." -- Groucho Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4290-books-to-the-ceiling-books-to-the-sky-my-pile</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 10:14:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by Arnold Lobel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4290-books-to-the-ceiling-books-to-the-sky-my-pile]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books to the ceiling,
Books to the sky,
My pile of books is a mile high.
How I love them! How I need them!
I'll have a long beard by the time I read them." -- Arnold Lobel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121923-you-help-yourself-to-a-hug-whenever-you-want-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2008 18:28:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by Diane Hammond]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121923-you-help-yourself-to-a-hug-whenever-you-want-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You help yourself to a hug whenever you want one, sugar. They're warm, and they're free." -- Diane Hammond]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125743-don-t-you-think-it-s-better-to-be-extremely-happy-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 09:32:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125743-don-t-you-think-it-s-better-to-be-extremely-happy-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't you think it's better to be extremely happy for a short while, even if you lose it, than to be just okay for your whole life?" -- Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23342-it-s-dark-now-and-i-am-very-tired-i-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 09:33:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23342-it-s-dark-now-and-i-am-very-tired-i-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s dark now and I am very tired. I love you, always. Time is nothing." -- Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124641-there-is-only-one-page-left-to-write-on-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 09:33:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124641-there-is-only-one-page-left-to-write-on-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is only one page left to write on. I will fill it with words of only one syllable. I love. I have loved. I will love." -- Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43441-why-is-love-intensified-by-absence</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 09:33:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43441-why-is-love-intensified-by-absence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why is love intensified by absence?" -- Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22293-long-ago-men-went-to-sea-and-women-waited-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 09:59:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22293-long-ago-men-went-to-sea-and-women-waited-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Long ago, men went to sea, and women waited for them, standing on the edge of the water, scanning the horizon for the tiny ship. Now I wait for Henry. He vanishes unwillingly, without warning. I wait for him. Each moment that I wait feels like a year, an eternity. Each moment is as slow and transparent as glass. Through each moment I can see infinite moments lined up, waiting. Why has he gone where I cannot follow?" -- Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 10:48:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 10:48:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15251-so-please-oh-please-we-beg-we-pray-go-throw</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 11:20:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by Roald Dahl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15251-so-please-oh-please-we-beg-we-pray-go-throw]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So, please, oh please, we beg, we pray, go throw your TV set away, and in its place you can install, a lovely bookcase on the wall." -- Roald Dahl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174690-those-who-don-t-believe-in-magic-will-never-find-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 11:21:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by Roald Dahl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174690-those-who-don-t-believe-in-magic-will-never-find-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who don't believe in magic will never find it." -- Roald Dahl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/849309-this-is-where-the-pivotal-events-of-my-childhood-unfolded</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 12:47:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by Jo Ann Beard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/849309-this-is-where-the-pivotal-events-of-my-childhood-unfolded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is where the pivotal events of my childhood unfolded, while I ate banana and root beer Popsicles, two by two, tucking the sticks neatly under the skirt of the chair. It's where Sunnybank Lad met Lady, Ken met his friend Flicka, Atlanta burned, Manderley burned, Lassie came home, Jim ran away, Alice got small, Wilbur got big, David Copperfield was born, Beth died, and, on an endless gloomy winter afternoon, Jody shot his yearling." -- Jo Ann Beard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437516-you-should-date-a-girl-who-reads-date-a-girl</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 11:27:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by Rosemarie Urquico]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437516-you-should-date-a-girl-who-reads-date-a-girl]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You should date a girl who reads.
Date a girl who reads. Date a girl who spends her money on books instead of clothes, who has problems with closet space because she has too many books. Date a girl who has a list of books she wants to read, who has had a library card since she was twelve.

Find a girl who reads. You’ll know that she does because she will always have an unread book in her bag. She’s the one lovingly looking over the shelves in the bookstore, the one who quietly cries out when she has found the book she wants. You see that weird chick sniffing the pages of an old book in a secondhand book shop? That’s the reader. They can never resist smelling the pages, especially when they are yellow and worn.

She’s the girl reading while waiting in that coffee shop down the street. If you take a peek at her mug, the non-dairy creamer is floating on top because she’s kind of engrossed already. Lost in a world of the author’s making. Sit down. She might give you a glare, as most girls who read do not like to be interrupted. Ask her if she likes the book.

Buy her another cup of coffee.

Let her know what you really think of Murakami. See if she got through the first chapter of Fellowship. Understand that if she says she understood James Joyce’s Ulysses she’s just saying that to sound intelligent.  Ask her if she loves Alice or she would like to be Alice.

It’s easy to date a girl who reads. Give her books for her birthday, for Christmas, for anniversaries. Give her the gift of words, in poetry and in song. Give her Neruda, Pound, Sexton, Cummings. Let her know that you understand that words are love. Understand that she knows the difference between books and reality but by god, she’s going to try to make her life a little like her favorite book. It will never be your fault if she does.

She has to give it a shot somehow.

Lie to her. If she understands syntax, she will understand your need to lie. Behind words are other things: motivation, value, nuance, dialogue. It will not be the end of the world.

Fail her. Because a girl who reads knows that failure always leads up to the climax. Because girls who read understand that all things must come to end, but that you can always write a sequel. That you can begin again and again and still be the hero. That life is meant to have a villain or two.

Why be frightened of everything that you are not? Girls who read understand that people, like characters, develop. Except in the Twilight series.

If you find a girl who reads, keep her close. When you find her up at 2 AM clutching a book to her chest and weeping, make her a cup of tea and hold her. You may lose her for a couple of hours but she will always come back to you. She’ll talk as if the characters in the book are real, because for a while, they always are.

You will propose on a hot air balloon. Or during a rock concert. Or very casually next time she’s sick. Over Skype.

You will smile so hard you will wonder why your heart hasn’t burst and bled out all over your chest yet. You will write the story of your lives, have kids with strange names and even stranger tastes. She will introduce your children to the Cat in the Hat and Aslan, maybe in the same day. You will walk the winters of your old age together and she will recite Keats under her breath while you shake the snow off your boots.

Date a girl who reads because you deserve it. You deserve a girl who can give you the most colorful life imaginable. If you can only give her monotony, and stale hours and half-baked proposals, then you’re better off alone. If you want the world and the worlds beyond it, date a girl who reads.

Or better yet, date a girl who writes." -- Rosemarie Urquico]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
