<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/138787-kelli]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/138787-kelli" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 12:02:36 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27047-let-me-live-love-and-say-it-well-in-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 12:02:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27047-let-me-live-love-and-say-it-well-in-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["let me live, love, and say it well in good sentences" -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 07:01:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always imagined that Paradise will be a kind of library." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224399-maybe-if-i-could-slip-into-sylvia-s-mind-sort-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 19:21:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Kelli Russell Agodon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224399-maybe-if-i-could-slip-into-sylvia-s-mind-sort-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe if I could slip into Sylvia's mind, sort out the spices in her rack, alphabetize them and dust them off. Maybe then I'd understand how it's the little things that pull you under." -- Kelli Russell Agodon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209856-dude-the-place-is-filling-up-i-say-it-feels</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 11:29:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209856-dude-the-place-is-filling-up-i-say-it-feels]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dude, the place is filling up,&quot; I say. &quot;It feels like we're living in the bottom half of an hourglass.&quot;
Like somehow we're running out of time." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/370675-science-is-the-key-to-our-future-and-if-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 12:06:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Bill Nye]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/370675-science-is-the-key-to-our-future-and-if-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Science is the key to our future, and if you don’t believe in science, then you’re holding everybody back. And it’s fine if you as an adult want to run around pretending or claiming that you don’t believe in evolution, but if we educate a generation of people who don’t believe in science, that’s a recipe for disaster. We talk about the Internet. That comes from science. Weather forecasting. That comes from science. The main idea in all of biology is evolution. To not teach it to our young people is wrong." -- Bill Nye]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8499-seize-the-moment-remember-all-those-women-on-the-titanic</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 11:20:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Erma Bombeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8499-seize-the-moment-remember-all-those-women-on-the-titanic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Seize the moment. Remember all those women on the 'Titanic' who waved off the dessert cart." -- Erma Bombeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7147-you-must-have-chaos-within-you-to-give-birth-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 11:25:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7147-you-must-have-chaos-within-you-to-give-birth-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must have chaos within you to give birth to a dancing star." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384-painting-is-poetry-that-is-seen-rather-than-felt-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 11:25:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Leonardo da Vinci]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384-painting-is-poetry-that-is-seen-rather-than-felt-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Painting is poetry that is seen rather than felt, and poetry is painting that is felt rather than seen." -- Leonardo da Vinci]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65611-i-am-an-excitable-person-who-only-understands-life-lyrically</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 11:25:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65611-i-am-an-excitable-person-who-only-understands-life-lyrically]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am an excitable person who only understands life lyrically, musically, in whom feelings are much stronger as reason. I am so thirsty for the marvelous that only the marvelous has power over me. Anything I can not transform into something marvelous, I let go. Reality doesn't impress me. I only believe in intoxication, in ecstasy, and when ordinary life shackles me, I escape, one way or another. No more walls." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10320-we-don-t-make-mistakes-just-happy-little-accidents</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 11:25:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Bob Ross]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10320-we-don-t-make-mistakes-just-happy-little-accidents]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't make mistakes, just happy little accidents." -- Bob Ross]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29278-i-haven-t-the-slightest-idea-how-to-change-people-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 10:30:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29278-i-haven-t-the-slightest-idea-how-to-change-people-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I haven't the slightest idea how to change people, but still I keep a long list of prospective candidates just in case I should ever figure it out." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391508-on-the-first-day-of-november-last-year-sacred-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 10:59:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Mary Rose O'Reilley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391508-on-the-first-day-of-november-last-year-sacred-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the first day of November last year, sacred to many religious calendars but especially the Celtic, I went for a walk among bare oaks and birch. Nothing much was going on. Scarlet sumac had passed and the bees were dead. The pond had slicked overnight into that shiny and deceptive glaze of delusion, first ice. It made me remember sakes and conjure a vision of myself skimming backward on one foot, the other extended; the arms become wings. Minnesota girls know that this is not a difficult maneuver if one's limber and practices even a little after school before the boys claim the rink for hockey. I think I can still do it - one thinks many foolish things when November's bright sun skips over the entrancing first freeze.

A flock of sparrows reels through the air looking more like a flying net than seventy conscious birds, a black veil thrown on the wind. When one sparrow dodges, the whole net swerves, dips: one mind. Am I part of anything like that?

Maybe not. The last few years of my life have been characterized by stripping away, one by one, loves and communities that sustain the soul. A young colleague, new to my English department, recently asked me who I hang around with at school. &quot;Nobody,&quot; I had to say, feeling briefly ashamed. This solitude is one of the surprises of middle age, especially if one's youth has been rich in love and friendship and children. If you do your job right, children leave home; few communities can stand an individual's most pitiful, amateur truth telling. So the soul must stand in her own meager feathers and learn to fly - or simply take hopeful jumps into the wind.

In the Christian calendar, November 1 is the Feast of All Saints, a day honoring not only those who are known and recognized as enlightened souls, but more especially the unknowns, saints who walk beside us unrecognized down the millennia. In Buddhism, we honor the bodhisattvas - saints - who refuse enlightenment and return willingly to the wheel of karma to help other beings. Similarly, in Judaism, anonymous holy men pray the world from its well-merited destruction. We never know who is walking beside us, who is our spiritual teacher. That one - who annoys you so - pretends for a day that he's the one, your personal Obi Wan Kenobi. The first of November is a splendid, subversive holiday.

Imagine a hectic procession of revelers - the half-mad bag lady; a mumbling, scarred janitor whose ravaged face made the children turn away; the austere, unsmiling mother superior who seemed with great focus and clarity to do harm; a haunted music teacher, survivor of Auschwitz. I bring them before my mind's eye, these old firends of my soul, awakening to dance their day. Crazy saints; but who knows what was home in the heart? This is the feast of those who tried to take the path, so clumsily that no one knew or notice, the feast, indeed, of most of us.

It's an ugly woods, I was saying to myself, padding along a trail where other walkers had broken ground before me. And then I found an extraordinary bouquet. Someone had bound an offering of dry seed pods, yew, lyme grass, red berries, and brown fern and laid it on the path: &quot;nothing special,&quot; as Buddhists say, meaning &quot;everything.&quot; Gathered to formality, each dry stalk proclaimed a slant, an attitude, infinite shades of neutral.

All contemplative acts, silences, poems, honor the world this way. Brought together by the eye of love, a milkweed pod, a twig, allow us to see how things have been all along.  A feast of being." -- Mary Rose O'Reilley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162802-it-s-a-very-american-illness-the-idea-of-giving-yourself</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2013 09:11:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162802-it-s-a-very-american-illness-the-idea-of-giving-yourself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s a very American illness, the idea of giving yourself away entirely to the idea of working in order to achieve some sort of brass ring that usually involves people feeling some way about you – I mean, people wonder why we walk around feeling alienated and lonely and stressed out." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361150-i-d-like-to-be-the-sort-of-person-who-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2013 09:12:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361150-i-d-like-to-be-the-sort-of-person-who-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd like to be the sort of person who can enjoy things at the time, instead of having to go back in my head and enjoy them." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/817934-never-miss-a-party-good-for-the-nerves--like-celery</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 07:31:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/817934-never-miss-a-party-good-for-the-nerves--like-celery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never miss a party...good for the nerves--like celery." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7038-kiss-me-and-you-will-see-how-important-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 10:23:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7038-kiss-me-and-you-will-see-how-important-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kiss me, and you will see how important I am." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21847-there-is-nothing-i-would-not-do-for-those-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 10:08:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21847-there-is-nothing-i-would-not-do-for-those-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing I would not do for those who are really my friends. I have no notion of loving people by halves, it is not my nature." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2014 09:36:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460006-to-burn-with-desire-and-keep-quiet-about-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 20:32:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Federico García Lorca]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460006-to-burn-with-desire-and-keep-quiet-about-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To burn with desire and keep quiet about it is the greatest punishment we can bring on ourselves." -- Federico García Lorca]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240867-but-hurry-let-s-entwine-ourselves-as-one-our-mouth-broken</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 20:32:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Federico Garcia Lorca]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240867-but-hurry-let-s-entwine-ourselves-as-one-our-mouth-broken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But hurry, let's entwine ourselves as one, our mouth broken, our soul bitten by love, so time discovers us safely destroyed." -- Federico Garcia Lorca]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152237-i-ve-often-lost-myself-in-order-to-find-the-burn</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 20:32:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Federico García-Lorca]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152237-i-ve-often-lost-myself-in-order-to-find-the-burn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've often lost myself,
in order to find the burn that keeps everything awake" -- Federico García-Lorca]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2314-so-we-beat-on-boats-against-the-current-borne-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 11:38:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2314-so-we-beat-on-boats-against-the-current-borne-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So we beat on, boats against the current, borne back ceaselessly into the past." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79844-you-see-i-am-a-poet-and-not-quite-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 20:58:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Edna St. Vincent Millay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79844-you-see-i-am-a-poet-and-not-quite-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You see, I am a poet, and not quite right in the head, darling. It’s only that." -- Edna St. Vincent Millay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41849-what-would-they-say-if-they-knew-i-sit-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 06:38:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Lorine Niedecker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41849-what-would-they-say-if-they-knew-i-sit-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What would they say if they knew
I sit for two months
on six lines of poetry?" -- Lorine Niedecker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63746-i-m-not-brave-any-more-darling-i-m-all-broken-they-ve</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2014 11:44:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63746-i-m-not-brave-any-more-darling-i-m-all-broken-they-ve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’m not brave any more darling. I’m all broken. They’ve broken me." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169453-and-you-ll-always-love-me-won-t-you-yes-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2014 11:45:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169453-and-you-ll-always-love-me-won-t-you-yes-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And you'll always love me won't you?
Yes
And the rain won't make any difference? 
No" -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12878-just-because-you-re-naked-doesn-t-mean-you-re-sexy-just-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 12:59:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12878-just-because-you-re-naked-doesn-t-mean-you-re-sexy-just-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just because you're naked doesn't mean you're sexy. Just because you're cynical doesn't mean you're cool." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1248777-look-up-and-see-the-madness-organized-in-the-stars</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 08:10:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Kelli Russell Agodon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1248777-look-up-and-see-the-madness-organized-in-the-stars]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...look up and see the madness
organized in the stars." -- Kelli Russell Agodon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1248783-i-don-t-believe-we-should-carry-backup-plans-in-life-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 08:14:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Kelli Russell Agodon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1248783-i-don-t-believe-we-should-carry-backup-plans-in-life-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don’t believe we should carry backup
plans in life’s suitcase—

they’re too easy to unpack 
like living a life in yoga pants, 
so comfortable our hips spread
into new timezones..." -- Kelli Russell Agodon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1248793-to-suffer-together-is-to-suffer-with-beauty</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 08:20:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelli add a quote by Kelli Russell Agodon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1248793-to-suffer-together-is-to-suffer-with-beauty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To suffer together is to suffer 
with beauty..." -- Kelli Russell Agodon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
