<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/139406-lindsay]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/139406-lindsay" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2009 01:21:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/766-where-you-used-to-be-there-is-a-hole-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2009 01:21:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lindsay add a quote by Edna St. Vincent Millay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/766-where-you-used-to-be-there-is-a-hole-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where you used to be, there is a hole in the world, which I find myself constantly walking around in the daytime, and falling in at night.  I miss you like hell." -- Edna St. Vincent Millay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117884-i-have-gone-out-a-possessed-witch-haunting-the-black</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2009 01:23:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lindsay add a quote by Anne Sexton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117884-i-have-gone-out-a-possessed-witch-haunting-the-black]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have gone out, a possessed witch,
haunting the black air, braver at night;
dreaming evil, I have done my hitch
over the plain houses, light by light:
lonely thing, twelve-fingered, out of mind.
A woman like that is not a woman, quite.
I have been her kind.

I have found the warm caves in the woods,
filled them with skillets, carvings, shelves,
closets, silks, innumerable goods;
fixed the suppers for the worms and the elves:
whining, rearranging the disaligned.
A woman like that is misunderstood.
I have been her kind.

I have ridden in your cart, driver,
waved my nude arms at villages going by,
learning the last bright routes, survivor
where your flames still bite my thigh
and my ribs crack where your wheels wind.
A woman like that is not ashamed to die.
I have been her kind." -- Anne Sexton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69658-i-wish-in-the-past-i-had-tried-more-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 13:39:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lindsay add a quote by Chris Onstad]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69658-i-wish-in-the-past-i-had-tried-more-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish in the past I had tried more things 'cause now I know that being in trouble is a fake idea." -- Chris Onstad]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239094-it-comes-out-of-my-mouth-like-water-the-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 21:21:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lindsay add a quote by Jessica Blank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239094-it-comes-out-of-my-mouth-like-water-the-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It comes out of my mouth like water: the things he said at the beginning, what it's like to know a person's smell, the anxious catch that now has dulled to normal when I hold the pay phone and it rings and rings. How underneath I don't believe he's coming anymore, and I wish I could turn the air beside me into something solid to fill the hole he leaves. How sometimes when he'd touch me I'd go out onto the very edges of myself, far like on a tightrope or a plank, and balance knowing there was only air to catch me; how he'd hold me there till it got scary, sometimes longer, and it was realer and more raw than any thing I'd ever felt. How he would always close his eyes and seem so comfortable, casual even, and I was always amazed at that: how brave he must be for it not to scare him at all. How sometimes it broke me into two pieces, and I'd lie there under him naked and stretched out past my skin, and another me would watch from the ceiling. Even if it was too much I had to grow to hold it, because it belonged to me now, and I belonged to him, and if I let any of the pressure of it spill like water from my faucet mouth, it would all leak out and be gone from me forever. That's what he always said. " -- Jessica Blank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/528994-what-if-i-forgave-myself-i-thought-what-if-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 12:41:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lindsay add a quote by Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/528994-what-if-i-forgave-myself-i-thought-what-if-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What if I forgave myself? I thought. What if I forgave myself even though I'd done something I shouldn't have? What if I was a liar and a cheat and there was no excuse for what I'd done other than because it was what I wanted and needed to do? What if I was sorry, but if I could go back in time I wouldn't do anything differently than I had done? What if I'd actually wanted to fuck every one of those men? What if heroin taught me something? What if yes was the right answer instead of no? What if what made me do all those things everyone thought I shouldn't have done was what also had got me here? What if I was never redeemed? What if I already was?" -- Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
