<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/139599-kimberly]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/139599-kimberly" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 16:52:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215601-how-do-i-do-it-well-it-s-always-a-mystery</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 16:52:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Vandana Shiva]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215601-how-do-i-do-it-well-it-s-always-a-mystery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[How do I do it?] Well, it's always a mystery, because you don't know why you get depleted or recharged. But this much I know. I do not allow myself to be overcome by hopelessness, no matter how tough the situation. I believe that if you just do your little bit without thinking of the bigness of what you stand against, if you turn to the enlargement of your own capacities, just that itself creates new potential. And I've learned from the Bhagavad-Gita and other teachings of our culture to detach myself from the results of what I do, because those are not in my hands. The context is not in your control, but your commitment is yours to make, and you can make the deepest commitment with a total detachment about where it will take you. You want it to lead to a better world, and you shape your actions and take full responsibility for them, but then you have detachment. And that combination of deep passion and deep detachment allows me to take on the next challenge, because I don't cripple myself, I don't tie myself in knots. I function like a free being. I think getting that freedom is a social duty because I think we owe it to each not to burden each other with prescription and demands. I think what we owe each other is a celebration of life and to replace fear and hopelessness with fearlessness and joy." -- Vandana Shiva]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1262-love-does-not-begin-and-end-the-way-we-seem</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2011 22:27:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by James A. Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1262-love-does-not-begin-and-end-the-way-we-seem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love does not begin and end the way we seem to think it does. Love is a battle, love is a war; love is a growing up." -- James A. Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223846-29-elegant-things-a-white-coat-worn-over-a-violet</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2011 15:44:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Sei Shōnagon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223846-29-elegant-things-a-white-coat-worn-over-a-violet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["29. Elegant things

A white coat worn over a violet waist coat.
Duck eggs.
Shaved ice mixed with liana syrup and put in a new silver bowl.
A rosary of rock crystal.
Wisteria blossoms. Plum blossoms covered with snow.
A pretty child eating strawberries." -- Sei Shōnagon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
