<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/139749-jenn]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/139749-jenn" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 10:03:28 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67300-in-order-to-tell-you-a-story-about-who-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 10:03:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Annette Simmons]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67300-in-order-to-tell-you-a-story-about-who-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In order to tell you a story about who I am and why I am here, I must spend a little time asking myself...questions. This is usually done at a superficial level as quickly as possible.&quot;

The self-diagnostic process that finds meaningful stories scares the hell out of people who aren't sure they are living meaningful lives. Once they reflect, most people do find that their lives are plenty meaningful (if a little out of balance). However, the process of self-examination tests your faith that your organization and your group are basically good people with good intentions. Groups that avoid deep examination seem to be anxious that honest self-examination might expose hypocrisy or emptiness. I've found that anxiety to be overstated in most cases.&quot;

First attempts at group stories are often highly aspirational in that the story is more about who we wished we were, rather than who we are. Stories that aspire to more than we can back up risk sounding hypocritical.&quot;

When our stories are sought and found from the subjective statement that &quot;I have a lot to learn from other people&quot;, they invite difference...Gathering stories teaches you how to get outside your own experiences and experience life as others might." -- Annette Simmons]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69986-the-real-scholar-must-choose-truth-and-somehow-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 10:14:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Walter Prescott Webb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69986-the-real-scholar-must-choose-truth-and-somehow-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The real scholar must choose truth and somehow it is better if it is made so ugly that nobody could doubt its virginity." -- Walter Prescott Webb]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
