<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/140165-bart-everson]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/140165-bart-everson" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 19:53:53 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93716-he-uses-statistics-as-a-drunken-man-uses-lamp-posts-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 19:53:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bart add a quote by Andrew Lang]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93716-he-uses-statistics-as-a-drunken-man-uses-lamp-posts-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He uses statistics as a drunken man uses lamp-posts... for support rather than illumination." -- Andrew Lang]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102206-how-it-is-that-animals-understand-things-i-do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 05:25:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bart add a quote by Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102206-how-it-is-that-animals-understand-things-i-do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How it is that animals understand things I do not know, but it is certain that they do understand. Perhaps there is a language which is not made of words and everything in the world understands it. Perhaps there is a soul hidden in everything and it can always speak, without even making a sound, to another soul." -- Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/528455-so-you-are-tired-of-your-life-young-man-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 07:43:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bart add a quote by Marie Corelli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/528455-so-you-are-tired-of-your-life-young-man-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So you are tired of your life, young man! All the more reason have you to live. Anyone can die. A murderer has moral force enough to jeer at his hangman. It is very easy to draw the last breath. It can be accomplished successfully by a child or a warrior. One pang of far less anguish than the toothache, and all is over. There is nothing heroic about it, I assure you! It is as common as going to bed; it is almost prosy. &lt;em&gt;Life&lt;/em&gt; is heroism, if you like; but death is a mere cessation of business. And to make a rapid and rude exit off the stage before the prompter gives the sign is always, to say the least of it, ungraceful. Act the part out, no matter how bad the play. What say you?" -- Marie Corelli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186466-all-men-dream-but-not-equally-those-who-dream-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 07:49:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bart add a quote by Thomas E. Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186466-all-men-dream-but-not-equally-those-who-dream-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All men dream, but not equally. Those who dream by night in the dusty recesses of their minds, wake in the day to find that it was vanity: but the dreamers of the day are dangerous men, for they may act on their dreams with open eyes, to make them possible. " -- Thomas E. Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11340-all-men-dream-but-not-equally-those-who-dream-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 07:50:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bart add a quote by T.E. Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11340-all-men-dream-but-not-equally-those-who-dream-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All men dream:  but not equally.  Those who dream by night in the dusty recesses of their minds wake up in the day to find it was vanity, but the dreamers of the day are dangerous men, for they may act their dreams with open eyes, to make it possible." -- T.E. Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/631286-for-the-last-century-almost-all-top-political-appointments-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 09:31:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bart add a quote by Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/631286-for-the-last-century-almost-all-top-political-appointments-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the last century, almost all top political appointments [on the planet Earth] had been made by random computer selection from the pool of individuals who had the necessary qualifications. It had taken the human race several thousand years to realize that there were some jobs that should never be given to the people who volunteered for them, especially if they showed too much enthusiasm. As one shrewed political commentator had remarked: “We want a President who has to be carried screaming and kicking into the White House — but will then do the best job he possibly can, so that he’ll get time off for good behavior." -- Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84842-one-life-is-all-we-have-and-we-live-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 10:30:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bart add a quote by Joan of Arc]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84842-one-life-is-all-we-have-and-we-live-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One life is all we have and we live it as we believe in living it. But to sacrifice what you are and to live without belief, that is a fate more terrible than dying." -- Joan of Arc]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/551184-there-is-something-pagan-in-me-that-i-cannot-shake</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 12:05:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bart add a quote by Lord Byron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/551184-there-is-something-pagan-in-me-that-i-cannot-shake]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...there is something Pagan in me that I cannot shake off. In short, I deny nothing, but doubt everything." -- Lord Byron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4078-the-saddest-aspect-of-life-right-now-is-that-science</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 15:55:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bart add a quote by Isaac Asimov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4078-the-saddest-aspect-of-life-right-now-is-that-science]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The saddest aspect of life right now is that science gathers knowledge faster than society gathers wisdom." -- Isaac Asimov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26758-the-things-that-make-us-happy-make-us-wise</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 17:08:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bart add a quote by John Crowley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26758-the-things-that-make-us-happy-make-us-wise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The things that make us happy make us wise.  " -- John Crowley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195956-call-me-ishmael-some-years-ago---never-mind-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2013 06:53:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bart add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195956-call-me-ishmael-some-years-ago---never-mind-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Call me Ishmael. Some years ago - never mind how long precisely - having little or no money in my purse, and nothing particular to interest me on shore, I thought I would sail about a little and see the watery part of the world. It is a way I have of driving off the spleen, and regulating the circulation. Whenever I find myself growing grim about the mouth; whenever it is a damp, drizzly November in my soul; whenever I find myself involuntarily pausing before coffin warehouses, and bringing up the rear of every funeral I meet; and especially whenever my hypos get such an upper hand of me, that it requires a strong moral principle to prevent me from deliberately stepping into the street, and methodically knocking people's hats off - then, I account it high time to get to sea as soon as I can. This is my substitute for pistol and ball. With a philosophical flourish Cato throws himself upon his sword; I quietly take to the ship." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26967-and-what-is-so-rare-as-a-day-in-june</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 16:53:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bart add a quote by James Russell Lowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26967-and-what-is-so-rare-as-a-day-in-june]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["AND what is so rare as a day in June?
      Then, if ever, come perfect days;
Then Heaven tries earth if it be in tune,
     And over it softly her warm ear lays;
Whether we look, or whether we listen,
We hear life murmur, or see it glisten;" -- James Russell Lowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/760902-we-but-mirror-the-world-all-the-tendencies-present-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 13:22:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bart add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/760902-we-but-mirror-the-world-all-the-tendencies-present-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We but mirror the world. All the tendencies present in the outer world are to be found in the world of our body. If we could change ourselves, the tendencies in the world would also change. As a man changes his own nature, so does the attitude of the world change towards him. This is the divine mystery supreme. A wonderful thing it is and the source of our happiness. We need not wait to see what others do." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508603-in-the-midst-of-winter-i-found-there-was-within</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 12:36:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bart add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508603-in-the-midst-of-winter-i-found-there-was-within]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the midst of winter, I found there was, within me, an invincible summer.

And that makes me happy. For it says that no matter how hard the world pushes against me, within me, there’s something stronger – something better, pushing right back." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1235421-when-a-young-man-who-has-been-going-to-church</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 07:35:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bart add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1235421-when-a-young-man-who-has-been-going-to-church]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a young man who has been going to church in a routine way honestly realises that he does not believe in Christianity and stops going — provided he does it for honesty's sake and not just to annoy his parents — the spirit of Christ is probably nearer to him than it ever was before." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
