<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/140567-catharine]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/140567-catharine" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 13:40:26 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40501-enjoy-the-power-and-beauty-of-your-youth-oh-nevermind</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 13:40:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catharine add a quote by Baz Luhrmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40501-enjoy-the-power-and-beauty-of-your-youth-oh-nevermind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Enjoy the power and beauty of your youth; oh nevermind; you will not 
understand the power and beauty of your youth until they have faded. 
But trust me, in 20 years you’ll look back at photos of yourself and 
recall in a way you can’t grasp now how much possibility lay before 
you and how fabulous you really looked….You’re not as fat as you 
imagine. Don’t worry about the future; or worry, but know that worrying is as 
effective as trying to solve an algebra equation by chewing 
bubblegum. The real troubles in your life are apt to be things that 
never crossed your worried mind; the kind that blindside you at 4pm 
on some idle Tuesday. Do one thing everyday that scares you Sing Don’t be reckless with other people’s hearts, don’t put up with 
people who are reckless with yours. Floss Don’t waste your time on jealousy; sometimes you’re ahead, sometimes 
you’re behind…the race is long, and in the end, it’s only with 
yourself. Remember the compliments you receive, forget the insults; if you 
succeed in doing this, tell me how. Keep your old love letters, throw away your old bank statements. Stretch Don’t feel guilty if you don’t know what you want to do with your 
life…the most interesting people I know didn’t know at 22 what they 
wanted to do with their lives, some of the most interesting 40 year 
olds I know still don’t. Get plenty of calcium. Be kind to your knees, you’ll miss them when they’re gone. Maybe you’ll marry, maybe you won’t, maybe you’ll have children,maybe 
you won’t, maybe you’ll divorce at 40, maybe you’ll dance the funky 
chicken on your 75th wedding anniversary…what ever you do, don’t 
congratulate yourself too much or berate yourself either – your 
choices are half chance, so are everybody else’s. Enjoy your body, 
use it every way you can…don’t be afraid of it, or what other people 
think of it, it’s the greatest instrument you’ll ever 
own.. Dance…even if you have nowhere to do it but in your own living room. Read the directions, even if you don’t follow them. Do NOT read beauty magazines, they will only make you feel ugly. Get to know your parents, you never know when they’ll be gone for 
good. Be nice to your siblings; they are the best link to your past and the 
people most likely to stick with you in the future. Understand that friends come and go,but for the precious few you 
should hold on. Work hard to bridge the gaps in geography and 
lifestyle because the older you get, the more you need the people you 
knew when you were young." -- Baz Luhrmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 06:57:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catharine add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 06:58:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catharine add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be the change that you wish to see in the world." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 06:58:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catharine add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one can make you feel inferior without your consent." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 06:58:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catharine add a quote by Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Insanity is doing the same thing, over and over again, but expecting different results." -- Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467-life-is-what-happens-to-you-while-you-re-busy-making</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 13:52:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catharine add a quote by Allen Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467-life-is-what-happens-to-you-while-you-re-busy-making]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is what happens to you while you're busy making other plans." -- Allen Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 08:07:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catharine add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 08:08:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catharine add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/987-there-are-only-two-ways-to-live-your-life-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 08:08:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catharine add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/987-there-are-only-two-ways-to-live-your-life-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are only two ways to live your life. One is as though nothing is a miracle. The other is as though everything is a miracle." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12221-because-we-don-t-know-when-we-will-die-we-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2011 01:07:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catharine add a quote by Paul Bowles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12221-because-we-don-t-know-when-we-will-die-we-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because we don't know when we will die, we get to think of life as an inexhaustible well. Yet everything happens only a certain number of times, and a very small number really. How many more times will you remember a certain afternoon of your childhood, an afternoon that is so deeply a part of your being that you can't even conceive of your life without it? Perhaps four, five times more, perhaps not even that. How many more times will you watch the full moon rise? Perhaps 20. And yet it all seems limitless." -- Paul Bowles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265356-all-sorrows-can-be-born-if-you-put-them-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 06:37:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catharine add a quote by Isak Dinesen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265356-all-sorrows-can-be-born-if-you-put-them-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All sorrows can be born if you put them in a story or tell a story about them." -- Isak Dinesen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
