<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/140816-jon]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/140816-jon" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 22:16:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408505-you-like-all-animals-at-that-moment-although-no-doubt</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 22:16:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408505-you-like-all-animals-at-that-moment-although-no-doubt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You like all animals at that moment, although no doubt you will one day choose your favorites. Your own nature will triumph. We are all born with our natures. You popped out of your mother’s belly, I saw your eyes, and I knew that you were already you. And I think back over my own life and I realize that my own nature--the core me--essentially hasn’t changed over all these years. When I wake up in the morning, for those first few moments before I remember where I am or when I am, I still feel the same way I did when I woke up at the age of five. Sometimes I wonder if natures can be changed at all of if we are stuck with them as surely as a dog wants bones or as a cat chases mice." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257125-kekul-dreams-the-great-serpent-holding-its-own-tail-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 01:27:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257125-kekul-dreams-the-great-serpent-holding-its-own-tail-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kekulé dreams the Great Serpent holding its own tail in its mouth, the dreaming Serpent which surrounds the World. But the meanness, the cynicism with which this dream is to be used. The Serpent that announces, &quot;The World is a closed thing, cyclical, resonant, eternally-returning,&quot; is to be delivered into a system whose only aim is to violate the Cycle. Taking and not giving back, demanding that &quot;productivity&quot; and &quot;earnings&quot; keep on increasing with time, the System removing from the rest of the World these vast quantities of energy to keep its own tiny desperate fraction showing a profit: and not only most of humanity—most of the World, animal, vegetable, and mineral, is laid waste in the process. The System may or may not understand that it's only buying time. And that time is an artificial resource to begin with, of no value to anyone or anything but the System, which must sooner or later crash to its death, when its addiction to energy has become more than the rest of the World can supply, dragging with it innocent souls all along the chain of life. Living inside the System is like riding across the country in a bus driven by a maniac bent on suicide . . . though he's amiable enough, keeps cracking jokes back through the loudspeaker . . ." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/421465-that-what-appears-to-be-egoism-so-often-isn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2012 16:21:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/421465-that-what-appears-to-be-egoism-so-often-isn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That what appears to be egoism so often isn't." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371203-the-next-suitable-person-you-re-in-light-conversation-with-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2012 16:21:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371203-the-next-suitable-person-you-re-in-light-conversation-with-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The next suitable person you’re in light conversation with, you stop suddenly in the middle of the conversation and look at the person closely and say, “What’s wrong?” You say it in a concerned way.  He’ll say, “What do you mean?” You say, “Something’s wrong. I can tell. What is it?” And he’ll look stunned and say, “How did you know?” He doesn’t realize something’s always wrong, with everybody. Often more than one thing. He doesn’t know everybody’s always going around all the time with something wrong and believing they’re exerting great willpower and control to keep other people, for whom they think nothing’s ever wrong, from seeing it." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/567622-do-you-suppose-it-s-so-much-easier-to-make-conversation</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2012 16:24:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/567622-do-you-suppose-it-s-so-much-easier-to-make-conversation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you suppose it's so much easier to make conversation with someone you already know well than with someone you don't know at all primarily because of all the previously exchanged information and shared experiences between two people who know each other well, or because maybe it's only with people we already know well and know know us well that we don't go through the awkward mental process of subjecting everything we think of saying or bringing up as a topic of light conversation to a self-conscious critical analysis and evaluation that manages to make anything we think of proposing to say the other person seem dull or stupid or banal or on the other hand maybe overly intimate or tension-producing?" -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136690-fickt-nicht-mit-dem-raketemensch</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 22:29:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136690-fickt-nicht-mit-dem-raketemensch]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fickt nicht mit dem Raketemensch!" -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427531-i-have-a-strong-propensity-in-me-to-begin-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2013 17:31:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Laurence Sterne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427531-i-have-a-strong-propensity-in-me-to-begin-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have a strong propensity in me to begin this chapter very nonsensically, and I will not balk my fancy.--Accordingly I set off thus:" -- Laurence Sterne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237758-when-they-were-introduced-he-made-a-witticism-hoping-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 22:17:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237758-when-they-were-introduced-he-made-a-witticism-hoping-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When they were introduced, he made a witticism, hoping to be liked. She laughed extremely hard, hoping to be liked. Then each drove home alone, staring straight ahead, with the very same twist to their faces.

The man who'd introduced them didn't much like either of them, though he acted as if he did, anxious as he was to preserve good relations at all times. One never knew, after all, now did one now did one now did one." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420886-their-boredom-becomes-more-and-more-terrible-they-realize-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 19:52:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Nathanael West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420886-their-boredom-becomes-more-and-more-terrible-they-realize-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Their boredom becomes more and more terrible. They realize that they’ve been tricked and burn with resentment. Every day of their lives they read the newspapers and went to the movies. Both fed them on lynchings, murder, sex crimes, explosions, wrecks, love nests, fires, miracles, revolutions, war. This daily diet made sophisticates of them. The sun is a joke. Oranges can’t titillate their jaded palates. Nothing can ever be violent enough to make taut their slack minds and bodies. They have been cheated and betrayed. They have slaved and saved for nothing." -- Nathanael West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606595-perhaps-i-can-make-you-understand-let-s-start-from-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 19:53:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Nathanael West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606595-perhaps-i-can-make-you-understand-let-s-start-from-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps I can make you understand. Let’s start from the beginning. A man is hired to give advice to the readers of a newspaper. The job is a circulation stunt and the whole staff considers it a joke. He welcomes the job, for it might lead to a gossip column, and anyway he’s tired of being a leg man. He too considers the job a joke, but after several months at it, the joke begins to escape him. He sees that the majority of the letters are profoundly humble pleas for moral and spiritual advice, and they are inarticulate expressions of genuine suffering. He also discovers that his correspondents take him seriously. For the first time in his life, he is forced to examine the values by which he lives. This examination shows him that he is the victim of the joke and not its perpetrator." -- Nathanael West]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
