<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/140928-kathy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/140928-kathy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 14:34:44 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21796-enjoy-every-sandwich</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 14:34:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Warren Zevon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21796-enjoy-every-sandwich]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Enjoy every sandwich." -- Warren Zevon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7558-art-never-responds-to-the-wish-to-make-it-democratic</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 17:21:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7558-art-never-responds-to-the-wish-to-make-it-democratic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Art never responds to the wish to make it democratic; it is not for everybody; it is only for those who are willing to undergo the effort needed to understand it." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1921-tell-me-what-is-it-you-plan-to-do-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 09:47:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1921-tell-me-what-is-it-you-plan-to-do-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tell me, what is it you plan to do 
with your one wild and precious life?" -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1288-i-don-t-know-about-you-but-i-m-kind-of-fed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 17:53:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Audrey Niffenger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1288-i-don-t-know-about-you-but-i-m-kind-of-fed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know about you, but I'm kind of fed up with realism. After all, there's enough reality already; why make more of it? Why not leave realism for the memoirs of drug addicts, the histories of salt, the biographies of porn stars? Why must we continue to read about the travails of divorced people or mildly depressed Canadians when we could be contemplating the shopping habits of zombies, or the difficulties that ensue when living and dead people marry each other? We should be demanding more stories about faery handbags and pyjamas inscribed with the diaries of strange women. We should not rest until someone writes about a television show that features the Free People's World-Tree Library, with its elaborate waterfalls and Forbidden Books and Pirate-Magicians. We should be pining for a house haunted by rabbits." -- Audrey Niffenger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52044-we-are-traditionally-rather-proud-of-ourselves-for-having-slipped</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 09:38:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52044-we-are-traditionally-rather-proud-of-ourselves-for-having-slipped]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are traditionally rather proud of ourselves for having slipped creative work in there between the domestic chores and obligations. I'm not sure we deserve such big A-pluses for all that." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1313-alice-heard-a-woman-say-before-i-start-writing-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2008 19:08:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Joy Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1313-alice-heard-a-woman-say-before-i-start-writing-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alice heard a woman say, 'Before I start writing I feel affectionate, interested, and frustrated. In that order. Afterwards I feel relieved, disgusted, and confused. Sometimes I don't think it's worth it." -- Joy Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31911-mornings-out-in-the-garden-she-would-at-times-read</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2008 19:09:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Joy Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31911-mornings-out-in-the-garden-she-would-at-times-read]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mornings, out in the garden, she would, at times, read aloud from one of her many overdue library books. Dew as radiant as angel spit glittered on the petals of Jack's roses. Jack was quite the gardener. Miriam thought she knew why her particularly favored roses. The inside of a rose does not at all correspond with its exterior beauty. If one tears off all the petals of the corolla, all that remains is a sordid-looking tuft. Roses would be right up Jack's alley, all right.

&quot;Here's something for you, Jack,&quot; Miriam said. You'll appreciate this. Beckett describes tears as 'liquified brain.'

&quot;God, Miriam,&quot; Jack said. &quot;Why are you sharing that with me? Look at this day, it's a beautiful day! Stop pumping out the cesspit! Leave the cesspit alone!" -- Joy Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/332176-swirled-tight-trussed-manic-most-trusted-you-love-hills-swells</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 14:11:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Carol Guess]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/332176-swirled-tight-trussed-manic-most-trusted-you-love-hills-swells]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Swirled tight, trussed, manic, most trusted. You love hills, swells, waves of sand, waves of water. You love traffic on bridges that might split in two. You love stairs leading to stairs leading to ice cream stands. Shards of pottery as good as a map. You love fractured control towers and the very broken Alaskan Way Viaduct.  You love squat corner stores and barber-pole signs. You love the idea of privacy in a city of windows, the idea of light in a city of shadows." -- Carol Guess]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/664320-hat-s-the-paradox-the-only-time-most-people-feel-alive</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2012 10:41:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Ted Hughes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/664320-hat-s-the-paradox-the-only-time-most-people-feel-alive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["hat’s the paradox: the only time most people feel alive is when they’re suffering, when something overwhelms their ordinary, careful armour, and the naked child is flung out onto the world. That’s why the things that are worst to undergo are best to remember. But when that child gets buried away under their adaptive and protective shells—he becomes one of the walking dead, a monster. So when you realise you’ve gone a few weeks and haven’t felt that awful struggle of your childish self — struggling to lift itself out of its inadequacy and incompetence — you’ll know you’ve gone some weeks without meeting new challenge, and without growing, and that you’ve gone some weeks towards losing touch with yourself. The only calibration that counts is how much heart people invest, how much they ignore their fears of being hurt or caught out or humiliated. And the only thing people regret is that they did’t live boldly enough, that they didn’t invest enough heart, didn’t love enough. Nothing else really counts at all." -- Ted Hughes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131591-nothing-is-original-steal-from-anywhere-that-resonates-with-inspiration</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2012 17:46:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Jim Jarmusch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131591-nothing-is-original-steal-from-anywhere-that-resonates-with-inspiration]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing is original. Steal from anywhere that resonates with inspiration or fuels your imagination. Devour old films, new films, music, books, paintings, photographs, poems, dreams, random conversations, architecture, bridges, street signs, trees, clouds, bodies of water, light and shadows. Select only things to steal from that speak directly to your soul. If you do this, your work (and theft) will be authentic. Authenticity is invaluable; originality is non-existent. And don’t bother concealing your thievery - celebrate it if you feel like it. In any case, always remember what Jean-Luc Godard said: “It’s not where you take things from - it’s where you take them to.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;MovieMaker Magazine&lt;/i&gt; #53 - Winter, January 22, 2004 ]" -- Jim Jarmusch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/500042-writers-fish-for-the-right-words-like-fishermen-fish-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 07:21:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Jarod Kintz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/500042-writers-fish-for-the-right-words-like-fishermen-fish-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writers fish for the right words like fishermen fish for, um, whatever those aquatic creatures with fins and gills are called.  " -- Jarod Kintz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485209-set-wide-the-window-let-me-drink-the-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 10:05:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485209-set-wide-the-window-let-me-drink-the-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Set wide the window. Let me drink the day." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/718290-you-re-supposed-to-expand-your-mind-to-fit-the-art</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 17:01:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Steven Soderbergh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/718290-you-re-supposed-to-expand-your-mind-to-fit-the-art]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You’re supposed to expand your mind to fit the art, you’re not supposed to chop the art down to fit your mind." -- Steven Soderbergh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129764-so-much-of-science-proceeds-by-telling-stories</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 06:30:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Stephen J. Gould]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129764-so-much-of-science-proceeds-by-telling-stories]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So much of science proceeds by telling stories." -- Stephen J. Gould]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173916-i-want-art-that-makes-the-world-seem-more-unreal</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2014 07:11:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Lincoln Michel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173916-i-want-art-that-makes-the-world-seem-more-unreal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want art that makes the world seem more unreal. I want fiction that can crumble the world and build it back into something new." -- Lincoln Michel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1212534-in-my-experience-cutting-back-is-the-crucial-act-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 07:39:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Pamela Erens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1212534-in-my-experience-cutting-back-is-the-crucial-act-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In my experience, cutting back is the crucial act that allows the vitality, precision and emotional heart of a piece of writing to emerge." -- Pamela Erens]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
