<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/141004-melissa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/141004-melissa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 21:06:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60487-all-of-the-designers-i-have-met-up-to-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 21:06:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by David Rakoff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60487-all-of-the-designers-i-have-met-up-to-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All of the designers I have met up to this point have been very nice, although upon being introduced to Karl Lagerfeld, he looks me up and down and dismisses me with the not super-kind, &quot;What can you write that hasn't been written already?&quot; 

He's absolutely right, I have no idea. I can but try. The only thing I can come up with right now is that Lagerfeld's powdered white ponytail has dusted the shoulders of his suit with what looks like dandruff but isn't....seated on a tiny velvet chair, with his large doughy rump dominating the miniature piece of furniture like a loose, flabby, ass-flavored muffin over-risen from its pan, he resembles a Daumier caricature of some corpulent, overfed, inhumane oligarch drawn sitting on a commode, stuffing his greedy throat with the corpses of dead children, while from his other end he shits out huge, malodorous piles of tainted money. How's that for new and groundbreaking, Mr. L.?
" -- David Rakoff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282608-the-connections-we-make-in-the-course-of-a-life--maybe</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 12:05:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Fred Rogers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282608-the-connections-we-make-in-the-course-of-a-life--maybe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The connections we make in the course of a life--maybe that's what heaven is." -- Fred Rogers]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
