<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/142097-laini]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/142097-laini" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 10:33:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102198-books-have-to-be-read-worse-luck-it-takes-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 10:33:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laini add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102198-books-have-to-be-read-worse-luck-it-takes-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books have to be read (worse luck it takes so long a time). It is the only way of discovering what they contain. A few savage tribes eat them, but reading is the only method of assimilation revealed to the West." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108071-sir-the-fact-that-the-book-is-in-a-public</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 14:59:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laini add a quote by Harold Laski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108071-sir-the-fact-that-the-book-is-in-a-public]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sir, the fact that the book is in a public library brings no comfort.Books are the one element in which I am personally and nakedly acquisitive. If it weren't for the law I would steal them. If it weren't for my purse I would buy them." -- Harold Laski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84171-critics-who-treat-adult-as-a-term-of-approval-instead</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2009 08:10:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laini add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84171-critics-who-treat-adult-as-a-term-of-approval-instead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Critics who treat 'adult' as a term of approval, instead of as a merely descriptive term, cannot be adult themselves. To be concerned about being grown up, to admire the grown up because it is grown up, to blush at the suspicion of being childish; these things are the marks of childhood and adolescence. And in childhood and adolescence they are, in moderation, healthy symptoms. Young things ought to want to grow. But to carry on into middle life or even into early manhood this concern about being adult is a mark of really arrested development. When I was ten, I read fairy tales in secret and would have been ashamed if I had been found doing so. Now that I am fifty I read them openly. When I became a man I put away childish things, including the fear of childishness and the desire to be very grown up." -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
