<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/14208-dave-schumaker]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/14208-dave-schumaker" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2010 10:40:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102209-it-took-me-a-long-time-and-most-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2010 10:40:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Gregory David Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102209-it-took-me-a-long-time-and-most-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It took me a long time and most of the world to learn what I know about love and fate and the choices we make, but the heart of it came to me in an instant, while I was chained to a wall and being tortured. I realised, somehow, through the screaming of my mind, that even in that shackled, bloody helplessness, I was still free: free to hate the men who were torturing me, or to forgive them. It doesn’t sound like much, I know. But in the flinch and bite of the chain, when it’s all you’ve got, that freedom is an universe of possibility. And the choice you make between hating and forgiving, can become the story of your life." -- Gregory David Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18373-tune-your-television-to-any-channel-it-doesn-t-receive-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 12:41:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18373-tune-your-television-to-any-channel-it-doesn-t-receive-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tune your television to any channel it doesn't receive and about 1 percent of the dancing static you see is accounted for by this ancient remnant of the Big Bang. The next time you complain that there is nothing on, remember that you can always watch the birth of the universe." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286185-no-geologist-worth-anything-is-permanently-bound-to-a-desk</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 10:44:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286185-no-geologist-worth-anything-is-permanently-bound-to-a-desk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No Geologist worth anything is permanently bound to a desk or laboratory, but the charming notion that true science can only be based on unbiased observation of nature in the raw is mythology. Creative work, in geology and anywhere else, is interaction and synthesis: half-baked ideas from a bar room, rocks in the field, chains of thought from lonely walks, numbers squeezed from rocks in a laboratory, numbers from a calculator riveted to a desk, fancy equipment usually malfunctioning on expensive ships, cheap equipment in the human cranium, arguments before a road cut." -- Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/493251-maybe-ever-body-in-the-whole-damn-world-is-scared-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 13:04:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/493251-maybe-ever-body-in-the-whole-damn-world-is-scared-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe ever’body in the whole damn world is scared of each other." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/918190-you-know-how-you-finish-a-bag-of-chips-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 12:40:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/918190-you-know-how-you-finish-a-bag-of-chips-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know how you finish a bag of chips and you hate yourself? You know you’ve done nothing good for yourself. That’s the same feeling, and you know it is, after some digital binge. You feel wasted and hollow and diminished." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1121438-the-longest-golf-drive-recorded-was-hit-on-the-moon</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 23:33:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1121438-the-longest-golf-drive-recorded-was-hit-on-the-moon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The longest golf drive recorded was hit on the moon. Man has yet to return to the Challenger Deep. The lesson from this is that it is easier for human beings to push outwards than it is for them to explore inwards. The wind that carries you away like a kite will blow you on your back if you turn to face it. Consider how the surface area of a balloon grows when air is blown into it. When we push out, we create new frontiers we might populate. When we take the air out of a balloon, it deflates, and becomes shrivelled." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
