<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/142801-gale-martin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/142801-gale-martin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 17:58:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/544806-there-was-before-her-and-now-there-is-after-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 17:58:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gale add a quote by John Burnham Schwartz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/544806-there-was-before-her-and-now-there-is-after-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was before her and now there is after her, and that is the difference in my life." -- John Burnham Schwartz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/544808-i-sat-thinking-how-it-was-she-who-d-mentioned-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 17:57:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gale add a quote by John Burnham Schwartz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/544808-i-sat-thinking-how-it-was-she-who-d-mentioned-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I sat thinking. How it was she who'd mentioned love first. How she seemed to be waiting, the door still between us, for me to act. And I imagined that if I reached for her I would find her where she lay waiting in the water, and my fingers would glide over her bare wet skin until every inch of her, every crook and hollow, would become mine. I would vouch for her with my life." -- John Burnham Schwartz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204349-inaction-is-not-the-same-thing-as-patience-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 17:58:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gale add a quote by John Burnham Schwartz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204349-inaction-is-not-the-same-thing-as-patience-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Inaction is not the same thing as patience. It is instead a kind of perpetual waiting room, a sterile holding pen for unlived desire, a negative sanctuary. You wait and wait, but the receptionist is very stern and, somehow, the appointment book always full. To make matters worse, crowded into the adjoining cell like so many desperate immigrants, and separated from you by nothing more than the thin permeable wall of your own fear, are all the anticipated rejections of your life. You would think it might be noisy in there, but you'd be wrong. It is totally silent. There's a small Plexiglas window through which you can study these things, this silence, if you have the inclination and the nerve. And eventually, if you have been a diligent enough student and not wasted your time in dreaming, you come to understand that it is not the rejections that make this a prison, not the defeats, but rather your own grim expectation of defeat; not life but its bodily outline drawn in chalk, where the body should be but isn't, where it once was, this ingrained cowardly pessimism, this relentless betting against love and instinct. This is where the silence comes from." -- John Burnham Schwartz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2384-moral-indignation-is-jealousy-with-a-halo</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 17:53:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gale add a quote by H.G. Wells]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2384-moral-indignation-is-jealousy-with-a-halo]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Moral indignation is jealousy with a halo." -- H.G. Wells]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1120971-if-you-ve-ever-grown-zucchini-you-know-they-all-ripen</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 18:41:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gale add a quote by Gale Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1120971-if-you-ve-ever-grown-zucchini-you-know-they-all-ripen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you’ve ever grown zucchini, you know they all ripen the same day. You wait all of June and July for zucchini. August rolls around, and one day—bam! You have more zucchini than you know what to do with. You start handing them out to your neighbors and friends at work because there’s no way any single person can handle all that zucchini. Not even if you’re smart and resourceful and have accumulated dozens of good recipes, not even a person who likes zucchini as much as I do.--Grace Savage" -- Gale Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1145681-for-a-woman-to-be-taken-as-seriously-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 19:12:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gale add a quote by Gale Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1145681-for-a-woman-to-be-taken-as-seriously-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For a woman to be taken as seriously as a man she must be three times as effective. Happily, this is not difficult.--Simone de Beauvoir" -- Gale Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
