<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/144329-rebeck]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/144329-rebeck" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 01:30:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39364-there-is-enough-mystery-in-the-facts-as-we-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 01:30:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rebeck add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39364-there-is-enough-mystery-in-the-facts-as-we-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is enough mystery in the facts as we know them, enough of conspiracy, coincidence, loose ends, dead ends, multiple interpretations. There is no need […] to invent the grand and masterful scheme, the plot that reaches flawlessly in a dozen directions. - Agent Branch (58)" -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160125-stop-i-cried-imploringly-to-my-god-like-mind</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 01:38:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rebeck add a quote by John Kennedy Toole]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160125-stop-i-cried-imploringly-to-my-god-like-mind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stop!' I cried imploringly to my god-like mind." -- John Kennedy Toole]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122038-most-of-us-have-learned-to-be-dispassionate-about-evil</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 17:29:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rebeck add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122038-most-of-us-have-learned-to-be-dispassionate-about-evil]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most of us have learned to be dispassionate about evil, to look it in the face and find, as often as not, our own grinning reflections with which we do not argue, but good is another matter. Few have stared at that long enough to accept that its face too is grotesque, that in us the good is something under construction. The modes of evil usually receive worthy expression. The modes of good have to be satisfied with a cliche or a smoothing down that will soften their real look." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360617-some-days-i-feel-like-playing-it-smooth-some-days</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 00:54:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rebeck add a quote by Raymond Chandler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360617-some-days-i-feel-like-playing-it-smooth-some-days]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some days I feel like playing it smooth. Some days I feel like playing it like a waffle iron." -- Raymond Chandler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/509469-every-day-the-new-york-times-carries-a-motto-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2012 13:45:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rebeck add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/509469-every-day-the-new-york-times-carries-a-motto-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every day, the New York Times carries a motto in a box on its front page. &quot;All the News That's Fit to Print,&quot; it says. It's been saying it for decades, day in and day out. I imagine most readers of the canonical sheet have long ceased to notice this bannered and flaunted symbol of its mental furniture. I myself check every day to make sure that the bright, smug, pompous, idiotic claim is still there. Then I check to make sure that it still irritates me. If I can still exclaim, under my breath, why do they insult me and what do they take me for and what the hell is it supposed to mean unless it's as obviously complacent and conceited and censorious as it seems to be, then at least I know I still have a pulse. You may wish to choose a more rigorous mental workout but I credit this daily infusion of annoyance with extending my lifespan." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271995-i-was-the-shadow-of-the-waxwing-slain-by-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 23:24:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rebeck add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271995-i-was-the-shadow-of-the-waxwing-slain-by-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was the shadow of the waxwing slain
By the false azure in the windowpane;
I was the smudge of ashen fluff -and I
Lived on, flew on, in the reflected sky.
And from the inside, too, I'd duplicate
Myself, my lamp, an apple on a plate:
Uncurtaining the night, I'd let dark glass
Hang all the furniture above the grass,
And how delightful when a fall of snow
Covered my glimpse of lawn and reached up so
As to make chair and bed exactly stand
Upon that snow, out in that crystal land!" -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
