<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/145461-rindis]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/145461-rindis" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 10:52:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4454-three-rings-for-the-elven-kings-under-the-sky-seven-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 10:52:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by J. R. R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4454-three-rings-for-the-elven-kings-under-the-sky-seven-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Three Rings for the Elven-kings under the sky,
 Seven for the Dwarf-lords in halls of stone,
Nine for Mortal Men, doomed to die,
 One for the Dark Lord on his dark throne
In the Land of Mordor where the Shadows lie.
 One Ring to rule them all, One Ring to find them,
 One Ring to bring them all and in the darkness bind them.
In the Land of Mordor where the Shadows lie." -- J. R. R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1-the-story-so-far-in-the-beginning-the-universe-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 14:00:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1-the-story-so-far-in-the-beginning-the-universe-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The story so far:
In the beginning the Universe was created.
This has made a lot of people very angry and been widely regarded as a bad move." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/285-now-at-this-very-moment-i-knew-that-the-united</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 17:34:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/285-now-at-this-very-moment-i-knew-that-the-united]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now at this very moment I knew that the United States was in the war, up to the neck and in to the death. So we had won after all! ... How long the war would last or in what fashion it would end no man could tell, nor did I at this moment care ... We should not be wiped out. Our history would not come to an end ... Hitler's fate was sealed. Mussolini's fate was sealed. As for the Japanese, they would be ground to a powder. All the rest was merely the proper application of overwhelming force." -- Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/349-the-purpose-of-the-referee-is-to-present-obstacles-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 10:56:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Marc W. Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/349-the-purpose-of-the-referee-is-to-present-obstacles-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The purpose of the referee is to present obstacles for players to overcome as they go about seeking their goals, not to constantly make trouble for them. This is a subtle distinction, and one that many beginners have trouble with." -- Marc W. Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289-my-dinner-party-miles-grated-it-s-just-breaking-up-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 10:56:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289-my-dinner-party-miles-grated-it-s-just-breaking-up-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My dinner party,' Miles grated. 'It's just breaking up.' &lt;i&gt;And sinking. All souls feared lost.&lt;/i&gt;" -- Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/811-for-instance-on-the-planet-earth-man-had-always-assumed</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 10:56:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/811-for-instance-on-the-planet-earth-man-had-always-assumed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For instance, on the planet Earth, man had always assumed that he was more intelligent than dolphins because he had achieved so much&amp;mdash;the wheel, New York, wars and so on&amp;mdash;whilst all the dolphins had ever done was muck about in the water having a good time. But conversely, the dolphins had always believed that they were far more intelligent than man&amp;mdash;for precisely the same reasons." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240-reality-is-merely-an-illusion-albeit-a-very-persistent-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 10:56:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240-reality-is-merely-an-illusion-albeit-a-very-persistent-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reality is merely an illusion, albeit a very persistent one." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14168-no-one-would-have-believed-in-the-last-years-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 10:56:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by H.G. Wells]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14168-no-one-would-have-believed-in-the-last-years-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one would have believed in the last years of the nineteenth century that this world was being watched keenly and closely by intelligences greater than man's and yet as mortal as his own; that as men busied themselves about their various concerns they were scrutinised and studied, perhaps almost as narrowly as a man with a microscope might scrutinise the transient creatures that swarm and multiply in a drop of water." -- H.G. Wells]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1132-deserves-it-i-daresay-he-does-many-that-live-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 10:56:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1132-deserves-it-i-daresay-he-does-many-that-live-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Deserves it! I daresay he does. Many that live deserve death. And some that die deserve life. Can you give it to them? Then do not be too eager to deal out death in judgement. For even the very wise cannot see all ends." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21638-there-are-two-ways-of-constructing-a-software-design-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 10:56:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by C. A. R. Hoare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21638-there-are-two-ways-of-constructing-a-software-design-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two ways of constructing a software design: One way is to make it so simple that there are obviously no deficiencies, and the other way is to make it so complicated that there are no obvious deficiencies. The first method is far more difficult." -- C. A. R. Hoare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142700-you-re-a-hopeless-romantic-said-faber-it-would-be-funny</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 12:47:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142700-you-re-a-hopeless-romantic-said-faber-it-would-be-funny]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're a hopeless romantic,&quot; said Faber. &quot;It would be funny if it were not serious. It's not books you need, it's some of the things that once were in books. The same things could be in the 'parlor families' today. The same infinite detail and awareness could be projected through the radios, and televisors, but are not. No,no it's not books at all you're looking for! Take it where you can find it, in old phonograph records, old motion pictures, and in old friends; look for it in nature and look for it in yourself. Books were only one type or receptacle where we stored a lot of things we were afraid we might forget. There is nothing magical in them at all. The magic is only in what books say, how they stitched the patches of the universe together into one garment for us. Of course you couldn't know this, of course you still can't understand what i mean when i say all this. You are intuitively right, that's what counts." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277-everything-must-be-made-as-simple-as-possible-but-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 12:47:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277-everything-must-be-made-as-simple-as-possible-but-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything must be made as simple as possible. But not simpler." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120687-it-must-be-remembered-that-the-iliad-and-odyssey-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 10:58:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Nic Fields]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120687-it-must-be-remembered-that-the-iliad-and-odyssey-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It must be remembered that the &lt;i&gt;Iliad&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Odyssey&lt;/i&gt; were composed as epic tales and not as historical texts. To use Shakespeare's &lt;i&gt;Macbeth&lt;/i&gt; as a source for 11th-century Scottish politics would rather miss the point of the play, and the same is true of the Homeric epics." -- Nic Fields]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8667-it-takes-a-great-deal-of-bravery-to-stand-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 12:37:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8667-it-takes-a-great-deal-of-bravery-to-stand-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It takes a great deal of bravery to stand up to our enemies, but just as much to stand up to our friends." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23231-even-the-king-s-erkynguard-might-have-wished-to-be-elsewhere</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 12:37:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Tad Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23231-even-the-king-s-erkynguard-might-have-wished-to-be-elsewhere]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even the king's Erkynguard might have wished to be elsewhere, rather than here on this killing ground where duty brought them and loyalty prisoned them. Only the mercenaries were here by choice. To Simon, the minds of men who would come to this of their own will were suddenly as incomprehensible as the thoughts of spiders or lizards—less so, even, for the small creatures of the earth almost always fled from danger. These were madmen, Simon realized, and that was the direst problem of the world: that madmen should be strong and unafraid, so that they could force their will on the weak and peace-loving. If God allowed such madness to be, Simon could not help thinking, then He was an old god who had lost His grip." -- Tad Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1816-you-may-say-i-m-a-dreamer-but-i-m-not-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 10:57:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1816-you-may-say-i-m-a-dreamer-but-i-m-not-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may say I'm a dreamer, but I'm not the only one. I hope someday you'll join us. And the world will live as one." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126315-someday-i-must-read-this-scholar-everyone-he-seems-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 10:57:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Tamora Pierce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126315-someday-i-must-read-this-scholar-everyone-he-seems-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Someday I must read this scholar Everyone. He seems to have written so much--all of it wrong." -- Tamora Pierce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141837-you-fed-it-the-badger-sighed-sometimes-i-think-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 10:57:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Tamora Pierce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141837-you-fed-it-the-badger-sighed-sometimes-i-think-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You fed it.' The badger sighed. 'Sometimes I think you'll feed &lt;i&gt;anything&lt;/i&gt;." -- Tamora Pierce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32374-and-when-he-died-i-suddenly-realized-i-wasn-t-crying</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 10:57:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32374-and-when-he-died-i-suddenly-realized-i-wasn-t-crying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And when he died, I suddenly realized I wasn’t crying for him at all, but for the things he did. I cried because he would never do them again, he would never carve another piece of wood or help us raise doves and pigeons in the backyard or play the violin the way he did, or tell us jokes the way he did. He was part of us and when he died, all the actions stopped dead and there was no one to do them the way he did. He was individual. He was an important man. I’ve never gotten over his death. Often I think what wonderful carvings never came to birth because he died. How many jokes are missing from the world, and how many homing pigeons untouched by his hands? He shaped the world. He did things to the world. The world was bankrupted of ten million fine actions the night he passed on." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283628-english-is-the-product-of-a-saxon-warrior-trying-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 19:06:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by H. Beam Piper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283628-english-is-the-product-of-a-saxon-warrior-trying-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["English is the product of a Saxon warrior trying to make a date with an Angle bar-maid, and as such is no more legitimate than any of the other products of that conversation." -- H. Beam Piper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57121-we-ll-just-start-walking-today-and-see-the-world-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 19:06:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57121-we-ll-just-start-walking-today-and-see-the-world-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We'll just start walking today and see the world and the way the world walks around and talks, the way it really looks. I want to see everything now. And while none of it well be me when it goes in, after a while it'll all gather together inside and it'll be me. Look at the world out there, my God, my God, look at it out there, outside me, out there beyond my face and the only way to really touch it is to put it where it's finally me, where it's in the blood, where it pumps around a thousand times ten thousand a day. I get hold of it so it'll never run off. I'll hold onto the world tight some day. I've got one finger on it now; that's a beginning." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4804-and-wherever-men-are-fighting-against-barbarism-tyranny-and-massacre</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 19:06:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4804-and-wherever-men-are-fighting-against-barbarism-tyranny-and-massacre]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And wherever men are fighting against barbarism, tyranny, and massacre, for freedom, law, and honour, let them remember that the fame of their deeds, even though they themselves be exterminated, may perhaps be celebrated as long as the world rolls round." -- Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147314-to-the-greeks-the-macedonians-were-uncouth-semi-civilized-barbarians-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 19:05:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Nicholas Sekunda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147314-to-the-greeks-the-macedonians-were-uncouth-semi-civilized-barbarians-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To the Greeks [the Macedonians] were uncouth, semi-civilized barbarians. The Macedonians for their part despised the Greeks as effete, wishy-washy Greeklings. Both regarded the Thracians as scarcely capable of walking on their hind legs." -- Nicholas Sekunda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116993-why-aren-t-you-in-school-i-see-you-every-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 19:05:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116993-why-aren-t-you-in-school-i-see-you-every-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why aren't you in school? I see you every day wandering around.&quot;
&quot;Oh, they don't miss me,&quot; she said. &quot;I'm antisocial, they say. I don't mix. It's so strange. I'm very social indeed. It all depends on what you mean by social, doesn't it? Social to me means talking to you about things like this.&quot; She rattled some chestnuts that had fallen off the tree in the front yard. &quot;Or talking about how strange the world is. Being with people is nice. But I don't think it's social to get a bunch of people together and then not let them talk, do you? An hour of TV class, an hour of basketball or baseball or running, another hour of transcription history or painting pictures, and more sports, but do you know, we never ask questions, or at least most don't; they just run the answers at you, bing, bing, bing, and us sitting there for four more hours of film-teacher. That's not social to me at all. It's a lot of funnels and lot of water poured down the spout and out the bottom, and them telling us it's wine when it's not. They run us so ragged by the end of the day we can't do anything but go to bed or head for a Fun Park to bully people around, break windowpanes in the Window Smasher place or wreck cars in the Car Wrecker place with the big steel ball.  Or go out in the cars and race on the streets, trying to see how close you can get to lampposts, playing 'chicken' and 'knock hubcaps.'  I guess I'm everything they say I am, all right. I haven't any friends. That's supposed to prove I'm abnormal.  But everyone I know is either shouting or dancing around like wild or beating up one another.  Do you notice how people hurt each other nowadays?" -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21606-the-most-sophisticated-people-i-know---inside-they-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 15:19:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Jim Henson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21606-the-most-sophisticated-people-i-know---inside-they-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most sophisticated people I know - inside they are all children. " -- Jim Henson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4788-personally-i-m-always-ready-to-learn-although-i-do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 15:19:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4788-personally-i-m-always-ready-to-learn-although-i-do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Personally, I'm always ready to learn, although I do not always like being taught." -- Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533056-the-patriarch-joseph-after-agreeing-with-the-latins-that-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 19:29:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Steven Runciman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533056-the-patriarch-joseph-after-agreeing-with-the-latins-that-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Patriarch Joseph, after agreeing with the Latins that their formula of the Holy Ghost proceeding &lt;i&gt;from&lt;/i&gt; the Son meant the same as the Greek formula of the Holy Ghost proceeding &lt;i&gt;through&lt;/i&gt; the Son, fell ill and died. An unkind scholar remarked that after muddling his prepositions what else could he decently do?" -- Steven Runciman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/859045-for-a-time-the-word-weltpolitik-seemed-to-capture-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 11:56:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Christopher Munro Clark]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/859045-for-a-time-the-word-weltpolitik-seemed-to-capture-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For a time, the word &lt;i&gt;Weltpolitik&lt;/i&gt; seemed to capture the mood of the German middle classes and the national-minded quality press. The word resonated because it bundled together so many contemporary aspirations. &lt;i&gt;Weltpolitik&lt;/i&gt; meant the quest to expand foreign markets (at a time of declining export growth); it meant escaping from the constraints of the continental alliance system to operate on a broader world arena. It expressed the appetite for genuinely national projects that would help knit together the disparate regions of the German Empire and reflected the almost universal conviction that Germany, a late arrival at the imperial feast, would have to play catch-up if it wished to earn the respect of the other great powers. Yet, while it connoted all these things, &lt;i&gt;Weltpolitik&lt;/i&gt; never acquired a stable or precise meaning. Even Bernhard von Bulow, widely credited with establishing &lt;i&gt;Weltpolitik&lt;/i&gt; as the guiding principle of German foreign policy, never produced a definitive account of what it was. His contradictory utterances on the subject suggest that it was little more than the old policy of the &quot;free hand&quot; with a larger navy and more menacing mood music. &quot;We are supposed to be pursuing &lt;i&gt;Weltpolitik&lt;/i&gt;,&quot; the former chief of the General Staff General Alfred von Waldersee noted grumpily in his diary in January 1900. &quot;If only I knew what that was supposed to be." -- Christopher Munro Clark]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171027-it-d-be-a-poor-kind-of-world-where-there-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 19:05:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Diane Duane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171027-it-d-be-a-poor-kind-of-world-where-there-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’d be a poor kind of world where there was just one explanation for things. ---Rhiow" -- Diane Duane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508042-don-t-wish-to-be-normal-wish-to-be-yourself-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 08:43:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rindis add a quote by Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508042-don-t-wish-to-be-normal-wish-to-be-yourself-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't wish to be normal. Wish to be yourself. To the hilt. Find out what you're best at, and develop it, and hopscotch your weaknesses. Wish to be great at whatever you are." -- Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
