<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/145936-tish]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/145936-tish" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 02:28:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4786-every-day-we-slaughter-our-finest-impulses-that-is-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 02:28:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tish add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4786-every-day-we-slaughter-our-finest-impulses-that-is-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every day we slaughter our finest impulses. That is why we get a heartache when we read those lines written by the hand of a master and recognize them as our own, as the tender shoots which we stifled because we lacked the faith to believe in our own powers, our own criterion of truth and beauty. Every man, when he gets quiet, when he becomes desperately honest with himself, is capable of uttering profound truths. We all derive from the same source. there is no mystery about the origin of things. We are all part of creation, all kings, all poets, all musicians; we have only to open up, only to discover what is already there." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156390-listen-to-the-people-who-love-you-believe-that-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 06:30:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tish add a quote by Andrew Solomon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156390-listen-to-the-people-who-love-you-believe-that-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen to the people who love you.  Believe that they are worth living for even when you don't believe it.  Seek out the memories depression takes away and project them into the future. Be brave; be strong; take your pills.  Exercise because it's good for you even if every step weighs a thousand pounds. Eat when food itself disgusts you.  Reason with yourself when you have lost your reason." -- Andrew Solomon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
