<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/146086-geraldine-kim]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/146086-geraldine-kim" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 21:51:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/370431-t-he-whole-thing-is-really-a-dazzling-illusion-empty-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 21:51:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geraldine add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/370431-t-he-whole-thing-is-really-a-dazzling-illusion-empty-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…[T]he whole thing is really a dazzling illusion empty of all perception, an astonishing farce of misperception. And yet what are we to do about this terribly significant business of other people, which gets bled of the significance we think it has and takes on instead a significance that is ludicrous, so ill-equipped are we all to envision one another’s interior workings and invisible aims? Is everyone to go off and lock the door and sit secluded like the lonely writers do, in a soundproof cell, summoning people out of words and then proposing that these word people are closer to the real thing than the real people that we mangle with our ignorance every day?" -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185704-writing-turns-you-into-somebody-who-s-always-wrong-the-illusion</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 21:52:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geraldine add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185704-writing-turns-you-into-somebody-who-s-always-wrong-the-illusion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing turns you into somebody who's always wrong.  The illusion that you may get it right someday is the perversity that draws you on." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/370433-he-is-not-simply-looking-into-the-mirror-because-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 21:52:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geraldine add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/370433-he-is-not-simply-looking-into-the-mirror-because-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He is not simply looking into the mirror because he is transfixed by what he sees. Rather, the artist’s success depends as much as anything on his powers of detachment, on de-narcissizing himself… Freud… studied his own dreams not because he was a “narcissist,” but because he was a student of dreams. And whose were at once the least and most accessible of dreams, if not his own?" -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/370434-though-frankly-tarnapol-as-he-is-called-is-beginning-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 21:53:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geraldine add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/370434-though-frankly-tarnapol-as-he-is-called-is-beginning-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Though frankly… Tarnapol, as he is called, is beginning to seem as imaginary as my Zuckermans anyway, or at least as detached from the memoir-ist – his revelations coming to seem like still another “useful fiction,” and not because I am telling lies. I am trying to keep to the facts. Maybe all I’m saying is that words, being words, only approximate the real thing, and so no matter how close I come, I only come close." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
