<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/147228-melinda-chadwick]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/147228-melinda-chadwick" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 17:44:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95859-share-and-enjoy-is-the-company-motto-of-the-hugely</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 17:44:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95859-share-and-enjoy-is-the-company-motto-of-the-hugely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Share and Enjoy' is the company motto of the hugely successful Sirius Cybernetics Corporation Complaints Division, which now covers the major land masses of three medium-sized planets and is the only part of the Corporation to have shown a consistent profit in recent years.  
The motto stands-- or rather stood-- in three mile high illuminated letters near the Complaints Department spaceport on Eadrax.  Unfortunately its weight was such that shortly after it was erected, the ground beneath the letters caved in and they dropped for nearly half their length through the offices of many talented young Complaints executives-- now deceased.
The protruding upper halves of the letters now appear, in the local language, to read &quot;Go stick your head in a pig,&quot; and are no longer illuminated, except at times of special celebration." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124577-he-was-just-hungry-papa-he-s-going-to-die-he-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2008 16:56:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124577-he-was-just-hungry-papa-he-s-going-to-die-he-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was just hungry, Papa.  He's going to die.
He's going to die anyway.
He's so scared, Papa.
The man squatted and looked at him.  I'm scared, he said.  Do you understand?  I'm scared.
The boy didn't answer.  He just sat there with his head down, sobbing.
You're not the one who has to worry about everything.
The boy said something but he couldn't understand him.  What? He said.
He looked up, his wet and grimy face.  Yes I am, he said.  I am the one." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126934-i-could-not-help-feeling-that-they-were-evil-things--</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 06:16:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126934-i-could-not-help-feeling-that-they-were-evil-things--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I could not help feeling that they were evil things-- mountains of madness whose farther slopes looked out over some accursed ultimate abyss. That seething , half-luminous cloud-background held ineffable suggestions of a vague, ethereal beyondness far more than terrestrially spatial; and gave appalling reminders of the utter remoteness, separateness, desolation, and aeon-long death of this untrodden and unfathomed austral world." -- H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128048-as-i-raced-out-of-the-office-i-could-hear</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 17:39:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Lauren Weisberger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128048-as-i-raced-out-of-the-office-i-could-hear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As I raced out of the office, I could hear Emily rapid-fire dialing four-digit extensions and all but screaming, 'She's on her way-- tell everyone.'  It took me only three seconds to wind through the hallways and pass through the fashion department, but I had already heard panicked cries of 'Emily said she's on her way in' and 'Miranda's coming!' and a particularly blood curdling cry of 'She's baaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaack!" -- Lauren Weisberger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136390-you-know-i-love-you-said-the-other-mother-flatly</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2009 18:47:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136390-you-know-i-love-you-said-the-other-mother-flatly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know I love you,' said the other mother flatly.
'You have a very funny way of showing it,' said Coraline." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151422-it-was-only-when-the-giant-got-halfway-down-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 04:32:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151422-it-was-only-when-the-giant-got-halfway-down-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was only when the giant got halfway down the incline that he suddenly, happily, burst into flame and continued his trip saying, &quot;NO SURVIVORS, NO SURVIVORS!&quot; in a manner that could only indicate deadly sincerity.

It was seeing him happily burning and advancing that startled the Brute Squad to screaming.  And once that happened, why, everybody panicked and ran..." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157102-obviously-i-have-always-wished-i-could-remember-what-happened</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 14:34:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Tana French]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157102-obviously-i-have-always-wished-i-could-remember-what-happened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…Obviously, I have always wished I could remember what happened in that wood.  The very few people who know about the whole Knocknaree thing invariably suggest, sooner or later, that I should try hypnotic regression, but for some reason  I find the idea distasteful.  I’m deeply suspicious of anything with a whiff of the New Age about it—not because of the practices themselves, which as far as I can tell from a safe distance may well have a lot to them, but because of the people who get involved who always seem to be the kind who corner you at parties to explain how they discovered that they are survivors and deserve to be happy.  I worry that I might come out of hypnosis with that sugar-high glaze of self-satisfied enlightenment, like a seventeen-year-old who’s just discovered Kerouak, and start proselytizing strangers in pubs…" -- Tana French]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171686-the-lights-were-off-so-that-his-heads-could-avoid</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 21:04:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171686-the-lights-were-off-so-that-his-heads-could-avoid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The lights were off so that his heads could avoid looking at each other because neither of them was currently a particular engaging sight, nor had they been since he had made the error of looking into his soul.
It had indeed been an error.
It had been late one night-- of course.
It had been a difficult day-- of course.
There had been soulful music playing on the ship's sound system-- of course.
And he had, of course, been slightly drunk.
In other words, all the usual conditions that bring on a bout of soul searching had applied, but it had, nevertheless, clearly been an error." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175791-the-black-bird-cocked-its-head-to-one-side-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 13:59:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175791-the-black-bird-cocked-its-head-to-one-side-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The black bird cocked its head to one side, and then said, in a voice like stones being struck, 'You shadow man.'
'I'm Shadow,' said Shadow.  The bird hopped up onto the fawn's rump, raised its head, ruffled its crown and neck feathers. It was enormous and its eyes were black beads. There was something intimidating about a bird that size, this close.
'Says he will see you in Kay-ro.' tokked the raven.  Shadow wondered which of Odin's ravens this was: Huginn or Munnin, Memory or Thought.
'Kay-ro?' he asked.
'In Egypt.'
'How am I going to go to Egypt?'
'Follow Mississippi.  Go south.  Find Jackal.'
'Look,' said Shadow, 'I don't want to seem like I'm-- Jesus, look...' he paused. Regrouped. He was cold, standing in a wood, talking to a big black bird who was currently brunching on Bambi. 'Okay. What I'm trying to say is I don't want mysteries.'
'Mysteries,' agreed the bird helpfully.
'What I want is explanations. Jackal in Kay-ro. This does not help me. It's a line from a bad spy thriller." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182955-it-goes-in-streaks-but-some-things-never-go-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 17:47:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Katherine Dunn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182955-it-goes-in-streaks-but-some-things-never-go-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It goes in streaks.  But some things never go out of fashion.'  Hunger artists, fat folks, giants, and dog acts come and go but real freaks never lose their appeal." -- Katherine Dunn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247651-he-was-having-more-fun-than-a-barrelful-of-monkeys</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 03:34:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247651-he-was-having-more-fun-than-a-barrelful-of-monkeys]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was having more fun than a barrelful of monkeys.*

*Several years earlier Spider had actually been tremendously disappointed by a barrelful of monkeys. It had done nothing he had considered particularly entertaining, apart from emit interesting noises, and eventually, once the noises had stopped and the monkeys were no longer doing anything at all—except possibly on an organic level—had needed to be disposed of in the dead of night." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260095-dr-ransome-marked-the-exercises-in-the-algebra-textbook-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 04:53:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by J.G. Ballard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260095-dr-ransome-marked-the-exercises-in-the-algebra-textbook-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dr. Ransome marked the exercises in the algebra textbook and gave him two strips of rice-paper bandage on which to solve the simultaneous equations.  As he stood up, Dr. Ransome removed the three tomatoes from Jim's pocket.  He laid them on the table by the wax tray.
'Did they come from the hospital garden?'
'Yes.' Jim gazed back frankly at Dr. Ransome.  Recently he had begun to see him with a more adult eye.  The long years of imprisonment, the constant disputes with the Japanese had made this young physician seem middle-aged.  Dr. Ransome was often unsure of himself, as he was of Jim's theft.
'I have to give Basie something whenever I see him.'
'I know.  It's a good thing that you're friends with Basie.  He's a survivor, though survivors can be dangerous.  Wars exist for people like Basie.' Dr. Ransome placed the tomatoes in Jim's hand.  'I want you to eat them, Jim.  I'll get you something for Basie." -- J.G. Ballard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289439-if-such-a-thing-had-happened-once-it-must-surely</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2010 02:46:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289439-if-such-a-thing-had-happened-once-it-must-surely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If such a thing had happened once, it must surely have happened many times in this galaxy of a hundred billion suns." -- Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/344642-beauty-and-perfection-do-not-guarantee-grace-and-fulfillment-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 06:05:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Kate Horsley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/344642-beauty-and-perfection-do-not-guarantee-grace-and-fulfillment-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beauty and perfection do not guarantee grace and fulfillment and are always sacrificed.  Life itself seems a ritual of sacrifice, and the world the alter on which plants and animals lay down their own lives for the sustenance of others, and on which we lay our youth, our well-being, our loved ones, and finally our lives.  I am an ignorant woman who has sacrificed all of these things but the last, and cannot say for whom or what I perform this unrelenting ritual." -- Kate Horsley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420461-sin-is-the-only-real-colour-element-left-in-modern-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 10:44:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420461-sin-is-the-only-real-colour-element-left-in-modern-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sin is the only real colour-element left in modern life.'
'You really must not say things like that before Dorian, Harry.'
'Before which Dorian? The one who is pouring out tea for us, or the one in the picture?'
'Before either.'
'I should like to come to the theatre with you, Lord Henry,' said the lad.
'Then you shall come; and you will come, too, Basil, won't you?'
'I can't, really.  I would sooner not.  I have a lot of work to do.'
'Well, then you and I will go alone, Mr. Gray.'
'I should like that awfully.'
The painter bit his lip and walked over, cup in hand, to the picture.  'I shall stay with the real Dorian,' he said, sadly." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420465-the-writing-seemed-like-the-books-that-held-it-crumbly</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 10:50:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Lauren Groff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420465-the-writing-seemed-like-the-books-that-held-it-crumbly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The writing seemed like the books that held it; crumbly and antique and bearing the stink of centuries.  Still, it was compelling.  His voice was smooth and kind, and once in a while an observation that would ring so true it vibrated like flicked crystal." -- Lauren Groff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142048-from-even-the-greatest-of-horrors-irony-is-seldom-absent</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 20:06:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142048-from-even-the-greatest-of-horrors-irony-is-seldom-absent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From even the greatest of horrors irony is seldom absent." -- H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12428-i-want-to-stand-as-close-to-the-edge-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2012 04:22:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12428-i-want-to-stand-as-close-to-the-edge-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to stand as close to the edge as I can without going over. Out on the edge you see all kinds of things you can't see from the center." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4078-the-saddest-aspect-of-life-right-now-is-that-science</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 06:01:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Isaac Asimov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4078-the-saddest-aspect-of-life-right-now-is-that-science]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The saddest aspect of life right now is that science gathers knowledge faster than society gathers wisdom." -- Isaac Asimov]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
