<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/148332-whiskeyb]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/148332-whiskeyb" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 12:07:59 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4703-the-aim-of-life-is-to-live-and-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 12:07:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4703-the-aim-of-life-is-to-live-and-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The aim of life is to live, and to live means to be aware, joyously, drunkenly, serenely, divinely aware." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21700-sit-be-still-and-listen-because-you-re-drunk-and-we-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 12:14:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by Rumi ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21700-sit-be-still-and-listen-because-you-re-drunk-and-we-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sit, be still, and listen,
because you're drunk
and we're at
the edge of the roof." -- Rumi ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6233-what-would-an-ocean-be-without-a-monster-lurking-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 12:17:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by Werner Herzog]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6233-what-would-an-ocean-be-without-a-monster-lurking-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What would an ocean be without a monster lurking in the dark?  It would be like sleep without dreams." -- Werner Herzog]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25712-some-years-ago---never-mind-how-long-precisely--</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 12:22:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25712-some-years-ago---never-mind-how-long-precisely--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some years ago - never mind how long precisely - having little or no money in my purse, and nothing particular to interest me on shore, I thought I would sail about a little and see the watery part of the world. It is a way I have of driving off the spleen, and regulating the circulation. Whenever I find myself growing grim about the mouth; whenever it is a damp, drizzly November in my soul; whenever I find myself involuntarily pausing before coffin warehouses, and bringing up the rear of every funeral I meet; and especially whenever my hypos get such an upper hand of me, that it requires a strong moral principle to prevent me from deliberately stepping into the street, and methodically knocking people's hats off - then, I account it high time to get to sea as soon as I can. This is my substitute for pistol and ball. With a philosophical flourish Cato throws himself upon his sword; I quietly take to the ship. There is nothing surprising in this. If they but knew it, almost all men in their degree, some time or other, cherish very nearly the same feelings towards the ocean with me." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113074-i-feel-the-way-bank-robbers-must-feel-before-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 05:43:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by Joey Comeau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113074-i-feel-the-way-bank-robbers-must-feel-before-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I feel the way bank robbers must feel before they go out on that last job that ends up getting them all killed. That is to say, optimistic." -- Joey Comeau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12694-when-your-mama-was-the-geek-my-dreamlets-papa-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 05:45:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by Katherine Dunn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12694-when-your-mama-was-the-geek-my-dreamlets-papa-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When your mama was the geek, my dreamlets,&quot; Papa would say, &quot;she made the nipping off of noggins such a crystal mystery that the hens themselves yearned toward her, waltzing around her, hypnotized with longing." -- Katherine Dunn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19276-words-at-night-were-feral-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2009 09:29:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by Joy Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19276-words-at-night-were-feral-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Words at night were feral things." -- Joy Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2009 08:25:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are bored and disgusted by politics and don't bother to vote, you are in effect voting for the entrenched Establishments of the two major parties, who please rest assured are not dumb, and who are keenly aware that it is in their interests to keep you disgusted and bored and cynical and to give you every possible reason to stay at home doing one-hitters and watching MTV on primary day.  By all means stay home if you want, but don't bullshit yourself that you're not voting.  In reality, there is &lt;i&gt;no such thing as not voting:&lt;/i&gt; you either vote by voting, or you vote by staying home and tacitly doubling the value of some Diehard's vote." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111246-the-next-real-literary-rebels-in-this-country-might-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2009 19:10:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111246-the-next-real-literary-rebels-in-this-country-might-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The next real literary “rebels” in this country might well emerge as some weird bunch of anti-rebels, born oglers who dare somehow to back away from ironic watching, who have the childish gall actually to endorse and instantiate single-entendre principles. Who treat of plain old untrendy human troubles and emotions in U.S. life with reverence and conviction. Who eschew self-consciousness and hip fatigue. These anti-rebels would be outdated, of course, before they even started. Dead on the page. Too sincere. Clearly repressed. Backward, quaint, naive, anachronistic. Maybe that’ll be the point. Maybe that’s why they’ll be the next real rebels. Real rebels, as far as I can see, risk disapproval. The old postmodern insurgents risked the gasp and squeal: shock, disgust, outrage, censorship, accusations of socialism, anarchism, nihilism. Today’s risks are different. The new rebels might be artists willing to risk the yawn, the rolled eyes, the cool smile, the nudged ribs, the parody of gifted ironists, the “Oh how banal.” To risk accusations of sentimentality, melodrama. Of overcredulity. Of softness. Of willingness to be suckered by a world of lurkers and starers who fear gaze and ridicule above imprisonment without law. Who knows. " -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125589-fuck-concepts-don-t-be-afraid-to-be-confused-try-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 16:40:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125589-fuck-concepts-don-t-be-afraid-to-be-confused-try-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fuck concepts.  Don't be afraid to be confused.  Try to remain permanently confused.  Anything is possible.  Stay open, forever, so open it hurts, and then open up some more, until the day you die, world without end, amen." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20673-sleep-tight-ya-morons</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 17:02:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20673-sleep-tight-ya-morons]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sleep tight, ya morons!" -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3172-and-i-urge-you-to-please-notice-when-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 11:35:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3172-and-i-urge-you-to-please-notice-when-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I urge you to please notice when you are happy, and exclaim or murmur or think at some point, 'If this isn't nice, I don't know what is." -- Kurt Vonnegut Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130841-it-s-like-you-took-a-bottle-of-ink-and-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 12:22:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by Alan Watts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130841-it-s-like-you-took-a-bottle-of-ink-and-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's like you took a bottle of ink and you threw it at a wall. Smash! And all that ink spread. And in the middle, it's dense, isn't it? And as it gets out on the edge, the little droplets get finer and finer and make more complicated patterns, see? So in the same way, there was a big bang at the beginning of things and it spread. And you and I, sitting here in this room, as complicated human beings, are way, way out on the fringe of that bang. We are the complicated little patterns on the end of it. Very interesting. But so we define ourselves as being only that. If you think that you are only inside your skin, you define yourself as one very complicated little curlique, way out on the edge of that explosion. Way out in space, and way out in time. Billions of years ago, you were a big bang, but now you're a complicated human being. And then we cut ourselves off, and don't feel that we're still the big bang. But you are. Depends how you define yourself. You are actually--if this is the way things started, if there was a big bang in the beginning-- you're not something that's a result of the big bang. You're not something that is a sort of puppet on the end of the process. You are still the process. You are the big bang, the original force of the universe, coming on as whoever you are. When I meet you, I see not just what you define yourself as--Mr so-and- so, Ms so-and-so, Mrs so-and-so--I see every one of you as the primordial energy of the universe coming on at me in this particular way. I know I'm that, too. But we've learned to define ourselves as separate from it. " -- Alan Watts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82020-flies-die-in-so-many-lonely-places--roberta-rohbeson</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2012 18:52:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by Lynda Barry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82020-flies-die-in-so-many-lonely-places--roberta-rohbeson]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Flies die in so many lonely places.

-Roberta Rohbeson" -- Lynda Barry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497004-as-i-enter-the-small-intestine-i-get-squeezed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2012 18:55:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by Lynda Barry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497004-as-i-enter-the-small-intestine-i-get-squeezed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As I enter the small intestine I get squeezed by muscles.  Its dark and the walls look like slimey crushed velvet theres pancreas juice on me help me I am disintigrating." -- Lynda Barry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364574-all-i-could-think-of-when-i-got-a-look</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 13:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by Shirley Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364574-all-i-could-think-of-when-i-got-a-look]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All I could think of when I got a look at the place from the outside was what fun it would be to stand out there and watch it burn down." -- Shirley Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584874-true-enough-said-mrs-copperfield-bringing-her-fist-down-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 13:18:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by Jane Bowles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584874-true-enough-said-mrs-copperfield-bringing-her-fist-down-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["True enough,” said Mrs. Copperfield, bringing her fist down on the table and looking very mean. “I have gone to pieces, which is a thing I’ve wanted to do for years. I know I am as guilty as I can be, but I have my happiness, which I guard like a wolf, and I have authority now and a certain amount of daring, which, if you remember correctly, I never had before." -- Jane Bowles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310648-we-know-summer-is-the-height-of-of-being-alive</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 17:18:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by Gary Shteyngart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310648-we-know-summer-is-the-height-of-of-being-alive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We know summer is the height of of being alive. We don't believe in God or the prospect of an afterlife mostly, so we know that we're only given eighty summers or so per lifetime, and each one has to be better then the last, has to encompass a trip to that arts center up at Bard, a seemingly mellow game of badminton over at some yahoo's Vermont cottage, and a cool, wet, slightly dangerous kayak trip down an unforgiving river. Otherwise, how would you know that you have lived your summertime best? What is you missed out on some morsel of shaded nirvana?" -- Gary Shteyngart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402012-summer-is-a-latvian-chicken-we-make-foolish-choices-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 17:19:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by Gary Shteyngart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402012-summer-is-a-latvian-chicken-we-make-foolish-choices-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Summer is a Latvian chicken. We make foolish choices. We think we’re young again. We run with outstretched arms toward an object of love and it pecks us and pecks us until we’re standing there snot-nosed and teary in the middle of Astor Place and the sun sets fire to our Penguin shirts and all that is left to do is go to our air-conditioned homes and ponder the cruelty of our finest season." -- Gary Shteyngart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259090-for-those-who-like-that-sort-of-thing-said-miss</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 18:06:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whiskeyb add a quote by Muriel Spark]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259090-for-those-who-like-that-sort-of-thing-said-miss]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For those who like that sort of thing,&quot; said Miss Brodie in her best Edinburgh voice, &quot;That is the sort of thing they like." -- Muriel Spark]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
