<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/149147-paige]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/149147-paige" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 18:10:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18653-to-photograph-people-is-to-violate-them-by-seeing-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 18:10:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[paige add a quote by Susan Sontag]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18653-to-photograph-people-is-to-violate-them-by-seeing-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To photograph people is to violate them, by seeing them as they never see themselves, by having knowledge of them that they can never have; it turns people into objects that can be symbolically possessed. Just as a camera is a sublimation of the gun, to photograph someone is a subliminal murder - a soft murder, appropriate to a sad, frightened time." -- Susan Sontag]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34654-do-stuff-be-clenched-curious-not-waiting-for-inspiration-s-shove</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 18:10:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[paige add a quote by Susan Sontag]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34654-do-stuff-be-clenched-curious-not-waiting-for-inspiration-s-shove]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do stuff. be clenched, curious. Not waiting for inspiration's shove or society's kiss on your forehead. Pay attention. It's all about paying attention. attention is vitality. It connects you with others. It makes you eager. stay eager." -- Susan Sontag]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13120-written-on-the-body-is-a-secret-code-only-visible</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 18:13:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[paige add a quote by jeanette winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13120-written-on-the-body-is-a-secret-code-only-visible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Written on the body is a secret code only visible in certain lights: the accumulations of a lifetime gather there. In places the palimpsest is so heavily worked that the letters feel like Braille. I like to keep my body rolled up away from prying eyes, never unfold too much, or tell the whole story. I didn't know that Louise would have reading hands. She has translated me into her own book." -- jeanette winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13830-when-my-friend-melot-set-the-trap-i-think-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 18:14:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[paige add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13830-when-my-friend-melot-set-the-trap-i-think-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When my friend Melot set the trap, I think I knew it. I turned to death full face, as I had turned to love with my whole body. I would let death enter me as you had entered me. You had crept along my blood vessels through the wound, and the blood that circulates returns to the heart. You circulated me, you made me blush like a girl in the hoop of your hands. You were in my arteries and my lymph, you were the colour just under my skin, and if I cut myself, it was you I bled. Red Isolde, alive on my fingers, and always the force of blood pushing you back to my heart." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23178-there-are-many-forms-of-love-and-affection-some-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 18:14:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[paige add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23178-there-are-many-forms-of-love-and-affection-some-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are many forms of love and affection, some people can spend their whole lives together without knowing each other's names. Naming is a difficult and time-consuming process; it concerns essences, and it means power. But on the wild nights who can call you home? Only the one who knows your name." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4141-the-buddhists-say-there-are-149-ways-to-god-i-m</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 18:14:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[paige add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4141-the-buddhists-say-there-are-149-ways-to-god-i-m]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Buddhists say there are 149 ways to God. I'm not looking for God, only for myself, and that is far more complicated. God has had a great deal written about Him; nothing has been written about me. God is bigger, like my mother, easier to find, even in the dark. I could be anywhere, and since I can't describe myself I can't ask for help." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53169-we-read-deeply-for-varied-reasons-most-of-them-familiar</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 15:25:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[paige add a quote by Harold Bloom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53169-we-read-deeply-for-varied-reasons-most-of-them-familiar]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We read deeply for varied reasons, most of them familiar: that we cannot know enough people profoundly enough; that we need to know ourselves better; that we require knowledge, not just of self and others, but of the way things are.  Yet the strongest, most authentic motive for deep reading…is the search for a difficult pleasure." -- Harold Bloom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2338-if-i-can-t-dance-to-it-it-s-not-my-revolution</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 15:25:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[paige add a quote by Emma Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2338-if-i-can-t-dance-to-it-it-s-not-my-revolution]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I can't dance to it, it's not my revolution." -- Emma Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
