<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/150872-mary]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/150872-mary" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 19:03:59 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7552-don-t-let-the-bastards-grind-you-down</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 19:03:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7552-don-t-let-the-bastards-grind-you-down]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't let the bastards grind you down." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17533-i-carry-your-heart-with-me-i-carry-it-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 16:56:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by E.E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17533-i-carry-your-heart-with-me-i-carry-it-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I carry your heart with me (I carry it in my heart)I am never without it (anywhere
I go you go,my dear; and whatever is done by only me is your doing,my darling)
I fear no fate (for you are my fate,my sweet)I want no world (for beautiful you are my world,my true)
and it's you are whatever a moon has always meant and whatever a sun will always sing is you

here is the deepest secret nobody knows
(here is the root of the root and the bud of the bud and the sky of the sky of a tree called life; which grows
higher than the soul can hope or mind can hide)
and this is the wonder that's keeping the stars apart

I carry your heart (I carry it in my heart)" -- E.E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4889-to-be-nobody-but-yourself-in-a-world-which-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 16:57:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by e.e. cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4889-to-be-nobody-but-yourself-in-a-world-which-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be nobody but 
yourself in a world 
which is doing its best day and night to make you like 
everybody else means to fight the hardest battle 
which any human being can fight and never stop fighting." -- e.e. cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15935-if-you-are-a-dreamer-come-in-if-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 16:57:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Shel Silverstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15935-if-you-are-a-dreamer-come-in-if-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are a dreamer come in
If you are a dreamer a wisher a liar
A hoper a pray-er a magic-bean-buyer
If youre a pretender com sit by my fire
For we have some flax golden tales to spin
Come in! 
Come in!" -- Shel Silverstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115748-contentment-is-natural-wealth-luxury-is-artificial-poverty</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:37:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Socrates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115748-contentment-is-natural-wealth-luxury-is-artificial-poverty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Contentment is natural wealth, luxury is artificial poverty." -- Socrates]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30407-first-of-all-love-is-a-joint-experience-between-two</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 22:50:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by carson mccullers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30407-first-of-all-love-is-a-joint-experience-between-two]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First of all, love is a joint experience between two persons — but the fact that it is a joint experience does not mean that it is a similar experience to the two people involved. There are the lover and the beloved, but these two come from different countries. Often the beloved is only a stimulus for all the stored-up love which had lain quiet within the lover for a long time hitherto. And somehow every lover knows this. He feels in his soul that his love is a solitary thing. He comes to know a new, strange loneliness and it is this knowledge which makes him suffer. So there is only one thing for the lover to do. He must house his love within himself as best he can; he must create for himself a whole new inward world — a world intense and strange, complete in himself. Let it be added here that this lover about whom we speak need not necessarily be a young man saving for a wedding ring — this lover can be man, woman, child, or indeed any human creature on this earth.

Now, the beloved can also be of any description. The most outlandish people can be the stimulus for love. A man may be a doddering great-grandfather and still love only a strange girl he saw in the streets of Cheehaw one afternoon two decades past. The preacher may love a fallen woman. The beloved may be treacherous, greasy-headed, and given to evil habits. Yes, and the lover may see this as clearly as anyone else — but that does not affect the evolution of his love one whit. A most mediocre person can be the object of a love which is wild, extravagant, and beautiful as the poison lilies of the swamp. A good man may be the stimulus for a love both violent and debased, or a jabbering madman may bring about in the soul of someone a tender and simple idyll. Therefore, the value and quality of any love is determined solely by the lover himself.

It is for this reason that most of us would rather love than be loved. Almost everyone wants to be the lover. And the curt truth is that, in a deep secret way, the state of being beloved is intolerable to many. The beloved fears and hates the lover, and with the best of reasons. For the lover is forever trying to strip bare his beloved. The lover craves any possible relation with the beloved, even if this experience can cause him only pain." -- carson mccullers]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
