<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/150874-pankaj]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/150874-pankaj" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 02:11:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 02:11:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183399-only-the-educated-are-free</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 02:12:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Epictetus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183399-only-the-educated-are-free]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only the educated are free." -- Epictetus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6806-the-more-that-you-read-the-more-things-you-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2008 20:19:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6806-the-more-that-you-read-the-more-things-you-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The more that you read, the more things you will know. The more that you learn, the more places you'll go." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 02:12:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be the change that you wish to see in the world." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2253-live-as-if-you-were-to-die-tomorrow-learn-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 02:12:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2253-live-as-if-you-were-to-die-tomorrow-learn-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2658-happiness-is-when-what-you-think-what-you-say-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 02:13:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2658-happiness-is-when-what-you-think-what-you-say-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is when what you think, what you say, and what you do are in harmony." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11416-the-best-way-to-find-yourself-is-to-lose-yourself</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 02:13:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11416-the-best-way-to-find-yourself-is-to-lose-yourself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/747-if-we-knew-what-it-was-we-were-doing-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 02:14:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/747-if-we-knew-what-it-was-we-were-doing-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we knew what it was we were doing, it would not be called research, would it?" -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5793-creativity-is-knowing-how-to-hide-your-sources</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 02:14:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5793-creativity-is-knowing-how-to-hide-your-sources]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Creativity is knowing how to hide your sources" -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362-if-you-don-t-stand-for-something-you-will-fall-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 02:20:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Gordon A. Eadie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362-if-you-don-t-stand-for-something-you-will-fall-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you don't stand for something you will fall for anything." -- Gordon A. Eadie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 02:21:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 02:22:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 13:05:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4590-without-music-life-would-be-a-mistake</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 13:05:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4590-without-music-life-would-be-a-mistake]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without music, life would be a mistake." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440-who-knows-how-to-make-love-stay-1-tell-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 12:25:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440-who-knows-how-to-make-love-stay-1-tell-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who knows how to make love stay?

1. Tell love you are going to Junior's Deli on Flatbush Avenue in Brooklyn to pick up a cheesecake, and if loves stays, it can have half. It will stay.

2. Tell love you want a momento of it and obtain a lock of its hair. Burn the hair in a dime-store incense burner with yin/yang symbols on three sides. Face southwest. Talk fast over the burning hair in a convincingly exotic language. Remove the ashes of the burnt hair and use them to paint a moustache on your face. Find love. Tell it you are someone new. It will stay.

3. Wake love up in the middle of the night. Tell it the world is on fire. Dash to the bedroom window and pee out of it. Casually return to bed and assure love that everything is going to be all right. Fall asleep. Love will be there in the morning." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14851-a-sense-of-humor-is-superior-to-any-religion-so-far</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 12:26:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14851-a-sense-of-humor-is-superior-to-any-religion-so-far]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A sense of humor...is superior to any religion so far devised." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53798-you-should-never-hesitate-to-trade-your-cow-for-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 12:26:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53798-you-should-never-hesitate-to-trade-your-cow-for-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You should never hesitate to trade your cow for a handful of magic beans." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126098-all-depression-has-its-roots-in-self-pity-and-all-self-pity</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 12:28:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126098-all-depression-has-its-roots-in-self-pity-and-all-self-pity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All depression has its roots in self-pity, and all self-pity is rooted in people taking themselves too seriously.&quot;

At the time Switters had disputed her assertion.  Even at seventeen, he was aware that depression could have chemical causes.

&quot;The key word here is roots,&quot; Maestra had countered. &quot;The roots of depression. For most people, self-awareness and self-pity blossom simultaneously in early adolescence. It's about that time that we start viewing the world as something other than a whoop-de-doo playground, we start to experience personally how threatening it can e, how cruel and unjust. At the very moment when we become, for the first time, both introspective and socially conscientious, we receive the bad news that the world, by and large, doesn't give a rat's ass. Even an old tomato like me can recall how painful, scary, and disillusioning that realization was. So, there's a tendency, then, to slip into rage and self-pity, which if indulged, can fester into bouts of depression.&quot;

&quot;Yeah but Maestra - &quot;

&quot;Don't interrupt. Now, unless someone stronger and wiser - a friend, a parent, a novelist, filmmaker, teacher, or musician - can josh us out of it, can elevate us and show us how petty and pompous and monumentally useless it is to take ourselves so seriously, then depression can become a habit, which, in tern, can produce a neurological imprint. Are you with me? Gradually, our brain chemistry becomes conditioned to react to negative stimuli in a particular, predictable way. One thing'll go wrong and it'll automatically switch on its blender and mix us that black cocktail, the ol' doomsday daiquiri, and before we know it, we're soused to the gills from the inside out. Once depression has become electrochemically integrated, it can be extremely difficult to philosophically or psychologically override it; by then it's playing by physical rules, a whole different ball game. That's why Switters my dearest, every time you've shown signs of feeling sorry for yourself, I've played my blues records really loud or read to you from The Horse's Mouth. And that's why when you've exhibited the slightest tendency toward self-importance, I've reminded you that you and me - you and I: excuse me - may be every bit as important as the President or the pope or the biggest prime-time icon in Hollywood, but none of us is much more than a pimple on the ass-end of creation, so let's not get carried away with ourselves. Preventive medicine, boy. It's preventive medicine.&quot;

&quot;But what about self-esteem?&quot;

&quot;Heh! Self-esteem is for sissies. Accept that you're a pimple and try to keep a lively sense of humor about it. That way lies grace - and maybe even glory." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32254-curiosity-especially-intellectual-inquisitiveness-is-what-separates-the-truly-alive</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 12:31:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32254-curiosity-especially-intellectual-inquisitiveness-is-what-separates-the-truly-alive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Curiosity, especially intellectual inquisitiveness, is what separates the truly alive from those who are merely going through the motions." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289762-in-the-end-just-three-things-matter-how-well-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 11:48:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Jack Kornfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289762-in-the-end-just-three-things-matter-how-well-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the end, just three things matter:

How well we have lived
How well we have loved
How well we have learned to let go" -- Jack Kornfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/444289-people-are-unreasonable-illogical-and-self-centered-love-them-anyway-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 11:59:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pankaj add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/444289-people-are-unreasonable-illogical-and-self-centered-love-them-anyway-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People are unreasonable, illogical, and self-centered. Love them anyway. If you do good, people may accuse you of selfish motives. Do good anyway. If you are successful, you may win false friends and true enemies. Succeed anyway. The good you do today may be forgotten tomorrow. Do good anyway. Honesty and transparency make you vulnerable. Be honest and transparent anyway. What you spend years building may be destroyed overnight. Build anyway. People who really want help may attack you if you help them. Help them anyway. Give the world the best you have and you may get hurt. Give the world your best anyway." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
