<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/151419-dusie-press]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/151419-dusie-press" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:06:22 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25-we-are-all-in-the-gutter-but-some-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:06:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25-we-are-all-in-the-gutter-but-some-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all in the gutter, but some of us are looking at the stars." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71-the-fool-doth-think-he-is-wise-but-the-wise</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:06:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71-the-fool-doth-think-he-is-wise-but-the-wise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fool doth think he is wise, but the wise man knows himself to be a fool." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:06:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the world were merely seductive, that would be easy. If it were merely challenging, that would be no problem. But I arise in the morning torn between a desire to improve the world and a desire to enjoy the world. This makes it hard to plan the day." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422-there-are-years-that-ask-questions-and-years-that-answer</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:20:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422-there-are-years-that-ask-questions-and-years-that-answer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are years that ask questions and years that answer." -- Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:21:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 21:57:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always imagined that Paradise will be a kind of library." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1338-those-who-find-ugly-meanings-in-beautiful-things-are-corrupt</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:22:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1338-those-who-find-ugly-meanings-in-beautiful-things-are-corrupt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who find ugly meanings in beautiful things are corrupt without being charming. This is a fault. Those who find beautiful meanings in beautiful things are the cultivated. For these there is hope. They are the elect to whom beautiful things mean only Beauty. There is no such thing as a moral or an immoral book. Books are well written, or badly written. That is all." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4642-i-m-just-going-to-write-because-i-cannot-help-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:23:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4642-i-m-just-going-to-write-because-i-cannot-help-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm just going to write because I cannot help it." -- Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1895-you-can-never-be-overdressed-or-overeducated</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:41:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1895-you-can-never-be-overdressed-or-overeducated]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can never be overdressed or overeducated." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1858-for-most-of-history-anonymous-was-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:41:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1858-for-most-of-history-anonymous-was-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For most of history, Anonymous was a woman." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4819-when-you-consider-things-like-the-stars-our-affairs-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:41:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Virginia Woolf ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4819-when-you-consider-things-like-the-stars-our-affairs-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you consider things like the stars, our affairs don't seem to matter very much, do they?" -- Virginia Woolf ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1862-the-truth-is-i-often-like-women-i-like-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:41:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1862-the-truth-is-i-often-like-women-i-like-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is, I often like women. I like their unconventionality. I like their completeness. I like their anonymity. " -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1860-one-cannot-think-well-love-well-sleep-well-if-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:41:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1860-one-cannot-think-well-love-well-sleep-well-if-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One cannot think well, love well, sleep well, if one has not dined well." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2147-she-could-have-wept-it-was-bad-it-was-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:41:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2147-she-could-have-wept-it-was-bad-it-was-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She could have wept. It was bad, it was bad, it was infinitely bad! She could have done it differently of course; the colour could have been thinned and faded; the shapes etherealised; that was how Paunceforte would have seen it. But then she did not see it like that. She saw the colour burning on a framework of steel; the light of a butterfly’s wing lying upon the arches of a cathedral. Of all that only a few random marks scrawled upon the canvas remained. And it would never be seen; never be hung even, and there was Mr Tansley whispering in her ear, “Women can’t paint, women can’t write ...”

She now remembered what she had been going to say about Mrs Ramsay. She did not know how she would have put it; but it would have been something critical. She had been annoyed the other night by some highhandedness. Looking along the level of Mr Bankes’s glance at her, she thought that no woman could worship another woman in the way he worshipped; they could only seek shelter under the shade which Mr Bankes extended over them both. Looking along his beam she added to it her different ray, thinking that she was unquestionably the loveliest of people (bowed over her book); the best perhaps; but also, different too from the perfect shape which one saw there. But why different, and how different? she asked herself, scraping her palette of all those mounds of blue and green which seemed to her like clods with no life in them now, yet she vowed, she would inspire them, force them to move, flow, do her bidding tomorrow. How did she differ? What was the spirit in her, the essential thing, by which, had you found a crumpled glove in the corner of a sofa, you would have known it, from its twisted finger, hers indisputably? She was like a bird for speed, an arrow for directness. She was willful; she was commanding (of course, Lily reminded herself, I am thinking of her relations with women, and I am much younger, an insignificant person, living off the Brompton Road). She opened bedroom windows. She shut doors. (So she tried to start the tune of Mrs Ramsay in her head.) Arriving late at night, with a light tap on one’s bedroom door, wrapped in an old fur coat (for the setting of her beauty was always that—hasty, but apt), she would enact again whatever it might be—Charles Tansley losing his umbrella; Mr Carmichael snuffling and sniffing; Mr Bankes saying, “The vegetable salts are lost.” All this she would adroitly shape; even maliciously twist; and, moving over to the window, in pretence that she must go,—it was dawn, she could see the sun rising,—half turn back, more intimately, but still always laughing, insist that she must, Minta must, they all must marry, since in the whole world whatever laurels might be tossed to her (but Mrs Ramsay cared not a fig for her painting), or triumphs won by her (probably Mrs Ramsay had had her share of those), and here she saddened, darkened, and came back to her chair, there could be no disputing this: an unmarried woman (she lightly took her hand for a moment), an unmarried woman has missed the best of life. The house seemed full of children sleeping and Mrs Ramsay listening; shaded lights and regular breathing." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2149-i-told-you-in-the-course-of-this-paper-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:42:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2149-i-told-you-in-the-course-of-this-paper-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I told you in the course of this paper that Shakespeare had a sister; but do not look for her in Sir Sidney Lee’s life of the poet. She died young—alas, she never wrote a word. She lies buried where the omnibuses now stop, opposite the Elephant and Castle. Now my belief is that this poet who never wrote a word and was buried at the cross–roads still lives. She lives in you and in me, and in many other women who are not here to–night, for they are washing up the dishes and putting the children to bed. But she lives; for great poets do not die; they are continuing presences; they need only the opportunity to walk among us in the flesh. This opportunity, as I think, it is now coming within your power to give her. For my belief is that if we live another century or so—I am talking of the common life which is the real life and not of the little separate lives which we live as individuals—and have five hundred a year each of us and rooms of our own; if we have the habit of freedom and the courage to write exactly what we think; if we escape a little from the common sitting–room and see human beings not always in their relation to each other but in relation to reality; and the sky. too, and the trees or whatever it may be in themselves; if we look past Milton’s bogey, for no human being should shut out the view; if we face the fact, for it is a fact, that there is no arm to cling to, but that we go alone and that our relation is to the world of reality and not only to the world of men and women, then the opportunity will come and the dead poet who was Shakespeare’s sister will put on the body which she has so often laid down. Drawing her life from the lives of the unknown who were her forerunners, as her brother did before her, she will be born. As for her coming without that preparation, without that effort on our part, without that determination that when she is born again she shall find it possible to live and write her poetry, that we cannot expect, for that would he impossible. But I maintain that she would come if we worked for her, and that so to work, even in poverty and obscurity, is worth while." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2961-and-even-a-tea-party-means-apprehension-breakage</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:42:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2961-and-even-a-tea-party-means-apprehension-breakage]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["and even a tea party means apprehension, breakage" -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4732-i-don-t-believe-in-aging-i-believe-in-forever-altering</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:42:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4732-i-don-t-believe-in-aging-i-believe-in-forever-altering]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't believe in aging. I believe in forever altering one's aspect to the sun. " -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3498-she-had-the-perpetual-sense-as-she-watched-the-taxi</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:42:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3498-she-had-the-perpetual-sense-as-she-watched-the-taxi]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had the perpetual sense, as she watched the taxi cabs, of being out, out, far out to sea and alone; she always had the feeling that it was very, very, dangerous to live even one day." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3287-but-the-close-withdrew-the-hand-softened-it-was-over--</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:42:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3287-but-the-close-withdrew-the-hand-softened-it-was-over--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the close withdrew: the hand softened.  It was over-- the moment." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1002-nancy-waded-out-to-her-own-rocks-and-searched-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:42:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1002-nancy-waded-out-to-her-own-rocks-and-searched-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nancy waded out to her own rocks and searched her own pools and let that couple look after themselves. She crouched low down and touched the smooth rubber-like sea anemones, who were stuck like lumps of jelly to the side of the rock. Brooding, she changed the pool into the sea, and made the minnows into sharks and whales, and cast vast clouds over this tiny world by holding her hand against the sun, and so brought darkness and desolation, like God himself, to millions of ignorant and innocent creatures, and then took her hand away suddenly and let the sun stream down. Out on the pale criss-crossed sand, high-stepping, fringed, gauntleted, stalked some fantastic leviathan (she was still enlarging the pool), and slipped into the vast fissures of the mountain side. And then, letting her eyes slide imperceptibly above the pool and rest on that wavering line of sea and sky, on the tree trunks which the smoke of steamers made waver on the horizon, she became with all that power sweeping savagely in and inevitably withdrawing, hypnotised, and the two senses of that vastness and this tininess (the pool had diminished again) flowering within it made her feel that she was bound hand and foot and unable to move by the intensity of feelings which reduced her own body, her own life, and the lives of all the people in the world, for ever, to nothingness. So listening to the waves, crouching over the pool, she brooded." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2807-as-a-woman-i-have-no-country-as-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 07:42:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by virginia woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2807-as-a-woman-i-have-no-country-as-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As a woman I have no country. As a woman I want no country. As a woman, my country is the whole world." -- virginia woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4962-i-act-as-the-tongue-of-you-tied-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 08:02:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4962-i-act-as-the-tongue-of-you-tied-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I act as the tongue of you,
... tied in your mouth . . . . in mine it begins to be loosened." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7690-my-patience-has-dreadful-chilblains-from-standing-so-long-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2007 04:38:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Elizabeth Barrett Browning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7690-my-patience-has-dreadful-chilblains-from-standing-so-long-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My patience has dreadful chilblains from standing so long on a monument." -- Elizabeth Barrett Browning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/922-i-took-a-deep-breath-and-listened-to-the-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2008 04:32:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/922-i-took-a-deep-breath-and-listened-to-the-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I took a deep breath and listened to the old brag of my heart. I am, I am, I am." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7038-kiss-me-and-you-will-see-how-important-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2008 04:32:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7038-kiss-me-and-you-will-see-how-important-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kiss me, and you will see how important I am." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4641-jane-be-still-don-t-struggle-so-like-a-wild-frantic</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 10:47:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4641-jane-be-still-don-t-struggle-so-like-a-wild-frantic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jane, be still; don't struggle so like a wild, frantic bird, that is rending its own plumage in its desperation.&quot;
&quot;I am no bird; and no net ensnares me; I am a free human being, with an independent will; which I now exert to leave you." -- Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3847-it-was-at-that-age-that-poetry-came-in-search</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 10:54:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3847-it-was-at-that-age-that-poetry-came-in-search]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was at that age
that poetry came in search of me." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22946-i-once-typed-vagina-dentata-into-dictionary-com-and-it-asked</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 13:23:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Juliet Cook]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22946-i-once-typed-vagina-dentata-into-dictionary-com-and-it-asked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I once typed 'vagina dentata' into dictionary.com and it asked me, 'Did you mean giant anteater?" -- Juliet Cook]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9481-if-all-else-perished-and-he-remained-i-should-still</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 04:40:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Emily Jane Brontë ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9481-if-all-else-perished-and-he-remained-i-should-still]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If all else perished, and he remained, I should still continue to be; and if all else remained, and he were annihilated, the universe would turn to a mighty stranger." -- Emily Jane Brontë ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13578-be-with-me-always---take-any-form---drive</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 04:40:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dusie Press add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13578-be-with-me-always---take-any-form---drive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be with me always - take any form - drive me mad! only do not leave me in this abyss, where I cannot find you! Oh, God! it is unutterable! I can not live without my life! I can not live without my soul!" -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
