<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/152111-carmen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/152111-carmen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2008 20:24:49 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1695-the-thing-that-hath-been-it-is-that-which-shall</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2008 20:24:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carmen add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1695-the-thing-that-hath-been-it-is-that-which-shall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The thing that hath been, it is that which shall be; and that which is done is that which shall be done: and there is no new thing under the sun." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31224-it-is-a-profound-and-necessary-truth-that-the-deep</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 11:00:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carmen add a quote by Robert Oppenheimer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31224-it-is-a-profound-and-necessary-truth-that-the-deep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a profound and necessary truth that the deep things in science are not found because they are useful; they are found because it was possible to find them." -- Robert Oppenheimer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5539-a-few-light-taps-upon-the-pane-made-him-turn</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 18:50:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carmen add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5539-a-few-light-taps-upon-the-pane-made-him-turn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A few light taps upon the pane made him turn to the window. It had begun to snow again. He watched sleepily the flakes, silver and dark, falling obliquely against the lamplight. The time had come for him to set out on his journey westward. Yes, the newspapers were right: snow was general all over Ireland. It was falling on every part of the dark central plain, on the treeless hills, falling softly upon the Bog of Allen and, farther westward, softly falling into the dark mutinous Shannon waves. It was falling, too, upon every part of the lonely churchyard on the hill where Michael Furey lay buried. It lay thickly drifted on the crooked crosses and headstones, on the spears of the little gate, on the barren thorns. His soul swooned slowly as he heard the snow falling faintly through the universe and faintly falling, like the descent of their last end, upon all the living and the dead." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82472-what-s-great-about-this-country-is-america-started-the-tradition</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2009 12:17:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carmen add a quote by Andy Warhol]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82472-what-s-great-about-this-country-is-america-started-the-tradition]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What's great about this country is America started the tradition where the richest consumers buy essentially the same things as the poorest. You can be watching TV and see Coca-Cola, and you can know that the President drinks Coke, Liz Taylor drinks Coke, and just think, you can drink Coke, too. A Coke is a Coke and no amount of money can get you a better Coke than the one the bum on the corner is drinking. All the Cokes are the same and all the Cokes are good." -- Andy Warhol]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203978-whenever-i-find-myself-growing-grim-about-the-mouth-whenever</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2010 21:38:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carmen add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203978-whenever-i-find-myself-growing-grim-about-the-mouth-whenever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever I find myself growing grim about the mouth; whenever it is a damp, drizzly November in my soul; whenever I find myself involuntarily pausing before coffin warehouses, and bringing up the rear of every funeral I meet; and especially whenever my hypos get such an upper hand of me, that it requires a strong moral principle to prevent me from deliberately stepping into the street, and methodically knocking people's hats off--then, I account it high time to get to sea as soon as I can. This is my substitute for pistol and ball. With a philosophical flourish Cato throws himself upon his sword; I quietly take to the ship." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3692-i-have-written-a-wicked-book-and-feel-spotless-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 15:24:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carmen add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3692-i-have-written-a-wicked-book-and-feel-spotless-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have written a wicked book, and feel spotless as the lamb." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/624-if-i-read-a-book-and-it-makes-my-whole</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 09:39:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carmen add a quote by Emily Dickinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/624-if-i-read-a-book-and-it-makes-my-whole]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I read a book and it makes my whole body so cold no fire can warm me, I know that is poetry. If I feel physically as if the top of my head were taken off, I know that is poetry. These are the only ways I know it. Is there any other way?" -- Emily Dickinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/517587-numberless-are-the-world-s-wonders-but-none-more-wonderful-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 12:12:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carmen add a quote by Sophocles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/517587-numberless-are-the-world-s-wonders-but-none-more-wonderful-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Numberless are the world's wonders, but none
More wonderful than man; the storm gray sea
Yields to his prows, the huge crests bear him high;
Earth, holy and inexhaustible, is graven
With shining furrows where his plows have gone
Year after year, the timeless labor of stallions.

The light-boned birds and beasts that cling to cover,
The lithe fish lighting their reaches of dim water,
All are taken, tamed in the net of his mind;
The lion on the hill, the wild horse windy-maned,
Resign to him; and his blunt yoke has broken
The sultry shoulders of the mountain bull.

Words also, and thought as rapid as air,
He fashions to his good use; statecraft is his
And his the skill that deflects the arrows of snow,
The spears of winter rain: from every wind
He has made himself secure--from all but one:
In the late wind of death he cannot stand.

O clear intelligence, force beyond all measure!
O fate of man, working both good and evil!
When the laws are kept, how proudly his city stands!
When the laws are broken, what of his city then?
Never may the anarchic man find rest at my hearth,
Never be it said that my thoughts are his thoughts." -- Sophocles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30824-art-like-morality-consists-of-drawing-the-line-somewhere</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 06:32:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carmen add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30824-art-like-morality-consists-of-drawing-the-line-somewhere]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Art, like morality, consists of drawing the line somewhere." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/594266-i-found-rome-built-of-bricks-i-leave-her-clothed</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 06:40:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carmen add a quote by Caesar Augustus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/594266-i-found-rome-built-of-bricks-i-leave-her-clothed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I found Rome built of bricks; I leave her clothed in marble." -- Caesar Augustus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9840-we-shall-not-cease-from-exploration-and-the-end-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 07:35:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carmen add a quote by T. S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9840-we-shall-not-cease-from-exploration-and-the-end-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We shall not cease from exploration
And the end of all our exploring
Will be to arrive where we started
And know the place for the first time." -- T. S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311153-without-any-wind-blowing-the-sheer-weight-of-a-raindrop</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2013 18:07:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carmen add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311153-without-any-wind-blowing-the-sheer-weight-of-a-raindrop]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without any wind blowing, the sheer weight of a raindrop, shining in parasitic luxury on a cordate leaf, caused its tip to dip, and what looked like a globule of quicksilver performed a sudden glissando down the centre vein, and then, having shed its bright load, the relieved leaf unbent. Tip, leaf, dip, relief - the instant it all took to happen seemed to me not so much a fraction of time as a fissure in it, a missed heartbeat, which was refunded at once by a patter of rhymes: I say 'patter' intentionally, for when a gust of wind did come, the trees would briskly start to drip all together in as crude an imitation of the recent downpour as the stanza I was already muttering resembled the shock of wonder I had experienced when for a moment heart and leaf had been one." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
