<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/152523-dani]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/152523-dani" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 23:06:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154538-where-am-i-or-what-from-what-causes-do-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 23:06:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dani add a quote by David Hume]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154538-where-am-i-or-what-from-what-causes-do-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where am I, or what? From what causes do I derive my existence, and to what condition shall I return? ... I am confounded with all these questions, and begin to fancy myself in the most deplorable condition imaginable, environed with the deepest darkness, and utterly deprived of the use of every member and faculty.

Most fortunately it happens, that since Reason is incapable of dispelling these clouds, Nature herself suffices to that purpose, and cures me of this philosophical melancholy and delirium, either by relaxing this bent of mind, or by some avocation, and lively impression of my senses, which obliterate all these chimeras. I dine, I play a game of backgammon, I converse, and am merry with my friends. And when, after three or four hours' amusement, I would return to these speculations, they appear so cold, and strained, and ridiculous, that I cannot find in my heart to enter into them any farther." -- David Hume]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/634032-i-know-you-are-asking-what-if-i-am-wrong</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 20:42:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dani add a quote by John Hodgman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/634032-i-know-you-are-asking-what-if-i-am-wrong]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I Know you are asking: What if I am wrong?
What if RAGNAROK does not come? What if it does not happen the way I say it is going to happen? 
I suppose that is a possibility.
Perhaps the Mayans WERE wrong.
Maybe we WILL enter a new era of consciousness.
Maybe we will NOT destroy ourselves with technology.
Perhaps it will be that some new old god comes. Say his name is DOZGOTH, the 701st, and say he takes pity on us. And a thousand years after all the suffering of RAGNOROK, he will retcon us back to the very day this book was pusblished.
You will remember nothing of what happened or what you did to survive. The only evidence that any of this ever happened will be this book, and the fact that ou now have a tentacle instead of an arm. But you will explain that away simply by saying you are wearing an octopus sleeve. The mind can explain so many things when it wants to close its eyes and sleep.
Perhaps only one person will remember what really happened, and he will be named Jonathan Coulton. But he cannot tell anyone, for he is but an animal." -- John Hodgman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110733-both-described-at-the-same-time-how-it-was-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2013 06:54:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dani add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110733-both-described-at-the-same-time-how-it-was-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Both described at the same time how it was always March there and always Monday, and then they understood that José Arcadio Buendía was not as crazy as the family said, but that he was the only one who had enough lucidity to sense the truth of the fact that time also stumbled and had accidents and could therefore splinter and leave an eternalized fragment in a room." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40690-thus-i-rediscovered-what-writers-have-always-known-and-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2013 04:15:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dani add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40690-thus-i-rediscovered-what-writers-have-always-known-and-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thus I rediscovered what writers have always known (and have told us again and again): books always speak of other books, and every story tells a story that has already been told." -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115220-until-then-i-had-thought-each-book-spoke-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2013 04:21:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dani add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115220-until-then-i-had-thought-each-book-spoke-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until then I had thought each book spoke of the things, human or divine, that lie outside books.  Now I realized that not infrequently books speak of books: it is as if they spoke among themselves.  In the light of this reflection, the library seemed all the more disturbing to me.  It was then the place of a long, centuries-old murmuring, an imperceptible dialogue between one parchment and another, a living thing, a receptacle of powers not to be ruled by a human mind, a treasure of secrets emanated by many minds, surviving the death of those who had produced them or had been their conveyors." -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139175-it-is-a-terrible-thing-this-kindess-that-human-beings</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 20:13:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dani add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139175-it-is-a-terrible-thing-this-kindess-that-human-beings]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a terrible thing, this kindess that human beings do not lose. Terrible, because when we are finally naked in the dark and cold, it is all we have. We who are so rich, so full of strength, we end up with that small change. We have nothing else to give. " -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220607-the-unknown-said-faxe-s-soft-voice-in-the-forest-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 20:15:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dani add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220607-the-unknown-said-faxe-s-soft-voice-in-the-forest-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The unknown,&quot; said Faxe's soft voice in the forest, &quot;the unforetold, the unproven, that is what life is based on. Ignorance is the ground of thought. Unproof is the ground of action. If it were proven that there is no God there would be no religion. No Handdara, no Yomesh, no hearthgods, nothing. But also if it were proven that there is a God, there would be no religion. ... Tell me, Genry, what is known? What is sure, unpredictable, inevitable -- the one certain thing you know concerning your future, and mine?&quot;

That we shall die.&quot;

Yes, There's really only one question that can be answered, Genry, and we already know the answer. ... The only thing that makes life possible is permanent, intolerable uncertainty: not knowing what comes next." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
