<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/153062-kristen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/153062-kristen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2011 17:20:46 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23275-god-wants-us-to-choose-to-love-him-freely-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2011 17:20:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Philip Yancey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23275-god-wants-us-to-choose-to-love-him-freely-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God wants us to choose to love him freely, even when that choice involves pain, because we are committed to him, not to our own good feelings and rewards.  He wants us to cleave to him, as Job did, even when we have every reason to deny him hotly.  That, I believe, is the central message of Job.  Satan had taunted God with the accusation that humans are not truly free.  Was Job being faithful simply because God had allowed him a prosperous life?  Job's fiery trials proved the answer beyond doubt.  Job clung to God's justice when he was the best example in history of God's apparent injustice.  He did not seek the Giver because of his gifts; when all gifts were removed he still sought the Giver." -- Philip Yancey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23295-mama-s-love-had-always-been-the-kind-that-acted-itself</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2011 17:20:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Corrie Ten Boom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23295-mama-s-love-had-always-been-the-kind-that-acted-itself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mama's love had always been the kind that acted itself out with soup pot and sewing basket. But now that these things were taken away, the love seemed as whole as before. She sat in her chair at the window and loved us. She loved the people she saw in the street-- and beyond: her love took in the city, the land of Holland, the world. And so I learned that love is larger than the walls which shut it in. " -- Corrie Ten Boom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198195-it-is-a-long-way-to-ireland-janet-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2011 17:21:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198195-it-is-a-long-way-to-ireland-janet-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a long way to Ireland, Janet, and I am sorry to send my little friend on such weary travels: but if I can't do better, how is it to be helped? Are you anything akin to me, do you think, Jane?&quot;

I could risk no sort of answer by this time: my heart was still. 

&quot;Because, he said, &quot;I sometimes have a queer feeling with regard to you - especially when you are near me, as now: it is as if I had a string somewhere under my left ribs, tightly and inextricably knotted to a similar string situated in the corresponding quarter of your little frame. And if that boisterous channel, and two hundred miles or so of land some broad between us, I am afraid that cord of communion will be snapt; and then I've a nervous notion I should take to bleeding inwardly. As for you, - you'd forget me." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140393-being-in-a-minority-even-in-a-minority-of-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2011 17:21:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140393-being-in-a-minority-even-in-a-minority-of-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being in a minority, even in a minority of one, did not make you mad.  There was truth and there was untruth, and if you clung to the truth even against the whole world, you were not mad." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23289-and-your-will-shall-decide-your-destiny-he-said-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2011 17:21:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23289-and-your-will-shall-decide-your-destiny-he-said-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And your will shall decide your destiny,&quot; he said: &quot;I offer you my hand, my heart, and a share of all my possessions.&quot; 

You play a farce, which I merely laugh at.&quot; 

I ask you to pass through life at my side--to be my second self, and best earthly companion.&quot; 

For that fate you have already made your choice, and must abide by it.&quot; 

Jane, be still a few moments: you are over-excited: I will be still too.&quot; 

A waft of wind came sweeping down the laurel-walk, and trembled through the boughs of the chestnut: it wandered away--away--to an indefinite distance--it died. The nightingale's song was then the only voice of the hour: in listening to it, I again wept. Mr. Rochester sat quiet, looking at me gently and seriously. Some time passed before he spoke; he at last said - 

Come to my side, Jane, and let us explain and understand one another.&quot; 

I will never again come to your side: I am torn away now, and cannot return.&quot; 

But, Jane, I summon you as my wife: it is you only I intend to marry.&quot; 

I was silent: I thought he mocked me. 

Come, Jane--come hither.&quot; 

Your bride stands between us.&quot; 

He rose, and with a stride reached me. 

My bride is here,&quot; he said, again drawing me to him, &quot;because my equal is here, and my likeness. Jane, will you marry me?" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
