<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/153021-susan-ronnenberg]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/153021-susan-ronnenberg" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 09:48:23 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73427-in-fact-that-is-why-the-lives-of-most-women</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 09:48:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Brenda Ueland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73427-in-fact-that-is-why-the-lives-of-most-women]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In fact that is why the lives of most women are so vaguely unsatisfactory. They are always doing secondary and menial things (that do not require all their gifts and ability) for others and never anything for themselves. Society and husbands praise them for it (when they get too miserable or have nervous breakdowns) though always a little perplexedly and half-heartedly and just to be consoling. The poor wives are reminded that that is just why wives are so splendid -- because they are so unselfish and self-sacrificing and that is the wonderful thing about them! But inwardly women know that something is wrong. They sense that if you are always doing something for others, like a servant or nurse, and never anything for yourself, you cannot do others any good. You make them physically more comfortable. But you cannot affect them spiritually in any way at all. For to teach, encourage, cheer up, console, amuse, stimulate or advise a husband or children or friends, you have to be something yourself. [...]&quot;If you would shut your door against the children for an hour a day and say; 'Mother is working on her five-act tragedy in blank verse!' you would be surprised how they would respect you. They would probably all become playwrights." -- Brenda Ueland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11268-it-makes-you-wonder-all-the-brilliant-things-we-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 10:02:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Ann Patchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11268-it-makes-you-wonder-all-the-brilliant-things-we-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It makes you wonder. All the brilliant things we might have done with our lives if only we suspected we knew how." -- Ann Patchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11331-he-wondered-if-what-he-had-taken-for-the-richness</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 10:04:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11331-he-wondered-if-what-he-had-taken-for-the-richness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He wondered if what he had taken for the richness of silence was really the poverty of never being heard [...].  How could he have forgotten what he had always known:  there is no match for the silence of God." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33881-the-truth-is-the-thing-i-invented-so-i-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 10:06:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33881-the-truth-is-the-thing-i-invented-so-i-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is the thing I invented so I could live." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47521-franz-kafka-is-dead-he-died-in-a-tree-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 10:07:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47521-franz-kafka-is-dead-he-died-in-a-tree-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Franz Kafka is Dead
 
He died in a tree from which he wouldn't come down. &quot;Come down!&quot; they cried to him. &quot;Come down! Come down!&quot; Silence filled the night, and the night filled the silence, while they waited for Kafka to speak. &quot;I can't,&quot; he finally said, with a note of wistfulness. &quot;Why?&quot; they cried. Stars spilled across the black sky. &quot;Because then you'll stop asking for me.&quot; The people whispered and nodded among themselves. They put their arms around each other, and touched their children's hair. They took off their hats and raised them to the small, sickly man with the ears of a strange animal, sitting in his black velvet suit in the dark tree. Then they turned and started for home under the canopy of leaves. Children were carried on their fathers' shoulders, sleepy from having been taken to see who wrote his books on pieces of bark he tore off the tree from which he refused to come down. In his delicate, beautiful, illegible handwriting. And they admired those books, and they admired his will and stamina. After all: who doesn't wish to make a spectacle of his loneliness? One by one families broke off with a good night and a squeeze of the hands, suddenly grateful for the company of neighbors. Doors closed to warm houses. Candles were lit in windows. Far off, in his perch in the trees , Kafka listened to it all: the rustle of the clothes being dropped to the floor, or lips fluttering along naked shoulders, beds creaking along the weight of tenderness. It all caught in the delicate pointed shells of his ears and rolled like pinballs through the great hall of his mind. 

That night a freezing wind blew in. When the children woke up, they went to the window and found the world encased in ice. One child, the smallest, shrieked out in delight and her cry tore through the silence and exploded the ice of a giant oak tree. The world shone. 

They found him frozen on the ground like a bird. It's said that when they put their ears to the shell of his ears, they could hear themselves." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3390-holding-hands-for-example-is-a-way-to-remember-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 10:07:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3390-holding-hands-for-example-is-a-way-to-remember-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Holding hands, for example, is a way to remember how it feels to say nothing together." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71213-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-who-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 11:08:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71213-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-who-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time there was a boy who loved a girl, and her laughter was a question he wanted to spend his whole life answering." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1718-the-very-least-you-can-do-in-your-life-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 10:23:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1718-the-very-least-you-can-do-in-your-life-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The very least you can do in your life is figure out what you hope for. And the most you can do is live inside that hope. Not admire it from a distance but live right in it, under its roof." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19727-solitude-is-a-human-presumption-every-quiet-step-is-thunder</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 10:24:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19727-solitude-is-a-human-presumption-every-quiet-step-is-thunder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Solitude is a human presumption. Every quiet step is thunder to beetle life underfoot, a tug of impalpable thread on the web pulling mate to mate and predator to prey, a beginning or an end. Every choice is a world made new for the chosen." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11323-there-s-such-a-gulf-between-yourself-and-who-you-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 10:24:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11323-there-s-such-a-gulf-between-yourself-and-who-you-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's such a gulf between yourself and who you were then, but people speak to that other person and it answers; it's like having a stranger as a house guest in your skin." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38534-april-is-the-cruelest-month-t-s-eliot-wrote-by-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 10:25:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38534-april-is-the-cruelest-month-t-s-eliot-wrote-by-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["April is the cruelest month, T.S. Eliot wrote, by which I think he meant (among other things) that springtime makes people crazy. We expect too much, the world burgeons with promises it can't keep, all passion is really a setup, and we're doomed to get our hearts broken yet again. I agree, and would further add: Who cares? Every spring I go out there anyway, around the bend, unconditionally. ... Come the end of the dark days, I am more than joyful. I'm nuts. " -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28069-i-attempted-briefly-to-consecrate-myself-in-the-public-library</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 10:26:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28069-i-attempted-briefly-to-consecrate-myself-in-the-public-library]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I attempted briefly to consecrate myself in the public library, believing every crack in my soul could be chinked with a book." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56776-the-power-is-in-the-balance-we-are-our-injuries</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 10:26:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56776-the-power-is-in-the-balance-we-are-our-injuries]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The power is in the balance: we are our injuries, as much as we are our successes." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61090-close-the-door-write-with-no-one-looking-over-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 10:27:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61090-close-the-door-write-with-no-one-looking-over-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Close the door. Write with no one looking over your shoulder. Don't try to figure out what other people want to hear from you; figure out what you have to say. It's the one and only thing you have to offer." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31770-households-that-have-lost-the-soul-of-cooking-from-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 10:27:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31770-households-that-have-lost-the-soul-of-cooking-from-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Households that have lost the soul of cooking from their routines may not know what they are missing: the song of a stir-fry sizzle, the small talk of clinking measuring spoons, the yeasty scent of rising dough, the painting of flavors onto a pizza before it slides into the oven." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11646-tortolita-let-me-tell-you-a-story-estevan-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 10:30:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11646-tortolita-let-me-tell-you-a-story-estevan-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["	“Tortolita, let me tell you a story,” Estevan said.  “This is a South American, wild Indian story about heaven and hell.”  Mrs. Parsons made a prudish face, and Estevan went on.  “If you go visit hell, you will see a room like this kitchen.  There is a pot of delicious stew on the table, with the most delicate aroma you can imagine.  All around, people sit, like us.  Only they are dying of starvation.  They are jibbering and jabbering,” he looked extra hard at Mrs. Parsons, “but they cannot get a bit of this wonderful stew God has made for them.  Now, why is that?”
	“Because they’re choking?  For all eternity?” Lou Ann asked.  Hell, for Lou Ann, would naturally be a place filled with sharp objects and small round foods.
	“No,” he said.  “Good guess, but no.  They are starving because they only have spoons with very long handles.  As long as that.”  He pointed to the mop, which I had forgotten to put away.  “With these ridiculous, terrible spoons, the people in hell can reach into the pot but they cannot put the food in their mouths.  Oh, how hungry they are!  Oh, how they swear and curse each other!” he said, looking again at Virgie.  He was enjoying this.
	“Now,” he went on, “you can go and visit heaven.  What?  You see a room just like the first one, the same table, the same pot of stew, the same spoons as long as a sponge mop.  But these people are all happy and fat.”
	“Real fat, or do you mean just well-fed?” Lou Ann asked.
	“Just well-fed,” he said.  “Perfectly, magnificently well-fed, and very happy.  Why do you think?”
	He pinched up a chunk of pineapple in his chopsticks, neat as you please, and reached all the way across the table to offer it to Turtle.  She took it like a newborn bird." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60593-memory-is-a-complicated-thing-a-relative-to-truth-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 10:30:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60593-memory-is-a-complicated-thing-a-relative-to-truth-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Memory is a complicated thing, a relative to truth, but not its twin." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63936-cooking-is-80-percent-confidence-a-skill-best-acquired-starting</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 10:30:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63936-cooking-is-80-percent-confidence-a-skill-best-acquired-starting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cooking is 80 percent confidence, a skill best acquired starting from when the apron strings wrap around you twice." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
