<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/153443-maureen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/153443-maureen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2010 19:54:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82918-with-friends-if-you-keep-making-an-effort-to-reach</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2010 19:54:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Tori Spelling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82918-with-friends-if-you-keep-making-an-effort-to-reach]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With friends, if you keep making an effort to reach out and you keep getting hurt, you eventually stop trying. But it's much harder to give up on family. Somewhere deep down you want it to work so badly that you keep making the same mistake over and over again." -- Tori Spelling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331595-i-know-now-one-must-plan-one-s-old-age-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 05:15:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Elizabeth Forsythe Hailey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331595-i-know-now-one-must-plan-one-s-old-age-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know now one must plan one’s old age as surely as one plans any other stage of life. The tragedy of Cousin Josie’s life is that she never knew what she wanted at any age—only what she did not want. She never wanted to marry nor to pursue a career, and in life, unlike grammar, double negatives do not produce an affirmative." -- Elizabeth Forsythe Hailey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331598-life-causes-estrangement-enough-why-do-we-add-to-it-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 05:15:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Elizabeth Forsythe Hailey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331598-life-causes-estrangement-enough-why-do-we-add-to-it-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life causes estrangement enough—why do we add to it out of misplaced pride?" -- Elizabeth Forsythe Hailey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38257-there-is-no-happiness-like-that-of-being-loved-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 19:21:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38257-there-is-no-happiness-like-that-of-being-loved-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no happiness like that of being loved by your fellow creatures, and feeling that your presence is an addition to their comfort." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346856-do-you-think-because-i-am-poor-obscure-plain-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 19:22:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346856-do-you-think-because-i-am-poor-obscure-plain-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you think, because I am poor, obscure, plain and little, I am soulless and heartless? You think wrong! - I have as much soul as you, - and full as much heart! And if God had gifted me with some beauty and much wealth, I should have made it as hard for you to leave me, as it is now for me to leave you!" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42145-the-best-remedy-for-those-who-are-afraid-lonely-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 15:05:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42145-the-best-remedy-for-those-who-are-afraid-lonely-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best remedy for those who are afraid, lonely or unhappy is to go outside, somewhere where they can be quite alone with the heavens, nature and God.  Because only then does one feel  that all is as it should be and that God wishes to see people happy, amidst the simple beauty of nature.  As longs as this exists, and it certainly always will, I know that then there will always be comfort for every sorrow, whatever the circumstances may be.  And I firmly believe that nature brings solace in all troubles." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11341-talk-is-cheap-and-easy-making-dreams-real-takes-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 12:20:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Peter Jenkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11341-talk-is-cheap-and-easy-making-dreams-real-takes-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Talk is cheap and easy; making dreams real takes hard, humble work.  Dreams in the Midwest are acceptable, just keep them to yourself.  Maybe tell your family, but don't just talk—do something about it." -- Peter Jenkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15849-make-a-radical-change-in-your-lifestyle-and-begin-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 10:51:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15849-make-a-radical-change-in-your-lifestyle-and-begin-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["make a radical change in your lifestyle and begin to boldly do things which you may previously never have thought of doing, or been too hesitant to attempt. So many people live within unhappy circumstances and yet will not take the initiative to change their situation because they are conditioned to a life of security, conformity, and conservation, all of which may appear to give one peace of mind, but in reality nothing is more damaging to the adventurous spirit within a man than a secure future. The very basic core of a man's living spirit is his passion for adventure. The joy of life comes from our encounters with new experiences, and hence there is no greater joy than to have an endlessly changing horizon, for each day to have a new and different sun. If you want to get more out of life, you must lose your inclination for monotonous security and adopt a helter-skelter style of life that will at first appear to you to be crazy. But once you become accustomed to such a life you will see its full meaning and its incredible beauty." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31708-love-is-like-the-wind-you-can-t-see-it-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 05:18:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31708-love-is-like-the-wind-you-can-t-see-it-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is like the wind, you can't see it but you can feel it." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280130-it-happens-the-world-over---we-love-ourselves-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2011 05:06:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Irene Hunt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280130-it-happens-the-world-over---we-love-ourselves-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It happens the world over - we love ourselves more than we do the one we say we love.  We all want to be Number One, we've got to be Number One or nothing! We can't see that we could make ourselves loved and needed in the Number Two, or Three, or Four spot.  No sir, we've got to be Number One, and if we can't make it, we'll rip and tear at the loved one till we've ruined every smidgin of love that was ever there." -- Irene Hunt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71213-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-who-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2011 06:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71213-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-who-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time there was a boy who loved a girl, and her laughter was a question he wanted to spend his whole life answering." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107311-if-you-hide-your-ignorance-no-one-will-hit-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2011 11:39:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107311-if-you-hide-your-ignorance-no-one-will-hit-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you hide your ignorance, no one will hit you and you'll never learn." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213991-we-cannot-tell-the-precise-moment-when-friendship-is-formed</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2011 11:41:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213991-we-cannot-tell-the-precise-moment-when-friendship-is-formed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We cannot tell the precise moment when friendship is formed. As in filling a vessel drop by drop, there is at last a drop which makes it run over; so in a series of kindnesses there is at last one which makes the heart run over." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9120-if-we-listened-to-our-intellect-we-d-never-have-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2011 15:00:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9120-if-we-listened-to-our-intellect-we-d-never-have-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we listened to our intellect we'd never have a love affair. We'd never have a friendship. We'd never go in business because we'd be cynical: &quot;It's gonna go wrong.&quot; Or &quot;She's going to hurt me.&quot; Or,&quot;I've had a couple of bad love affairs, so therefore . . .&quot; Well, that's nonsense. You're going to miss life. You've got to jump off the cliff all the time and build your wings on the way down." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4959-you-don-t-have-to-burn-books-to-destroy-a-culture</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2011 15:00:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4959-you-don-t-have-to-burn-books-to-destroy-a-culture]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't have to burn books to destroy a culture. Just get people to stop reading them." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52574-the-answer-is-never-the-answer-what-s-really-interesting-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2011 07:16:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Ken Kesey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52574-the-answer-is-never-the-answer-what-s-really-interesting-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The answer is never the answer. What's really interesting is the mystery. If you seek the mystery instead of the answer, you'll always be seeking. I've never seen anybody really find the answer. They think they have, so they stop thinking. But the job is to seek mystery, evoke mystery, plant a garden in which strange plants grow and mysteries bloom. The need for mystery is greater than the need for an answer." -- Ken Kesey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366987-we-re-all-fools-said-clemens-all-the-time-it-s-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 05:27:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366987-we-re-all-fools-said-clemens-all-the-time-it-s-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're all fools,&quot; said Clemens, &quot;all the time. It's just we're a different kind each day. We think, I'm not a fool today. I've learned my lesson. I was a fool yesterday but not this morning. Then tomorrow we find out that, yes, we were a fool today too. I think the only way we can grow and get on in this world is to accept the fact we're not perfect and live accordingly." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61787-i-would-always-rather-be-happy-than-dignified</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 05:00:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61787-i-would-always-rather-be-happy-than-dignified]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would always rather be happy than dignified." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378554-while-the-sound-mixing-was-underway-bonzo-was-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 19:01:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Stephen Davis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378554-while-the-sound-mixing-was-underway-bonzo-was-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["While the sound mixing was underway, Bonzo was on the loose, taking care of buisness his own way. One night he showed up backstage at a Deep Purple concert at the Nassau Coliseum on Long Island. Bonzo was drunk and in very high spirits, and was wobbling on his feet in the wings when he noticed a free microphone during a lull in the music. Staggering forward, Bonzo walked out onto the stage before the Deep Purple roadies could grab him. The group stopped playing, amazed, as Bonzo grabbed the mike and shouted, 'My name is John Bonham of Led Zeppelin, and I just wanna tell ya that we got a new album comin' out and that it's fuckin' great!!' Then Bonzo turned to leave, but before he went he turned back and gratuitously insulted Deep Purple's guitarist. 'And as far as Tommy Bolin is concerned, he can't play for shit!!" -- Stephen Davis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 21:08:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Kent M. Keith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Paradoxical Commandments

People are illogical, unreasonable, and self-centered.
Love them anyway.

If you do good, people will accuse you of selfish ulterior motives.
Do good anyway.

If you are successful, you will win false friends and true enemies.
Succeed anyway.

The good you do today will be forgotten tomorrow.
Do good anyway.

Honesty and frankness make you vulnerable.
Be honest and frank anyway.

The biggest men and women with the biggest ideas can be shot down by the smallest men and women with the smallest minds.
Think big anyway.

People favor underdogs but follow only top dogs.
Fight for a few underdogs anyway.

What you spend years building may be destroyed overnight.
Build anyway.

People really need help but may attack you if you do help them.
Help people anyway.

Give the world the best you have and you'll get kicked in the teeth.
Give the world the best you have anyway." -- Kent M. Keith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3506-there-are-few-people-whom-i-really-love-and-still</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 21:07:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3506-there-are-few-people-whom-i-really-love-and-still]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are few people whom I really love, and still fewer of whom I think well. The more I see of the world, the more am I dissatisfied with it; and every day confirms my belief of the inconsistency of all human characters, and of the little dependence that can be placed on the appearance of merit or sense." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221523-guy-don-t-need-no-sense-to-be-a-nice-fella</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 07:38:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221523-guy-don-t-need-no-sense-to-be-a-nice-fella]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Guy don't need no sense to be a nice fella. Seems to me sometimes it jus' works the other way around. Take a real smart guy and he ain't hardly ever a nice fella." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199770-memories-even-your-most-precious-ones-fade-surprisingly-quickly-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 15:42:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199770-memories-even-your-most-precious-ones-fade-surprisingly-quickly-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Memories, even your most precious ones, fade surprisingly quickly. But I don’t go along with that. The memories I value most, I don’t ever see them fading." -- Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269882-we-took-away-your-art-because-we-thought-it-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 15:42:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269882-we-took-away-your-art-because-we-thought-it-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We took away your art because we thought it would reveal your souls. Or to put it more finely, we did it to prove you had souls at all." -- Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16238-some-people-never-go-crazy-what-truly-horrible-lives-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 03:39:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16238-some-people-never-go-crazy-what-truly-horrible-lives-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people never go crazy. What truly horrible lives they must lead." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739-when-i-despair-i-remember-that-all-through-history-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 07:58:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739-when-i-despair-i-remember-that-all-through-history-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I despair, I remember that all through history the way of truth and love have always won. There have been tyrants and murderers, and for a time, they can seem invincible, but in the end, they always fall. Think of it--always." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66512-i-believe-in-pink-i-believe-that-laughing-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 07:59:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66512-i-believe-in-pink-i-believe-that-laughing-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in pink. I believe that laughing is the best calorie burner. I believe in kissing, kissing a lot. I believe in being strong when everything seems to be going wrong. I believe that happy girls are the prettiest girls. I believe that tomorrow is another day and I believe in miracles." -- Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6384-imperfection-is-beauty-madness-is-genius-and-it-s-better-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 08:00:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6384-imperfection-is-beauty-madness-is-genius-and-it-s-better-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imperfection is beauty, madness is genius and it's better to be absolutely ridiculous than absolutely boring." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61620-goodnight-you-princes-of-maine-you-kings-of-new-england</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 15:54:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61620-goodnight-you-princes-of-maine-you-kings-of-new-england]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Goodnight you princes of Maine, you kings of New England." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98483-human-beings-may-be-miserable-specimens-in-the-main-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 13:23:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Orson Scott Card]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98483-human-beings-may-be-miserable-specimens-in-the-main-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human beings may be miserable specimens, in the main, but we can learn, and, through learning, become decent people." -- Orson Scott Card]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
