<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/154362-mirna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/154362-mirna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 05:59:49 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12227-how-often-since-then-has-she-wondered-what-might-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 05:59:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirna add a quote by Michael Cunningham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12227-how-often-since-then-has-she-wondered-what-might-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How often since then has she wondered what might have happened if she'd tried to remain with him; if she’d returned Richards kiss on the corner of Bleeker and McDougal, gone off somewhere (where?) with him, never bought the packet of incense or the alpaca coat with rose-shaped buttons. Couldn’t they have discovered something larger and stranger than what they've got. It is impossible not to imagine that other future, that rejected future, as taking place in Italy or France, among big sunny rooms and gardens; as being full of infidelities and great battles; as a vast and enduring romance laid over friendship so searing and profound it would accompany them to the grave and possibly even beyond. She could, she thinks, have entered another world. She could have had a life as potent and dangerous as literature itself.

Or then again maybe not, Clarissa tells herself. That's who I was. This is who I am--a decent woman with a good apartment, with a stable and affectionate marriage, giving a party. Venture too far for love, she tells herself, and you renounce citizenship in the country you've made for yourself. You end up just sailing from port to port.

Still, there is this sense of missed opportunity. Maybe there is nothing, ever, that can equal the recollection of having been young together. Maybe its as simple as that. Richard was the person Clarissa loved at her most optimistic moment. Richard had stood beside her at the ponds edge at dusk, wearing cut-off jeans and rubber sandals. Richard had called her Mrs. Dalloway, and they had kissed. His mouth had opened to hers; (exciting and utterly familiar, she'd never forget it) had worked its way shyly inside until she met its own. They'd kissed and walked around the pond together.

It had seemed like the beginning of happiness, and Clarissa is still sometimes shocked, more than thirty years later to realize that it was happiness; that the entire experience lay in a kiss and a walk. The anticipation of dinner and a book. The dinner is by now forgotten; Lessing has been long overshadowed by other writers. What lives undimmed in Clarissa's mind more than three decades later is a kiss at dusk on a patch of dead grass, and a walk around a pond as mosquitoes droned in the darkening air. There is still that singular perfection, and its perfect in part because it seemed, at the time, so clearly to promise more. Now she knows: That was the moment, right then. There has been no other." -- Michael Cunningham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122352-good-night-my--he-stopped-bit-his-lip-and-abruptly-left</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 23:04:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirna add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122352-good-night-my--he-stopped-bit-his-lip-and-abruptly-left]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good-night, my-&quot; He stopped, bit his lip, and abruptly left me." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346240-am-i-hideous-jane-very-sir-you-always-were-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 23:05:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirna add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346240-am-i-hideous-jane-very-sir-you-always-were-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Am I hideous, Jane?
Very, sir: you always were, you know." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/330167-the-eagerness-of-a-listener-quickens-the-tongue-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 23:07:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirna add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/330167-the-eagerness-of-a-listener-quickens-the-tongue-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The eagerness of a listener quickens the tongue of a narrator." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164423-when-his-first-born-was-put-into-his-arms-he-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 23:08:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirna add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164423-when-his-first-born-was-put-into-his-arms-he-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When his first-born was put into his arms, he could see that the boy had inherited his own eyes, as they once were - large, brilliant, and black." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78381-the-first-words-that-are-read-by-seekers-of-enlightenment</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2013 06:07:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirna add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78381-the-first-words-that-are-read-by-seekers-of-enlightenment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first words that are read by seekers of enlightenment in the secret, gong-banging, yeti-haunted valleys near the hub of the world, are when they look into The Life of Wen the Eternally Surprised.

The first question they ask is: 'Why was he eternally surprised?'

And they are told: 'Wen considered the nature of time and understood that the universe is, instant by instant, recreated anew. Therefore, he understood, there is in truth no past, only a memory of the past. Blink your eyes, and the world you see next did not exist when you closed them. Therefore, he said, the only appropriate state of the mind is surprise. The only appropriate state of the heart is joy. The sky you see now, you have never seen before. The perfect moment is now. Be glad of it.'

The first words read by the young Lu-Tze when he sought perplexity in the dark, teeming, rain-soaked city of Ankh-Morpork were: 'Rooms For Rent, Very Reasonable.' And he was glad of it." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
