<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/155441-chris]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/155441-chris" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2011 07:34:19 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217366-if-religion-is-the-opiate-of-the-people-tradition-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2011 07:34:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217366-if-religion-is-the-opiate-of-the-people-tradition-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If religion is the opiate of the people, tradition is an even more sinister analgesic, simply because it rarely appears sinister. If religion is a tight band, a throbbing vein, and a needle, tradition is a far homelier concoction: poppy seeds ground into tea; a sweet cocoa drink laced with cocaine; the kind of thing your grandmother might have made." -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432703-men-do-not-know-why-they-award-fame-to-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2011 18:55:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Thomas Mann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432703-men-do-not-know-why-they-award-fame-to-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men do not know why they award fame to one work of art rather than another. Without being in the faintest connoisseurs, they think to justify the warmth of their commendations by discovering it in a hundred virtues, whereas the real ground of their applause is inexplicable--it is sumpathy." -- Thomas Mann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84171-critics-who-treat-adult-as-a-term-of-approval-instead</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 06:39:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84171-critics-who-treat-adult-as-a-term-of-approval-instead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Critics who treat 'adult' as a term of approval, instead of as a merely descriptive term, cannot be adult themselves. To be concerned about being grown up, to admire the grown up because it is grown up, to blush at the suspicion of being childish; these things are the marks of childhood and adolescence. And in childhood and adolescence they are, in moderation, healthy symptoms. Young things ought to want to grow. But to carry on into middle life or even into early manhood this concern about being adult is a mark of really arrested development. When I was ten, I read fairy tales in secret and would have been ashamed if I had been found doing so. Now that I am fifty I read them openly. When I became a man I put away childish things, including the fear of childishness and the desire to be very grown up." -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
