<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/155411-michael]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/155411-michael" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 09:02:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/611386-we-are-here-to-inscribe-ourselves-on-the-universe-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 09:02:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Kim Stanley Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/611386-we-are-here-to-inscribe-ourselves-on-the-universe-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are here to inscribe ourselves on the universe, and it is not inappropriate to remind ourselves of this when blank slates are given us." -- Kim Stanley Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/375711-it-has-occurred-to-me-that-the-thing-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 09:02:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by James A. Garfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/375711-it-has-occurred-to-me-that-the-thing-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It has occurred to me that the thing you have, that all men have enough of, is perhaps the thing that you care for the best, and that is your leisure - the leisure you have to think; the leisure you have to be let alone; the leisure you have to throw the plummet into your mind, and sound the depth and dive for things below." -- James A. Garfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183951-joy-is-in-the-ears-that-hear</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 09:02:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Stephen R Donaldson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183951-joy-is-in-the-ears-that-hear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Joy is in the ears that hear." -- Stephen R Donaldson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70275-the-term-is-over-the-holidays-have-begun-the-dream</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 09:03:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70275-the-term-is-over-the-holidays-have-begun-the-dream]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The term is over: the holidays have begun. The dream is ended: this is the morning." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156779-we-will-go-out-into-the-world-and-plant-gardens</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 09:03:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Kim Stanley Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156779-we-will-go-out-into-the-world-and-plant-gardens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We will go out into the world and plant gardens and orchards to the horizons, we will build roads through the mountains and across the deserts, and terrace the mountains and irrigate the deserts until there will be garden everywhere, and plenty for all, and there will be no more empires or kingdoms, no more caliphs, sultans, emirs, khans, or zamindars, no more kings or queens or princes, no more quadis or mullahs or ulema, no more slavery and no more usury, no more property and no more taxes, no more rich and no more poor, no killing or maiming or torture or execution, no more jailers and no more prisoners, no more generals, soldiers, armies or navies, no more patriarchy, no more caste, no more hunger, no more suffering than what life brings us for being born and having to die, and then we will see for the first time what kind of creatures we really are." -- Kim Stanley Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183958-the-world-is-a-huge-space-but-the-space-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 09:03:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183958-the-world-is-a-huge-space-but-the-space-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is a huge space, but the space that will take you in - and it doesn't have to be very big - is nowhere to be found. You seek a voice, but what do you get? Silence. You look for silence, but guess what? All you hear over and over and over is the voice of this omen. And sometimes this prophetic voice pushes a secret switch hidden deep inside your brain.

Your heart is like a great river after a long spell of rain, spilling over its banks. All signposts that once stood on the ground are gone, inundated and carried away by that rush of water. And still the rain beats down on the surface of the river. Every time you see a flood like that on the news you tell yourself: That's it. That's my heart." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5464-the-odor-of-bowel-wind-is-known-to-every-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2010 09:41:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by James Morrow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5464-the-odor-of-bowel-wind-is-known-to-every-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The odor of bowel wind is known to every human, but the fragrance of book glue has crossed only a fraction of mortal nostrils. And yet it behooves us not to judge the unlettered too harshly. We must stay the impulse to write CHUCKLEHEAD above their doors and carve DOLT upon their tombstones." -- James Morrow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250262-i-will-not-deny-but-that-the-best-apology-against</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2010 09:40:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by John Milton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250262-i-will-not-deny-but-that-the-best-apology-against]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will not deny but that the best apology against false accusers is silence and sufferance, and honest deeds set against dishonest words." -- John Milton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156829-hence-the-strong-attraction-which-magic-and-science-alike-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2010 09:40:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by James George Frazer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156829-hence-the-strong-attraction-which-magic-and-science-alike-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hence the strong attraction which magic and science alike have exercised on the human mind; hence the powerful stimulus that both have given to the pursuit of knowledge. They lure the weary enquirer, the footsore seeker, on through the wilderness of disappointment in the present by their endless promises of the future: they take him up to the top of an exceeding high mountain and show him, beyond the dark clouds and rolling mists at his feet, a vision of the celestial city, far off, it may be, but radiant with unearthly splendour, bathed in the light of dreams." -- James George Frazer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42175-the-quality-of-mercy-is-not-strain-d-it-droppeth-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2009 17:54:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42175-the-quality-of-mercy-is-not-strain-d-it-droppeth-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The quality of mercy is not strain'd,
It droppeth as the gentle rain from heaven
Upon the place beneath: it is twice blest;
It blesseth him that gives and him that takes:
'Tis mightiest in the mightiest: it becomes
The throned monarch better than his crown;
His sceptre shows the force of temporal power,
The attribute to awe and majesty,
Wherein doth sit the dread and fear of kings;
But mercy is above this sceptred sway;
It is enthroned in the hearts of kings,
It is an attribute to God himself;
And earthly power doth then show likest God's
When mercy seasons justice." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41193-friends-are-god-s-way-of-apologizing-for-your-family</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 21:25:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Dr. Wayne W. Dyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41193-friends-are-god-s-way-of-apologizing-for-your-family]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friends are God's way of apologizing for your family." -- Dr. Wayne W. Dyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/725336-i-would-be-quite-content-to-go-to-their-children-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 20:47:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/725336-i-would-be-quite-content-to-go-to-their-children-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would be quite content to go to their children's bar mitzvahs, to marvel at their Gothic cathedrals, to 'respect' their belief that the Koran was dictated, though exclusively in Arabic, to an illiterate merchant, or to interest myself in Wicca and Hindu and Jain consolations. And as it happens, I will continue to do this without insisting on the polite reciprocal condition - which is that they in turn leave me alone. But this, religion is ultimately incapable of doing." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
