<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/156639-sara]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/156639-sara" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 14:16:23 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206632-language-is-a-piss-poor-attempt-at-telepathy-is-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 14:16:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Tony Vigorito]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206632-language-is-a-piss-poor-attempt-at-telepathy-is-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Language is a piss poor attempt at telepathy is what it is. We try to put our thoughts into each other's heads through language...But half the intended meaning gets lost in the transmission, and the other half is filtered through existing assumptions. Everything is a half truth!

That's the whole problem! You can't understand me through the smog of your presumptions and prejudices. Multiply that six billion times and you'll begin to understand the desperation of our global situation" -- Tony Vigorito]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 14:16:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that's what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that is holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life.  

A true soul mate is probably the most important person you'll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake.  But to live with a soul mate forever?  Nah. Too painful.  Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then leave.  

A soul mates purpose is to shake you up, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light can get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you have to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269890-spontaneously-without-any-theological-training-i-a-child-grasped-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 11:14:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269890-spontaneously-without-any-theological-training-i-a-child-grasped-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Spontaneously, without any theological training, I, a child, grasped the incompatibility of God and shit and thus came to question the basic thesis of Christian anthropology, namely that man was created in God's image. Either/or: either man was created in God's image - and has intestines! - or God lacks intestines and man is not like him.

The ancient Gnostics felt as I did at the age of five. In the second century, the Great Gnostic master Valentinus resolved the damnable dilemma by claiming that Jesus &quot;ate and drank, but did not defecate.&quot;

Shit is a more onerous theological problem than is evil. Since God gave man freedom, we can, if need be, accept the idea that He is not responsible for man's crimes. The responsibility for shit, however, rests entirely with Him, the creator of man." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173699-when-we-want-to-give-expression-to-a-dramatic-situation</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 11:21:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173699-when-we-want-to-give-expression-to-a-dramatic-situation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we want to give expression to a dramatic situation in our lives, we tend to use metaphors of heaviness. We say that something has become a great burden to us. We either bear the burden or fail and go down with it, we struggle with it, win or lose. And Sabina - what had come over her? Nothing. She had left a man because she felt like leaving him. Had he persecuted her? Had he tried to take revenge on her? No. Her drama was a drama not of heaviness but of lightness. What fell to her lot was not the burden, but the unbearable lightness of being." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390261-nothing-could-go-wrong-because-nothing-had-i-meant-nothing-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 13:58:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390261-nothing-could-go-wrong-because-nothing-had-i-meant-nothing-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing could go wrong because nothing had...I meant &quot;nothing would.&quot; No - Then I quit trying to phrase it, realizing that if time travel ever became widespread, English grammar was going to have to add a whole new set of tenses to describe reflexive situations - conjugations that would make the French literary tenses and the Latin historical tenses look simple." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390263-madam-dorothea-shot-him-a-dark-look-if-you-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 14:01:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Cassandra Clare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390263-madam-dorothea-shot-him-a-dark-look-if-you-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Madam Dorothea shot him a dark look. &quot;If you were half as funny as you thought you were, my boy, you'd be twice as funny as you are." -- Cassandra Clare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174690-those-who-don-t-believe-in-magic-will-never-find-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 20:08:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Roald Dahl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174690-those-who-don-t-believe-in-magic-will-never-find-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who don't believe in magic will never find it." -- Roald Dahl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 18:11:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that everything happens for a reason. People change so that you can learn to let go, things go wrong so that you appreciate them when they're right, you believe lies so you eventually learn to trust no one but yourself, and sometimes good things fall apart so better things can fall together." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12867-if-you-can-make-a-woman-laugh-you-can-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 18:12:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12867-if-you-can-make-a-woman-laugh-you-can-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can make a woman laugh, you can make her do anything." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 18:14:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369145-all-a-girl-really-wants-is-for-one-guy-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 18:15:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369145-all-a-girl-really-wants-is-for-one-guy-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All a girl really wants is for one guy to prove to her that they are not all the same." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/469767-no-hospitals-she-says-i-know-where-are-we-going</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 11:36:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Richard Kadrey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/469767-no-hospitals-she-says-i-know-where-are-we-going]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No hospitals, she says.
I know.
Where are we going?
For ice cream. What's your favorite flavor?
Fuck you.
That's my favorite, too." -- Richard Kadrey]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
