<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/156826-katie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/156826-katie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 13:38:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/686432-i-knew-that-if-i-allowed-fear-to-overtake-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 13:38:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/686432-i-knew-that-if-i-allowed-fear-to-overtake-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I knew that if I allowed fear to overtake me, my journey was doomed. Fear, to a great extent, is born of a story we tell ourselves, and so I chose to tell myself a different story from the one women are told. I decided I was safe. I was strong. I was brave. Nothing could vanquish me." -- Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/458310-life-takes-us-to-unexpected-places-sometimes-the-future-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 13:39:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/458310-life-takes-us-to-unexpected-places-sometimes-the-future-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life takes us to unexpected places sometimes. The future is never set in stone, remember that." -- Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437142-the-circus-arrives-without-warning-no-announcements-precede-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 13:39:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437142-the-circus-arrives-without-warning-no-announcements-precede-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The circus arrives without warning. No announcements precede it. It is simply there, when yesterday it was not." -- Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429292-we-need-to-reclaim-the-word-feminism-we-need-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 13:46:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Caitlin Moran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429292-we-need-to-reclaim-the-word-feminism-we-need-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We need to reclaim the word 'feminism'. We need the word 'feminism' back real bad. When statistics come in saying that only 29% of American women would describe themselves as feminist - and only 42% of British women - I used to think, What do you think feminism IS, ladies? What part of 'liberation for women' is not for you? Is it freedom to vote? The right not to be owned by the man you marry? The campaign for equal pay? 'Vogue' by Madonna? Jeans? Did all that good shit GET ON YOUR NERVES? Or were you just DRUNK AT THE TIME OF THE SURVEY?" -- Caitlin Moran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265407-there-is-a-difference-between-interest-and-commitment-when-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2013 07:52:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Ken Blanchard ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265407-there-is-a-difference-between-interest-and-commitment-when-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a difference between interest and commitment. When you're interested in something, you do it only when it's convenient. When you're committed to something, you accept no excuses, only results." -- Ken Blanchard ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/714607-control-is-a-nice-concept-little-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2013 07:56:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Anna Quindlen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/714607-control-is-a-nice-concept-little-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Control is a nice concept, little more." -- Anna Quindlen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95737-we-throw-our-parties-we-abandon-our-families-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2013 10:42:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Michael Cunningham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95737-we-throw-our-parties-we-abandon-our-families-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We throw our parties; we abandon our families to live alone in Canada; we struggle to write books that do not change the world, despite our gifts and our unstinting efforts, our most extravagant hopes. We live our lives, do whatever we do, and then we sleep. It's as simple and ordinary as that. A few jump out windows, or drown themselves, or take pills; more die by accident; and most of us are slowly devoured by some disease, or, if we're very fortunate, by time itself. There's just this for consolation: an hour here or there when our lives seem, against all odds and expectations, to burst open and give us everything we've ever imagined, though everyone but children (and perhaps even they) know these hours will inevitably be followed by others, far darker and more difficult. Still, we cherish the city, the morning; we hope, more than anything, for more. Heaven only knows why we love it so..." -- Michael Cunningham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/463408-perhaps-we-don-t-like-what-we-see-our-hips-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2014 12:08:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Sufjan Stevens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/463408-perhaps-we-don-t-like-what-we-see-our-hips-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps we don't like what we see: our hips, our loss of hair, our shoe size, our dimples, our knuckles too big, our eating habits, our disposition. We have disclosed these things in secret, likes and dislikes, behind doors with locks, our lonely rooms, our messy desks, our empty hearts, our sudden bursts of energy, our sudden bouts of depression. Don’t worry. Put away your mirrors and your beauty magazines and your books on tape. There is someone right here who knows you more than you do, who is making room on the couch, who is fixing a meal, who is putting on your favorite record, who is listening intently to what you have to say, who is standing there with you, face to face, hand to hand, eye to eye, mouth to mouth. There is no space left uncovered. This is where you belong." -- Sufjan Stevens]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
