<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/157251-naomi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/157251-naomi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 22:04:40 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95621-verses-are-not-as-people-think-feelings-those-one-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 22:04:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Naomi add a quote by Rilke Rainer Maria]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95621-verses-are-not-as-people-think-feelings-those-one-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Verses are not, as people think, feelings (those one has early enough) -- they are experiences.  For the sake of a verse one must see many cities, men, and things, one must know the animals feel how birds fly, and know the gesture with which the little flowers open in the morning." -- Rilke Rainer Maria]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/359998-clocks-and-calendars-do-not-exist-to-remind-us-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 13:57:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Naomi add a quote by Orhan Pamuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/359998-clocks-and-calendars-do-not-exist-to-remind-us-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Clocks and calendars do not exist to remind us of the Time we've forgotten but to regulate our relations with others and indeed all of society, and this is how we use them." -- Orhan Pamuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407742-life-and-study-have-persuaded-me-of-the-openness-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 07:06:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Naomi add a quote by Fritz Stern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407742-life-and-study-have-persuaded-me-of-the-openness-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life and study have persuaded me of the openness of history.  There is no inevitability in history.  Thinking about what might have happened, what could have happened, is a necessary element in trying to understand what did happen.  And if, as I believe, individual acts of decency and courage make a difference, then they need to be recorded and remembered." -- Fritz Stern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408474-mine-is-a-most-peaceable-disposition-my-wishes-are-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 20:05:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Naomi add a quote by Heinrich Heine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408474-mine-is-a-most-peaceable-disposition-my-wishes-are-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mine is a most peaceable disposition.  My wishes are: a humble cottage with a thatched roof, but a good bed, good food, the freshest milk and butter, flowers before my window, and a few fine trees before my door; and if God wants to make my happiness complete, he will grant me the joy of seeing some six or seven of my enemies hanging from those trees.  Before death I shall, moved in my heart, forgive them all the wrong they did me in their lifetime.  One must, it is true, forgive one's enemies-- but not before they have been hanged." -- Heinrich Heine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384-painting-is-poetry-that-is-seen-rather-than-felt-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 14:13:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Naomi add a quote by Leonardo da Vinci]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384-painting-is-poetry-that-is-seen-rather-than-felt-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Painting is poetry that is seen rather than felt, and poetry is painting that is felt rather than seen." -- Leonardo da Vinci]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/568146-a-priest-s-life-is-spent-between-question-and-answer---or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 15:31:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Naomi add a quote by Naguib Mahfouz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/568146-a-priest-s-life-is-spent-between-question-and-answer---or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A priest's life is spent between question and answer-- or between a question and the attempt to answer it.  The question is the summary of the spiritual life." -- Naguib Mahfouz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/580810-nearly-everyone-in-the-world-has-appetites-and-impulses-trigger</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 09:00:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Naomi add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/580810-nearly-everyone-in-the-world-has-appetites-and-impulses-trigger]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nearly everyone in the world has appetites and impulses, trigger emotions, islands of selfishness, lusts just beneath the surface." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/611558-there-s-no-doubt-about-it-fun-people-are-fun-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 13:25:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Naomi add a quote by William Deresiewicz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/611558-there-s-no-doubt-about-it-fun-people-are-fun-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's no doubt about it: fun people are fun.  But I finally learned that there is something more important, in the people you know, than whether they are fun.  Thinking about those friends who had given me so much pleasure but who had also caused me so much pain, thinking about that bright, cruel world to which they'd introduced me, I saw that there's a better way to value people.  Not as fun or not fun, or stylish or not stylish, but as warm or cold, generous or selfish.  People who think about others and people who don't.  People who know how to listen, and people who only know how to talk." -- William Deresiewicz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625341-i-m-numb-and-i-m-tired-too-much-has-happened-today</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 20:29:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Naomi add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625341-i-m-numb-and-i-m-tired-too-much-has-happened-today]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm numb and I'm tired.  Too much has happened today.  I feel as if I'd been out in a pounding rain for forty-eight hours without an umbrella or a coat.  I'm soaked to the skin with emotion." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64515-but-i-m-glad-you-ll-see-me-as-i-am-above</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 07:58:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Naomi add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64515-but-i-m-glad-you-ll-see-me-as-i-am-above]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I'm glad you'll see me as I am. Above all, I wouldn't want people to think that I want to prove anything. I don't want to prove anything, I just want to live; to cause no evil to anyone but myself. I have that right, haven't I?" -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
