<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/157319-svnh]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/157319-svnh" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 11:53:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40147-but-more-than-that-no-unloving-words-were-ever-spoken</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 11:53:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40147-but-more-than-that-no-unloving-words-were-ever-spoken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But more than that, no unloving words were ever spoken, and everything was held up as another small piece of proof that it can be this way, it doesn't have to be that way; if there is no love in the world, we will make a new world, and we will give it heavy walls, and we will furnish it with soft red interiors, from the inside out, and give it a knocker that resonates like a diamond falling to a jeweler's felt so that we should never hear it.

Love me, because love doesn't exist, and I have tried everything that does." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45729-i-don-t-want-to-know-more-about-her-don-t-want</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 11:53:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Nadine Gordimer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45729-i-don-t-want-to-know-more-about-her-don-t-want]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't want to know more about her; don't want to know her weaknesses or calculate them. What I have is not for her; he gives me to understand she would not know what to do with it; it's not her fault. --One is married and there is nothing to be done.-- Yet he has said to me, I would marry you if I could, meaning: I want very much to marry you. I offended him a bit by not being moved. It's other things he's said that are the text I'm living by. I really do not know if I want any form of public statement, status, code; such as marriage. There's nothing more private and personal than the life of a mistress, is there? Outwardly, no one even knows we are responsible to each other....

'This is the creature that has never been'--he told me a line of poetry about that unicorn, translated from German. A mythical creature. Un paradis inventé. " -- Nadine Gordimer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45730-i-am-interested-in-language-because-it-wounds-or-seduces</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 11:53:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Roland Barthes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45730-i-am-interested-in-language-because-it-wounds-or-seduces]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am interested in language because it wounds or seduces me." -- Roland Barthes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45731-but-with-this-woman-it-is-as-if-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 11:53:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by J. M. Coetzee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45731-but-with-this-woman-it-is-as-if-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But with this woman it is as if there is no interior, only a surface across which I hunt back and forth seeking entry. Is this how her torturers felt hunting their secret, whatever they thought it was? For the first time I feel a dry pity for them: how natural a mistake to believe that you can burn or tear or hack your way into the secret body of the other! The girl lies in my bed, but there is no good reason why it should be a bed. I behave in some ways like a lover—I undress her, I bathe her, I stroke her, I sleep beside her—but I might equally well tie her to a chair and beat her, it would be no less intimate." -- J. M. Coetzee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5624-brod-s-life-was-a-slow-realization-that-the-world-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 11:53:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5624-brod-s-life-was-a-slow-realization-that-the-world-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Brod's life was a slow realization that the world was not for her, and that for whatever reason, she would never be happy and honest at the same time.  She felt as if she were brimming, always producing and hoarding more love inside her.  But there was no release...

So she had to satisfy herself with the idea of love--loving the loving of things whose existence she didn't care at all about.  Love itself became the object of her love.  She loved herself in love, she loved loving love, as love loves loving, and was able, in that way, to reconcile herself with a world that fell so short of what she would have hoped for.  It was not the world that was the great and saving lie, but her willingness to make it beautiful and fair, to live a once-removed life, in a world once-removed from the one in which everyone else seemed to exist." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119591-dear-daughter-i-won-t-try-to-call-my-feeling-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 11:53:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Katherine Dunn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119591-dear-daughter-i-won-t-try-to-call-my-feeling-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dear daughter, I won't try to call my feeling for Arty love. Call it focus. My focus on Art was an ailment, noncommunicable, and, even to me all these years later, incomprehensible. Now I despise myself. But even so I remember, in hot floods, the way he slept, still as death, with his face washed flat, stony as a carved tomb and exquisite. His weakness and his ravening bitter needs were terrible, and beautiful, and irresistible as an earthquake. He scalded or smothered anyone he needed, but his needing and the hurt that it caused me were the most life I ever had. Remember what a poor thing I have always been and forgive me.

He saw no use for you and you interfered with his use of me. I sent you away to please him, to prove my dedication to him, and to prevent him from killing you...

My job was to come back [from the convent] directly, with nothing leaking from beneath my dark glasses, to give Arty his rubdown and then paint him for the next show, nodding cheerfully all the while, never showing anything but attentive care for his muscular wonderfulness. Because he could have killed you. He could have cut off the money that schooled and fed you. He could have erased you so entirely that I never would have had those letters and report cards and photos, or your crayon pictures, or the chance to spy on you, and to love you secretly when everything else was gone." -- Katherine Dunn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119593-what-can-it-matter-to-me-that-i-succeed-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 11:53:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Samuel Beckett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119593-what-can-it-matter-to-me-that-i-succeed-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What can it matter to me, that I succeed or fail ? The undertaking is none of mine, if they want me to succeed I'll fail, and vice versa, so as not to be rid of my tormentors." -- Samuel Beckett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18729-in-the-sunset-of-dissolution-everything-is-illuminated-by-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 11:53:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18729-in-the-sunset-of-dissolution-everything-is-illuminated-by-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the sunset of dissolution, everything is illuminated by the aura of nostalgia, even the guillotine." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103873-what-are-your-ghosts-like-they-are-on-the-insides</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 11:44:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103873-what-are-your-ghosts-like-they-are-on-the-insides]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["(What are your ghosts like?)
(They are on the insides of the lids of my eyes.)
(This is also where my ghosts reside.)
(You have ghosts?)
(Of course I have ghosts.)
(But you are a child.)
(I am not a child.)
(But you have not known love.)
(These are my ghosts, the spaces amid love.)" -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202887-she-has-become-an-expert-at-confusing-what-is-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 20:50:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202887-she-has-become-an-expert-at-confusing-what-is-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She has become an expert at confusing &lt;i&gt;what is&lt;/i&gt; with &lt;i&gt;what was&lt;/i&gt; with &lt;i&gt;what should be&lt;/i&gt; with &lt;i&gt;what could be&lt;/i&gt;." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252945-you-are-the-only-one-who-has-understood-even-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 20:50:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252945-you-are-the-only-one-who-has-understood-even-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are the only one who has understood even a whisper of me, and I will tell you that I am the only person who has understood even a whisper of you." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202891-i-saw-herschel-and-he-saw-me-and-we-stood</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 20:55:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202891-i-saw-herschel-and-he-saw-me-and-we-stood]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I saw Herschel and he saw me and we stood next to each other because that is what friends do in the presence of evil or love." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226827-from-space-astronauts-can-see-people-making-love-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 20:55:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226827-from-space-astronauts-can-see-people-making-love-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From space, astronauts can see people making love as a tiny speck of light. Not light, exactly, but a glow that could be mistaken for light--a coital radiance that takes generations to pour like honey through the darkness to the astronaut's eyes.

In about one and a half centuries--after the lovers who made the glow will have long been laid permanently on their backs--metropolises will be seen from space. They will glow all year. Smaller cities will also be seen, but with great difficulty. Shtetls will be virtually impossible to spot. Individual couples, invisible.

The glow is born from the sum of thousands of loves: newlyweds and teenagers who spark like lighters out of butane, pairs of men who burn fast and bright, pairs of women who illuminate for hours with soft multiple glows, orgies like rock and flint toys sold at festivals, couples trying unsuccessfully to have children who burn their frustrated image on the continent like the bloom a bright light leaves on the eye after you turn away from it.

Some nights, some places are a little brighter. It's difficult to stare at New York City on Valentine's Day, or Dublin on St. Patrick's. The old walled city of Jerusalem lights up like a candle on each of Chanukah's eight nights...&lt;i&gt;We're here&lt;/i&gt;, the glow...will say in one and a half centuries. &lt;i&gt;We're here, and we're alive&lt;/i&gt;." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265339-i-used-to-think-that-humor-was-the-only-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 21:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265339-i-used-to-think-that-humor-was-the-only-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I used to think that humor was the only way to appreciate how wonderful and terrible the world is, to celebrate how big life is. But now I think the opposite. Humor is a way of shrinking from that wonderful and terrible world." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/471478-they-had-failed-to-understand-that-there-was-no-such</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 18:21:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Hans Fallada]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/471478-they-had-failed-to-understand-that-there-was-no-such]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They had failed to understand that there was no such thing as private life in wartime Germany. No amount of reticence could change the fact that every individual German belonged to the generality of Germans and must share in the general destiny of Germany, even as more and more bombs were falling on the just and unjust alike." -- Hans Fallada]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10722-i-love-you-as-certain-dark-things-are-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 09:42:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10722-i-love-you-as-certain-dark-things-are-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you as certain dark things are to be loved, 
in secret, between the shadow and the soul." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/543548-what-you-burnt-broke-and-tore-is-still-in-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:16:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/543548-what-you-burnt-broke-and-tore-is-still-in-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What you burnt, broke, and tore is still in my hands. I am the keeper of fragile things and I have kept of you what is indissoluble." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127631-she-was-a-genius-of-sadness-immersing-herself-in-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 17:52:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127631-she-was-a-genius-of-sadness-immersing-herself-in-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was a genius of sadness, immersing herself in it, separating its numerous strands, appreciating its subtle nuances. She was a prism through which sadness could be divided into its infinite spectrum." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81847-the-only-thing-more-painful-than-being-an-active-forgetter</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 17:52:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81847-the-only-thing-more-painful-than-being-an-active-forgetter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only thing more painful than being an active forgetter is to be an inert rememberer." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54041-let-s-face-it-we-re-undone-by-each-other-and-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 11:50:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Judith Butler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54041-let-s-face-it-we-re-undone-by-each-other-and-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let's face it. We're undone by each other. And if we're not, we're missing something. If this seems so clearly the case with grief, it is only because it was already the case with desire. One does not always stay intact. It may be that one wants to, or does, but it may also be that despite one's best efforts, one is undone, in the face of the other, by the touch, by the scent, by the feel, by the prospect of the touch, by the memory of the feel. And so when we speak about my sexuality or my gender, as we do (and as we must), we mean something complicated by it. Neither of these is precisely a possession, but both are to be understood as modes of being dispossessed, ways of being for another, or, indeed, by virtue of another." -- Judith Butler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167263-my-favourite-characters-are-people-who-think-they-re-normal-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 10:29:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by John Waters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167263-my-favourite-characters-are-people-who-think-they-re-normal-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My favourite characters are people who think they’re normal but they’re not. I live in Baltimore, and it’s full of people like that. I’ve also lived in New York, which is full of people who think they’re crazy, but they’re completely normal. I get my best material in Baltimore – you get dialogue that you just couldn’t imagine. I asked this guy in a bar what he did for a living and he said he traded deer meat for crack. I never realised that job even existed. You could make a whole movie about that person. And he was kind of cute too, if you could ignore his eyes rolling around his head. Although I did crack once, accidentally, and I thought: Oh my God, what, am I gonna rob my parents now? I prefer poppers – they’re legal in London, right? I used to do them on roller coasters. They’re illegal in Provincetown, which is the gay fishing village where I live in the summer. In the airport there are signs warning you to get rid of your poppers." -- John Waters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284631-life-is-nothing-if-you-re-not-obsessed</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 10:32:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by John Waters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284631-life-is-nothing-if-you-re-not-obsessed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is nothing if you're not obsessed." -- John Waters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43334-i-love-you-also-means-i-love-you-more-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 22:01:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43334-i-love-you-also-means-i-love-you-more-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you also means I love you more than anyone loves you, or has loved you, or will love you, and also, I love you in a way that no one loves you, or has loved you, or will love you, and also, I love you in a way that I love no one else, and never have loved anyone else, and never will love anyone else." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127614-he-awoke-each-morning-with-the-desire-to-do-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 22:02:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127614-he-awoke-each-morning-with-the-desire-to-do-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He awoke each morning with the desire to do right, to be a good and meaningful person, to be, as simple as it sounded and as impossible as it actually was, happy. And during the course of each day his heart would descend from his chest into his stomach. By early afternoon he was overcome by the feeling that nothing was right, or nothing was right for him, and by the desire to be alone. By evening he was fulfilled: alone in the magnitude of his grief, alone in his aimless guilt, alone even in his loneliness. &lt;i&gt;I am not sad,&lt;/i&gt; he would repeat to himself over and over, &lt;i&gt;I am not sad&lt;/i&gt;. As if he might one day convince himself. Or fool himself. Or convince others--the only thing worse than being sad is for others to know that you are sad. &lt;i&gt;I am not sad. I am not sad. &lt;/i&gt;Because his life had unlimited potential for happiness, insofar as it was an empty white room. He would fall asleep with his heart at the foot of his bed, like some domesticated animal that was no part of him at all. And each morning he would wake with it again in the cupboard of his rib cage, having become a little heavier, a little weaker, but still pumping. And by the midafternoon he was again overcome with the desire to be somewhere else, someone else, someone else somewhere else. &lt;i&gt;I am not sad.&lt;/i&gt;" -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33484-i-don-t-think-that-there-are-any-limits-to-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 22:04:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33484-i-don-t-think-that-there-are-any-limits-to-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't think that there are any limits to how excellent we could make life seem." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206781-while-it-is-always-possible-to-wake-a-person-who-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2013 11:49:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206781-while-it-is-always-possible-to-wake-a-person-who-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["While it is always possible to wake a person who's sleeping, no amount of noise will wake a person who is pretending to be asleep." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208548-if-nothing-matters-there-s-nothing-to-save</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2013 11:49:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208548-if-nothing-matters-there-s-nothing-to-save]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If nothing matters, there's nothing to save." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243365-perhaps-in-the-back-of-our-minds-we-already-understand</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2013 11:49:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243365-perhaps-in-the-back-of-our-minds-we-already-understand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps in the back of our minds we already understand, without all the science I've discussed, that something terribly wrong is happening. Our sustenance now comes from misery. We know that if someone offers to show us a film on how our meat is produced, it will be a horror film. We perhaps know more than we care to admit, keeping it down in the dark places of our memory-- disavowed. When we eat factory-farmed meat we live, literally, on tortured flesh. Increasingly, that tortured flesh is becoming our own." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205989-we-can-t-plead-ignorance-only-indifference-those-alive-today-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2013 11:50:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205989-we-can-t-plead-ignorance-only-indifference-those-alive-today-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can't plead ignorance, only indifference. Those alive today are the generations that came to know better. We have the burden and the opportunity of living in the moment when the critique of factory farming broke into the popular consciousness. We are the ones of whom it will be fairly asked, What did you do when you learned the truth about eating animals?" -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256680-if-we-are-not-given-the-option-to-live-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2013 11:50:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[svnh add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256680-if-we-are-not-given-the-option-to-live-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we are not given the option to live without violence, we are given the choice to center our meals around harvest or slaughter, husbandry or war. We have chosen slaughter. We have chosen war. That's the truest version of our story of eating animals.

Can we tell a new story?" -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
