<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/157420-sasha]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/157420-sasha" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 19:21:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48507-i-crave-your-mouth-your-voice-your-hair-silent-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 19:21:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48507-i-crave-your-mouth-your-voice-your-hair-silent-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I crave your mouth, your voice, your hair.
Silent and starving, I prowl through the streets. 
Bread does not nourish me, dawn disrupts me, all day 
I hunt for the liquid measure of your steps. 

I hunger for your sleek laugh, 
your hands the color of a savage harvest, 
hunger for the pale stones of your fingernails, 
I want to eat your skin like a whole almond. 

I want to eat the sunbeam flaring in your lovely body, 
the sovereign nose of your arrogant face, 
I want to eat the fleeting shade of your lashes, 

and I pace around hungry, sniffing the twilight, 
hunting for you, for your hot heart, 
Like a puma in the barrens of Quitratue." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10722-i-love-you-as-certain-dark-things-are-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 19:21:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10722-i-love-you-as-certain-dark-things-are-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you as certain dark things are to be loved, 
in secret, between the shadow and the soul." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7692-if-there-is-no-love-in-the-world-we-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 19:23:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7692-if-there-is-no-love-in-the-world-we-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there is no love in the world, we will make a new world, and we will give it walls, and we will furnish it with soft, red interiors, from the inside out, and give it a knocker that resonates like a diamond falling to a jeweller's felt so that we should never hear it. Love me, because love doesn't exist, and I have tried everything that does." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12018-love-is-the-ultimate-outlaw-it-just-won-t-adhere-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 19:25:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12018-love-is-the-ultimate-outlaw-it-just-won-t-adhere-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is the ultimate outlaw. It just won't adhere to any rules. The most any of us can do is to sign on as its accomplice. Instead of vowing to honor and obey, maybe we should swear to aid and abet. That would mean that security is out of the question. The words &quot;make&quot; and &quot;stay&quot; become inappropriate. My love for you has no strings attached. I love you for free." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12242-the-power-of-a-glance-has-been-so-much-abused</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 19:27:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Victor Hugo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12242-the-power-of-a-glance-has-been-so-much-abused]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The power of a glance has been so much abused in love stories, that it has come to be disbelieved in. Few people dare now to say that two beings have fallen in love because they have looked at each other. Yet it is in this way that love begins, and in this way only." -- Victor Hugo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/760256-words-are-the-oldest-information-storage-and-retrieval-system-ever</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2013 18:02:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Rick Moody]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/760256-words-are-the-oldest-information-storage-and-retrieval-system-ever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Words are the oldest information storage and retrieval system ever devised.  Words are probably older than the cave paintings in France, words have been here for tens of thousands of years longer than film, moving pictures, video, and digital video, and words will likely be here after those media too.  When the electromagnetic pulse comes in the wake of the nuclear blast?  Those computers and digital video cameras and videotape recorders that are not melted outright will be plastic and metal husks used to prop open doors.  Not so with the utterances of tongues.  Words will remain, and the highly complicated and idiosyncratic accounts assembled from them will provide us with the dark news about the blast.  The written word will remain, scribbled on collapsed highway overpasses, as a testament to love and rage, as evidence of the wanderers in the ruin." -- Rick Moody]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/894470-i-suppose-i-should-say-that-i-treasure-blasphemy-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2013 18:03:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Rick Moody]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/894470-i-suppose-i-should-say-that-i-treasure-blasphemy-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I suppose I should say that I treasure blasphemy, as a faith of the highest order." -- Rick Moody]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371743-many-waters-cannot-quench-love-neither-can-floods-drown-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 11:53:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371743-many-waters-cannot-quench-love-neither-can-floods-drown-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many waters cannot quench love, neither can floods drown it. What then kills love? Only this: Neglect. Not to see you when you stand before me. Not to think of you in the little things. Not to make the road wide for you, the table spread for you. To choose you out of habit not desire, to pass the flower seller without a thought. To leave the dishes unwashed, the bed unmade, to ignore you in the mornings, make use of you at night. To crave another while pecking your cheek. To say your name without hearing it, to assume it is mine to call." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
