<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/159633-ally-armistead]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/159633-ally-armistead" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 07:41:53 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346735-on-the-train-to-london-with-those-successfully-exposed-rolls</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 07:41:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ally add a quote by Robert Capa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346735-on-the-train-to-london-with-those-successfully-exposed-rolls]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the train to London, with those successfully exposed rolls in my bag, I hated myself and my profession. This sort of photography was only for undertakers, and I didn't like being one. If I was to share the funeral, I swore, I would have to share the procession." -- Robert Capa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148770-your-cold-mornings-are-filled-with-the-heartache-about-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 06:52:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ally add a quote by Paul Harding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148770-your-cold-mornings-are-filled-with-the-heartache-about-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your cold mornings are filled with the heartache about the fact that although we are not at ease in this world, it is all we have, that it is ours but that it is full of strife, so that all we can call our own is strife; but even that is better than nothing at all, isn't it? And as you split the frost-laced wood with numb hands, rejoice that your uncertainty is God's will and His grace toward you that that is beautiful, and a part of a greater certainty, as your own father always said in his sermons and to you at home.  And as the ax bites into  the wood, be comforted in the fact that the ache in your heart and the confusion in your soul means that you are still alive, still human, and still open to the beauty of the world, even though you have done nothing to deserve it. And when you resent the ache in your heart, remember: You will be dead and buried soon enough." -- Paul Harding]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/351980-during-the-air-war-of-1944-a-four-man-combat-crew</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 11:06:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ally add a quote by Sebastian Junger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/351980-during-the-air-war-of-1944-a-four-man-combat-crew]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["During the air war of 1944, a four-man combat crew on a B-17 bomber took a vow to never abandon one another no matter how desperate the situation. The aircraft was hit by flak during a mission and went into a terminal dive, and the pilot ordered everyone to bail out. The top turret gunner obeyed the order, but the ball turret gunner discovered that a piece of flak had jammed his turret and he could not get out. The other three men in his pact could have bailed out with the parachutes, but they stayed with him until the plan hit the ground and exploded. They all died." -- Sebastian Junger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/351981-the-cause-doesn-t-have-to-be-righteous-and-battle-doesn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 11:06:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ally add a quote by Sebastian Junger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/351981-the-cause-doesn-t-have-to-be-righteous-and-battle-doesn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The cause doesn't have to be righteous and battle doesn't have to be winnable; but over and over again throughout history, men have chosen to die in battle with their friends rather than to flee on their own and survive." -- Sebastian Junger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335599-the-army-might-screw-you-and-your-girlfriend-might-dump</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 11:07:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ally add a quote by Sebastian Junger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335599-the-army-might-screw-you-and-your-girlfriend-might-dump]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Army might screw you and your girlfriend might dump you and the enemy might kill you, but the shared commitment to safeguard one another’s lives is unnegotiable and only deepens with time. The willingness to die for another person is a form of love that even religions fail to inspire, and the experience of it changes a person profoundly." -- Sebastian Junger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108063-and-what-amazes-me-as-i-hit-the-motorway-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 14:28:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ally add a quote by Anne Enright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108063-and-what-amazes-me-as-i-hit-the-motorway-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And what amazes me as I hit the motorway is not the fact that everyone loses someone, but that everyone loves someone. It seems like such a massive waste of energy -- and we all do it, all the people beetling along between the white lines, merging, converging, overtaking. We each love someone, even though they will die. And we keep loving them, even when they are not there to love any more. And there is no logic or use to any of this, that I can see." -- Anne Enright]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
