<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/159917-jane-stubbs]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/159917-jane-stubbs" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 19:03:23 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/997-maera-lay-still-his-head-on-his-arms-his-face</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 19:03:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jane add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/997-maera-lay-still-his-head-on-his-arms-his-face]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maera lay still, his head on his arms, his face in the sand. He felt warm and sticky from the bleeding. Each time he felt the horn coming. Sometimes the bull only bumped him with his head. Once the horn went all the way through him and he felt it go into the sand. Some one had the bull by the tail. They were swearing at him and flopping the cape in his face. Then the bull was gone. Some men picked Maera up and started to run with him toward the barriers through the gate out the passageway around under the grandstand to the infirmary. They laid Maera down on the cot and one of the men went out for the doctor. The others stood around. The doctor came running from the coral where he had been sewing up picador horses. He had to stop and wash his hands. There was a great shouting going on in the grandstand overhead. Maera felt everything getting larger and larger and then smaller and smaller. Then it got larger and larger and larger and then smaller and smaller. Then everything commenced to run faster and faster as when they speed up a cinematograph film. Then he was dead." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/999-oh-jake-brett-said-we-could-have-had-such-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 19:08:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jane add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/999-oh-jake-brett-said-we-could-have-had-such-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh Jake,&quot; Brett said, &quot;We could have had such a damned good time together.&quot;
Ahead was a mounted policeman in khaki directing traffic. He raised his baton. The car slowed suddenly, pressing Brett against me.
Yes,&quot; I said. &quot;Isn't it pretty to think so?" -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1000-anyone-lived-in-a-pretty-how-town-with-up-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 19:10:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jane add a quote by E. E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1000-anyone-lived-in-a-pretty-how-town-with-up-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["anyone lived in a pretty how town
(with up so floating many bells down)
spring summer autumn winter
he sang his didn't he danced his did

Women and men(both little and small)
cared for anyone not at all
they sowed their isn't they reaped their same
sun moon stars rain

children guessed(but only a few
and down they forgot as up they grew
autumn winter spring summer)
that noone loved him more by more

when by now and tree by leaf
she laughed his joy she cried his grief
bird by snow and stir by still
anyone's any was all to her

someones married their everyones
laughed their cryings and did their dance
(sleep wake hope and then)they
said their nevers they slept their dream

stars rain sun moon
(and only the snow can begin to explain
how children are apt to forget to remember
with up so floating many bells down)

one day anyone died i guess
(and noone stooped to kiss his face)
busy folk buried them side by side
little by little and was by was

all by all and deep by deep
and more by more they dream their sleep
noone and anyone earth by april
wish by spirit and if by yes.

Women and men (both dong and ding)
summer autumn winter spring
reaped their sowing and went their came
sun moon stars rain" -- E. E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1002-nancy-waded-out-to-her-own-rocks-and-searched-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 19:17:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jane add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1002-nancy-waded-out-to-her-own-rocks-and-searched-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nancy waded out to her own rocks and searched her own pools and let that couple look after themselves. She crouched low down and touched the smooth rubber-like sea anemones, who were stuck like lumps of jelly to the side of the rock. Brooding, she changed the pool into the sea, and made the minnows into sharks and whales, and cast vast clouds over this tiny world by holding her hand against the sun, and so brought darkness and desolation, like God himself, to millions of ignorant and innocent creatures, and then took her hand away suddenly and let the sun stream down. Out on the pale criss-crossed sand, high-stepping, fringed, gauntleted, stalked some fantastic leviathan (she was still enlarging the pool), and slipped into the vast fissures of the mountain side. And then, letting her eyes slide imperceptibly above the pool and rest on that wavering line of sea and sky, on the tree trunks which the smoke of steamers made waver on the horizon, she became with all that power sweeping savagely in and inevitably withdrawing, hypnotised, and the two senses of that vastness and this tininess (the pool had diminished again) flowering within it made her feel that she was bound hand and foot and unable to move by the intensity of feelings which reduced her own body, her own life, and the lives of all the people in the world, for ever, to nothingness. So listening to the waves, crouching over the pool, she brooded." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12483-all-good-books-are-alike-in-that-they-are-truer</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2008 06:52:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jane add a quote by Ernest Hemingway ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12483-all-good-books-are-alike-in-that-they-are-truer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All good books are alike in that they are truer than if they had really happened and after you are finished reading one you will feel that all that happened to you and afterwards it all belongs to you: the good and the bad, the ecstasy, the remorse and sorrow, the people and the places and how the weather was. If you can get so that you can give that to people, then you are a writer." -- Ernest Hemingway ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5446-it-is-awfully-easy-to-be-hard-boiled-about-everything-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2008 06:53:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jane add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5446-it-is-awfully-easy-to-be-hard-boiled-about-everything-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is awfully easy to be hard-boiled about everything in the daytime, but at night it is another thing." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8206-do-i-contradict-myself-very-well-then-i-contradict-myself</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2008 07:28:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jane add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8206-do-i-contradict-myself-very-well-then-i-contradict-myself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do I contradict myself? Very well, then, I contradict myself; I am large -- I contain multitudes." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
