<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/160127-laura]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/160127-laura" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 20:51:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188308-there-is-neither-happiness-nor-misery-in-the-world-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 20:51:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188308-there-is-neither-happiness-nor-misery-in-the-world-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is neither happiness nor misery in the world; there is only the comparison of one state with another, nothing more. He who has felt the deepest grief is best able to experience supreme happiness." -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3867-for-what-do-we-live-but-to-make-sport-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 20:51:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3867-for-what-do-we-live-but-to-make-sport-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For what do we live, but to make sport for our neighbors, and laugh at them in our turn?" -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107836-human-nature-is-so-well-disposed-towards-those-who-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 20:51:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by jane austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107836-human-nature-is-so-well-disposed-towards-those-who-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human nature is so well disposed towards those who are in interesting situations, that a young person, who either marries or dies, is sure of being kindly spoken of." -- jane austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79936-i-ve-no-more-business-to-marry-edgar-linton-than-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 20:51:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79936-i-ve-no-more-business-to-marry-edgar-linton-than-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've no more business to marry Edgar Linton than I have to be in heaven and if the wicked man in there had not brought Heathcliff so low I shouldn't have thought of it. It would degrade me to marry Heathcliff now so he shall never know how I love him and that not because he's handsome Nelly but because he's more myself than I am. Whatever our souls are made of his and mine are the same and Linton's is as different as a moonbeam from lightning or frost from fire." -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188298-i-am-glad-you-are-no-relation-of-mine-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 20:50:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188298-i-am-glad-you-are-no-relation-of-mine-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am glad you are no relation of mine. I will never call you aunt again as long as I live. I will never come to visit you when I am grown up; and if any one asks me how I liked you, and how you treated me, I will say the very thought of you makes me sick, and that you treated me with miserable cruelty. . . . You think I have no feelings, and that I can do without one bit of love or kindness; but I cannot live so: and you have no pity. I shall remember how you thrust me back . . . into the red-room. . . . And that punishment you made me suffer because your wicked boy struck me—knocked me down for nothing. I will tell anybody who asks me questions this exact tale. ’Ere I had finished this reply, my soul began to expand, to exult, with the strangest sense of freedom, of triumph, I ever felt. It seemed as if an invisible bond had burst, and that I had struggled out into unhoped-for liberty. . . ." -- Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188300-shall-i-i-said-briefly-and-i-looked-at-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 20:50:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188300-shall-i-i-said-briefly-and-i-looked-at-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Shall I?” I said briefly; and I looked at his features, beautiful in their harmony, but strangely formidable in their still severity; at his brow, commanding, but not open; at his eyes, bright and deep and searching, but never soft; at his tall imposing figure; and fancied myself in idea his wife. Oh! it would never do! As his curate, his comrade, all would be right: I would cross oceans with him in that capacity; toil under Eastern suns, in Asian deserts with him in that office; admire and emulate his courage and devotion and vigour: accommodate quietly to his masterhood; smile undisturbed at his ineradicable ambition. . . . I should suffer often, no doubt, attached to him only in this capacity: my body would be under a rather stringent yoke, but my heart and mind would be free. I should still have my unblighted self to turn to: my natural unenslaved feelings with which to communicate in moments of loneliness. There would be recesses in my mind which would be only mine, to which he never came; and sentiments growing there, fresh and sheltered, which his austerity could never blight, nor his measured warrior-march trample down: but as his wife—at his side always, and always restrained, and always checked—forced to keep the fire of my nature continually low, to compel it to burn inwardly and never utter a cry, though the imprisoned flame consumed vital after vital—this would be unendurable." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23318-grief-turns-out-to-be-a-place-none-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 20:50:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23318-grief-turns-out-to-be-a-place-none-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Grief turns out to be a place none of us know until we reach it. We anticipate (we know) that someone close to us could die, but we do not look beyond the few days or weeks that immediately follow such an imagined death. We misconstrue the nature of even those few days or weeks. We might expect if the death is sudden to feel shock. We do not expect this shock to be obliterative, dislocating to both body and mind. We might expect that we will be prostrate, inconsolable, crazy with loss. We do not expect to be literally crazy, cool customers who believe their husband is about to return and need his shoes." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94420-until-the-day-when-god-shall-deign-to-reveal-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2009 21:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94420-until-the-day-when-god-shall-deign-to-reveal-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until the day when God shall deign to reveal the future to man, all human wisdom is summed up in these two words,-Wait and hope." -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127782-it-is-happy-for-you-that-you-possess-the-talent</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 20:50:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127782-it-is-happy-for-you-that-you-possess-the-talent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is happy for you that you possess the talent of flattering with delicacy. May I ask whether these pleasing attentions proceed from the impulse of the moment, or are they the result of previous study?" -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6041-indeed-i-am-very-sorry-to-be-right-in-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 20:50:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6041-indeed-i-am-very-sorry-to-be-right-in-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Indeed, I am very sorry to be right in this instance. I would much rather have been merry than wise." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381-to-die-would-be-an-awfully-big-adventure</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 20:50:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381-to-die-would-be-an-awfully-big-adventure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To die would be an awfully big adventure." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
