<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/160460-g-nter-voelker]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/160460-g-nter-voelker" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 17:37:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64329-we-re-all-going-to-die-all-of-us-what-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 17:37:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Günter add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64329-we-re-all-going-to-die-all-of-us-what-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're all going to die, all of us, what a circus! That alone should make us love each other but it doesn't. We are terrorized and flattened by trivialities, we are eaten up by nothing." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/528838-with-the-birth-of-akash-in-his-sudden-perfect-presence</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2012 00:36:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Günter add a quote by Jhumpa Lahiri]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/528838-with-the-birth-of-akash-in-his-sudden-perfect-presence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With the birth of Akash, in his sudden, perfect presence, Ruma had felt awe for the first time in her life. He still had the power to stagger her at times--simply the fact that he was breathing, that all his organs were in their proper places, that blood flowed quietly and effectively through his small, sturdy limbs. He was her flesh and blood, her mother had told her in the hospital the day Akash was born. Only the words her mother used were more literal, enriching the tired phrase with meaning: &quot;He is made from your meat and bone.&quot; It had caused Ruma to acknowledge the supernatural in everyday life. But death, too, had the power to awe, she knew this now-that a human being could be alive for years and years, thinking and breathing and eating, full of a million worries and feelings and thoughts, taking up space in the world, and then, in an instant, become absent, invisible." -- Jhumpa Lahiri]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
