<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/161569-christine-chapman]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/161569-christine-chapman" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 11:21:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176032-maybe-ian-doesn-t-come-from-london-at-all-but-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 11:21:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Alison Pace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176032-maybe-ian-doesn-t-come-from-london-at-all-but-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe Ian doesn't come from london at all, but from Idaho. And not the potato part of Idaho, but the crazy, inbred parents locking their children up in a cabin, away from schooling and vitamins, guarding 'em safe with a twelve-gauge shotgun, part of Idaho." -- Alison Pace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237472-i-have-been-to-the-world-s-end-and-back-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 11:31:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Kate Atkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237472-i-have-been-to-the-world-s-end-and-back-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have been to the world's end and back and now I know what I would put in my bottom drawer .I would put my sisters. " -- Kate Atkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 11:37:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May your coming year be filled with magic and dreams and good madness. I hope you read some fine books and kiss someone who thinks you're wonderful, and don't forget to make some art -- write or draw or build or sing or live as only you can. And I hope, somewhere in the next year, you surprise yourself." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123865-here-s-to-books-the-cheapest-vacation-you-can-buy</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 11:38:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Charlaine Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123865-here-s-to-books-the-cheapest-vacation-you-can-buy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here’s to books, the cheapest vacation you can buy." -- Charlaine Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28433-would-it-save-you-a-lot-of-time-if-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 11:39:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28433-would-it-save-you-a-lot-of-time-if-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Would it save you a lot of time if I just gave up and went mad now?" -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 11:40:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I say is, a town isn't a town without a bookstore. It may call itself a town, but unless it's got a bookstore it knows it's not fooling a soul." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15864-everyone-seems-to-have-a-clear-idea-of-how-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 11:42:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15864-everyone-seems-to-have-a-clear-idea-of-how-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone seems to have a clear idea of how other people should lead their lives, but none about his or her own." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3278-i-may-not-have-gone-where-i-intended-to-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 11:50:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by douglas adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3278-i-may-not-have-gone-where-i-intended-to-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I may not have gone where I intended to go, but I think I have ended up where I needed to be." -- douglas adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1-the-story-so-far-in-the-beginning-the-universe-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 11:50:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1-the-story-so-far-in-the-beginning-the-universe-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The story so far:
In the beginning the Universe was created.
This has made a lot of people very angry and been widely regarded as a bad move." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2397-there-is-a-theory-which-states-that-if-ever-anyone</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 11:51:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2397-there-is-a-theory-which-states-that-if-ever-anyone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a theory which states that if ever anyone discovers exactly what the Universe is for and why it is here, it will instantly disappear and be replaced by something even more bizarre and inexplicable. 
There is another theory which states that this has already happened." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 11:51:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81540-one-can-never-have-enough-socks-said-dumbledore-another-christmas</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 11:52:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81540-one-can-never-have-enough-socks-said-dumbledore-another-christmas]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One can never have enough socks,&quot; said Dumbledore. &quot;Another Christmas has come and gone and I didn't get a single pair. People will insist on giving me books." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59992-go-on-with-what-your-heart-tells-you-or-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 11:53:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Rick Riordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59992-go-on-with-what-your-heart-tells-you-or-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Go on with what your heart tells you, or you will lose all." -- Rick Riordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4708-i-think-it-s-perfectly-possible-to-explain-how-the-universe</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 11:58:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4708-i-think-it-s-perfectly-possible-to-explain-how-the-universe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think it's perfectly possible to explain how the universe came about without bringing God into it, but I don't know everything, and there may well be a God somewhere, hiding away. Actually, if he is keeping out of sight, it's because he's ashamed of his followers and all the cruelty and ignorance they're responsible for promoting in his name. If I were him, I'd want nothing to do with them." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290776-fire-is-catching-and-if-we-burn-you-burn-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 12:00:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290776-fire-is-catching-and-if-we-burn-you-burn-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fire is catching! And if we burn, you burn with us!" -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291217-it-takes-ten-times-as-long-to-put-yourself-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 12:08:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291217-it-takes-ten-times-as-long-to-put-yourself-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It takes ten times as long to put yourself back together as it does to fall apart." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290767-what-i-need-is-the-dandelion-in-the-spring-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 12:10:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290767-what-i-need-is-the-dandelion-in-the-spring-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I need is the dandelion in the spring. The bright yellow that means rebirth instead of destruction. The promise that life can go on, no matter how bad our losses. That it can be good again." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35497-after-nourishment-shelter-and-companionship-stories-are-the-thing-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 12:15:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35497-after-nourishment-shelter-and-companionship-stories-are-the-thing-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After nourishment, shelter and companionship, stories are the thing we need most in the world." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72605-your-eyes-show-the-strength-of-your-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 12:19:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Paulo Coehlo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72605-your-eyes-show-the-strength-of-your-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your eyes show the strength of your soul." -- Paulo Coehlo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53166-the-best-fantasy-is-written-in-the-language-of-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 12:23:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53166-the-best-fantasy-is-written-in-the-language-of-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best fantasy is written in the language of dreams. It is alive as dreams are alive, more real than real ... for a moment at least ... that long magic moment before we wake.

     Fantasy is silver and scarlet, indigo and azure, obsidian veined with gold and lapis lazuli. Reality is plywood and plastic, done up in mud brown and olive drab. Fantasy tastes of habaneros and honey, cinnamon and cloves, rare red meat and wines as sweet as summer. Reality is beans and tofu, and ashes at the end. Reality is the strip malls of Burbank, the smokestacks of Cleveland, a parking garage in Newark. Fantasy is the towers of Minas Tirith, the ancient stones of Gormenghast, the halls of Camelot. Fantasy flies on the wings of Icarus, reality on Southwest Airlines. Why do our dreams become so much smaller when they finally come true?

     We read fantasy to find the colors again, I think. To taste strong spices and hear the songs the sirens sang. There is something old and true in fantasy that speaks to something deep within us, to the child who dreamt that one day he would hunt the forests of the night, and feast beneath the hollow hills, and find a love to last forever somewhere south of Oz and north of Shangri-La.

     They can keep their heaven. When I die, I'd sooner go to middle Earth." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39828-i-ve-come-up-with-a-set-of-rules-that-describe</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 12:26:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39828-i-ve-come-up-with-a-set-of-rules-that-describe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've come up with a set of rules that describe our reactions to technologies:
1. Anything that is in the world when you’re born is normal and ordinary and is just a natural part of the way the world works.
2. Anything that's invented between when you’re fifteen and thirty-five is new and exciting and revolutionary and you can probably get a career in it.
3. Anything invented after you're thirty-five is against the natural order of things." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228647-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 12:28:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228647-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up. You build up all these defenses, you build up a whole suit of armor, so that nothing can hurt you, then one stupid person, no different from any other stupid person, wanders into your stupid life...You give them a piece of you. They didn't ask for it. They did something dumb one day, like kiss you or smile at you, and then your life isn't your own anymore. Love takes hostages. It gets inside you. It eats you out and leaves you crying in the darkness, so simple a phrase like 'maybe we should be just friends' turns into a glass splinter working its way into your heart. It hurts. Not just in the imagination. Not just in the mind. It's a soul-hurt, a real gets-inside-you-and-rips-you-apart pain. I hate love." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40546-any-fool-knows-men-and-women-think-differently-at-times</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 12:31:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Robert Jordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40546-any-fool-knows-men-and-women-think-differently-at-times]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any fool knows men and women think differently at times, but the biggest difference is this. Men forget, but never forgive; women forgive, but never forget." -- Robert Jordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201096-my-gran-had-always-told-me-that-a-woman--any-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 13:01:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Charlaine Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201096-my-gran-had-always-told-me-that-a-woman--any-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My gran had always told me that a woman--any woman worth her salt--could do whatever she had to." -- Charlaine Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6711-a-common-mistake-that-people-make-when-trying-to-design</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 07:29:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6711-a-common-mistake-that-people-make-when-trying-to-design]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A common mistake that people make when trying to design something completely foolproof is to underestimate the ingenuity of complete fools." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320152-oh-i-m-starting-to-cry-again-that-s-what-happens-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 19:15:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by L.J. Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320152-oh-i-m-starting-to-cry-again-that-s-what-happens-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh, I'm starting to cry again.  That's what happens when you think about life being fair.  And I can't explain why it isn't . . . I don't think it's something anybody knows." -- L.J. Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37408-in-this-hour-i-do-not-believe-that-any-darkness</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 18:25:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37408-in-this-hour-i-do-not-believe-that-any-darkness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In this hour, I do not believe that any darkness will endure." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133585-the-beginning-is-the-word-and-the-end-is-silence</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 18:31:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Kate Atkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133585-the-beginning-is-the-word-and-the-end-is-silence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The beginning is the word and the end is silence. And in between are all the stories." -- Kate Atkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 18:33:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a soul, Doctor. You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; a soul. You &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a body, temporarily." -- Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 18:33:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by William Nicholson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We read to know we're not alone." -- William Nicholson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
