<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/162084-sherwood-smith]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/162084-sherwood-smith" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2012 12:17:52 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2801-but-the-effect-of-her-being-on-those-around-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2012 12:17:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sherwood add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2801-but-the-effect-of-her-being-on-those-around-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the effect of her being on those around her was incalculably diffusive: for the growing good of the world is partly dependent on unhistoric acts; and that things are not so ill with you and me as they might have been, is half owing to the number who lived faithfully a hidden life, and rest in unvisited tombs." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1013344-the-aristocrat-the-devil-is-a-gentleman-and-asks-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 05:40:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sherwood add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1013344-the-aristocrat-the-devil-is-a-gentleman-and-asks-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Aristocrat

The Devil is a gentleman, and asks you down to stay
At his little place at What'sitsname (it isn't far away).
They say the sport is splendid; there is always something new,
And fairy scenes, and fearful feats that none but he can do;
He can shoot the feathered cherubs if they fly on the estate,
Or fish for Father Neptune with the mermaids for a bait;
He scaled amid the staggering stars that precipice, the sky,
And blew his trumpet above heaven, and got by mastery
The starry crown of God Himself, and shoved it on the shelf;
But the Devil is a gentleman, and doesn't brag himself.

O blind your eyes and break your heart and hack your hand away,
And lose your love and shave your head; but do not go to stay
At the little place in What'sitsname where folks are rich and clever;
The golden and the goodly house, where things grow worse for ever;
There are things you need not know of, though you live and die in vain,
There are souls more sick of pleasure than you are sick of pain;
There is a game of April Fool that's played behind its door,
Where the fool remains for ever and the April comes no more,
Where the splendour of the daylight grows drearier than the dark,
And life droops like a vulture that once was such a lark:
And that is the Blue Devil that once was the Blue Bird;
For the Devil is a gentleman, and doesn't keep his word." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
