<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/162024-christopher]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/162024-christopher" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 17:25:32 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221298-i-have-crossed-the-seas-i-have-left-cities-behind</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 17:25:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Jean-Paul Sartre]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221298-i-have-crossed-the-seas-i-have-left-cities-behind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have crossed the seas, I have left cities behind me,
and I have followed the source of rivers towards their
source or plunged into forests, always making for other
cities. I have had women, I have fought with men ; and
I could never turn back any more than a record can spin
in reverse. And all that was leading me where ?
To this very moment..." -- Jean-Paul Sartre]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174534-regardless-of-the-staggering-dimensions-of-the-world-about-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 17:26:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174534-regardless-of-the-staggering-dimensions-of-the-world-about-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Regardless of the staggering dimensions of the world about us, the density of our ignorance, the risks of catastrophes to come, and our individual weakness within the immense collectivity, the fact remains that we are absolutely free today if we choose to will our existence in its finiteness, a finiteness which is open on the infinite. And in fact, any man who has known real loves, real revolts, real desires, and real will knows quite well that he has no need of any outside guarantee to be sure of his goals; their certitude comes from his own drive." -- Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243455-sky-is-not-a-limit-for-me-because-i-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 17:27:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Temitope Owosela]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243455-sky-is-not-a-limit-for-me-because-i-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sky is not a limit for me; because I have no limit for myself in life. Because life is a world full of risk taking and possibilities. No matter how hard or easy life is; I will always find a way to enjoy myself; even in the mist of circumstances; because problems is a sense of adventure in sheep's clothing." -- Temitope Owosela]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184208-you-look-up-when-you-wish-to-be-exalted-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 17:27:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184208-you-look-up-when-you-wish-to-be-exalted-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You look up when you wish to be exalted. And I look down because I am exalted." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178471-some-care-is-needed-in-using-descartes-argument-i-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 17:28:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178471-some-care-is-needed-in-using-descartes-argument-i-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some care is needed in using Descartes' argument. &quot;I think, therefore I am&quot; says rather more than is strictly certain. It might seem as though we are quite sure of being the same person to-day as we were yesterday, and this is no doubt true in some sense. But the real Self is as hard to arrive at as the real table, and does not seem to have that absolute, convincing certainty that belongs to particular experiences." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/332019-you-say-i-and-you-are-proud-of-this-word</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 17:29:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/332019-you-say-i-and-you-are-proud-of-this-word]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You say 'I' and you are proud of this word. But greater than this- although you will not believe in it - is your body and its great intelligence, which does not say 'I' but performs 'I'." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111894-all-that-is-transitory-is-but-a-metaphor</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 17:29:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111894-all-that-is-transitory-is-but-a-metaphor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that is transitory is but a metaphor." -- Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/894567-i-had-travelled-from-spain-into-morocco-and-from-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 15:59:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Paul Bogard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/894567-i-had-travelled-from-spain-into-morocco-and-from-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had travelled from Spain into Morocco and from there south to the Atlas Mountains, at the edge of the Sahara Desert…one night, in a youth hostel that was more like a stable, I woke and walked out into a snowstorm. But it wasn’t the snow I was used to in Minnesota, or anywhere else I had been.  Standing bare chest to cool night, wearing flip-flops and shorts, I let a storm of stars swirl around me. I remember no light pollution, heck, I remember no lights. But I remember the light around me-the sense of being lit by starlight- and that I could see the ground to which the stars seemed to be floating down. I saw the sky that night in three dimensions- the sky had depth, some stars seemingly close and some much farther away, the Milky Way so well defined it had what astronomers call “structure”, that sense of its twisting depths. I remember stars from one horizon to another, making a night sky so plush it still seems like a dream.
It was a time in my life when I was every day experiencing something new.  I felt open to everything, as though I was made of clay, and the world was imprinting on me its breathtaking beauty (and terrible reality.) Standing nearly naked under that Moroccan sky, skin against the air, the dark, the stars, the night pressed its impression, and my lifelong connection was sealed." -- Paul Bogard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/709599-anything-which-is-just-born-which-has-just-come-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 16:03:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Ken Wilber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/709599-anything-which-is-just-born-which-has-just-come-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anything which is just born, which has just come into existence, has no past behind it. Birth, in other words, is the condition of having no past. And likewise, anything which now dies, which has just ceased to be, has no future left in front of it. Death is the condition of having no future. But we have already seen that this present moment has both no past and no future simultaneously. That is, birth and death are one in this present moment. This moment is just now being born—you can never find a past to this present moment, you can never find something before it. Yet also, this moment is just now dying — you can never find a future to this moment, never find something after it. This present, then, is a coincidence of opposites, a unity of birth and death, being and non-being, living and dying. As Ippen put it, &quot;Every moment is the last moment and every moment is a rebirth." -- Ken Wilber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/709597-because-we-demand-a-future-we-live-each-moment-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 16:03:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Ken Wilber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/709597-because-we-demand-a-future-we-live-each-moment-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because we demand a future, we live each moment in expectation and unfulfillment. We live each moment in passing. In just this way the real nunc stans, the timeless present, is reduced to the nunc fluens, the fleeting present, the passing present of a mere one or two seconds. We expect each moment to pass on to a future moment, for in this fashion we pretend to avoid death by always rushing toward an imagined future. We want to meet ourselves in the future. We don’t want just now—we want another now, and another, and another, tomorrow and tomorrow and tomorrow. And thus, paradoxically, our impoverished present is fleeting precisely because we demand that it end! We want it to end so that it can thereby pass on to yet another moment, a future moment, which will in turn live only to pass." -- Ken Wilber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1265154-hating-l-a-was-in-my-northern-california-dna-we-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 17:11:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Antonia Crane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1265154-hating-l-a-was-in-my-northern-california-dna-we-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hating L.A. was in my Northern California DNA. We even had a burl plaque that hung on our living room wall that read, “We Don’t Give a Damn How it’s Done in L.A." -- Antonia Crane]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
