<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/162095-bahare-shirzad]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/162095-bahare-shirzad" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 20:47:22 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 20:47:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bahare add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2058-there-is-no-friend-as-loyal-as-a-book</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 20:49:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bahare add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2058-there-is-no-friend-as-loyal-as-a-book]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no friend as loyal as a book." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 20:54:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bahare add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that no matter what happens, or how bad it seems today, life does go on, and it will be better tomorrow. I've learned that you can tell a lot about a person by the way he/she handles these three things: a rainy day, lost luggage, and tangled Christmas tree lights. I've learned that regardless of your relationship with your parents, you'll miss them when they're gone from your life. I've learned that making a &quot;living&quot; is not the same thing as making a &quot;life.&quot; I've learned that life sometimes gives you a second chance. I've learned that you shouldn't go through life with a catcher's mitt on both hands; you need to be able to throw something back. I've learned that whenever I decide something with an open heart, I usually make the right decision. I've learned that even when I have pains, I don't have to be one. I've learned that every day you should reach out and touch someone. People love a warm hug, or just a friendly pat on the back. I've learned that I still have a lot to learn. I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47188-life-should-not-be-a-journey-to-the-grave-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 11:34:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bahare add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47188-life-should-not-be-a-journey-to-the-grave-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life should not be a journey to the grave with the intention of arriving safely in a pretty and well preserved body, but rather to skid in broadside in a cloud of smoke, thoroughly used up, totally worn out, and loudly proclaiming &quot;Wow! What a Ride!" -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14485-but-i-don-t-want-to-go-among-mad-people-alice</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 11:34:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bahare add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14485-but-i-don-t-want-to-go-among-mad-people-alice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I don’t want to go among mad people,&quot; Alice remarked.
&quot;Oh, you can’t help that,&quot; said the Cat: &quot;we’re all mad here. I’m mad. You’re mad.&quot;
&quot;How do you know I’m mad?&quot; said Alice.
&quot;You must be,&quot; said the Cat, or you wouldn’t have come here." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223700-what-day-is-it-it-s-today-squeaked-piglet-my-favorite</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 21:08:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bahare add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223700-what-day-is-it-it-s-today-squeaked-piglet-my-favorite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What day is it?&quot;
It's today,&quot; squeaked Piglet.
My favorite day,&quot; said Pooh." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302101-how-do-you-spell-love---piglet-you-don-t-spell</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 21:10:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bahare add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302101-how-do-you-spell-love---piglet-you-don-t-spell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How do you spell 'love'?&quot; - Piglet
&quot;You don't spell it...you feel it.&quot; - Pooh" -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2424-would-you-tell-me-please-which-way-i-ought-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 21:23:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bahare add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2424-would-you-tell-me-please-which-way-i-ought-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Would you tell me, please, which way I ought to go from here?&quot;
&quot;That depends a good deal on where you want to get to.&quot;
&quot;I don't much care where –&quot;
&quot;Then it doesn't matter which way you go." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/576841-i-m-always-telling-myself-i-don-t-have-many-feelings-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 00:25:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bahare add a quote by Herta Müller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/576841-i-m-always-telling-myself-i-don-t-have-many-feelings-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm always telling myself I don't have many feelings. Even when something does affect me I'm only moderately moved. I almost never cry. It's not that I'm stronger than the ones with teary eyes, I'm weaker. They have courage. When all you are is skin and bones, feelings are a brave thing. I'm more of a coward. The difference is minimal though, I just use my strength not to cry. When I do allow myself a feeling, I take the part that hurts and bandage it up with a story that doesn't cry, that doesn't dwell on homesickness." -- Herta Müller]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
