<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/162759-margaret]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/162759-margaret" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 14:50:52 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9770-i-cannot-live-without-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 14:50:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9770-i-cannot-live-without-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot live without books." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214541-there-is-absolutely-no-such-thing-as-reading-but-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 14:52:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Charles Lamb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214541-there-is-absolutely-no-such-thing-as-reading-but-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is absolutely no such thing as reading but by a candle. We have tried the affectation of a book at noon-day in gardens, and in sultry arbours, but it was labor thrown away. Those gay motes in the beam come about you, hovering and teasing, like so many coquets, that will have you all to their self, and are jealous of your abstractions. By the midnight taper, the writers digests his meditations. By the same light we must approach to their perusal, if we would catch the flame, the odour." -- Charles Lamb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51160-to-be-a-book-collector-is-to-combine-the-worst-characteristics</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 15:57:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Robertson Davies]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51160-to-be-a-book-collector-is-to-combine-the-worst-characteristics]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be a book-collector is to combine the worst characteristics of a dope fiend with those of a miser." -- Robertson Davies]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214956-i-had-written-short-stories-that-were-thought-worthy-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 20:40:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214956-i-had-written-short-stories-that-were-thought-worthy-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had written short stories that were thought worthy of preservation! Was it the same insignificant I that I had always known? Any one walking along the streets might go into any bookshop, and say: 'Please give me Edith Wharton's book'; and the clerk, without bursting into incredulous laughter, would produce it, and be paid for it, and the purchaser would walk home with it and read it, and talk of it, and pass it on to other people to read!" -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90740-i-am-satisfied-that-if-a-book-is-a-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 20:40:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Anne Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90740-i-am-satisfied-that-if-a-book-is-a-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am satisfied that if a book is a good one, it is so whatever the sex of the author may be. All novels are or should be written for both men and women to read, and I am at a loss to conceive how a man should permit himself to write anything that would be really disgraceful to a woman, or why a woman should be censured for writing anything that would be proper and becoming for a man." -- Anne Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257363-so-this-is-supposed-to-be-about-the-how-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 16:45:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257363-so-this-is-supposed-to-be-about-the-how-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So this is supposed to be about the how, and when, and why, and what of reading -- about the way that, when reading is going well, one book leads to another and to another, a paper trail of theme and meaning; and how, when it's going badly, when books don't stick or take, when your mood and the mood of the book are fighting like cats, you'd rather do anything but attempt the next paragraph, or reread the last one for the tenth time." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266855-a-fine-gentleman-like-that-they-said-had-no-need</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 20:40:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266855-a-fine-gentleman-like-that-they-said-had-no-need]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A fine gentleman like that, they said, had no need of books. Let him leave books, they said, to the palsied or the dying.  But worse was to come.  For once the disease of reading has laid hold upon the system it weakens it so that it falls an easy prey to that other scourge which dwells in the ink pot and festers in the quill.  The wretch takes to writing." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55235-look-said-janet-irritated-if-the-thing-you-liked-best</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 22:05:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Pamela Dean]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55235-look-said-janet-irritated-if-the-thing-you-liked-best]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look,&quot; said Janet, irritated, &quot;if the thing you liked best to do in the world was read, and somebody offered to pay you room and board and give you a liberal arts degree if you would just read for four years, wouldn't you do it?" -- Pamela Dean]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338740-if-you-love-books-enough-books-will-love-you-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2011 18:16:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Jo Walton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338740-if-you-love-books-enough-books-will-love-you-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you love books enough, books will love you back." -- Jo Walton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36027-it-is-in-vain-to-say-human-beings-ought-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 14:12:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36027-it-is-in-vain-to-say-human-beings-ought-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is in vain to say human beings ought to be satisfied with tranquillity: they must have action; and they will make it if they cannot find it. Millions are condemned to a stiller doom than mine, and millions are in silent revolt against their lot. Nobody knows how many rebellions besides political rebellions ferment in the masses of life which people earth. Women are supposed to be very calm generally: but women feel just as men feel; they need exercise for their faculties, and a field for their efforts, as much as their brothers do; they suffer from too rigid a restraint, to absolute a stagnation, precisely as men would suffer; and it is narrow-minded in their more privileged fellow-creatures to say that they ought to confine themselves to making puddings and knitting stockings, to playing on the piano and embroidering bags. It is thoughtless to condemn them, or laugh at them, if they seek to do more or learn more than custom has pronounced necessary for their sex." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442990-only-a-person-who-is-congenitally-self-centered-has-the-effrontery</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 19:35:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442990-only-a-person-who-is-congenitally-self-centered-has-the-effrontery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only a person who is congenitally self-centered has the effrontery and the stamina to write essays." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476148-so----i-confess-i-have-been-a-rake-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 16:20:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Robertson Davies]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476148-so----i-confess-i-have-been-a-rake-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So -- I confess I have been a rake at reading. I have read those things which I ought not to have read, and I have not read those things which I ought to have read, and there is no health in me -- if by health you mean an inclusive and coherent knowledge of any body of great literature. I can only protest, like all rakes in their shameful senescence, that I have had a good time." -- Robertson Davies]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
