<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/162797-stacy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/162797-stacy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2010 02:49:59 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279616-when-people-dis-fantasy-mainstream-readers-and-sf-readers-alike-they-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2010 02:49:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by China Miéville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279616-when-people-dis-fantasy-mainstream-readers-and-sf-readers-alike-they-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When people dis fantasy—mainstream readers and SF readers alike—they are almost always talking about one sub-genre of fantastic literature. They are talking about [author:Tolkien|656983], and Tolkien's innumerable heirs. Call it 'epic', or 'high', or 'genre' fantasy, this is what fantasy has come to mean. Which is misleading as well as unfortunate.

Tolkien is the wen on the arse of fantasy literature. His oeuvre is massive and contagious—you can't ignore it, so don't even try. The best you can do is consciously try to lance the boil. And there's a lot to dislike—his cod-Wagnerian pomposity, his boys-own-adventure glorying in war, his small-minded and reactionary love for hierarchical status-quos, his belief in absolute morality that blurs moral and political complexity. Tolkien's clichés—elves 'n' dwarfs 'n' magic rings—have spread like viruses. He wrote that the function of fantasy was 'consolation', thereby making it an article of policy that a fantasy writer should mollycoddle the reader.

That is a revolting idea, and one, thankfully, that plenty of fantasists have ignored. From the Surrealists through the pulps—via [author:Mervyn Peake|22018] and [author:Mikhael Bulgakov|3873] and [author:Stefan Grabiński|285729] and [author:Bruno Schulz|142899] and [author:Michael Moorcock|16939] and [author:M. John Harrison|10765] and I could go on—the best writers have used the fantastic aesthetic precisely to challenge, to alienate, to subvert and undermine expectations.

Of course I'm not saying that any fan of Tolkien is no friend of mine—that would cut my social circle considerably. Nor would I claim that it's impossible to write a good fantasy book with elves and dwarfs in it—Michael Swanwick's superb &lt;i&gt;[book:Iron Dragon's Daughter|25781]&lt;/i&gt; gives the lie to that. But given that the pleasure of fantasy is supposed to be in its limitless creativity, why not try to come up with some different themes, as well as unconventional monsters? Why not use fantasy to challenge social and aesthetic lies?

Thankfully, the alternative tradition of fantasy has never died. And it's getting stronger. [author:Chris Wooding|81096], [author:Michael Swanwick|14454], [author:Mary Gentle|58654], [author:Paul di Filippo|162927], [author:Jeff VanderMeer|33919], and many others, are all producing works based on fantasy's radicalism. Where traditional fantasy has been rural and bucolic, this is often urban, and frequently brutal. Characters are more than cardboard cutouts, and they're not defined by race or sex. Things are gritty and tricky, just as in real life. This is fantasy not as comfort-food, but as challenge.

The critic Gabe Chouinard has said that we're entering a new period, a renaissance in the creative radicalism of fantasy that hasn't been seen since the New Wave of the sixties and seventies, and in echo of which he has christened the Next Wave. I don't know if he's right, but I'm excited. This is a radical literature. It's the literature we most deserve." -- China Miéville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119749-nature-is-not-a-place-to-visit-it-is-home</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 08:29:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Gary Snyder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119749-nature-is-not-a-place-to-visit-it-is-home]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nature is not a place to visit. It is home." -- Gary Snyder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283050-but-rhett-you-mustn-t-bring-me-anything-else-so-expensive</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 04:47:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283050-but-rhett-you-mustn-t-bring-me-anything-else-so-expensive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But Rhett, you mustn't bring me anything else so expensive. It's awfully kind of you, but I really couldn't accept anything else.&quot;
&quot;Indeed? Well, I shall bring you presents so long as it pleases me and so long as I see things that will enhance your charms. I shall bring you dark-green watered silk for a frock to match the bonnet. And I warn you that I am not kind. I am tempting you with bonnets and bangles and leading you into a pit. Always remember I never do anything without reason and I never give anything without expecting something in return. I always get paid." -- Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156046-seventeen-eh-said-hagrid-as-he-accepted-a-bucket-sized-glass</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 04:11:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156046-seventeen-eh-said-hagrid-as-he-accepted-a-bucket-sized-glass]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Seventeen, eh!&quot; said Hagrid as he accepted a bucket-sized glass of wine from Fred.
&quot;Six years to the day we met, Harry, d’yeh remember it?&quot;
&quot;Vaguely,&quot; said Harry, grinning up at him. &quot;Didn’t you smash down the front door, give Dudley a pig’s tail, and tell me I was a wizard?&quot;
&quot;I forge’ the details,&quot; Hagrid chortled." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11631-well-behaved-women-seldom-make-history</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 03:26:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Laurel Thatcher Ulrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11631-well-behaved-women-seldom-make-history]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well-behaved women seldom make history." -- Laurel Thatcher Ulrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/888526-all-these-years-there-had-been-a-tupperware-container-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 12:56:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Liane Moriarty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/888526-all-these-years-there-had-been-a-tupperware-container-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All these years there had been a Tupperware container of bad language in her head, and now she opened it and all those crisp, crunchy words were fresh and lovely, ready to be used." -- Liane Moriarty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/992122-none-of-us-ever-know-all-the-possible-courses-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 12:56:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Liane Moriarty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/992122-none-of-us-ever-know-all-the-possible-courses-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["None of us ever know all the possible courses our lives could have, and maybe should have taken." -- Liane Moriarty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004683-it-wasn-t-logical-but-the-better-you-knew-someone-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 12:57:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Liane Moriarty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004683-it-wasn-t-logical-but-the-better-you-knew-someone-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It wasn’t logical, but the better you knew someone, the more blurry they became. The accumulation of facts made them disappear. It was more interesting wondering if someone did or didn’t like country music than knowing one way or the other." -- Liane Moriarty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/888407-do-you-think-you-were-locked-in-a-cupboard-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 12:57:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by liane moriarty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/888407-do-you-think-you-were-locked-in-a-cupboard-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you think you were locked in a cupboard as a child?” Cecilia had asked him once (she wouldn’t have put it past his mother), but he said he was pretty sure he wasn’t." -- liane moriarty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1036565-when-you-were-young-you-talked-about-falling-in-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 12:57:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Liane Moriarty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1036565-when-you-were-young-you-talked-about-falling-in-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you were young you talked about ‘falling in love’ with such amusing gravity, as if it were an actual recordable event, when what was it really? Chemicals. Hormones. A trick of the mind." -- Liane Moriarty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227218-some-people-are-easier-to-love-when-you-don-t-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 13:09:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Irvine Welsh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227218-some-people-are-easier-to-love-when-you-don-t-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people are easier to love when you don't have to be around them." -- Irvine Welsh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629543-now-there-is-apparently-a-causal-link-between-heroin-addiction</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 13:10:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Irvine Welsh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629543-now-there-is-apparently-a-causal-link-between-heroin-addiction]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now there is apparently a causal link between heroin addiction and vegetarianism." -- Irvine Welsh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113041-when-the-sky-is-as-grey-as-this---impeccably</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 13:12:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113041-when-the-sky-is-as-grey-as-this---impeccably]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["when the sky is as grey as this - impeccably grey, a denial, really of the very concept of colour - and the stooped millions lift their heads, it's hard to tell the air from the impurities in our human eyes, as if the sinking climbing paisley curlicues of grit were part of the element itself, rain, spores, tears, film, dirt. Perhaps, at such moments, the sky is no more then the sum of the dirt that lives in our human eyes." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/612923-oh-man-sometimes-i-wake-up-feel-like-a-cat</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 13:13:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacy add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/612923-oh-man-sometimes-i-wake-up-feel-like-a-cat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh man sometimes I wake up feel like a cat runover.
Are you familiar with the stoical aspects of hard drinking, of heavy drinking? Oh it's heavy. Oh it's hard. It isn't easy. Jesus, I never meant me any harm. All I wanted was a good time." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
