<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/165682-marcelo]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/165682-marcelo" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2010 05:25:59 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32030-i-detest-the-idea-that-love-between-two-persons-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2010 05:25:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcelo add a quote by Rainer Werner Fassbinder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32030-i-detest-the-idea-that-love-between-two-persons-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I detest the idea that love between two persons can lead to salvation.  All my life I have fought against this oppressive type of relationship.  Instead, I believe in searching for a kind of love that somehow involves all of humanity." -- Rainer Werner Fassbinder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128689-until-one-is-committed-there-is-hesitancy-the-chance-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 16:19:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcelo add a quote by William Hutchison Murray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128689-until-one-is-committed-there-is-hesitancy-the-chance-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until one is committed, there is hesitancy, the chance to draw back,  always ineffectiveness.  Concerning all acts of initiative (and creation), there is one elementary truth that ignorance of which kills countless ideas and splendid plans: that the moment one definitely commits oneself, then Providence moves too. All sorts of things occur to help one that would never otherwise have occurred. A whole stream of events issues from the decision, raising in one's favor all manner of unforeseen incidents and meetings and material assistance, which no man could have dreamed would have come his way. Whatever you can do, or dream you can do, begin it. Boldness has genius, power, and magic in it. Begin it now." -- William Hutchison Murray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29007-every-day-think-as-you-wake-up-today-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 03:56:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcelo add a quote by The Dalai Lama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29007-every-day-think-as-you-wake-up-today-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every day, think as you wake up, today I am fortunate to be alive, I have a precious human life, I am not going to waste it. I am going to use all my energies to develop myself, to expand my heart out to others; to achieve enlightenment for the benefit of all beings. I am going to have kind thoughts towards others, I am not going to get angry or think badly about others. I am going to benefit others as much as I can." -- The Dalai Lama]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
