<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/166302-mrlunch]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/166302-mrlunch" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 08:21:25 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295725-bunny-sue-was-nineteen-she-had-honey-bobbed-hair-and-candid</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 08:21:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mrlunch add a quote by Frederick Exley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295725-bunny-sue-was-nineteen-she-had-honey-bobbed-hair-and-candid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bunny Sue was nineteen. She had honey-bobbed hair and candid, near-insolent green eyes. She had a snub, delightful nose, a cool, regal, and tapering neck, a fine, intelligent mouth that covered teeth so startling they might have been cleansed by sun gods. Without any makeup save lipstick, her complexion was as milk flecked with butter, the odor she cast as wholesome as bread. On my first breathless vision of her, I wanted to bury my teeth, Dracula-like, into her flanks, knowing that she would bleed pure butterscotch." -- Frederick Exley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117407-people-like-it-when-you-tell-them-things-in-suitable</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 10:02:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mrlunch add a quote by Per Petterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117407-people-like-it-when-you-tell-them-things-in-suitable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People like it when you tell them things, in suitable portions, in a modest, intimate tone, and they think they know you, but they do not, they know _about_ you, for what they are let in on are facts, not feelings, not what your opinion is about anything at all, not how what has happened to you and how all the decisions you have made have turned you into who you are. What they do is they fill in with their own feelings and opinions and assumptions, and they compose a new life which has precious little to do with yours, and that lets you off the hook. No-one can touch you unless you yourself want them to." -- Per Petterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/688880-valetta-he-said-thinking-she-still-looked-good-then-abandoning</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 09:04:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mrlunch add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/688880-valetta-he-said-thinking-she-still-looked-good-then-abandoning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Valetta,&quot; he said, thinking she still looked good, then abandoning his Spidey sense long enough to let her take him in her arms, the skin of her bare shoulder in a halter top cool against his shoulder, the lady most definitely giving off that heavy 1978 Spencer's smell of love candles and sandlewood incense but, laid over top of it, the stink of cigarette, the instant-potatoes smell you might find in the interior of a beat-to-shit Toronado. &quot;Damn." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
