<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/166576-jillrock]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/166576-jillrock" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 10:54:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 10:54:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JillRock add a quote by Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He's like a drug for you, Bella." -- Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37150-there-are-random-moments---tossing-a-salad-coming-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 11:01:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JillRock add a quote by Elizabeth Berg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37150-there-are-random-moments---tossing-a-salad-coming-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are random moments - tossing a salad, coming up the driveway to the house, ironing the seams flat on a quilt square, standing at the kitchen window and looking out at the delphiniums, hearing a burst of laughter from one of my children's rooms - when I feel a wavelike rush of joy. This is my true religion: arbitrary moments of of nearly painful happiness for a life I feel privileged to lead." -- Elizabeth Berg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64972-well-most-women-are-full-to-the-brim-that-s-all-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 11:01:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JillRock add a quote by Elizabeth Berg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64972-well-most-women-are-full-to-the-brim-that-s-all-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, most women are full to the brim, that's all...We are, most of us, ready to explode, especially when our children are small and we are so weary with the demands for love and attention and the kind of service that makes you feel you should be wearing a uniform with &quot;Mommy&quot; embroidered over the left breast, over the heart...If a stranger had come up to me and said, &quot;Do you want to talk about it?  I have time to listen,&quot; I think I might have burst into tears at the relief of it." -- Elizabeth Berg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/451559-i-wasn-t-sure-lorraine-and-others-like-her-ones-who-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 17:49:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JillRock add a quote by Elizabeth Berg, The Year of Pleasures]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/451559-i-wasn-t-sure-lorraine-and-others-like-her-ones-who-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wasn't sure Lorraine and others like her-ones who were so despairing of marriage, ones who were so sure their expectations could never be met-understood that it was these small moments of caretaking that meant the most, that forged the real relationship. The way one pulled the blanket over the sleeping other, the way one prepared a snack for oneself, but made enough to share. Such moments made for the team of two, which made for one's sword and shield." -- Elizabeth Berg, The Year of Pleasures]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146237-i-hadn-t-realized-how-much-i-d-been-needing-to-meet</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 18:03:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JillRock add a quote by Elizabeth Berg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146237-i-hadn-t-realized-how-much-i-d-been-needing-to-meet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hadn't realized how much I'd been needing to meet someone I might be able to say everything to." -- Elizabeth Berg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77634-i-always-think-incipent-miracles-surround-us-waiting-only-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 18:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JillRock add a quote by Elizabeth Berg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77634-i-always-think-incipent-miracles-surround-us-waiting-only-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I always think incipent miracles surround us, waiting only to see if our faith is strong enough. We won't have to understand it; it will just work, like a beating heart, like love. Really, no matter how frightened and discouraged I may become about the future, I look forward to it. In spite of everything I see all around me every day, I have a shaky assurance that everything will turn out fine. I don't think I'm the only one. Why else would the phrase &quot;everything's all right&quot; ease a deep and troubled place in so many of us? We just don't know, we never know so much, yet we have such faith. We hold our hands over our hurts and lean forward, full of yearning and forgiveness. It is how we keep on, this kind of hope." -- Elizabeth Berg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/345523-but-it-seemed-to-me-that-this-was-the-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 18:04:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JillRock add a quote by Elizabeth Berg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/345523-but-it-seemed-to-me-that-this-was-the-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But it seemed to me that this was the way we all lived: full to the brim with gratitude and joy one day, wrecked on the rocks the next. Finding the balance between the two was the art and the salvation." -- Elizabeth Berg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16962-sometimes-when-you-pick-up-your-child-you-can-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 18:08:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JillRock add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16962-sometimes-when-you-pick-up-your-child-you-can-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes when you pick up your child you can feel the map of your own bones beneath your hands, or smell the scent of your skin in the nape of his neck. This is the most extraordinary thing about motherhood - finding a piece of yourself separate and apart that all the same you could not live without." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64971-through-the-blur-i-wondered-if-i-was-alone-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 18:08:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JillRock add a quote by Debra Ginsberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64971-through-the-blur-i-wondered-if-i-was-alone-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Through the blur, I wondered if I was alone or if other parents felt the same way I did - that everything involving our children was painful in some way.  The emotions, whether they were joy, sorrow, love or pride, were so deep and sharp that in the end they left you raw, exposed and yes, in pain.  The human heart was not designed to beat outside the human body and yet, each child represented just that - a parent's heart bared, beating forever outside its chest." -- Debra Ginsberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157717-it-s-come-at-last-she-thought-the-time-when-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 18:09:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JillRock add a quote by Betty Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157717-it-s-come-at-last-she-thought-the-time-when-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's come at last&quot;, she thought, &quot;the time when you can no longer stand between your children and heartache." -- Betty Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134447-the-great-motherhood-friendships-are-the-ones-in-which-two</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 18:10:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JillRock add a quote by Anna Quindlen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134447-the-great-motherhood-friendships-are-the-ones-in-which-two]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The great motherhood friendships are the ones in which two women can admit [how difficult mothering is] quietly to each other, over cups of tea at a table sticky with spilled apple juice and littered with markers without tops." -- Anna Quindlen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38303-supermom-wasn-t-a-bad-job-description-the-pay-was-lousy</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 18:11:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JillRock add a quote by Roxanne Henke ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38303-supermom-wasn-t-a-bad-job-description-the-pay-was-lousy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Supermom wasn't a bad job description.  The pay was lousy if you were talking about real money.  But the payoff was priceless in so many other ways." -- Roxanne Henke ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401386-motherhood-is-a-choice-you-make-everyday-to-put-someone</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 18:12:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[JillRock add a quote by Donna Ball]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401386-motherhood-is-a-choice-you-make-everyday-to-put-someone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Motherhood is a choice you make everyday, to put someone else's happiness and well-being ahead of your own, to teach the hard lessons, to do the right thing even when you're not sure what the right thing is...and to forgive yourself, over and over again, for doing everything wrong." -- Donna Ball]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
