<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/166535-john]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/166535-john" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 12:39:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/692075-if-you-could-figure-out-how-to-live-with-family</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 12:39:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ben Fountain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/692075-if-you-could-figure-out-how-to-live-with-family]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you could figure out how to live with family then you'd gone a long way toward finding your peace." -- Ben Fountain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/691641-without-ever-exactly-putting-his-mind-to-it-he-s-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 12:40:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ben Fountain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/691641-without-ever-exactly-putting-his-mind-to-it-he-s-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without ever exactly putting his mind to it, he's come to believe that loss is the standard trajectory.  Something new appears in the world-a baby, say, or a car or a house, or an individual shows some special talent-with luck and huge expenditures of soul and effort you might keep the project stoked for a while, but eventually, ultimately, its going down.  This is a truth so brutally self-evident that he can't fathom why it's not more widely percieved, hence his contempt for the usual public shock and outrage when a particular situation goes to hell.  The war is fucked?  Well, duh.  Nine-eleven? Slow train coming.  They hate our freedoms? Yo, they hate our actual guts!  Billy suspects his fellow Americans secretly know better, but something in the land is stuck on teenage drama, on extravagant theatrics of ravaged innocence and soothing mud wallows of self-justifying pity." -- Ben Fountain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/688852-not-that-she-means-anything-by-it-he-knows-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 12:41:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ben Fountain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/688852-not-that-she-means-anything-by-it-he-knows-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not that she means anything by it, he knows. This is simply her lifelong habit of moderation at work, her need to tamp everything down to the routine, the modest, the tepid everyday. He understands the whole concept of boundaries, but there’s a point where this mania for normalizing turns toxic." -- Ben Fountain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777928-he-wonders-by-what-process-virtually-any-discussion-about-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 12:43:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ben Fountain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777928-he-wonders-by-what-process-virtually-any-discussion-about-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...he wonders by what process virtually any discussion about the war seems to profane these ultimate matters of life and death. As if to talk of such things properly we need a mode of speech near the equal of prayer, otherwise just shut, shut your yap and sit on it, silence being truer to the experience than the star-spangled spasm, the bittersweet sob, the redeeming hug, or whatever this fucking closure is that everybody's always talking about. They want it to be easy and it's just not going to be." -- Ben Fountain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/636309-outside-in-the-barnlot-he-looked-up-and-the-pale</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 12:44:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by William Gay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/636309-outside-in-the-barnlot-he-looked-up-and-the-pale]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Outside in the barnlot he looked up and the pale moon was directly over him and all-encompassing. It appeared to be lowering itself onto the earth and he could make out mountains and ranges of hills and hollows and dark shadowed areas of mystery he judged to be timber and he wondered what manner of beast thrived there and what their lives were like and the need to be there twisted in his heart like an old pain that will not dissipate." -- William Gay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403228-how-can-you-come-to-understand-your-life-when-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 12:46:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Dan Chaon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403228-how-can-you-come-to-understand-your-life-when-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How can you come to understand your life when even the beginning is so complicated: a single cell imprinted with the color of your eyes and the shape of your face the pattern on your palm and the moods that will shadow you through your life. How can you be alive when every choice you make breaks the world into a thousand filaments each careless step branching into long tributaries of alternate lives shuddering outward and outward like sheet lightning." -- Dan Chaon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/655931-because-they-do-burn-leaves-here-the-older-folks-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 12:48:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Megan Abbott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/655931-because-they-do-burn-leaves-here-the-older-folks-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because they do burn leaves here, the older folks do, and I remember now that I love it and always have. The way fall feels at night because of it, because of the crackling sound and walking around the sidewalks, like when you’re a kid, and kicking those soft piles, and seeing smoke from backyards and Mr. Kilstrap standing over the metal drum with the holes in the top, the sparking embers at his feet." -- Megan Abbott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/709680-the-sooner-that-layla-understands-that-we-are-nothing-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 08:14:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Claire Vaye Watkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/709680-the-sooner-that-layla-understands-that-we-are-nothing-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sooner that Layla understands that we are nothing but the sum of that which we endure, the better." -- Claire Vaye Watkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1210995-on-a-wednesday-morning-in-mid-june-eli-sharpe-was-sitting</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 16:30:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Max Everhart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1210995-on-a-wednesday-morning-in-mid-june-eli-sharpe-was-sitting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On a Wednesday morning in mid-June, Eli Sharpe was sitting at his desk treating jetlag with strong coffee when he heard a knock on his apartment door. After a second, more insistent knock, he added a dash of George Dickel to his Folgers and hid the pint in a desk drawer.
    “It’s open,” he said loudly and stood up to receive his visitor.
    In walked a tall blonde, her high heels stabbing the scuffed- up hardwoods, her perfume battling the smell of coffee and dust permeating Eli’s six-hundred square foot studio apartment that doubled as a working office. Her perfume won the battle: Light Blue by Dolce &amp; Gabbana. Same scent his third fiancée used to wear." -- Max Everhart]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
