<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/167540-stephen-horvath]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/167540-stephen-horvath" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 06:48:22 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31582-whenever-serious-and-competent-people-need-to-get-things-done</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 06:48:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephen add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31582-whenever-serious-and-competent-people-need-to-get-things-done]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever serious and competent people need to get things done in the real world, all considerations of tradition and protocol fly out the window." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68545-nell-the-constable-continued-indicating-through-his-tone-of-voice</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 06:49:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephen add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68545-nell-the-constable-continued-indicating-through-his-tone-of-voice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nell,&quot; the Constable continued, indicating through his tone of voice that the lesson was concluding, &quot;the difference between ignorant and educated people is that the latter know more facts. But that has nothing to do with whether they are stupid or intelligent. The difference between stupid and intelligent people—and this is true whether or not they are well-educated—is that intelligent people can handle subtlety. They are not baffled by ambiguous or even contradictory situations—in fact, they expect them and are apt to become suspicious when things seem overly straightforward." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21279-to-condense-fact-from-the-vapor-of-nuance</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 06:49:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephen add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21279-to-condense-fact-from-the-vapor-of-nuance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To condense fact from the vapor of nuance." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199153-when-i-saw-any-of-those-kinds-of-beauty</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 06:55:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephen add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199153-when-i-saw-any-of-those-kinds-of-beauty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["... when I saw any of those kinds of beauty I knew I was alive, and not just in the sense that when I hit my thumb with a hammer I knew I was alive, but rather in the sense that I was partaking of something--something was passing through me that it was in my nature to be a part of." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145350-nell-did-not-imagine-that-constable-moore-wanted-to-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 06:55:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephen add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145350-nell-did-not-imagine-that-constable-moore-wanted-to-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nell did not imagine that Constable Moore wanted to get into a detailed discussion of recent events, so she changed the subject. &quot;I think I have finally worked out what you were trying to tell me, years ago, about being intelligent,&quot; she said.
 
The Constable brightened all at once. &quot;Pleased to hear it.&quot;
 
The Vickys have an elaborate code of morals and conduct. It grew out of the moral squalor of an earlier generation, just as the original Victorians were preceded by the Georgians and the Regency. The old guard believe in that code because they came to it the hard way. They raise their children to believe in that code– but their children believe it for entirely different reasons.&quot;
 
They believe it,&quot; the Constable said, &quot;because they have been indoctrinated to believe it.&quot;
 
Yes. Some of them never challenge it– they grow up to be smallminded people, who can tell you what they believe but not why they believe it. Others become disillusioned by the hypocrisy of the society and rebel– as did Elizabeth Finkle-McGraw.&quot;
 
Which path do you intend to take, Nell?&quot; said the Constable, sounding very interested. &quot;Conformity or rebellion?&quot;
 
Neither one. Both ways are simple-minded– they are only for people who cannot cope with contradiction and ambiguity." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4954-without-contraries-is-no-progression-attraction-and-repulsion-reason-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 06:01:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephen add a quote by William Blake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4954-without-contraries-is-no-progression-attraction-and-repulsion-reason-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without contraries is no progression. Attraction and repulsion, reason and energy, love and hate, are necessary to human existence." -- William Blake]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
