<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/167534-allison]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/167534-allison" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 09:46:28 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93239-charlie-kaufman-there-was-this-time-in-high-school-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 09:46:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Charlie Kaufman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93239-charlie-kaufman-there-was-this-time-in-high-school-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Charlie Kaufman: There was this time in high school. I was watching you out the library window. You were talking to Sarah Marsh.
Donald Kaufman: Oh, God. I was so in love with her.
Charlie Kaufman: I know. And you were flirting with her. And she was being really sweet to you.
Donald Kaufman: I remember that.
Charlie Kaufman: Then, when you walked away, she started making fun of you with Kim Canetti. And it was like they were laughing at *me*. You didn't know at all. You seemed so happy.
Donald Kaufman: I knew. I heard them.
Charlie Kaufman: How come you looked so happy?
Donald Kaufman: I loved Sarah, Charles. It was mine, that love. I owned it. Even Sarah didn't have the right to take it away. I can love whoever I want.
Charlie Kaufman: But she thought you were pathetic.
Donald Kaufman: That was her business, not mine. You are what you love, not what loves you. That's what I decided a long time ago.
Donald Kaufman: What's up?
Charlie Kaufman: Thank you.
Donald Kaufman: For what? " -- Charlie Kaufman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/91569-you-are-what-you-love-not-what-loves-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 09:46:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Charlie Kaufman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/91569-you-are-what-you-love-not-what-loves-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are what you love, not what loves you. " -- Charlie Kaufman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156662-everything-is-more-complicated-than-you-think-you-only-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 09:47:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Charlie Kaufman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156662-everything-is-more-complicated-than-you-think-you-only-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything is more complicated than you think. You only see a tenth of what is true. There are a million little strings attached to every choice you make; you can destroy your life every time you choose. But maybe you won't know for twenty years. And you'll never ever trace it to its source. And you only get one chance to play it out. Just try and figure out your own divorce. And they say there is no fate, but there is: it's what you create. Even though the world goes on for eons and eons, you are here for a fraction of a fraction of a second. Most of your time is spent being dead or not yet born. But while alive, you wait in vain, wasting years, for a phone call or a letter or a look from someone or something to make it all right. And it never comes or it seems to but doesn't really. And so you spend your time in vague regret or vaguer hope for something good to come along. Something to make you feel connected, to make you feel whole, to make you feel loved." -- Charlie Kaufman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110800-i-know-that-as-a-very-young-child-i-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 09:48:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Charlie Kaufman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110800-i-know-that-as-a-very-young-child-i-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know that as a very young child, I was afraid of death. Many children become aware of the notion of death early and it can be a very troubling thing. We're all in this continuum: I'm this age now, and if I live long enough I'll be that age. I was 20 once, I was 10, I was 4. People who are 20 now will be 50 one day. They don't know that! They know it in the abstract, but they don't know it. I'd like them to know it, because I think it gives you compassion." -- Charlie Kaufman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
