<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/168149-maurice]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/168149-maurice" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2008 11:57:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57245-writing-has-nothing-to-do-with-meaning-it-has-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2008 11:57:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maurice add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57245-writing-has-nothing-to-do-with-meaning-it-has-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing has nothing to do with meaning. It has to do with landsurveying and cartography, including the mapping of countries yet to come." -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43278-the-self-is-a-relation-which-relates-itself-to-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2009 10:56:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maurice add a quote by Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43278-the-self-is-a-relation-which-relates-itself-to-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The self is a relation which relates itself to its own self, or it is that in the relation that the relation relates itself to its own self; the self is not the relation but that the relation relates itself to its own self." -- Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384722-man-is-a-rope-stretched-between-the-animal-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 16:27:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maurice add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384722-man-is-a-rope-stretched-between-the-animal-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man is a rope stretched between the animal and the Superman--a rope over an abyss. 

A dangerous crossing, a dangerous wayfaring, a dangerous looking-back, a dangerous trembling and halting. 

What is great in man is that he is a bridge and not a goal:  what is lovable in man is that he is an OVER-GOING and a DOWN-GOING. 

I love those that know not how to live except as down-goers, for they are the over-goers. 

I love the great despisers, because they are the great adorers, and arrows of longing for the other shore. 

I love those who do not first seek a reason beyond the stars for going down and being sacrifices, but sacrifice themselves to the earth, that the earth of the Superman may hereafter arrive. 

I love him who lives in order to know, and seeks to know in order that the Superman may hereafter live.  Thus seeks he his own down-going. 

I love him who labors and invents, that he may build the house for the Superman, and prepare for him earth, animal, and plant:  for thus seeks he his own down-going. 

I love him who loves his virtue:  for virtue is the will to down-going, and an arrow of longing. 

I love him who reserves no share of spirit for himself, but wants to be wholly the spirit of his virtue:  thus walks he as spirit over the bridge. 

I love him who makes his virtue his inclination and destiny:  thus, for the sake of his virtue, he is willing to live on, or live no more. 

I love him who desires not too many virtues.  One virtue is more of a virtue than two, because it is more of a knot for one's destiny to cling to. 

I love him whose soul is lavish, who wants no thanks and does not give back:  for he always bestows, and desires not to keep for himself. 

I love him who is ashamed when the dice fall in his favor, and who then asks:  &quot;Am I a dishonest player?&quot;--for he is willing to succumb. 

I love him who scatters golden words in advance of his deeds, and always does more than he promises:  for he seeks his own down-going. 

I love him who justifies the future ones, and redeems the past ones: for he is willing to succumb through the present ones. 

I love him who chastens his God, because he loves his God:  for he must succumb through the wrath of his God. 

I love him whose soul is deep even in the wounding, and may succumb through a small matter:  thus goes he willingly over the bridge. 

I love him whose soul is so overfull that he forgets himself, and all things that are in him:  thus all things become his down-going. 

I love him who is of a free spirit and a free heart:  thus is his head only the bowels of his heart; his heart, however, causes his down-going. 

I love all who are like heavy drops falling one by one out of the dark cloud that lowers over man:  they herald the coming of the lightning, and succumb as heralds. 

Lo, I am a herald of the lightning, and a heavy drop out of the cloud:  the lightning, however, is the SUPERMAN.--" -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142400-one-man-doesn-t-believe-in-god-at-all-while-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 20:34:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maurice add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142400-one-man-doesn-t-believe-in-god-at-all-while-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One man doesn't believe in god at all, while the other believes in him so thoroughly that he prays as he murders men!" -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392575-don-t-be-afraid-the-darkness-you-re-in-is-no-greater</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 07:56:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maurice add a quote by José Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392575-don-t-be-afraid-the-darkness-you-re-in-is-no-greater]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't be afraid, the darkness you're in is no greater than the darkness inside your own body, they are two darknesses separated by a skin, I bet you've never thought of that, you carry a darkness about with you all the time and that doesn't frighten you...my dear chap, you have to learn to live with the darkness outside just as you learned to live with the darkness inside" -- José Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
