<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/169020-lee-lacy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/169020-lee-lacy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 06:00:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47067-dixon-was-alive-again-consciousness-was-upon-him-before-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 06:00:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lee add a quote by Kingsley Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47067-dixon-was-alive-again-consciousness-was-upon-him-before-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dixon was alive again. Consciousness was upon him before he could get out of the way; not for him the slow, gracious wandering from the halls of sleep, but a summary, forcible ejection. He lay sprawled, too wicked to move, spewed up like a broken spider-crab on the tarry shingle of morning. The light did him harm, but not as much as looking at things did; he resolved, having done it once, never to move his eyeballs again. A dusty thudding in his head made the scene before him beat like a pulse. His mouth had been used as a latrine by some small creature of the night, and then as its mausoleum. During the night, too, he'd somehow been on a cross-country run and then been expertly beaten up by secret police. He felt bad." -- Kingsley Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1182407-i-can-but-pray-the-father-o-a-to-haud</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 09:31:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lee add a quote by George MacDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1182407-i-can-but-pray-the-father-o-a-to-haud]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can but pray the Father o' a' to haud his e'e upon her, an' his airms aboot her, an' keep aff the hardenin' o' the hert 'at despises coonsel!" -- George MacDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1184243-i-had-always-detested-the-meddlesome-alarmist-who-veils-ignorance</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 07:58:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lee add a quote by Erskine Childers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1184243-i-had-always-detested-the-meddlesome-alarmist-who-veils-ignorance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had always detested the meddlesome alarmist, who veils ignorance under noisiness, and for ever wails his chant of lugubrious pessimism." -- Erskine Childers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1184257-i-am-going-to-make-you-what-you-may-perhaps</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 08:09:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lee add a quote by Marie Corelli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1184257-i-am-going-to-make-you-what-you-may-perhaps]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am going to make you what you may perhaps consider rather a singular proposition. It is this, that if you don’t like me, say so at once, and we will part now, before we have time to know anything more of each other, and I will endeavour not to cross your path again unless you seek me out. But if on the contrary, you do like me,—if you find something in my humour or turn of mind congenial to your own disposition, give me your promise that you will be my friend and comrade for a while, say for a few months at any rate. I can take you into the best society, and introduce you to the prettiest women in Europe as well as the most brilliant men. I know them all, and I believe I can be useful to you. But if there is the smallest aversion to me lurking in the depths of your nature”—here he paused,—then resumed with extraordinary solemnity—“in God’s name give it full way and let me go,—because I swear to you in all sober earnest that I am not what I seem!" -- Marie Corelli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1184263-beauty-combined-with-wantonness-frequently-ends-in-the-drawn-twitch</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 08:16:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lee add a quote by Marie Corelli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1184263-beauty-combined-with-wantonness-frequently-ends-in-the-drawn-twitch]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beauty combined with wantonness frequently ends in the drawn twitch, fixed eye and helpless limbs of life-in-death. It is Nature’s revenge on the outraged body,—and do you know, Eternity’s revenge on the impure Soul is extremely similar?" -- Marie Corelli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1184270-had-any-one-dared-to-say-this-truth-to-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 08:21:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lee add a quote by Marie Corelli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1184270-had-any-one-dared-to-say-this-truth-to-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Had any one dared to say this truth to me then, I should have bade him go and preach nonsense to children,—but now,—when I recall those white leaves of days that were unrolled before me fresh and blank with every sunrise, and with which I did nothing save scrawl my own Ego in a foul smudge across each one, I tremble, and inwardly pray that I may never be forced to send back my self-written record!" -- Marie Corelli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1184276-if-men-were-true-to-their-immortal-instincts-and-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 08:30:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lee add a quote by Marie Corelli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1184276-if-men-were-true-to-their-immortal-instincts-and-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If men were true to their immortal instincts and to the God that made them,—if they were generous, honest, fearless, faithful, reverent, unselfish, ... if women were pure, brave, tender and loving,—can you not imagine that in the strong force and fairness of such a world, ‘Lucifer, son of the Morning’ would be moved to love instead of hate?—that the closed doors of Paradise would be unbarred—and that he, lifted towards his Creator on the prayers of pure lives, would wear again his Angel’s crown? Can you not realize this, even by way of a legendary story?" -- Marie Corelli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1189412-one-boy-s-a-boy-two-boys-be-half-a-boy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 16:13:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lee add a quote by Flora Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1189412-one-boy-s-a-boy-two-boys-be-half-a-boy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One boy's a boy; two boys be half a boy, and three boys be no boy at all', ran the old country saying." -- Flora Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
