<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/170961-double-c]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/170961-double-c" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 18:54:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36874-sometimes-you-just-have-to-pee-in-the-sink</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 18:54:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Double add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36874-sometimes-you-just-have-to-pee-in-the-sink]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes you just have to pee in the sink." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50205-there-is-a-loneliness-in-this-world-so-great-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 19:26:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Double add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50205-there-is-a-loneliness-in-this-world-so-great-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["there is a loneliness in this world so great that you can see it in the slow movement of the hands of a clock" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128232-listening-now-it-occured-to-me-that-i-hadn-t-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 10:52:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Double add a quote by Frederick Exley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128232-listening-now-it-occured-to-me-that-i-hadn-t-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listening now, it occured to me that I hadn't come very far over the yars -- no farther really than from one &quot;gang bang&quot; to another, save that I had learned, as B. had yet to learn, that tomorrow the pain would be even greater." -- Frederick Exley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128234-unlike-some-men-i-had-never-drunk-for-boldness-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 10:55:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Double add a quote by Frederick Exley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128234-unlike-some-men-i-had-never-drunk-for-boldness-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Unlike some men, I had never drunk for boldness or charm or wit; I had used alcohol for precisely what it was, a depressant to check the mental exhilaration produced by extended sobriety." -- Frederick Exley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128235-whenever-i-think-of-the-man-i-was-in-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 10:57:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Double add a quote by Frederick Exley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128235-whenever-i-think-of-the-man-i-was-in-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever I think of the man I was in those days, cutting across the nat-cropped grass of the campus, burdened down by the weight of the books in which I sought the consolation of other men's grief, and aburdened futher by the large weight of my own bitterness, the whole vision seems a nightmare.  There were girls all about me, so near and yet so out of reach, a pastel nightmare of honey-blond, pink-lipped, golden-legged, lemon-sweatered girls" -- Frederick Exley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128236-i-certainly-didn-t-want-to-fight-with-him-i-did</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 11:00:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Double add a quote by Frederick Exley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128236-i-certainly-didn-t-want-to-fight-with-him-i-did]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I certainly didn't want to fight with him.  I did, however, want to shout, &quot;Listen, you son of a bitch, life isn't all a goddam football game!  You won't always get the girl!  Life is rejection and pain and loss&quot; -- all those things I so cherishly cuddled in my slef-pitying bosom.  I didn't, of course, say any such thing" -- Frederick Exley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128240-the-two-waiters-inside-the-cafe-knew-that-theo-ld</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 11:07:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Double add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128240-the-two-waiters-inside-the-cafe-knew-that-theo-ld]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The two waiters inside the cafe knew that theo ld man was a little drunk, and while he was a good client they knew that if he became too drunk he would leave without paying, so they kept watch on him.
Last week he tried to commit suicide,&quot; one waiter said.
Why?&quot;
He was in despair.&quot;
What about?&quot;
Nothing.&quot;
How do you know it was nothing.&quot;
He has plenty of money." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128241-2-p-m-beer-nothing-matters-but-flopping-on-a-mattress</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 11:11:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Double add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128241-2-p-m-beer-nothing-matters-but-flopping-on-a-mattress]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["2 p.m. beer

nothing matters
but flopping on a mattress
with cheap dreams and a beer
as the leaves die and the horses die
and the landladies stare in the halls;
brisk the music of pulled shades,
a last man's cave
in an eternity of swarm
and explosion;
nothing but the dripping sink,
the empty bottle,
euphoria,
youth fenced in,
stabbed and shaven,
taught words
propped up
to die." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128242-pull-a-string-a-puppet-moves-each-man-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 11:15:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Double add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128242-pull-a-string-a-puppet-moves-each-man-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["pull a string, a puppet moves ...

each man must realize
that it can all disappear very
quickly:
the cat, the woman, the job,
the front tire,
the bed, the walls, the
room; all our necessities
including love,
rest on foundations of sand --
and any given cause,
no matter how unrelated:
the death of a boy in Hong Kong
or a blizzard in Omaha ...
can serve as your undoing.
all your chinaware crashing to the
kitchen floor, your girl will enter
and you'll be standing, drunk,
in the center of it and she'll ask:
my god, what's the matter?
and you'll answer:  I don't know,
I don't know ..." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128250-i-like-to-change-liquor-stores-frequently-because-the-clerks</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 11:27:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Double add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128250-i-like-to-change-liquor-stores-frequently-because-the-clerks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like to change liquor stores frequently because the clerks got to know your habits if you went in night and day and bought huge quantities.  I could feel them wondering why I wasn't dead yet and it made me uncomfortable.  They probably weren't thinking any such thing, but then a man gets paranoid when he has 300 hangovers a year." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128258-edmund-then-with-alcoholic-talkativeness-you-ve-just-told-me-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 12:12:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Double add a quote by Eugene O'Neill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128258-edmund-then-with-alcoholic-talkativeness-you-ve-just-told-me-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["EDMUND
*Then with alcoholic talkativeness
You've just told me some high spots in your memories.  Want to hear mine?  They're all connected with the sea.  Here's one.  When I was on the Squarehead square rigger, bound for Buenos Aires.  Full moon in the Trades.  The old hooker driving fourteen knots.  I lay on the bowsprit, facing astern, with the water foaming into spume under me, the masts with every sail white in the moonlight, towering high above me.  I became drunk with the beauty and signing rhythm of it, and for a moment I lost myself -- actually lost my life.  I was set free!  I dissolved in the sea, became white sails and flying spray, became beauty and rhythm, became moonlight and the ship and the high dim-starred sky!  I belonged, without past or future, within peace and unity and a wild joy, within something greater than my own life, or the life of Man, to Life itself!  To God, if you want to put it that way.  Then another time, on the American Line, when I was lookout on the crow's nest in the dawn watch.  A calm sea, that time.  Only a lazy ground swell and a slow drowsy roll of the ship.  The passengers asleep and none of the crew in sight.  No sound of man.  Black smoke pouring from the funnels behind and beneath me.  Dreaming, not keeping looking, feeling alone, and above, and apart, watching the dawn creep like a painted dream over the sky and sea which slept together.  Then the moment of ecstatic freedom came.  the peace, the end of the quest, the last harbor, the joy of belonging to a fulfillment beyond men's lousy, pitiful, greedy fears and hopes and dreams!  And several other times in my life, when I was swimming far out, or lying alone on a beach, I have had the same experience.  Became the sun, the hot sand, green seaweed anchored to a rock, swaying in the tide.  Like a saint's vision of beatitude.  Like a veil of things as they seem drawn back by an unseen hand.  For a second you see -- and seeing the secret, are the secret.  For a second there is meaning!  Then the hand lets the veil fall and you are alone, lost in the fog again, and you stumble on toward nowhere, for no good reason!
*He grins wryly.
It was a great mistake, my being born a man, I would have been much more successful as a sea gull or a fish.  As it is, I will always be a stranger who never feels at home, who does not really want and is not really wanted, who can never belong, who must always be a a little in love with death!

TYRONE
*Stares at him -- impressed.
Yes, there's the makings of a poet in you all right.
*Then protesting uneasily.
But that's morbid craziness about not being wanted and loving death.

EDMUND
*Sardonically
The *makings of a poet.  No, I'm afraid I'm like the guy who is always panhandling for a smoke.  He hasn't even got the makings.  He's got only the habit.  I couldn't touch what I tried to tell you just now.  I just stammered.  That's the best I'll ever do, I mean, if I live.  Well, it will be faithful realism, at least.  Stammering is the native eloquence of us fog people." -- Eugene O'Neill]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
