<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/171522-martha]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/171522-martha" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 13:00:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394174-the-basic-scam-in-the-internet-age-is-pretty-easy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 13:00:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Matt Taibbi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394174-the-basic-scam-in-the-internet-age-is-pretty-easy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The basic scam in the Internet age is pretty easy even for the financially illiterate to grasp. It was as if banks like Goldman were wrapping ribbons around watermelons, tossing them out fiftieth-story windows, and opening the phones for bids. In this game you were a winner only if you took your money out before the melon hit the pavement." -- Matt Taibbi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2012 14:51:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to write the book that wants to be written. And if the book will be too difficult for grown-ups, then you write it for children." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17243-many-years-later-as-he-faced-the-firing-squad-colonel</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2012 14:51:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17243-many-years-later-as-he-faced-the-firing-squad-colonel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many years later, as he faced the firing squad, Colonel Aureliano Buendía was to remember that distant afternoon when his father took him to discover ice..." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121293-i-was-helpless-in-trying-to-return-people-s-kindness-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 11:45:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Rob Sheffield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121293-i-was-helpless-in-trying-to-return-people-s-kindness-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was helpless in trying to return people's kindness, but also helpless to resist it. Kindness is a scarier force than cruelty, that's for sure. Cruelty isn't that hard to understand. I had no trouble comprehending why the phone company wanted to screw me over; they just wanted to steal some money, it was nothing personal. That's the way of the world. It made me mad, but it didn't make me feel stupid. If anything, it flattered my intelligence. Accepting all that kindness, though, made me feel stupid.

Human benevolence is totally unfair. We don't live in a kind or generous world, yet we are kind and generous. We know the universe is out to burn us, and it gets us all the way it got Renee, but we don't burn each other, not always. We are kind people in an unkind world, to paraphrase Wallace Stevens. How do you pretend you don't know about it, after you see it? How do you go back to acting like you don't need it? How do you even the score and walk off a free man? You can't. I found myself forced to let go of all sorts of independence I thought I had, independence I had spent years trying to cultivate. That world was all gone, and now I was a supplicant, dependent on the mercy of other people's psychic hearts." -- Rob Sheffield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73463-when-one-has-nothing-left-make-ceremonies-out-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 20:52:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73463-when-one-has-nothing-left-make-ceremonies-out-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When one has nothing left make ceremonies out of the air and breathe upon them." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/681218-how-we-gentle-our-losses-into-paler-ghosts</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 01:56:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Peter Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/681218-how-we-gentle-our-losses-into-paler-ghosts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How we gentle our losses into paler ghosts." -- Peter Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/804217-did-you-ever-read-the-bible-i-mean-sit-down</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 01:27:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Peter Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/804217-did-you-ever-read-the-bible-i-mean-sit-down]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did you ever read the Bible? I mean sit down and read it like it was a book? Check out Lamentations. That's where we're at, pretty much. Pretty much lamenting. Pretty much pouring our hearts out like water." -- Peter Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
