<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/173174-robert-ross]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/173174-robert-ross" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 01:20:22 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83304-it-s-possible-in-a-poem-or-short-story-to-write</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 01:20:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Raymond Carver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83304-it-s-possible-in-a-poem-or-short-story-to-write]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's possible, in a poem or short story, to write about commonplace things and objects using commonplace but precise language, and to endow those things—a chair, a window curtain, a fork, a stone, a woman's earring—with immense, even startling power." -- Raymond Carver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78670-if-personality-is-an-unbroken-series-of-successful-gestures-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 23:14:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78670-if-personality-is-an-unbroken-series-of-successful-gestures-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If personality is an unbroken series of successful gestures, then there was something gorgeous about him, some heightened sensitivity to the promise of life, as if he were related to one of those intricate machines that register earthquakes ten thousand miles away. This responsiveness had nothing to do with that flabby impressionability which is dignified under the name of the 'creative temperament'--it was an extraordinary gift for hope, a romantic readiness such as I have never found in any other person and which it is not likely I shall ever find again. No--Gatsby turned out all right at the end; it is what preyed on Gatsby, what foul dust floated in the wake of his dreams that temporarily closed out my interest in the abortive sorrows and short-winded elations of men." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195996-i-will-be-very-careful-the-next-time-i-fall</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 20:04:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Richard Brautigan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195996-i-will-be-very-careful-the-next-time-i-fall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;i&gt;I will be very careful the next time I fall in love&lt;/i&gt;, she told herself. Also, she had made a promise to herself that she intended on keeping. She was never going to go out with another writer: no matter how charming, sensitive, inventive or fun they could be. They weren't worth it in the long run.  They were emotionally too expensive and the upkeep was complicated. They were like having a vacuum cleaner around the house that broke all the time and only Einstein could fix it. 
    She wanted her next lover to be a broom." -- Richard Brautigan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135212-from-whence-shall-we-expect-the-approach-of-danger-shall</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 05:37:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135212-from-whence-shall-we-expect-the-approach-of-danger-shall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From whence shall we expect the approach of danger? Shall some trans-Atlantic military giant step the earth and crush us at a blow? Never. All the armies of Europe and Asia...could not by force take a drink from the Ohio River or make a track on the Blue Ridge in the trial of a thousand years. No, if destruction be our lot we must ourselves be its author and finisher. As a nation of free men we will live forever or die by suicide." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/634764-arturo-bandini--what-does-happiness-mean-to-you-camilla-camilla</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 06:59:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by John Fante]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/634764-arturo-bandini--what-does-happiness-mean-to-you-camilla-camilla]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Arturo Bandini: -What does happiness mean to you Camilla? 
Camilla: -That you can fall in love with whoever you want to, 
and not feel ashamed of it." -- John Fante]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492854-but-they-hushed-all-at-once-and-quite-abruptly-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 08:21:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Denis Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492854-but-they-hushed-all-at-once-and-quite-abruptly-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But they hushed, all at once and quite abruptly, when he stood still at center stage, his arms straight out from his shoulders, and went rigid, and began to tremble with a massive inner dynamism. Nobody present had ever seen anyone stand so still and yet so strangely mobile. He laid his head back until his scalp contacted his spine, that far back, and opened his throat, and a sound rose in the auditorium like a wind coming from all four directions, low and terrifying, rumbling up from the ground beneath the floor, and it gathered into a roar that sucked at the hearing itself, and coalesced into a voice that penetrated into the sinuses and finally into the very minds of those hearing it, taking itself higher and higher, more and more awful and beautiful, the originating ideal of all such sounds ever made, of the foghorn and the ship’s horn, the locomotive’s lonesome whistle, of opera singing and the music of flutes and the continuous moanmusic of bagpipes. And suddenly it all went black. And that time was gone forever." -- Denis Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219675-don-t-patronize-the-chain-bookstores-every-time-i-see-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 15:19:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Lawrence Ferlinghetti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219675-don-t-patronize-the-chain-bookstores-every-time-i-see-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't patronize the chain bookstores. Every time I see some author scheduled to read and sign his books at a chain bookstore, I feel like telling him he's stabbing the independent bookstores in the back." -- Lawrence Ferlinghetti]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
