<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/173276-kate]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/173276-kate" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 08:27:32 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4368-when-the-shadow-of-the-sash-appeared-on-the-curtains</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 08:27:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4368-when-the-shadow-of-the-sash-appeared-on-the-curtains]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the shadow of the sash appeared on the curtains it was between seven and eight o' clock and then I was in time again, hearing the watch. It was Grandfather's and when Father gave it to me he said I give you the mausoleum of all hope and desire; it's rather excruciating-ly apt that you will use it to gain the reducto absurdum of all human experience which can fit your individual needs no better than it fitted his or his father's. I give it to you not that you may remember time, but that you might forget it now and then for a moment and not spend all your breath trying to conquer it. Because no battle is ever won he said. They are not even fought. The field only reveals to man his own folly and despair, and victory is an illusion of philosophers and fools." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241918-for-west-is-where-we-all-plan-to-go-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 07:26:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241918-for-west-is-where-we-all-plan-to-go-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For West is where we all plan to go some day. It is where you go when the land gives out and the old-field pines encroach. It is where you go when you get the letter saying: Flee, all is discovered. It is where you go when you look down at the blade in your hand and the blood on it. It is where you go when you are told that you are a bubble on the tide of empire. It is where you go when you hear that thar's gold in them-thar hills. It is where you go to grow up with the country. It is where you go to spend your old age. Or it is just where you go." -- Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440977-the-child-comes-home-and-the-parent-puts-the-hooks</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 07:26:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440977-the-child-comes-home-and-the-parent-puts-the-hooks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The child comes home and the parent puts the hooks in him. The old man, or the woman, as the case may be, hasn’t got anything to say to the child. All he wants is to have that child sit in a chair for a couple of hours and then go off to bed under the same roof. It’s not love. I am not saying that there is not such a thing as love. I am merely pointing to something which is different from love but which sometimes goes by the name of love. It may well be that without this thing which I am talking about there would not be any love. But this thing in itself is not love. It is just something in the blood. It is a kind of blood greed, and it is the fate of a man. It is the thing which man has which distinguishes him from the happy brute creation. When you got born your father and mother lost something out of themselves, and they are going to bust a hame trying to get it back, and you are it. They know they can’t get it all back but they will get as big a chunk out of you as they can." -- Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/515202-dirt-s-a-funny-thing-the-boss-said-come-to-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 07:26:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/515202-dirt-s-a-funny-thing-the-boss-said-come-to-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dirt's a funny thing,' the Boss said. 'Come to think of it, there ain't a thing but dirt on this green God's globe except what's under water, and that's dirt too. It's dirt makes the grass grow. A diamond ain't a thing in the world but a piece of dirt that got awful hot. And God-a-Mighty picked up a handful of dirt and blew on it and made you and me and George Washington and mankind blessed in faculty and apprehension. It all depends on what you do with the dirt. That right?" -- Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274884-however-a-good-laugh-is-a-mighty-good-thing-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 10:00:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274884-however-a-good-laugh-is-a-mighty-good-thing-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["However, a good laugh is a mighty good thing, and rather too scarce a good thing; the more's the pity. So, if any one man, in his own proper person, afford stuff for a good joke to anybody, let him not be backward, but let him cheerfully allow himself to spend and to be spent in that way. And the man that has anything bountifully laughable about him, be sure there is more in that man than you perhaps think for." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/573269-what-corpus-body-corpse-good-idea-the-latin-stupifies-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 11:38:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/573269-what-corpus-body-corpse-good-idea-the-latin-stupifies-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What? Corpus. Body. Corpse. Good idea the Latin. Stupifies them first. Hospice for the dying. They don't seem to chew it; only swallow it down." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/561185-chicago-happened-slowly-like-a-migraine-first-they-were-driving</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 09:39:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/561185-chicago-happened-slowly-like-a-migraine-first-they-were-driving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chicago happened slowly, like a migraine. First they were driving through countryside, then, imperceptibly, the occasional town became a low suburban sprawl, and the sprawl became the city." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236453-learning-became-her-she-loved-the-smell-of-the-book</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 13:00:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Robert Goolrick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236453-learning-became-her-she-loved-the-smell-of-the-book]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Learning became her.  She loved the smell of the book from the shelves, the type on the pages, the sense that the world was an infinite but knowable place.  Every fact she learned seemed to open another question, and for every question there was another book." -- Robert Goolrick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101535-in-the-soft-grey-silence-he-could-hear-the-bump</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 14:48:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101535-in-the-soft-grey-silence-he-could-hear-the-bump]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the soft grey silence he could hear the bump of the balls: and from here and from there through the quiet air the sound of the cricket bats: pick, pack, pock, puck: like drops of water in a fountain falling softly in the brimming bowl." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134085-it-s-hard-to-say-who-s-a-greater-threat-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2013 14:20:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134085-it-s-hard-to-say-who-s-a-greater-threat-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's hard to say who's a greater threat to the world, an ambitious CEO with a big ad budget or a crafty cleric with an obsolete Bible verse." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/838659-the-pain-of-love-does-not-break-hearts-it-merely</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2013 14:21:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/838659-the-pain-of-love-does-not-break-hearts-it-merely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The pain of love does not break hearts, it merely seasons them. The disappointed heart revives itself and grows meaty and piquant. Sorrow expands it and makes it pithy. The spirit, on the other hand, can snap like a bone and may never fully knit" -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/976250-he-walked-with-equipoise-possibly-in-either-city-schr-dinger-s-pedestrian</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 10:51:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by China Miéville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/976250-he-walked-with-equipoise-possibly-in-either-city-schr-dinger-s-pedestrian]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He walked with equipoise, possibly in either city. Schrödinger’s pedestrian." -- China Miéville]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
