<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/173838-tiffany]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/173838-tiffany" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 02:56:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84678-the-family-is-the-cradle-of-the-world-s-misinformation-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 02:56:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tiffany add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84678-the-family-is-the-cradle-of-the-world-s-misinformation-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The family is the cradle of the world’s misinformation. There must be something in family life that generates factual error. Over-closeness, the noise and heat of being. Perhaps even something deeper like the need to survive. Murray says we are fragile creatures surrounded by a world of hostile facts. Facts threaten our happiness and security. The deeper we delve into things, the looser our structure may seem to become. The family process works towards sealing off the world. Small errors grow heads, fictions proliferate. I tell Murray that ignorance and confusion can’t possibly be the driving forces behind family solidarity. What an idea, what a subversion. He asks me why the strongest family units exist in the least developed societies. Not to know is a weapon of survival, he says. Magic and superstition become entrenched as the powerful orthodoxy of the clan. The family is strongest where objective reality is most likely to be misinterpreted. What a heartless theory, I say. But Murray insists it’s true." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6665-everything-is-blooming-most-recklessly-if-it-were-voices-instead</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 14:45:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tiffany add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6665-everything-is-blooming-most-recklessly-if-it-were-voices-instead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything is blooming most recklessly; if it were voices instead of colors, there would be an unbelievable shrieking into the heart of the night." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98516-there-s-a-place-beyond-words-where-experience-first-occurs-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 13:27:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tiffany add a quote by Jerzy Kosinski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98516-there-s-a-place-beyond-words-where-experience-first-occurs-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's a place beyond words where experience first occurs to which I always want to return. I suspect that whenever I articulate my thoughts or translate my impulses into words, I am betraying the real thoughts and impulses which remain hidden." -- Jerzy Kosinski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98515-it-seems-that-what-i-really-want-is-a-drug</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 13:27:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tiffany add a quote by Jerzy Kosinski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98515-it-seems-that-what-i-really-want-is-a-drug]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seems that what I really want is a drug that will increase my consciousness of others, not myself." -- Jerzy Kosinski]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
