<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/175771-yaffa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/175771-yaffa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 01:50:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 01:50:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yaffa add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May your coming year be filled with magic and dreams and good madness. I hope you read some fine books and kiss someone who thinks you're wonderful, and don't forget to make some art -- write or draw or build or sing or live as only you can. And I hope, somewhere in the next year, you surprise yourself." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64408-eventually-the-woodsman-spoke-we-all-have-our-routines-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 01:52:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yaffa add a quote by John Connolly]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64408-eventually-the-woodsman-spoke-we-all-have-our-routines-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eventually the Woodsman spoke. ‘We all have our routines,’ he said softly. ‘But they must have a purpose and provide an outcome that we can see and take some comfort from, or else they have no use at all. Without that, they are like the endless pacings of a caged animal. If they are not madness itself, then they are a prelude to it.’

The Woodsman stood and showed David his axe.

‘See here,’ he said, pointing with his finger at the blade. Every morning, I make certain that me axe is clean and keen. I look to my house and check that its windows and doors remain secure. I tend to my land, disposing of weeds and ensuring that the soil is watered. I walk through the forest, clearing those paths that need to be kept open. Where trees have been damaged, I do my best to repair what has been harmed. these are my routines and I enjoy doing them well.’

He laid a hand gently on David’s shoulder, and David saw understanding in his face. ‘Rules and routines are good, but they must give you satisfaction. Can you truly say you gain that from touching and counting?’

David shook his head. ‘No,’ he said, ‘but I get scared when I don’t do them. I’m afraid of what might happen.’

‘Then find routines that allow you to feel secure when they are done. You told me that you have a new brother: look to him each morning. Look to your father, and your stepmother. Tend to the flowers in the garden, or in the pots upon the window sill. Seek others who are weaker than you are, and try to give them comfort where you can. Let these be your routines, and the rules that govern your life." -- John Connolly]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64410-joe-arrived-late-again-but-cheerful-as-ever-he-told</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 01:54:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yaffa add a quote by Ben Cheever]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64410-joe-arrived-late-again-but-cheerful-as-ever-he-told]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Joe arrived late again, but cheerful as ever. He told us about dealing with the customer’s FACC. This stood for ‘Fear, Anxiety, Cynicism, and Confusion’.

Joe talked us through page four of the bible, regarding the Dichotomy within ‘the Prospect’. This ‘dichotomy’ was between the pospect’s ‘conscience mind’ and his ‘subconscience mind’. The gifted salesman found a link between the two. I waited a little while and then asked if Joe didn’t mean the prospect’s ‘conscious mind and his subconscious mind’. I hoped I’d get a laugh, but nobody noticed, nor was Joe openly thankful to me for the correction." -- Ben Cheever]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20714-calvin-isn-t-it-strange-that-evolution-would-give-us-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 08:10:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yaffa add a quote by Bill Watterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20714-calvin-isn-t-it-strange-that-evolution-would-give-us-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["CALVIN:
Isn't it strange that evolution would give us a sense of humor?

When you think about it, it's weird that we have a physiological response to absurdity. We laugh at nonsense. We like it. We think it's funny.

Don't you think it's odd that we appreciate absurdity? Why would we develop that way? How does it benefit us?

HOBBES:
I suppose if we couldn't laugh at the things that don't make sense, we couldn't react to a lot of life." -- Bill Watterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33959-you-know-hobbes-some-days-even-my-lucky-rocket-ship</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 08:11:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yaffa add a quote by Bill Watterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33959-you-know-hobbes-some-days-even-my-lucky-rocket-ship]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know, Hobbes, some days even my lucky rocket ship underpants don't help." -- Bill Watterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
