<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/175805-viktoria-jean]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/175805-viktoria-jean" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2008 02:39:54 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2008 02:39:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He's like a drug for you, Bella." -- Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 09:09:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4590-without-music-life-would-be-a-mistake</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 09:09:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4590-without-music-life-would-be-a-mistake]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without music, life would be a mistake." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2885-those-who-dance-are-considered-insane-by-those-who-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 09:09:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2885-those-who-dance-are-considered-insane-by-those-who-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who dance are considered insane by those who cannot hear the music." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4414-if-you-re-going-to-kick-authority-in-the-teeth-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 09:11:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Keith Richards]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4414-if-you-re-going-to-kick-authority-in-the-teeth-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're going to kick authority in the teeth, you might as well use two feet." -- Keith Richards]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20488-a-painter-paints-pictures-on-canvas-but-musicians-paint-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 09:11:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Leopold Stokowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20488-a-painter-paints-pictures-on-canvas-but-musicians-paint-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A painter paints pictures on canvas. But musicians paint their pictures on silence." -- Leopold Stokowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14821-what-you-re-supposed-to-do-when-you-don-t-like-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 09:17:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14821-what-you-re-supposed-to-do-when-you-don-t-like-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What you're supposed to do when you don't like a thing is change it. If you can't change it, change the way you think about it. Don't complain." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1928-if-you-re-looking-for-sympathy-you-ll-find-it-between-shit</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 09:20:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1928-if-you-re-looking-for-sympathy-you-ll-find-it-between-shit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're looking for sympathy you'll find it between shit and syphilis in the dictionary." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15618-for-attractive-lips-speak-words-of-kindness-emsp-for-lovely-eyes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 09:21:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Sam Levenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15618-for-attractive-lips-speak-words-of-kindness-emsp-for-lovely-eyes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For Attractive lips, speak words of kindness.
&amp;emsp;For lovely eyes, seek out the good in people.
&amp;emsp;For a slim figure, share your food with the hungry.
&amp;emsp;For beautiful hair, let a child run their fingers through it once a day.
&amp;emsp;For poise, walk with the knowledge that you never walk alone. 
&amp;emsp;People, more than things, have to be restored, renewed, revived, reclaimed, and redeemed. Remember, if you ever need a helping hand, you will find one at the end of each of your arms.
&amp;emsp;As you grow older, you will discover that you have two hands, one for helping yourself and the other for helping others." -- Sam Levenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66512-i-believe-in-pink-i-believe-that-laughing-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 09:23:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66512-i-believe-in-pink-i-believe-that-laughing-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in pink. I believe that laughing is the best calorie burner. I believe in kissing, kissing a lot. I believe in being strong when everything seems to be going wrong. I believe that happy girls are the prettiest girls. I believe that tomorrow is another day and I believe in miracles." -- Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15894-do-you-know-how-sometimes---when-you-are-riding</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2009 23:36:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15894-do-you-know-how-sometimes---when-you-are-riding]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you know how sometimes - when you are riding your bike and you start skidding across sand, or when you miss a step and start tumbling down the stairs - you have those long, long seconds to know that you are going to be hurt, and badly?" -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117434-nobody-wants-to-admit-to-this-but-bad-things-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 00:00:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117434-nobody-wants-to-admit-to-this-but-bad-things-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody wants to admit to this, but bad things will keep on happening. Maybe that's beause it's all a chain, and a long time ago someone did the first bad thing, and that led someone else to do another bad thing, and so on.

You know, like that game where you whisper a sentence into someone's ear, and that person whispers it to someone else, and it all comes out wrong in the end. 

But then again, maybe bad things happen because it's the only way we can keep remembering what good is supposed to look like." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76977-in-the-space-between-yes-and-no-there-s-a-lifetime</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 00:07:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76977-in-the-space-between-yes-and-no-there-s-a-lifetime]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the space between yes and no, there's a lifetime. It's the difference between the path you walk and the one you leave behind; it's the gap between who you thought you could be and who you really are; its the legroom for the lies you'll tell yourself in the future." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127723-take-it-from-me-love-has-all-the-lasting-permanence</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 00:08:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Jodi Picoult ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127723-take-it-from-me-love-has-all-the-lasting-permanence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Take it from me: love has all the lasting permanence of a rainbow- beautiful while it's there, and just as likely to have disappeared by the time you blink." -- Jodi Picoult ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144699-you-know-how-every-now-and-then-you-have-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 01:42:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144699-you-know-how-every-now-and-then-you-have-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know how every now and then, you have a moment where your whole life stretches out ahead of you like a forked road, and even as you choose one gritty path you've got your eyes on the other the whole time, certain that you're making a mistake." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74917-have-you-ever-lost-yourself-in-a-kiss-i-mean</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 08:31:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Saul Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74917-have-you-ever-lost-yourself-in-a-kiss-i-mean]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever lost yourself in a kiss? I mean pure psychedelic inebriation. Not just lustful petting but transcendental metamorphosis when you became aware that the greatness of this being was breathing into you. Licking the sides and corners of your mouth, like sealing a thousand fleshy envelopes filled with the essence of your passionate being and then opened by the same mouth and delivered back to you, over and over again - the first kiss of the rest of your life. A kiss that confirms that the universe is aligned, that the world's greatest resource is love, and maybe even that God is a woman. With or without a belief in God, all kisses are metaphors decipherable by allocations of time, circumstance, and understanding" -- Saul Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131148-i-read-once-that-the-ancient-egyptians-had-fifty-words</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 08:33:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Brian Andreas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131148-i-read-once-that-the-ancient-egyptians-had-fifty-words]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read once that the ancient Egyptians had fifty words for sand &amp; the Eskimos had a hundred words for snow. I wish I had a thousand words for love, but all that comes to mind is the way you move against me while you sleep &amp; there are no words for that." -- Brian Andreas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 05:47:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that no matter what happens, or how bad it seems today, life does go on, and it will be better tomorrow. I've learned that you can tell a lot about a person by the way he/she handles these three things: a rainy day, lost luggage, and tangled Christmas tree lights. I've learned that regardless of your relationship with your parents, you'll miss them when they're gone from your life. I've learned that making a &quot;living&quot; is not the same thing as making a &quot;life.&quot; I've learned that life sometimes gives you a second chance. I've learned that you shouldn't go through life with a catcher's mitt on both hands; you need to be able to throw something back. I've learned that whenever I decide something with an open heart, I usually make the right decision. I've learned that even when I have pains, I don't have to be one. I've learned that every day you should reach out and touch someone. People love a warm hug, or just a friendly pat on the back. I've learned that I still have a lot to learn. I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3549-there-is-never-a-time-or-place-for-true-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2009 12:04:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3549-there-is-never-a-time-or-place-for-true-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is never a time or place for true love. It happens accidentally, in a heartbeat, in a single flashing, throbbing moment." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27312-going-to-church-doesn-t-make-you-a-christian-any-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 09:57:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Billy Sunday]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27312-going-to-church-doesn-t-make-you-a-christian-any-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Going to church doesn’t make you a Christian any more than going to a garage makes you an automobile." -- Billy Sunday]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36501-perhaps-after-all-romance-did-not-come-into-one-s-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 19:52:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36501-perhaps-after-all-romance-did-not-come-into-one-s-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps, after all, romance did not come into one’s life with pomp and blare, like a gay knight riding down; perhaps it crept to one’s side like an old friend through quiet ways; perhaps it revealed itself in seeming prose, until some sudden shaft of illumination flung athwart its pages betrayed the rhythm and the music, perhaps . . . perhaps . . . love unfolded naturally out of a beautiful friendship, as a golden-hearted rose slipping from its green sheath." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49277-the-worst-thing-is-not-that-the-world-is-unfree</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 03:13:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49277-the-worst-thing-is-not-that-the-world-is-unfree]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worst thing is not that the world is unfree, but that people have unlearned their liberty.

The more indifferent people are to politics, to the interests of others, the more obsessed they become with their own faces. The individualism of our time.

Not being able to fall asleep and not allowing oneself to move: the marital bed.

If high culture is coming to an end, it is also the end of you and your paradoxical ideas, because paradox as such belongs to high culture and not to childish prattle. You remind me of the young men who supported the Nazis or communists not out of cowardice or out of opportunism but out of an excess of intelligence. For nothing requires a greater effort of thought than arguments to justify the rule of nonthought… You are the brilliant ally of your own gravediggers.

In the world of highways, a beautiful landscape means: an island of beauty connected by a long line with other islands of beauty.

How to live in a world with which you disagree? How to live with people when you neither share their suffering nor their joys? When you know that you don’t belong among them?... our century refuses to acknowledge anyone’s right to disagree with the world…All that remains of such a place is the memory, the ideal of a cloister, the dream of a cloister… 

Humor can only exist when people are still capable of recognizing some border between the important and the unimportant. And nowadays this border has become unrecognizable.

The majority of people lead their existence within a small idyllic circle bounded by their family, their home, and their work... They live in a secure realm somewhere between good and evil. They are sincerely horrified by the sight of a killer. And yet all you have to do is remove them from this peaceful circle and they, too, turn into murderers, without quite knowing how it happened.

The longing for order is at the same time a longing for death, because life is an incessant disruption of order. Or to put it the other way around: the desire for order is a virtuous pretext, an excuse for virulent misanthropy.

A long time a go a certain Cynic philosopher proudly paraded around Athens in a moth-eaten coat, hoping that everyone would admire his contempt for convention. When Socrates met him, he said: Through the hole in your coat I see your vanity. Your dirt, too, dear sir, is self-indulgent and your self-indulgence is dirty.

You are always living below the level of true existence, you bitter weed, you anthropomorphized vat of vinegar! You’re full of acid, which bubbles inside you like an alchemist’s brew. Your highest wish is to be able to see all around you the same ugliness as you carry inside yourself. That’s the only way you can feel for a few moments some kind of peace between yourself and the world. That’s because the world, which is beautiful, seems horrible to you, torments you and excludes you.

If the novel is successful, it must necessarily be wiser than its author. This is why many excellent French intellectuals write mediocre novels. They are always more intelligent than their books.

By a certain age, coincidences lose their magic, no longer surprise, become run-of-the-mill.

Any new possibility that existence acquires, even the least likely, transforms everything about existence." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72283-follow-your-inner-moonlight-don-t-hide-the-madness</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 03:15:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Allen Ginsberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72283-follow-your-inner-moonlight-don-t-hide-the-madness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Follow your inner moonlight; don't hide the madness." -- Allen Ginsberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175716-we-have-to-create-culture-don-t-watch-tv-don-t-read</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 03:41:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Terence McKenna]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175716-we-have-to-create-culture-don-t-watch-tv-don-t-read]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have to create culture, don't watch TV, don't read magazines, don't even listen to NPR. Create your own roadshow. The nexus of space and time where you are now is the most immediate sector of your universe, and if you're worrying about Michael Jackson or Bill Clinton or somebody else, then you are disempowered, you're giving it all away to icons, icons which are maintained by an electronic media so that you want to dress like X or have lips like Y. This is shit-brained, this kind of thinking. That is all cultural diversion, and what is real is you and your friends and your associations, your highs, your orgasms, your hopes, your plans, your fears. And we are told 'no', we're unimportant, we're peripheral. 'Get a degree, get a job, get a this, get a that.' And then you're a player, you don't want to even play in that game. You want to reclaim your mind and get it out of the hands of the cultural engineers who want to turn you into a half-baked moron consuming all this trash that's being manufactured out of the bones of a dying world." -- Terence McKenna]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60462-a-motion-picture-or-music-or-television-they-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 04:30:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60462-a-motion-picture-or-music-or-television-they-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A motion picture, or music, or television, they have to maintain a certain decorum in order to be broadcast to a vast audience. Other forms of mass media cost too much to produce a risk reaching only a limited audience. Only one person. But a book. . . . A book is cheap to print and bind. A book is as private and consensual as sex. A book takes time and effort to consume - something that gives a reader every chance to walk away. Actually, so few people make the effort to read that it's difficult to call books a &quot;mass medium.&quot; No one really gives a damn about books. No one has bothered to ban a book in decades." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 04:32:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Bob Moorehead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The paradox of our time in history is that we have taller buildings but 
shorter tempers, wider Freeways, but narrower viewpoints.  We spend more, 
but have less, we buy more, but enjoy less. We have bigger houses and 
smaller families, more conveniences, but less time.  We have more degrees 
but less sense, more knowledge, but less judgment, more experts, yet more 
problems, more medicine, but less wellness.

We drink too much, smoke too much, spend too recklessly, laugh too little, 
drive too fast, get too angry, stay up too late, get up too tired, read too 
little, watch TV too much, and pray too seldom.  We have multiplied our 
possessions, but reduced our values.  We talk too much, love too seldom, and 
hate too often.

We've learned how to make a living, but not a life. We've added years to 
life not life to years.  We've been all the way to the moon and back, but 
have trouble crossing the street to meet a new neighbor.  We conquered outer 
space but not inner space.  We've done larger things, but not better things.

We've cleaned up the air, but polluted the soul. We've conquered the atom, 
but not our prejudice.  We write more, but learn less.  We plan more, but 
accomplish less.  We've learned to rush, but not to wait.  We build more 
computers to hold more information, to produce more copies than ever, but we 
communicate less and less.

These are the times of fast foods and slow digestion, big men and small 
character, steep profits and shallow relationships.

These are the days of two incomes but more divorce, fancier houses, but 
broken homes.  These are days of quick trips, disposable diapers, throwaway 
morality, one night stands, overweight bodies, and pills that do everything 
from cheer, to quiet, to kill.  It is a time when there is much in the 
showroom window and nothing in the stockroom.  A time when technology can 
bring this letter to you, and a time when you can choose either to share 
this insight, or to just hit delete...

Remember, to spend some time with your loved ones, because they are not 
going to be around forever.  Remember, say a kind word to someone who looks 
up to you in awe, because that little person soon will grow up and leave 
your side.

Remember, to give a warm hug to the one next to you, because that is the 
only treasure you can give with your heart and it doesn't cost a cent.

Remember, to say, &quot;I love you&quot; to your partner and your loved ones, but most 
of all mean it.  A kiss and an embrace will mend hurt when it comes from 
deep inside of you.

Remember to hold hands and cherish the moment for someday that person might 
not be there again.  Give time to love, give time to speak! And give time to 
share the precious thoughts in your mind." -- Bob Moorehead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228647-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 07:44:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228647-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up. You build up all these defenses, you build up a whole suit of armor, so that nothing can hurt you, then one stupid person, no different from any other stupid person, wanders into your stupid life...You give them a piece of you. They didn't ask for it. They did something dumb one day, like kiss you or smile at you, and then your life isn't your own anymore. Love takes hostages. It gets inside you. It eats you out and leaves you crying in the darkness, so simple a phrase like 'maybe we should be just friends' turns into a glass splinter working its way into your heart. It hurts. Not just in the imagination. Not just in the mind. It's a soul-hurt, a real gets-inside-you-and-rips-you-apart pain. I hate love." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214759-the-voice-you-hear-when-you-read-silently-is-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 07:54:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Thomas Lux]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214759-the-voice-you-hear-when-you-read-silently-is-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["THE VOICE YOU HEAR WHEN YOU READ SILENTLY

 

is not silent, it is a speaking-

out-loud voice in your head;  it is *spoken*,

a voice is *saying* it

as you read.  It's the writer's words,

of course, in a literary sense

his or her &quot;voice&quot; but the sound

of that voice is the sound of *your* voice.

Not the sound your friends know

or the sound of a tape played back

but your voice

caught in the dark cathedral

of your skull, your voice heard

by an internal ear informed by internal abstracts

and what you know by feeling,

having felt.  It is your voice

saying, for example, the word &quot;barn&quot;

that the writer wrote

but the &quot;barn&quot; you say

is a barn you know or knew.  The voice

in your head, speaking as you read,

never says anything neutrally- some people

hated the barn they knew,

some people love the barn they know

so you hear the word loaded

and a sensory constellation

is lit:  horse-gnawed stalls,

hayloft, black heat tape wrapping

a water pipe, a slippery

spilled *chirr* of oats from a split sack,

the bony, filthy haunches of cows...

And &quot;barn&quot; is only a noun- no verb

or subject has entered into the sentence yet!

The voice you hear when you read to yourself

is the clearest voice:  you speak it

speaking to you.

 

                        ~~-Thomas Lux
" -- Thomas Lux]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6384-imperfection-is-beauty-madness-is-genius-and-it-s-better-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 11:56:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6384-imperfection-is-beauty-madness-is-genius-and-it-s-better-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imperfection is beauty, madness is genius and it's better to be absolutely ridiculous than absolutely boring." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84300-people-tend-to-think-that-happiness-is-a-stroke-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 12:01:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Viktoria Jean add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84300-people-tend-to-think-that-happiness-is-a-stroke-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People tend to think that happiness is a stroke of luck, something that will descend like fine weather if you're fortunate. But happiness is the result of personal effort. You fight for it, strive for it, insist upon it, and sometimes even travel around the world looking for it. You have to participate relentlessly." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
