<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/176683-deirdre-keating]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/176683-deirdre-keating" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 07:49:33 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 07:49:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2638-both-destiny-s-kisses-and-its-dope-slaps-illustrate-an-individual-person-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 08:01:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2638-both-destiny-s-kisses-and-its-dope-slaps-illustrate-an-individual-person-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Both destiny's kisses and its dope-slaps illustrate an individual person's basic personal powerlessness over the really meaningful events in his life: i.e. almost nothing important that ever happens to you happens because you engineer it.  Destiny has no beeper; destiny always leans trenchcoated out of an alley with some sort of Psst that you usually can't even hear because you're in such a rush to or from something important you've tried to engineer." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62349-in-dark-times-the-definition-of-good-art-would-seem</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 08:04:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62349-in-dark-times-the-definition-of-good-art-would-seem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In dark times, the definition of good art would seem to be art that locates and applies CPR to those elements of what's human and magical that still live and glow despite the times' darkness. Really good fiction could have as dark a worldview as it wished, but it'd find a way both to depict this world and to illuminate the possibilities for being alive and human in it." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14273-many-people-lose-the-small-joys-in-the-hope-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 08:52:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Pearl S. Buck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14273-many-people-lose-the-small-joys-in-the-hope-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many people lose the small joys in the hope for the big happiness." -- Pearl S. Buck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24378-the-young-do-not-know-enough-to-be-prudent-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 08:52:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by PEARL S. BUCK]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24378-the-young-do-not-know-enough-to-be-prudent-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The young do not know enough to be prudent, and therefore they attempt the impossible -- and achieve it, generation after generation." -- PEARL S. BUCK]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 09:07:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I went to the woods because I wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and see if I could not learn what it had to teach, and not, when I came to die, discover that I had not lived. I did not wish to live what was not life, living is so dear; nor did I wish to practise resignation, unless it was quite necessary. I wanted to live deep and suck out all the marrow of life, to live so sturdily and Spartan-like as to put to rout all that was not life, to cut a broad swath and shave close, to drive life into a corner, and reduce it to its lowest terms." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15629-if-a-man-does-not-keep-pace-with-his-companions</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 09:07:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15629-if-a-man-does-not-keep-pace-with-his-companions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a man does not keep pace with his companions, perhaps it is because he hears a different drummer. Let him step to the music he hears, however measured or far away." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/857-those-who-dream-by-day-are-cognizant-of-many-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 18:37:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/857-those-who-dream-by-day-are-cognizant-of-many-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who dream by day are cognizant of many things which escape those who dream only by night." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36491-two-things-cannot-be-in-one-place-where-you-tend</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 18:38:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36491-two-things-cannot-be-in-one-place-where-you-tend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things cannot be in one place. Where you tend a rose, my lad, a thistle cannot grow." -- Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32-we-are-all-travelers-in-the-wilderness-of-this-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 18:42:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Robert Louis Stevenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32-we-are-all-travelers-in-the-wilderness-of-this-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all travelers in the wilderness of this world, and the best we can find in our travels is an honest friend." -- Robert Louis Stevenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 18:44:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be yourself in a world that is constantly trying to make you something else is the greatest accomplishment." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1896-when-i-have-a-little-money-i-buy-books-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 18:45:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Desiderius Erasmus Roterodamus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1896-when-i-have-a-little-money-i-buy-books-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I have a little money, I buy books; and if I have any left, I buy food and clothes." -- Desiderius Erasmus Roterodamus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9717-time-stands-still-best-in-moments-that-look-suspiciously-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 06:25:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Brian Andreas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9717-time-stands-still-best-in-moments-that-look-suspiciously-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time stands still best in moments that look suspiciously like ordinary life." -- Brian Andreas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47070-there-is-a-vitality-a-life-force-an-energy-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 06:25:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Martha Graham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47070-there-is-a-vitality-a-life-force-an-energy-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a vitality, a life force, an energy, a quickening that is translated through you into action, and because there is only one of you in all of time, this expression is unique. And if you block it, it will never exist through any other medium and it will be lost. The world will not have it. It is not your business to determine how good it is nor how valuable nor how it compares with other expressions. It is your business to keep it yours clearly and directly, to keep the channel open. You do not even have to believe in yourself or your work. You have to keep yourself open and aware to the urges that motivate you. Keep the channel open. ... No artist is pleased. [There is] no satisfaction whatever at any time. There is only a queer divine dissatisfaction, a blessed unrest that keeps us marching and makes us more alive than the others" -- Martha Graham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104377-oh-it-s-always-the-same-she-sighed-if-you-want</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 22:09:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104377-oh-it-s-always-the-same-she-sighed-if-you-want]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh, it's always the same,' she sighed, 'if you want men to behave well to you, you must be beastly to them; if you treat them decently they make you suffer for it." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46656-we-can-learn-to-trust-our-maternal-selves-and-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 12:48:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Katrina Kenison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46656-we-can-learn-to-trust-our-maternal-selves-and-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["we can learn to trust our maternal selves and to have faith in the innate goodness and purity of our children - even when we feel overwhelmed and the kids are pushing all our buttons.  we can support one another....we can be understanding of each other and easier on ourselves." -- Katrina Kenison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 18:45:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know you're in love when you can't fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310818-do-not-throw-away-your-heart-keep-your-heart-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 07:20:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Gary Shteyngart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310818-do-not-throw-away-your-heart-keep-your-heart-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not throw away your heart.  Keep your heart.  Your heart is all that matters ... Throw away your ancestors!  ... Throw away your shyness and the anger that lies just a few inches beneath ... Accept the truth!  And if there is more than one truth, then learn to do the difficult work -- learn to choose.  You are good enough, you are HUMAN ENOUGH, to choose!" -- Gary Shteyngart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79587-in-the-end-i-think-the-relationships-that-survive-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2010 08:22:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79587-in-the-end-i-think-the-relationships-that-survive-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the end, I think the relationships that survive in this world are the ones where  two people can finish each other's sentences. Forget drama and torrid sex and the clash of opposites. Give me banter any day of the week. " -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363457-quite-the-narration-in-your-head-even-for-a-moment</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 12:32:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Karen Maezen Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363457-quite-the-narration-in-your-head-even-for-a-moment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...Quite the narration in your head, even for a moment, and see for yourself that life is life, and not one minute of it is a retelling or a foretelling. Some things happen; some things don't. That's what makes it all worth seeing, no matter where it goes or how it ends. There is no spinmeister steering it all to a forgone conclusion." -- Karen Maezen Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363458-all-practice-is-the-practice-of-making-a-turn-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 12:46:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Karen Maezen Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363458-all-practice-is-the-practice-of-making-a-turn-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All practice is the practice of making a turn in a different direction. Toward one thing and away from another; the particulars in any given situation don't matter, because you always know the right way. A different way. With practice, you get better at turning.

This is my practice. It's not anything special you need to learn. It is not some new information you neet to get. It is nothing you haven't heard before. It is just a turn you might not yet have made, or made again, and again, and again. A turn toward intimate engagement with the life you already have.

Fulfillment derives not from lofty achievements, but from ordinary feats. It arrives not once in a lifetime, but every moment of the livelong day." -- Karen Maezen Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123970-what-a-terrible-thing-it-is-to-botch-a-farewell</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2011 12:52:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123970-what-a-terrible-thing-it-is-to-botch-a-farewell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a terrible thing it is to botch a farewell. I am a person who believes in form, in the harmony of order. Where we can, we must give things a meaningful shape. For example - I wonder - could you tell my jumbled story in exactly one hundred chapters, not one more, not one less? I'll tell you, that's one thing I have about my nickname, the way the number runs on forever. It's important in life to conclude things properly. Only then can you let go. Otherwise you are left with words you should have said but never did, and your heart is heavy with remorse. That bungled goodbye hurts me to this day. I wish so much that I'd had one last look at him in the lifeboat, that I'd provoked him a little, so that I was on his mind. I wish I had said to him then - yes, I know, to a tiger, but still - I wish I had said, &quot;Richard Parker, it's over. We  have survived. Can you believe it? I owe you more gratitude than I can express I couldn't have done it without you. I would like to say it formally: Richard Parker, thank you. Thank you for saving my life. And now go where you must. You have known the confined freedom of a zoo most of your life; now you will know the free confinement of a jungle. I wish you all the best with it. Watch out for Man. He is not your friend. But I hope you will remember me as a friend. I will never forget you , that is certain. You will always be with me, in my heart. What is that hiss? Ah, our boat has touched sand. So farewell, Richard Parker, farewell. God be with you." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224683-as-for-me-i-believe-that-if-there-s-a-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2011 12:07:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Elizabeth McCracken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224683-as-for-me-i-believe-that-if-there-s-a-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As for me, I believe that if there's a God - and I am as neutral on the subject as is possible - then the most basic proof of His existence is black humor.  What else explains it, that odd, reliable comfort that billows up at the worst moments, like a beautiful sunset woven out of the smoke over a bombed city." -- Elizabeth McCracken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405920-i-know-it-doesn-t-sound-logical-but-that-s-the-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 09:51:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Marcelo Figueras]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405920-i-know-it-doesn-t-sound-logical-but-that-s-the-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know it doesn't sound logical but that's the way it is ' said papá. 'There are people who try to control the people they love or try to make them feel insecure or inferior or unworthy. They can be very hurtful but they're the sad people. They're afraid of being abandoned they're afraid of not being loved.' pg 116" -- Marcelo Figueras]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61085-in-books-i-have-traveled-not-only-to-other-worlds</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 18:58:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Anna Quindlen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61085-in-books-i-have-traveled-not-only-to-other-worlds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In books I have traveled, not only to other worlds, but into my own." -- Anna Quindlen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11500-i-would-be-most-content-if-my-children-grew-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 18:58:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Anna Quindlen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11500-i-would-be-most-content-if-my-children-grew-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would be most content if my children grew up to be the kind of people who think decorating consists mostly of building enough bookshelves." -- Anna Quindlen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25569-i-do-not-believe-that-sheer-suffering-teaches-if-suffering</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 21:28:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25569-i-do-not-believe-that-sheer-suffering-teaches-if-suffering]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not believe that sheer suffering teaches.  If suffering alone taught, all the world would be wise, since everyone suffers.  To suffering must be added mourning, understanding, patience, love, openness, and the willingness to remain vulnerable." -- Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263084-when-you-love-someone-you-do-not-love-them-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 21:29:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263084-when-you-love-someone-you-do-not-love-them-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you love someone, you do not love them all the time, in exactly the same way, from moment to moment. It is an impossibility. It is even a lie to pretend to. And yet this is exactly what most of us demand. We have so little faith in the ebb and flow of life, of love, of relationships. We leap at the flow of the tide and resist in terror its ebb. We are afraid it will never return. We insist on permanency, on duration, on continuity; when the only continuity possible, in life as in love, is in growth, in fluidity - in freedom, in the sense that the dancers are free, barely touching as they pass, but partners in the same pattern.

The only real security is not in owning or possessing, not in demanding or expecting, not in hoping, even. Security in a relationship lies neither in looking back to what was in nostalgia, nor forward to what it might be in dread or anticipation, but living in the present relationship and accepting it as it is now. Relationships must be like islands, one must accept them for what they are here and now, within their limits - islands, surrounded and interrupted by the sea, and continually visited and abandoned by the tides." -- Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298323-one-writes-not-to-be-read-but-to-breathe-one-writes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 21:31:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298323-one-writes-not-to-be-read-but-to-breathe-one-writes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One writes not to be read but to breathe...one writes to think, to pray, to analyze. One writes to clear one's mind, to dissipate one's fears, to face one's doubts, to look at one's mistakes--in order to retrieve them. One writes to capture and crystallize one's joy, but also to disperse one's gloom. Like prayer--you go to it in sorrow more than joy, for help, a road back to 'grace'." -- Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38669-there-is-so-much-about-my-fate-that-i-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 08:56:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deirdre add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38669-there-is-so-much-about-my-fate-that-i-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is so much about my fate that I cannot control, but other things do fall under the jurisdiction. I can decide how I spend my time, whom I interact with, whom I share my body and life and money and energy with. I can select what I can read and eat and study. I can choose how  I'm going to regard unfortunate circumstances in my life-whether I will see them as curses or opportunities. I can choose my words and the tone of voice in which I speak to others. And most of all, I can choose my thoughts." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
