<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/177057-melissa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/177057-melissa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 12:45:58 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290824-howard-roark-built-a-temple-to-the-human-spirit-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 12:45:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290824-howard-roark-built-a-temple-to-the-human-spirit-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Howard Roark built a temple to the human spirit. He saw man as strong, proud, clean, wise and fearless. He saw man as a heroic being. And he built a temple to that. A temple is a place where man is to experience exaltation. He thought that exaltation comes from the consciousness of being guiltless, of seeing the truth and achieving it, of living up to one’s highest possibility, of knowing no shame and having no cause for shame, of being able to stand naked in full sunlight. He thought that exaltation means joy and that joy is man’s birthright. He tho...ught that a place built as a setting for man is a sacred place. That is what Howard Roark thought of man and of exaltation." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19909-the-good-the-admirable-reader-identifies-himself-not-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 07:51:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19909-the-good-the-admirable-reader-identifies-himself-not-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The good, the admirable reader identifies himself not with the boy or the girl in the book, but with the mind that conceived and composed that book." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29348-some-people-and-i-am-one-of-them-hate-happy-ends-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 06:58:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29348-some-people-and-i-am-one-of-them-hate-happy-ends-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people—and I am one of them—hate happy ends. We feel cheated. Harm is the norm. Doom should not jam. The avalanche stopping in its tracks a few feet above the cowering village behaves not only unnaturally but unethically." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69388-in-this-dirty-minded-world-you-are-either-someone-s-wife</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 06:58:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69388-in-this-dirty-minded-world-you-are-either-someone-s-wife]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In this dirty minded world, you are either someone's wife or someone's whore." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10840-your-memory-is-a-monster-you-forget-it-doesn-t-it-simply</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 07:01:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10840-your-memory-is-a-monster-you-forget-it-doesn-t-it-simply]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your memory is a monster; you forget—it doesn't. It simply files things away. It keeps things for you, or hides things from you—and summons them to your recall with will of its own. You think you have a memory; but it has you!" -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1791-a-book-must-be-the-axe-for-the-frozen-sea</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 06:58:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1791-a-book-must-be-the-axe-for-the-frozen-sea]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book must be the axe for the frozen sea within us." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70082-and-never-forget-there-is-memory</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 19:02:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70082-and-never-forget-there-is-memory]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And never forget, there is memory." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235537-i-want-to-yell-so-loud-that-baby-girl-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 17:29:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235537-i-want-to-yell-so-loud-that-baby-girl-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to yell so loud that Baby Girl can hear me that dirty ain't a color, disease ain't the Negro side a town. I want to stop that moment from coming - and it come in ever white child's life - when they start to think that colored folks ain't as good as whites. ... I pray that wasn't her moment, Pray I still got time." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138374-not-only-will-you-sleep-with-me-but-you-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 05:51:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Ilona Andrews]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138374-not-only-will-you-sleep-with-me-but-you-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not only will you sleep with me, but you will say 'please.'&quot;
I stared at him, shocked. 
The smile widened. &quot;You will say 'please' before and 'thank you' after.&quot; 
Nervous laughter bubbled up. &quot;You've gone insane. All that peroxide in your hair finally did your brain in, Goldilocks." -- Ilona Andrews]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82437-you-ll-get-over-it-it-s-the-clich-s-that-cause-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2011 10:57:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82437-you-ll-get-over-it-it-s-the-clich-s-that-cause-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You’ll get over it…” It’s the clichés that cause the trouble. To lose someone you love is to alter your life for ever. You don’t get over it because ‘it” is the person you loved. The pain stops, there are new people, but the gap never closes. How could it? The particularness of someone who mattered enough to grieve over is not made anodyne by death. This hole in my heart is in the shape of you and no-one else can fit it. Why would I want them to?" -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442388-people-think-that-a-liar-gains-a-victory-over-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 10:27:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442388-people-think-that-a-liar-gains-a-victory-over-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think that a liar gains a victory over his victim. What I've learned is that a lie is an act of self-abdication, because one surrenders one's reality to the person to whom one lies, making that person one's master, comdemning oneself from then on to faking the sort of reality that person's view requires to be faked." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442390-you-don-t-have-to-see-through-the-eyes-of-others</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 10:27:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442390-you-don-t-have-to-see-through-the-eyes-of-others]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't have to see through the eyes of others, hold onto yours, stand on your own judgment, you know that what is, is–say it aloud, like the holiest of prayers, and don't let anyone tell you otherwise." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442392-fight-for-the-value-of-your-person-fight-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 10:28:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442392-fight-for-the-value-of-your-person-fight-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fight for the value of your person. Fight for the virtue of your pride. Fight for the essence of that which is man: for his sovereign rational mind. Fight with the radiant certainty and the absolute rectitude of knowing that yours is the Morality of Life and that yours is the battle for any achievement, any value, any grandeur, any goodness, any joy that has ever existed on this earth" -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442396-by-the-grace-of-reality-and-the-nature-of-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 10:31:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442396-by-the-grace-of-reality-and-the-nature-of-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By the grace of reality and the nature of life, man–every man–is an end in himself, he exists for his own sake, and the achievement of his own happiness is his highest moral purpose" -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36025-i-swear-by-my-life-and-my-love-of-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 10:32:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36025-i-swear-by-my-life-and-my-love-of-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I swear by my life and my love of it that I will never live for the sake of another man, nor ask another man to live for mine." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198073-you-have-been-the-one-encounter-in-my-life-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 10:47:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198073-you-have-been-the-one-encounter-in-my-life-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have been the one encounter in my life that can never be repeated" -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297084-spend-your-money-on-the-things-money-can-buy-spend</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 06:46:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297084-spend-your-money-on-the-things-money-can-buy-spend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Spend your money on the things money can buy. Spend your time on the things money can’t buy." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120869-learning-how-to-discipline-your-speech-is-a-way-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2012 08:04:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120869-learning-how-to-discipline-your-speech-is-a-way-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Learning how to discipline your speech is a way of preventing your energies from spilling out of you through the rupture of your mouth, exhausting you and filling the world with words, words, words instead of serenity, peace and bliss." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7139-do-not-let-your-fire-go-out-spark-by-irreplaceable</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2012 08:08:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7139-do-not-let-your-fire-go-out-spark-by-irreplaceable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not let your fire go out, spark by irreplaceable spark in the hopeless swamps of the not-quite, the not-yet, and the not-at-all. Do not let the hero in your soul perish in lonely frustration for the life you deserved and have never been able to reach. The world you desire can be won. It exists.. it is real.. it is possible.. it's yours." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/375982-you-know-everybody-dies-my-parents-died-your-father-died</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2012 08:10:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/375982-you-know-everybody-dies-my-parents-died-your-father-died]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know, everybody dies. My parents died. Your father died. Everybody dies. I'm going to die too. So will you. The thing is, to have a life before we die. It can be a real adventure having a life" -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7096-listen-to-the-mustn-ts-child-listen-to-the-don-ts-listen</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 07:45:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Shel Silverstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7096-listen-to-the-mustn-ts-child-listen-to-the-don-ts-listen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen to the mustn'ts, child. Listen to the don'ts. Listen to the shouldn'ts, the impossibles, the won'ts. Listen to the never haves, then listen close to me... Anything can happen, child. Anything can be." -- Shel Silverstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 07:46:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 09:04:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10889-we-re-as-common-as-rain-and-she-was-right-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 06:40:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10889-we-re-as-common-as-rain-and-she-was-right-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We’re as common as rain.”  And she was right: to each other, we were as normal and nice as the smell of bread, we were just a family.  In a family, even exaggerations make perfect sense; they are always logical exaggerations, nothing more." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36213-being-a-humanist-means-trying-to-behave-decently-without-expectation</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 06:24:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36213-being-a-humanist-means-trying-to-behave-decently-without-expectation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being a Humanist means trying to behave decently without expectation of rewards or punishment after you are dead." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
