<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/177609-katemfs]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/177609-katemfs" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 19:51:05 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81984-one-can-never-be-sure-whether-it-s-good-poetry-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 19:51:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81984-one-can-never-be-sure-whether-it-s-good-poetry-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["one can never be sure whether it's good poetry or bad acid" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75130-let-all-of-life-be-an-unfettered-howl</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 14:25:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75130-let-all-of-life-be-an-unfettered-howl]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let all of life be an unfettered howl." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22092-i-have-always-lived-violently-drunk-hugely-eaten-too-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 14:25:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22092-i-have-always-lived-violently-drunk-hugely-eaten-too-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always lived violently, drunk hugely, eaten too much or not at all, slept around the clock or missed two nights of sleeping, worked too hard and too long in glory, or slobbed for a time in utter laziness. I've lifted, pulled, chopped, climbed, made love with joy and taken my hangovers as a consequence, not as a punishment." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45508-there-s-a-moment-when-love-makes-you-believe-in-death</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 14:25:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Anne Michaels]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45508-there-s-a-moment-when-love-makes-you-believe-in-death]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's a moment when love makes you believe in death for the first time. You recognize the one whose loss, even contemplated, you'll carry forever, like a sleeping child. All grief, anyone's grief...is the weight of a sleeping child." -- Anne Michaels]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170352-in-the-first-place-you-re-way-off-when-you-start</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 14:26:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170352-in-the-first-place-you-re-way-off-when-you-start]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the first place, you’re way off when you start railing at things and people instead of at yourself. " -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32912-like-many-air-travelers-i-am-aware-that-airplanes-fly</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 14:26:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by J. Maarten Troost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32912-like-many-air-travelers-i-am-aware-that-airplanes-fly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like many air travelers, I am aware that airplanes fly aided by capricious fairies and invisible strings." -- J. Maarten Troost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1862-the-truth-is-i-often-like-women-i-like-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 11:04:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1862-the-truth-is-i-often-like-women-i-like-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is, I often like women. I like their unconventionality. I like their completeness. I like their anonymity. " -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60536-a-good-night-sleep-or-a-ten-minute-bawl-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 11:04:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60536-a-good-night-sleep-or-a-ten-minute-bawl-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A good night sleep, or a ten minute bawl, or a pint of chocolate ice cream, or all three together, is good medicine." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9257-we-need-not-to-be-let-alone-we-need-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 02:41:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9257-we-need-not-to-be-let-alone-we-need-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We need not to be let alone. We need to be really bothered once in a while. How long is it since you were really bothered? About something important, about something real?" -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71745-i-m-just-sick-of-ego-ego-ego-my-own-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 02:41:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71745-i-m-just-sick-of-ego-ego-ego-my-own-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’m just sick of ego, ego, ego. My own and everybody else’s. I’m sick of everybody that wants to get somewhere, do something distinguished and all, be somebody interesting. It’s disgusting." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68331-i-would-like-to-spare-the-time-and-effort-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 14:26:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68331-i-would-like-to-spare-the-time-and-effort-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would like to spare the time and effort of hack reviewers and, generally, persons who move their lips when reading." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23720-be-true-to-your-dick</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 02:41:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23720-be-true-to-your-dick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be true to your Dick." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33268-you-can-only-understand-people-if-you-feel-them-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 02:41:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33268-you-can-only-understand-people-if-you-feel-them-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can only understand people if you feel them in yourself." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19020-you-can-always-count-on-a-murderer-for-a-fancy</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 14:26:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19020-you-can-always-count-on-a-murderer-for-a-fancy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can always count on a murderer for a fancy prose style." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83895-it-was-love-at-first-sight-at-last-sight-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 14:26:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83895-it-was-love-at-first-sight-at-last-sight-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was love at first sight, at last sight, at ever and ever sight." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10744-if-you-can-t-or-won-t-think-of-seymour-then-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 02:41:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10744-if-you-can-t-or-won-t-think-of-seymour-then-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can't, or won't, think of Seymour, then you go right ahead and call in some ignorant psychoanalyst. You just do that. You just call in some analyst who's experienced in adjusting people to the joys of television, and Life magazine every Wednesday, and European travel, and the H-bomb, and Presidential elections, and the front page of the Times, and God knows what else that's gloriously normal." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68382-good-women-are-no-fun-the-only-good-woman-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 02:41:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68382-good-women-are-no-fun-the-only-good-woman-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good women are no fun... The only good woman I can recall in history was Betsy Ross. And all she ever made was a flag." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3724-what-a-strange-thing-to-be-alive-beneath-cherry-blossoms</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 02:41:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Kobayashi Issa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3724-what-a-strange-thing-to-be-alive-beneath-cherry-blossoms]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a strange thing!
to be alive
beneath cherry blossoms." -- Kobayashi Issa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127483-once-the-process-of-falsification-is-set-in-motion-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 02:41:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127483-once-the-process-of-falsification-is-set-in-motion-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once the process of falsification is set in motion, it won't stop. We're in a country where everything that can be falsified has been falsified: paintings in museums, gold ingots, bus tickets. The counterrevolution and the revolution fight with salvos of falsification: the result is that nobody can be sure what is true and what is false, the political police simulate revolutionary actions and the revolutionaries disguise themselves as policemen.&quot;

And who gains by it, in the end?&quot;

It's too soon to say. We have to see who can best exploit the falsifications, their own and those of the others: whether it's the police or our organization.&quot;

The taxi driver is pricking up his ears. You motion Corinna to restrain herself from making unwise remarks.

But she says, &quot;Don't be afraid. This is a fake taxi. What really alarms me, though, is that there is another taxi following us.&quot;

Fake or real?&quot;

Fake, certainly, but I don't know whether it belongs to the police or to us." -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92194-in-the-shop-window-you-have-promptly-identified-the-cover</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 02:41:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92194-in-the-shop-window-you-have-promptly-identified-the-cover]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the shop window you have promptly identified the cover with the title you were looking for. Following this visual trail, you have forced your way through the shop past the thick barricade of Books You Haven't Read, which were frowning at you from the tables and shelves, trying to cow you. But you know you must never allow yourself to be awed, that among them there extend for acres and acres the Books You Needn't Read, the Books Made For Purposes Other Than Reading, Books Read Even Before You Open Them Since They Belong To The Category Of Books Read Before Being Written. And thus you pass the outer girdle of ramparts, but then you are attacked by the infantry of the Books That If You Had More Than One Life You Would Certainly Also Read But Unfortunately Your Days Are Numbered. With a rapid maneuver you bypass them and move into the phalanxes of the Books You Mean To Read But There Are Others You Must Read First, the Books Too Expensive Now And You'll Wait Till They're Remaindered, the Books ditto When They Come Out In Paperback, Books You Can Borrow From Somebody, Books That Everybody's Read So It's As If You Had Read Them, Too. Eluding these assaults, you come up beneath the towers of the fortress, where other troops are holding out:

the Books You've Been Planning To Read For Ages,

the Books You've Been Hunting For Years Without Success,

the Books Dealing With Something You're Working On At The Moment,

the Books You Want To Own So They'll Be Handy Just In Case,

the Books You Could Put Aside Maybe To Read This Summer,

the Books You Need To Go With Other Books On Your Shelves,

the Books That Fill You With Sudden, Inexplicable Curiosity, Not Easily Justified,

Now you have been able to reduce the countless embattled troops to an array that is, to be sure, very large but still calculable in a finite number; but this relative relief is then undermined by the ambush of the Books Read Long Ago Which It's Now Time To Reread and the Books You've Always Pretended To Have Read And Now It's Time To Sit Down And Really Read Them." -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31245-i-have-never-listened-to-anyone-who-criticized-my-taste</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 02:41:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31245-i-have-never-listened-to-anyone-who-criticized-my-taste]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have never listened to anyone who criticized my taste in space travel, sideshows or gorillas. When this occurs, I pack up my dinosaurs and leave the room." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9123-don-t-think-thinking-is-the-enemy-of-creativity-it-s-self-conscious</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 02:41:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9123-don-t-think-thinking-is-the-enemy-of-creativity-it-s-self-conscious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't think. Thinking is the enemy of creativity. It's self-conscious and anything self-conscious is lousy. You can't &quot;try&quot; to do things. You simply &quot;must&quot; do things." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10579-you-know-one-of-the-tragedies-of-real-life-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 02:41:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Annie Proulx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10579-you-know-one-of-the-tragedies-of-real-life-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know, one of the tragedies of real life is that there is no background music." -- Annie Proulx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/553031-if-you-have-one-parent-who-loves-you-even-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 18:00:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Augusten Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/553031-if-you-have-one-parent-who-loves-you-even-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you have one parent who loves you, even if they can't buy you clothes, they're so poor and they make all kinds of mistakes and maybe sometimes they even give you awful advice, but never for one moment do you doubt their love for you--if you have this, you have incredibly good fortune.

If you have two parents who love you? You have won life's Lotto.

If you do not have parents, or if the parents you have are so broken and so, frankly, terrible that they are no improvement over nothing, this is fine.

It's not ideal because it's harder without adults who love you more than they love themselves. But harder is just harder, that's all." -- Augusten Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/851782-despite-all-of-the-time-he-spent-in-big-heart-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 11:42:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/851782-despite-all-of-the-time-he-spent-in-big-heart-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Despite all of the time he spent in Big Heart's, Wilson had never come to understand the social lives of Indians.  He did not know that, in the Indian world, there is not much social difference between a rich Indian and a poor one.  Generally speaking, Indian is Indian.  A few who gain wealth and power as lawyers, businessmen, artists, or doctors may marry white people and keep only white friends, but generally Indians of different classes interact freely with one another.  Most unemployed or working poor, some with good jobs and steady incomes, but all mixing together.  Wilson also did not realize how tribal distinctions were much more important than economic ones.  The rich and poor Spokanes may hang out together, but that doesn't necessarily mean the Spokanes are friendly with the Lakota or Navajo or any other tribe.  The Sioux still distrust the Crow because they served as scouts for Custer.  Hardly anybody likes the Pawnee.  Most important, though, Wilson did not understand that the white people who pretend to be Indian are gently teased, ignored, plainly ridiculed, or beaten, depending on their degree of whiteness." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/610715-there-s-no-way-to-know-what-makes-one-thing-happen</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 10:04:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/610715-there-s-no-way-to-know-what-makes-one-thing-happen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's no way to know what makes one thing happen and not another.  What leads to what.  What destroys what.  What causes what to flourish or die or take another course." -- Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/685057-he-kissed-me-hard-and-i-kissed-him-back-harder</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 10:05:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katemfs add a quote by Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/685057-he-kissed-me-hard-and-i-kissed-him-back-harder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He kissed me hard and I kissed him back harder, like it was the end of an era that had lasted all of my life." -- Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
