<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/178169-cathy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/178169-cathy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 05:42:47 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2229-to-be-hopeful-in-bad-times-is-not-just-foolishly</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 05:42:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2229-to-be-hopeful-in-bad-times-is-not-just-foolishly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["TO BE HOPEFUL in bad times is not just foolishly romantic. It is based on the fact that human history is a history not only of cruelty, but also of compassion, sacrifice, courage, kindness.
What we choose to emphasize in this complex history will determine our lives. If we see only the worst, it destroys our capacity to do something. If we remember those times and places—and there are so many—where people have behaved magnificently, this gives us the energy to act, and at least the possibility of sending this spinning top of a world in a different direction.
And if we do act, in however small a way, we don’t have to wait for some grand utopian future. The future is an infinite succession of presents, and to live now as we think human beings should live, in defiance of all that is bad around us, is itself a marvelous victory." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20797-any-humane-and-reasonable-person-must-conclude-that-if-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 05:42:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20797-any-humane-and-reasonable-person-must-conclude-that-if-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any humane and reasonable person must conclude that if the ends, however desireable, are uncertain and the means are horrible and certain, these means must not be employed." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71568-i-am-not-the-same-having-seen-the-moon-shine</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2009 17:43:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by mary anne radmacher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71568-i-am-not-the-same-having-seen-the-moon-shine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am not the same having seen the moon shine on the other side of the world." -- mary anne radmacher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 10:49:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12207-you-say-grace-before-meals-all-right-but-i-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2011 09:26:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by G. K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12207-you-say-grace-before-meals-all-right-but-i-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You say grace before meals. All right. But I say grace before the concert and the opera, and grace before the play and pantomime, and grace before I open a book, and grace before sketching, painting, swimming, fencing, boxing, walking, playing, dancing and grace before I dip the pen in the ink." -- G. K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177080-a-story-isn-t-a-charcoal-sketch-where-every-stroke-lies</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2011 09:27:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Amelia Atwater-Rhodes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177080-a-story-isn-t-a-charcoal-sketch-where-every-stroke-lies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A story isn't a charcoal sketch, where every stroke lies on the surface to be seen. It's an oil painting, filled with layers that the author must uncover so carefully to show its beauty." -- Amelia Atwater-Rhodes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122707-we-pencil-sketch-our-previous-life-so-we-can-contrast-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2011 09:27:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by David Levithan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122707-we-pencil-sketch-our-previous-life-so-we-can-contrast-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We pencil-sketch our previous life so we can contrast it to the technicolor of the moment. " -- David Levithan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97615-he-showed-me-a-sketch-he-d-drawn-once-during-meditation</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2011 09:27:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97615-he-showed-me-a-sketch-he-d-drawn-once-during-meditation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He showed me a sketch he'd drawn once during meditation.  It was an androgynous human figure, standing up, hands clasped in prayer.  But this figure had four legs, and no head.  Where the head should have been, there was only a wild foliage of ferns and flowers.  There was a small, smiling face drawn over the heart.  
To find the balance you want,&quot; Ketut spoke through his translator, &quot;this is what you must become.  You must keep your feet grounded so firmly on the earth that it's like you have four legs, instead of two.  That way, you can stay in the world.  But you must stop looking at the world through your head.  You must look through your heart, instead.  That way, you will know God." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169789-exercise-the-writing-muscle-every-day-even-if-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2011 09:28:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Jane Yolen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169789-exercise-the-writing-muscle-every-day-even-if-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Exercise the writing muscle every day, even if it is only a letter, notes, a title list, a character sketch, a journal entry. Writers are like dancers, like athletes. Without that exercise, the muscles seize up." -- Jane Yolen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176533-inspiration-is-a-byproduct-of-discipline-simply-getting-up-everyday</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2011 09:30:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Beverly Claridge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176533-inspiration-is-a-byproduct-of-discipline-simply-getting-up-everyday]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Inspiration is a byproduct of discipline... simply getting up everyday and planning, plotting, sketching, setting up or actually applying paint to a painting.  " -- Beverly Claridge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95262-as-long-as-we-continue-to-live-as-if-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 17:53:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95262-as-long-as-we-continue-to-live-as-if-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As long as we continue to live as if we are what we do, what we have, and what other people think about us, we will remain filled with judgments, opinions, evaluations, and condemnations. We will remain addicted to putting people and things in their &quot;right&quot; place." -- Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199291-dear-god-i-am-so-afraid-to-open-my-clenched</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 17:54:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199291-dear-god-i-am-so-afraid-to-open-my-clenched]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dear God,
I am so afraid to open my clenched fists!
Who will I be when I have nothing left to hold on to?
Who will I be when I stand before you with empty hands?
Please help me to gradually open my hands
and to discover that I am not what I own,
but what you want to give me." -- Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230436-over-the-years-i-have-come-to-realize-that-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 17:54:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230436-over-the-years-i-have-come-to-realize-that-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Over the years, I have come to realize that the greatest trap in our life is not success, popularity, or power, but self-rejection.  Success, popularity, and power can indeed present a great temptation, but their seductive quality often comes from the way they are part of the much larger temptation to self-rejection.  When we have come to believe in the voices that call us worthless and unlovable, then success, popularity, and power are easily perceived as attractive solutions.  The real trap, however, is self-rejection.  As soon as someone accuses me or criticizes me, as soon as I am rejected, left alone, or abandoned, I find myself thinking, &quot;Well, that proves once again that I am a nobody.&quot;  ... [My dark side says,] I am no good... I deserve to be pushed aside, forgotten, rejected, and abandoned.  Self-rejection is the greatest enemy of the spiritual life because it contradicts the sacred voice that calls us the &quot;Beloved.&quot;  Being the Beloved constitutes the core truth of our existence." -- Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258369-there-is-a-twilight-zone-in-our-hearts-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 17:56:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Henri Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258369-there-is-a-twilight-zone-in-our-hearts-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a twilight zone in our hearts that we ourselves cannot see. Even when we know quite a lot about ourselves-our gifts and weaknesses, our ambitions and aspirations, our motives and our drives-large parts of ourselves remain in the shadow of consciousness. This is a very good thing. We will always remain partially hidden to ourselves. Other people, especially those who love us, can often see our twilight zones better than we ourselves can. The way we are seen and understood by others is different from the way we see and understand ourselves. We will never fully know the significance of our presence in the lives of our friends. That's a grace, a grace that calls us not only to humility, but to a deep trust in those who love us. It is the twilight zones of our hearts where true friendships are born." -- Henri Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203711-as-soon-as-we-are-alone-inner-chaos-opens-up-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 17:55:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203711-as-soon-as-we-are-alone-inner-chaos-opens-up-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As soon as we are alone,...inner chaos opens up in us.  This chaos can be so disturbing and so confusing that we can hardly wait to get busy again.  Entering a private room and shutting the door, therefore, does not mean that we immediatel;y shut ou all our iner doubts, anxieities, fears, bad memories, unresolved conflicts, angry feelings and impulsive desires.  On the contrary, when we have removed our outer distraction, we often find that our inner distraction manifest themselves to us in full force.  We often use the outer distractions to shield ourselves from the interior noises.  This makes the discipline of solitude all the more important." -- Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258367-a-friend-is-more-than-a-therapist-or-confessor-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 17:55:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Henri Nowen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258367-a-friend-is-more-than-a-therapist-or-confessor-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A friend is more than a therapist or confessor, even though a friend can sometimes heal us and offer us God's forgiveness. A friend is that other person with whom we can share our solitude, our silence, and our prayer. A friend is that other person with whom we can look at a tree and say, &quot;Isn't that beautiful,&quot; or sit on the beach and silently watch the sun disappear under the horizon. With a friend we don't have to say or do something special. With a friend we can be still and know that God is there with both of us." -- Henri Nowen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257070-the-soul-of-the-artist-cannot-remain-hidden</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 17:57:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Henri Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257070-the-soul-of-the-artist-cannot-remain-hidden]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The soul of the artist cannot remain hidden." -- Henri Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215925-when-the-imitation-of-christ-does-not-mean-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 17:58:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215925-when-the-imitation-of-christ-does-not-mean-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["when the imitation of Christ does not mean to live a life like Christ, but to live your life as authentically as Christ lived his, then there are many ways and forms in which a man can be a Christian." -- Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203706-one-way-to-express-the-spiritual-crisis-of-our-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 17:59:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Henri Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203706-one-way-to-express-the-spiritual-crisis-of-our-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One way to express the spiritual crisis of our time is to say that most of us have an address but cannot be found there." -- Henri Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/469830-today-i-personally-believe-that-while-jesus-came-to-open</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 18:02:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/469830-today-i-personally-believe-that-while-jesus-came-to-open]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today I personally believe that while Jesus came to open the door to God's house, all human beings can walk through that door, whether they know about Jesus or not. Today I see it as my call to help every person claim his or her own way to God." -- Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31420-helped-are-those-who-are-content-to-be-themselves-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 18:15:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31420-helped-are-those-who-are-content-to-be-themselves-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["HELPED are those who are content to be themselves; they will never lack mystery in their lives and the joys of self-discovery will be constant.
HELPED are those who love the entire cosmos rather than their own tiny country, city, or farm, for to them will be shown the unbroken web of life and the meaning of infinity.
HELPED are those who live in quietness, knowing neither brand name nor fad; they shall live every day as if in eternity, and each moment shall be as full as it is long.
HELPED are those who love others unsplit off from their faults; to them will be given clarity of vision.
HELPED are those who create anything at all, for they shall relive the thrill of their own conception, and realize an partnership in the creation of the Universe that keeps them responsible and cheerful.
HELPED are those who love the Earth, their mother, and who willingly suffer that she may not die; in their grief over her pain they will weep rivers of blood, and in their joy in her lively response to love, they will converse with the trees.
HELPED are those whose ever act is a prayer for harmony in the Universe, for they are the restorers of balance to our planet. To them will be given the insight that every good act done anywhere in the cosmos welcomes the life of an animal or a child.
HELPED are those who risk themselves for others' sakes; to them will be given increasing opportunities for ever greater risks. Theirs will be a vision of the word in which no one's gift is despised or lost.
HELPED are those who strive to give up their anger; their reward will be that in any confrontation their first thoughts will never be of violence or of war.
HELPED are those whose every act is a prayer for peace; on them depends the future of the world.
HELPED are those who forgive; their reward shall be forgiveness of every evil done to them. It will be in their power, therefore, to envision the new Earth.
HELPED are those who are shown the existence of the Creator's magic in the Universe; they shall experience delight and astonishment without ceasing.
HELPED are those who laugh with a pure heart; theirs will be the company of the jolly righteous.
HELPED are those who love all the colors of all the human beings, as they love all the colors of the animals and plants; none of their children, nor any of their ancestors, nor any parts of themselves, shall be hidden from them.
HELPED are those who love the lesbian, the gay, and the straight, as they love the sun, the moon, and the stars. None of their children, nor any of their ancestors, nor any parts of themselves, shall be hidden from them.
HELPED are those who love the broken and the whole; none of their children, nor any of their ancestors, nor any parts of themselves, shall be hidden from them.
HELPED are those who do not join mobs; theirs shall be the understanding that to attack in anger is to murder in confusion.
HELPED are those who find the courage to do at least one small thing each day to help the existence of another--plant, animal, river, or human being. They shall be joined by a multitude of the timid.
HELPED are those who lose their fear of death; theirs is the power to envision the future in a blade of grass.
HELPED are those who love and actively support the diversity of life; they shall be secure in their differences.
HELPED are those who KNOW." -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69657-we-ve-got-a-sort-of-brainwashing-going-on-in-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 18:16:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69657-we-ve-got-a-sort-of-brainwashing-going-on-in-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We've got a sort of brainwashing going on in our country, Morrie sighed. Do you know how they brainwash people? They repeat something over and over. And that's what we do in this country. Owning things is good. More money is good. More property is good. More commercialism is good. More is good. More is good. We repeat it--and have it repeated to us--over and over until nobody bothers to even think otherwise. The average person is so fogged up by all of this, he has no perspective on what's really important anymore.

Wherever I went in my life, I met people wanting to gobble up something new. Gobble up a new car. Gobble up a new piece of property. Gobble up the latest toy. And then they wanted to tell you about it. 'Guess what I got? Guess what I got?'

You know how I interpreted that? These were people so hungry for love that they were accepting substitutes. They were embracing material things and expecting a sort of hug back. But it never works. You can't substitute material things for love or for gentleness or for tenderness or for a sense of comradeship.

Money is not a substitute for tenderness, and power is not a substitute for tenderness. I can tell you, as I'm sitting here dying, when you most need it, neither money nor power will give you the feeling you're looking for, no matter how much of them you have." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127039-a-friend-is-someone-who-inspires-who-challenges-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 18:26:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Steve Lopez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127039-a-friend-is-someone-who-inspires-who-challenges-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[".. a friend is someone who inspires, who challenges, who sends you in search of some truer sense of yourself.." -- Steve Lopez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16841-with-time-and-perspective-we-recognize-that-such-problems-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 18:28:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Jeffery R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16841-with-time-and-perspective-we-recognize-that-such-problems-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With time and perspective we recognize that such problems in life do come for a purpose, if only to allow the one who faces such despair to be convinced that he really does need divine strength beyond himself, that she really does need the offer of heaven’s hand. Those who feel no need for mercy usually never seek it and almost never bestow it. Those who have never had a heartache or a weakness or felt lonely or forsaken never have had to cry unto heaven for relief of such personal pain. Surely it is better to find the goodness of God and the grace of Christ, even at the price of despair, than to risk living our lives in a moral or material complacency that has never felt any need for faith or forgiveness, any need for redemption or relief." -- Jeffery R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131851-it-is-possible-to-cause-seemingly-biochemical-changes-through-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 18:30:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Steve Lopez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131851-it-is-possible-to-cause-seemingly-biochemical-changes-through-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is possible to cause seemingly biochemical changes through human emotional involvement. You literally have changed his chemistry by being his friend." -- Steve Lopez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165276-but-the-truth-is-it-s-hard-for-me-to-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 18:30:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165276-but-the-truth-is-it-s-hard-for-me-to-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the truth is it’s hard for me to know what I really think about any of the stuff I’ve written. It’s always tempting to sit back and make finger-steeples and invent impressive sounding theoretical justifications for what one does, but in my case most of it’d be horseshit. As time passes I get less and less nuts about anything I’ve published, and it gets harder to know for sure when its antagonistic elements are in there because they serve a useful purpose and when their just covert manifestations of this &quot;look-at-me-please-love-me-I-hate you&quot; syndrome I still sometimes catch myself falling into. Anyway, but what I think I meant by &quot;antagonize&quot; or &quot;aggravate&quot; has to do with the stuff in the TV essay about the younger writer trying to struggle against the cultural hegemony of TV. One thing TV does is help us deny that we’re lonely. With televised images, we can have the facsimile of a relationship without the work of a real relationship. It’s an anesthesia of &quot;form.&quot; The interesting thing is why we’re so desperate for this anesthetic against loneliness. You don’t have to think very hard to realize that our dread of both relationships and loneliness, both of which are like sub-dreads of our dread of being trapped inside a self (a psychic self, not just a physical self), has to do with angst about death, the recognition that I’m going to die, and die very much alone, and the rest of the world is going to go merrily on without me. I’m not sure I could give you a steeple-fingered theoretical justification, but I strongly suspect a big part of real art fiction’s job is to aggravate this sense of entrapment and loneliness and death in people, to move people to countenance it, since any possible human redemption requires us first to face what’s dreadful, what we want to deny." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236032-but-i-also-say-this-that-light-is-an-invitation</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 18:32:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236032-but-i-also-say-this-that-light-is-an-invitation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I also say this: that light is an invitation to happiness, and that happiness, when it's done right, is a kind of holiness, palpable and redemptive. " -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125477-in-the-moment-of-surrender-i-let-go-of-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 18:33:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Anne Rice]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125477-in-the-moment-of-surrender-i-let-go-of-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the moment of surrender, I let go of all the theological or social questions which had kept me from Him for countless years. I simply let them go. There was the sense, profound and wordless, that if He knew everything I did not have to know everything, and that, in seeking to know everything, I'd been, all of my life, missing the entire point. No social paradox, no historic disaster, no hideous record of injustice or misery should keep me from Him. No question of Scriptural integrity, no torment over the fate of this or that atheist or gay friend, no worry for those condemned and ostracized by my church or any other church should stand between me and Him….I didn't have to know how He was going to save the unlettered and the unbaptized, or how He would redeem the conscientious heathen who had never spoken His name. I didn't have to know how my gay friends would find their way to Redemption or how my hardworking secular humanist friends could or would receive the power of His Saving Grace. I didn't have to know why good people suffered agony or died in pain. He knew. And it was his knowing that overwhelmed me…" -- Anne Rice]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54624-no-matter-what-a-waste-one-has-made-of-one-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 18:35:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Charles Frazier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54624-no-matter-what-a-waste-one-has-made-of-one-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[No] matter what a waste one has made of one's life, it is ever possible to find some path to redemption, however partial." -- Charles Frazier]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
