<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/180115-kristen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/180115-kristen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 16:47:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2150-human-beings-do-not-live-forever-reuven-we-live-less</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 16:47:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Chaim Potok]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2150-human-beings-do-not-live-forever-reuven-we-live-less]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human beings do not live forever, Reuven. We live less than the time it takes to blink an eye, if we measure our lives against eternity. So it may be asked what value is there to a human life.  There is so much pain in the world. What does it mean to have to suffer so much if our lives are nothing more than the blink of an eye? 

I learned a long time ago, Reuven, that a blink of an eye in itself is nothing. But the eye that blinks, that is something. A span of life is nothing. But the man who lives that span, he is something.  He can fill that tiny span with meaning, so its quality is immeasurable though its quantity may be insignificant. Do you understand what I am saying? A man must fill his life with meaning, meaning is not automatically given to life. 

It is hard work to fill one's life with meaning. That I do not think you understand yet. A life filled with meaning is worthy of rest. I want to be worthy of rest when I am no longer here." -- Chaim Potok]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6019-i-wanted-you-to-see-what-real-courage-is-instead</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 16:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6019-i-wanted-you-to-see-what-real-courage-is-instead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted you to see what real courage is, instead of getting the idea that courage is a man with a gun in his hand. It's when you know you're licked before you begin, but you begin anyway and see it through no matter what.
- Atticus Finch" -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 16:52:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is our choices, Harry, that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2008 13:24:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by William Nicholson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We read to know we're not alone." -- William Nicholson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98535-she-conceived-of-life-as-a-road-down-which-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2008 13:33:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98535-she-conceived-of-life-as-a-road-down-which-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She conceived of life as a road down which one traveled, an easy enough road through a broad country, and that one's destination was there from the very beginning, a measured distance away, standing in the ordinary light like some plain house where one went in and was greeted by respectable people and was shown to a room where everything one had ever lost or put aside was gathered together, waiting." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104206-i-took-her-into-bed-with-me-and-propped-myself</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2008 13:37:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104206-i-took-her-into-bed-with-me-and-propped-myself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I took her into bed with me and propped myself up with pillows against the headboard to let her nurse. As she nursed and the milk came, she began a little low contented sort of singing. I would feel milk and love flowing from me to her as once it had flowed to me. It emptied me. As the baby fed, I seemed slowly to grow empty of myself, as if in the presence of that long flow of love even grief could not stand." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9157-they-re-certainly-entitled-to-think-that-and-they-re-entitled-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2008 13:38:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9157-they-re-certainly-entitled-to-think-that-and-they-re-entitled-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They're certainly entitled to think that, and they're entitled to full respect for their opinions... but before I can live with other folks I've got to live with myself.  The one thing that doesn't abide by majority rule is a person's conscience." -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2008 13:41:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fairy tales are more than true: not because they tell us that dragons exist, but because they tell us that dragons can be beaten." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58271-but-unless-we-are-creators-we-are-not-fully-alive</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 11:36:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58271-but-unless-we-are-creators-we-are-not-fully-alive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But unless we are creators we are not fully alive. What do I mean by creators? Not only artists, whose acts of creation are the obvious ones of working with paint of clay or words. Creativity is a way of living life, no matter our vocation or how we earn our living. Creativity is not limited to the arts, or having some kind of important career." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/723-it-is-not-often-that-someone-comes-along-who-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2009 22:16:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/723-it-is-not-often-that-someone-comes-along-who-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not often that someone comes along who is a true friend and a good writer." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145390-i-ve-developed-a-great-reputation-for-wisdom-by-ordering-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 07:24:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145390-i-ve-developed-a-great-reputation-for-wisdom-by-ordering-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've developed a great reputation for wisdom by ordering more books than I ever had time to read, and reading more books, by far, than I learned anything useful from, except, of course, that some very tedious gentlemen have written books." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135271-to-hurt-is-as-human-as-to-breathe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 20:24:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135271-to-hurt-is-as-human-as-to-breathe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To hurt is as human as to breathe." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12357-i-wish-it-need-not-have-happened-in-my-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 20:32:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12357-i-wish-it-need-not-have-happened-in-my-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish it need not have happened in my time,&quot; said Frodo.
&quot;So do I,&quot; said Gandalf, &quot;and so do all who live to see such times. But that is not for them to decide. All we have to decide is what to do with the time that is given us." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97289-from-that-time-on-the-world-was-hers-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 20:37:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Betty Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97289-from-that-time-on-the-world-was-hers-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From that time on, the world was hers for the reading. She would never be lonely again, never miss the lack of intimate friends. Books became her friends and there was one for every mood. There was poetry for quiet companionship. There was adventure when she tired of quiet hours. There would be love stories when she came into adolescence and when she wanted to feel a closeness to someone she could read a biography. On that day when she first knew she could read, she made a vow to read one book a day as long as she lived." -- Betty Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 00:37:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the world were merely seductive, that would be easy. If it were merely challenging, that would be no problem. But I arise in the morning torn between a desire to improve the world and a desire to enjoy the world. This makes it hard to plan the day." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1776-remember-if-the-time-should-come-when-you-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2010 20:11:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1776-remember-if-the-time-should-come-when-you-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember, if the time should come when you have to make a choice between what is right and what is easy, remember what happened to a boy who was good, and kind, and brave, because he strayed across the path of Lord Voldemort.  Remember Cedric Diggory." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41504-our-truest-response-to-the-irrationality-of-the-world-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 14:57:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41504-our-truest-response-to-the-irrationality-of-the-world-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our truest response to the irrationality of the world is to paint or sing or write, for only in such response do we find truth." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121089-i-cannot-remember-a-time-when-i-was-not-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 13:33:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Eudora Welty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121089-i-cannot-remember-a-time-when-i-was-not-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot remember a time when I was not in love with them--with the books themselves, cover and binding and the paper they were printed on, with their smell and their weight and with their possession in my arms, captured and carried off to myself." -- Eudora Welty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135126-the-point-of-the-resurrection-is-that-the-present-bodily-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2010 22:29:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by N.T. Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135126-the-point-of-the-resurrection-is-that-the-present-bodily-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The point of the resurrection…is that the present bodily life is not valueless just because it will die…What you do with your body in the present matters because God has a great future in store for it…What you do in the present—by painting, preaching, singing, sewing, praying, teaching, building hospitals, digging wells, campaigning for justice, writing poems, caring for the needy, loving your neighbor as yourself—will last into God's future. These activities are not simply ways of making the present life a little less beastly, a little more bearable, until the day when we leave it behind altogether (as the hymn so mistakenly puts it…). They are part of what we may call building for God's kingdom." -- N.T. Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9748-no-long-term-marriage-is-made-easily-and-there-have-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 00:37:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9748-no-long-term-marriage-is-made-easily-and-there-have-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No long-term marriage is made easily, and there have been times when I've been so angry or so hurt that I thought my love would never recover. And then, in the midst of near despair, something has happened beneath the surface. A bright little flashing fish of hope has flicked silver fins and the water is bright and suddenly I am returned to a state of love again — till next time. I've learned that there will always be a next time, and that I will submerge in darkness and misery, but that I won't stay submerged. And each time something has been learned under the waters; something has been gained; and a new kind of love has grown. The best I can ask for is that this love, which has been built on countless failures, will continue to grow. I can say no more than that this is mystery, and gift, and that somehow or other, through grace, our failures can be redeemed and blessed." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314245-in-the-sphere-of-religion-as-in-other-spheres-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 17:48:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by J. Gresham Machen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314245-in-the-sphere-of-religion-as-in-other-spheres-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the sphere of religion, as in other spheres, the things about which men are agreed are apt to be the things that are least worth holding; the really important things are the things about which men will fight." -- J. Gresham Machen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314246-from-the-beginning-christianity-was-certainly-a-way-of-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 17:52:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by J. Gresham Machen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314246-from-the-beginning-christianity-was-certainly-a-way-of-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From the beginning, Christianity was certainly a way of life; the salvation that it offered was a salvation from sin, and salvation from sin appeared not merely in a blessed hope but also in an immediate moral change. The early Christians, to the astonishment of their neighbors, lived a strange new kind of life—a life of honesty, of purity and of unselfishness. And from the Christian community all other types of life were excluded in the strictest way. From the beginning Christianity was certainly a life.

But how was the life produced? It might conceivably have been produced by exhortation. That method had often been tried in the ancient world; in the Hellenistic age there were many wandering preachers who told men how they ought to live. But such exhortation proved to be powerless. Although the ideals of the Cynic and Stoic preachers were high, these preachers never succeeded in transforming society. The strange thing about Christianity was that it adopted an entirely different method. It transformed the lives of men not by appealing to the human will, but by telling a story; not by exhortation, but by the narration of an event. It is no wonder that such a method seemed strange. Could anything be more impractical than the attempt to influence conduct by rehearsing events concerning the death of a religious teacher? That is what Paul called &quot;the foolishness of the message.&quot; It seemed foolish to the ancient world, and it seems foolish to liberal preachers today. But the strange thing is that it works. The effects of it appear even in this world. Where the most eloquent exhortation fails, the simple story of an event succeeds; the lives of men are transformed by a piece of news." -- J. Gresham Machen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316543-you-mustn-t-wish-for-another-life-you-mustn-t-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 10:34:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316543-you-mustn-t-wish-for-another-life-you-mustn-t-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You mustn’t wish for another life. You mustn’t want to be somebody else. What you must do is this:
“Rejoice evermore. 
Pray without ceasing.
 In everything give thanks.” 
I am not all the way capable of so much, but those are the right instructions." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3670-it-does-not-do-to-dwell-on-dreams-and-forget</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 14:00:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3670-it-does-not-do-to-dwell-on-dreams-and-forget]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It does not do to dwell on dreams and forget to live." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390853-redemption-transformation--god-how-she-wanted-these-things-every-day-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 14:19:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Jennifer Egan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390853-redemption-transformation--god-how-she-wanted-these-things-every-day-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Redemption, transformation--God how she wanted these things. Every day, every minute. Didn't everyone?" -- Jennifer Egan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470691-for-most-of-my-life-i-have-struggled-to-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 18:56:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470691-for-most-of-my-life-i-have-struggled-to-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For most of my life I have struggled to find God, to know God, to love God. I have tried hard to follow the guidelines of the spiritual life—pray always, work for others, read the Scriptures—and to avoid the many temptations to dissipate myself. I have failed many times but always tried again, even when I was close to despair.

Now I wonder whether I have sufficiently realized that during all this time God has been trying to find me, to know me, and to love me. The question is not “How am I to find God?” but “How am I to let myself be found by him?” The question is not “How am I to know God?” but “How am I to let myself be known by God?” And, finally, the question is not “How am I to love God?” but “How am I to let myself be loved by God?” God is looking into the distance for me, trying to find me, and longing to bring me home." -- Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470692-resentment-and-gratitude-cannot-coexist-since-resentment-blocks-the-perception</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 18:56:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470692-resentment-and-gratitude-cannot-coexist-since-resentment-blocks-the-perception]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Resentment and gratitude cannot coexist, since resentment blocks the perception and experience of life as a gift. My resentment tells me that I don't receive what I deserve. It always manifests itself in envy." -- Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1338-those-who-find-ugly-meanings-in-beautiful-things-are-corrupt</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 23:45:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1338-those-who-find-ugly-meanings-in-beautiful-things-are-corrupt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who find ugly meanings in beautiful things are corrupt without being charming. This is a fault. Those who find beautiful meanings in beautiful things are the cultivated. For these there is hope. They are the elect to whom beautiful things mean only Beauty. There is no such thing as a moral or an immoral book. Books are well written, or badly written. That is all." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14337-any-word-you-have-to-hunt-for-in-a-thesaurus</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 23:47:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14337-any-word-you-have-to-hunt-for-in-a-thesaurus]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any word you have to hunt for in a thesaurus is the wrong word. There are no exceptions to this rule." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21259-in-the-case-of-good-books-the-point-is-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 09:59:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Mortimer J. Adler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21259-in-the-case-of-good-books-the-point-is-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the case of good books, the point is not to see how many of them you can get through, but rather how many can get through to you." -- Mortimer J. Adler]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
