<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/180523-glenda-standish]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/180523-glenda-standish" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 10:54:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/168344-when-we-are-young-the-words-are-scattered-all-around</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 10:54:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Glenda add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/168344-when-we-are-young-the-words-are-scattered-all-around]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we are young, the words are scattered all around us. As they are assembled by experience, so also are we, sentence by sentence, until the story takes shape." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377070-old-love-middle-love-the-kind-of-love-that-knows</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 10:54:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Glenda add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377070-old-love-middle-love-the-kind-of-love-that-knows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Old love, middle love, the kind of love that knows itself and knows that nothing lasts, is a desperate shared wildness." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/288556-to-day-i-think-only-with-scents---scents-dead-leaves</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2013 11:18:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Glenda add a quote by Edward Thomas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/288556-to-day-i-think-only-with-scents---scents-dead-leaves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To-day I think
Only with scents, - scents dead leaves yield,
And bracken, and wild carrot's seed,
And the square mustard field;

Odours that rise
When the spade wounds the root of tree,
Rose, currant, raspberry, or goutweed,
Rhubarb or celery;

The smoke's smell, too,
Flowing from where a bonfire burns
The dead, the waste, the dangerous,
And all to sweetness turns.

It is enough
To smell, to crumble the dark earth,
While the robin sings over again
Sad songs of Autumn mirth.&quot;

- A poem called DIGGING." -- Edward Thomas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221344-i-ate-breakfast-in-the-kitchen-by-candle-light-and-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2013 11:18:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Glenda add a quote by Jean Webster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221344-i-ate-breakfast-in-the-kitchen-by-candle-light-and-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I ate breakfast in the kitchen by candle-light, and then drove the five miles to the station through the most glorious October colouring. The sun came up on the way, and the swamp maples and dogwood glowed crimson and orange and the stone walls and cornfields sparkled with hoar frost; the air was keen and clear and full of promise. I &lt;em&gt;knew&lt;/em&gt; something was going to happen. " -- Jean Webster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297593-you-are-not-a-mistake-you-are-not-a-problem</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 08:27:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Glenda add a quote by Geneen Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297593-you-are-not-a-mistake-you-are-not-a-problem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are not a mistake.  You are not a problem to be solved.  But you won't discover this until you are willing to stop banging your head against the wall of shaming and caging and fearing yourself. (p. 84)" -- Geneen Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297594-when-you-ignore-your-belly-you-become-homeless-you-spend</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 08:28:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Glenda add a quote by Geneen Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297594-when-you-ignore-your-belly-you-become-homeless-you-spend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you ignore your belly, you become homeless.  You spend your life trying to erase your own existence.  Apologizing for yourself.  Feeling like a ghost.  Eating to take up space, eating to give yourself the feeling that you have weight here, you belong here, you are allowed to be yourself -- but never quite believing it because you don't sense yourself directly.

. . . I started teaching a simple belly meditation in which I asked people to become aware of sensations in their belly (numbness and emptiness count as sensations).  Every time their mind wandered . . . I asked them to begin counting their breaths so they could anchor their concentration.  Starting with the number one and saying it on the out breath, they'd count to seven and begin again.  If they were able to stay concentrated on the sensations in their belly centers, they didn't need to use counting as a concentration anchor.

. . . you begin the process of bringing yourself back to your body, to your belly, to your breath because they -- not the mind medleys -- are here now.  And it is only here, only now that you can make a decision to eat or not eat.  To occupy your own body or to vacate your arms and your legs while still breathing and go through your days as a walking head.  

. . . Meditation is a tool to shake yourself awake.  A way to discover what you love.  A practice to return yourself to your body when the mind medleys threaten to usurp your sanity." -- Geneen Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
