<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/181464-aimee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/181464-aimee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 17:00:50 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5722-anyway-i-keep-picturing-all-these-little-kids-playing-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 17:00:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aimee add a quote by J. D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5722-anyway-i-keep-picturing-all-these-little-kids-playing-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyway, I keep picturing all these little kids playing some game in this big field of rye and all.  Thousands of little kids, and nobody's around - nobody big, I mean - except me.  And I'm standing on the edge of some crazy cliff.  What I have to do, I have to catch everybody if they start to go over the cliff - I mean if they're running and they don't look where they're going I have to come out from somewhere and catch them.  That's all I do all day.  I'd just be the catcher in the rye and all.  I know it's crazy, but that's the only thing I'd really like to be." -- J. D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15891-there-is-something-beautiful-about-a-billion-stars-held-steady</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 17:03:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aimee add a quote by Donald Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15891-there-is-something-beautiful-about-a-billion-stars-held-steady]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is something beautiful about a billion stars held steady by a God who knows what He is doing. (They hang there, the stars, like notes on a page of music, free-form verse, silent mysteries swirling in the blue like jazz.) And as I lay there, it occurred to me that God is up there somewhere. Of course, I had always known He was, but this time I felt it, I realized it, the way a person realizes they are hungry or thirsty. The knowledge of God seeped out of my brain and into my heart. I imagined Him looking down on this earth, half angry because His beloved mankind had cheated on Him, had committed adultery, and yet hopelessly in love with her, drunk with love for her." -- Donald Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119297-i-want-to-keep-walking-away-from-the-person-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 17:04:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aimee add a quote by Donald Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119297-i-want-to-keep-walking-away-from-the-person-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to keep walking away from the person I was a moment ago, because a mind was made fo figure things out, not to read the same page recurrently." -- Donald Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
