<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/181878-natalie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/181878-natalie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 08:50:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246360-when-the-rain-pours-down-especially-we-have-long-hours</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 08:50:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246360-when-the-rain-pours-down-especially-we-have-long-hours]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the rain pours down especially, we have long hours of captivity, in which my sisters determinedly grow bored. But are there books, books there are! Rattling words on the page calling my eyes to dance with them. Everyone else will finish with the singular plowing through, and Ada still has discoveries ahead and behind. " -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246361-the-christian-community-therefore-is-that-community-that-freely-becomes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 08:50:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by James H. Cone]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246361-the-christian-community-therefore-is-that-community-that-freely-becomes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Christian community, therefore, is that community that freely becomes oppressed, because they know that Jesus himself has defined humanity's liberation in the context of what happens to the little ones. Christians join the cause of the oppressed in the fight for justice not because of some philosophical principle of &quot;the Good&quot; or because of a religious feeling of sympathy for people in prison. Sympathy does not change the structures of injustice. The authentic identity of Christians with the poor is found in the claim which the Jesus-encounter lays upon their own life-style, a claim that connects the word &quot;Christian&quot; with the liberation of the poor. Christians fight not for humanity in general but for themselves and out of their love for concrete human beings." -- James H. Cone]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246356-at-such-times-a-mortal-knows-just-enough-of-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 08:50:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246356-at-such-times-a-mortal-knows-just-enough-of-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At such times, a mortal knows just enough of what his mind is doing, to form some glimmering conception of its mighty powers, its bounding from earth and spurning time and space, when freed from the restraint of its corporeal associate." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369290-whenever-we-engage-in-consumption-or-production-patterns-which-take</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:02:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Vandana Shiva]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369290-whenever-we-engage-in-consumption-or-production-patterns-which-take]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever we engage in consumption or production patterns which take more than we need, we are engaging in violence." -- Vandana Shiva]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3897-listen-to-live-is-to-be-marked-to-live-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:02:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3897-listen-to-live-is-to-be-marked-to-live-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen. To live is to be marked. To live is to change, to acquire the words of a story, and that is the only celebration we mortals really know. In perfect stillness, frankly, I've only found sorrow." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246357-her-life-had-been-altogether-artificial-she-had-always-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:02:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Ouida]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246357-her-life-had-been-altogether-artificial-she-had-always-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her life had been altogether artificial; she had always been a great garden lily in a hot-house, she had never known what it was to be blown by a fresh breeze on a sun-swept moorland like a heather flower. The hot-house shelters from all chills and is full of perfume, but you can see no horizon from it; that alone is the joy of the moorland." -- Ouida]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226267-guilt-is-not-a-response-to-anger-it-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2011 20:19:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226267-guilt-is-not-a-response-to-anger-it-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Guilt is not a response to anger; it is a response to one’s own actions or lack of action.  If it leads to change then it can be useful, since it is then no longer guilt but the beginning of knowledge.  Yet all too often, guilt is just another name for impotence, for defensiveness destructive of communication; it becomes a device to protect ignorance and the continuation of things the way they are, the ultimate protection for changelessness." -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/510797-and-my-grandfather-was-forever-knocked-into-that-middle-place</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 22:03:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/510797-and-my-grandfather-was-forever-knocked-into-that-middle-place]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And my grandfather... was forever knocked into that middle place, unable to worship a God in whose existence he could not wholly disbelieve. Permanent alteration: a hole." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386603-in-this-here-place-we-flesh-flesh-that-weeps-laughs</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2014 17:34:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386603-in-this-here-place-we-flesh-flesh-that-weeps-laughs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In this here place, we flesh; flesh that weeps, laughs; flesh that dances on bare feet in grass. Love it. Love it hard. Yonder they do not love your flesh. They despise it. They don't love your eyes; they'd just as soon pick em out. No more do they love the skin on your back. Yonder they flay it. And O my people they do not love your hands. Those they only use, tie, bind, chop off and leave empty. Love your hands! Love them. Raise them up and kiss them. Touch others with them, pat them together, stroke them on your face 'cause they don't love that either. You got to love it, you! And no, they ain't in love with your mouth. Yonder, out there, they will see it broken and break it again. What you say out of it they will not heed. What you scream from it they do not hear. What you put into it to nourish your body they will snatch away and give you leavins instead. No, they don't love your mouth. You got to love it. This is flesh I'm talking about here. Flesh that needs to be loved. Feet that need to rest and to dance; backs that need support; shoulders that need arms, strong arms I'm telling you. And O my people, out yonder, hear me, they do not love your neck unnoosed and straight. So love your neck; put a hand on it, grace it, stroke it and hold it up. and all your inside parts that they'd just as soon slop for hogs, you got to love them. The dark, dark liver--love it, love it and the beat and beating heart, love that too. More than eyes or feet. More than lungs that have yet to draw free air. More than your life-holding womb and your life-giving private parts, hear me now, love your heart. For this is the prize." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
