<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/182924-miranda]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/182924-miranda" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 13:56:11 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5622-as-he-watched-joe-stand-blazing-on-the-fire-escape</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 13:56:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Miranda add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5622-as-he-watched-joe-stand-blazing-on-the-fire-escape]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As he watched Joe stand, blazing, on the fire escape, Sammy felt an ache in his chest that turned out to be, as so often occurs when memory and desire conjoin with a transient effect of weather, the pang of creation.  The desire he felt, watching Joe, was unquestionably physical, but in the sense that Sammy wanted to inhabit the body of his cousin, not possess it.  It was, in part, a longing--common enough among the inventors of heroes--to be someone else; to be more than the result of two hundred regimens and scenarios and self-improvement campaigns that always ran afoul of his perennial inability to locate an actual self to be improved.  Joe Kavalier had an air of competence, of faith in his own abilities, that Sammy, by means of constant effort over the whole of his life, had finally learned only to fake.  " -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12623-the-ordinary-sized-stuff-which-is-our-lives-the-things-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 17:59:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Miranda add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12623-the-ordinary-sized-stuff-which-is-our-lives-the-things-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The ordinary-sized stuff which is our lives, the things people write poetry about—clouds—daffodils—waterfalls—what happens in a cup of coffee when the cream goes in—these things are full of mystery, as mysterious to us as the heavens were to the Greeks." -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116915-we-shed-as-we-pick-up-like-travellers-who-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 17:59:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Miranda add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116915-we-shed-as-we-pick-up-like-travellers-who-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We shed as we pick up, like travellers who must carry everything in their arms, and what we let fall will be picked up by those behind. The procession is very long and life is very short. We die on the march. But there is nothing outside the march so nothing can be lost to it. The missing plays of Sophocles will turn up piece by piece, or be written again in another language. Ancient cures for diseases will reveal themselves once more. Mathematical discoveries glimpsed and lost to view will have their time again. You do not suppose, my lady, that if all of Archimedes had been hiding in the great library of Alexandria, we would be at a loss for a corkscrew?" -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183413-the-unpredictable-and-the-predetermined-unfold-together-to-make-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 18:00:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Miranda add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183413-the-unpredictable-and-the-predetermined-unfold-together-to-make-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The unpredictable and the predetermined unfold together to make everything the way it is." -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706651-it-s-the-wanting-to-know-that-makes-us-matter</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 18:00:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Miranda add a quote by Tom Stoppard ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706651-it-s-the-wanting-to-know-that-makes-us-matter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's the wanting to know that makes us matter." -- Tom Stoppard ]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
