<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/184218-maggie-campbell]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/184218-maggie-campbell" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2009 14:36:19 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65481-falling-in-love-we-said-i-fell-for-him-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2009 14:36:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maggie add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65481-falling-in-love-we-said-i-fell-for-him-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Falling in love, we said; I fell for him. We were falling women. We believed in it, this downward motion: so lovely, like flying, and yet at the same time so dire, so extreme, so unlikely. God is love, they once said, but we reversed that, and love, like heaven, was always just around the corner. The more difficult it was to love the particular man beside us, the more we believed in Love, abstract and total. We were waiting, always, for the incarnation. That word, made flesh.

And sometimes it happened, for a time. That kind of love comes and goes and is hard to remember afterwards, like pain. You would look at the man one day and you would think, I loved you, and the tense would be past, and you would be filled with a sense of wonder, because it was such an amazing and precarious and dumb thing to have done; and you would know too why your friends had been evasive about it, at the time.

There is a good deal of comfort, now, in remembering this." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100497-what-is-more-humiliating-than-finding-the-object-of-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 16:29:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maggie add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100497-what-is-more-humiliating-than-finding-the-object-of-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is more humiliating than finding the object of your love unworthy?" -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3172-and-i-urge-you-to-please-notice-when-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 16:30:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maggie add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3172-and-i-urge-you-to-please-notice-when-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I urge you to please notice when you are happy, and exclaim or murmur or think at some point, 'If this isn't nice, I don't know what is." -- Kurt Vonnegut Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 16:58:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maggie add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hello babies. Welcome to Earth. It's hot in the summer and cold in the winter. It's round and wet and crowded. On the outside, babies, you've got a hundred years here. There's only one rule that I know of, babies-&quot;God damn it, you've got to be kind." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8574-what-a-terrible-mistake-to-let-go-of-something-wonderful</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 16:59:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maggie add a quote by Miranda July]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8574-what-a-terrible-mistake-to-let-go-of-something-wonderful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a terrible mistake to let go of something wonderful for something real." -- Miranda July]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121812-i-laughed-and-said-life-is-easy-what-i-meant</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 16:59:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maggie add a quote by Miranda July]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121812-i-laughed-and-said-life-is-easy-what-i-meant]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I laughed and said, Life is easy. What I meant was, Life is easy with you here, and when you leave, it will be hard again." -- Miranda July]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 17:06:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maggie add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be patient toward all that is unsolved in your heart and try to love the questions themselves, like locked rooms and like books that are now written in a very foreign tongue. Do not now seek the answers, which cannot be given you because you would not be able to live them. And the point is, to live everything. Live the questions now. Perhaps you will then gradually, without noticing it, live along some distant day into the answer." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209860-she-left-me-the-way-people-leave-a-hotel-room</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 17:09:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maggie add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209860-she-left-me-the-way-people-leave-a-hotel-room]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She left me the way people leave a hotel room. A hotel room is a place to be when you are doing something else. Of itself it is of no consequence to one's major scheme. A hotel room is convenient. But its convenience is limited to the time you need it while you are in that particular town on that particular business; you hope it is comfortable, but prefer, rather, that it be anoymous. It is not, after all, where you live." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
