<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/184603-april]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/184603-april" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 14:55:17 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100637-and-then-i-felt-sad-because-i-realized-that-once</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 14:55:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100637-and-then-i-felt-sad-because-i-realized-that-once]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And then I felt sad because I realized that once people are broken in certain ways, they can't ever be fixed, and this is something nobody ever tells you when you are young and it never fails to surprise you as you grow older as you see the people in your life break one by one. You wonder when your turn is going to be, or if it's already happened." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65737-i-don-t-deserve-a-soul-yet-i-still-have-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 14:55:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65737-i-don-t-deserve-a-soul-yet-i-still-have-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't deserve a soul, yet I still have one. I know because it hurts." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148090-when-you-re-young-you-always-feel-that-life-hasn-t-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 14:57:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148090-when-you-re-young-you-always-feel-that-life-hasn-t-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you're young, you always feel that life hasn't yet begun—that &quot;life&quot; is always scheduled to begin next week, next month, next year, after the holidays—whenever.  But then suddenly you're old and the scheduled life didn't arrive.  You find yourself asking, 'Well then, exactly what was it I was having—that interlude—the scrambly madness—all that time I had before?" -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65736-a-few-years-ago-it-dawned-on-me-that-everybody</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 14:59:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65736-a-few-years-ago-it-dawned-on-me-that-everybody]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A few years ago it dawned on me that everybody past a certain age ... pretty much constantly dreams of being able to escape from their lives. They don't want to be who they are any more. They want out. This list includes Thurston Howell the Third, Ann-Margret, the cat members of Rent, Václav Havel, space shuttle astronauts and Snuffleupagus. It's universal." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96280-what-else-i-also-believe-that-if-someone-comes-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 14:59:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96280-what-else-i-also-believe-that-if-someone-comes-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What else? I also believe that if someone comes up behind you on the freeway and flashes their lights to get you to move into the slow lane, they deserve whatever punishment you dole out to them. I promptly slow down and drive at the same speed as the car beside me so that I can punish Speed Racer for his impertinence.

Actually, it’s not the impertinence I’m punishing him for, it’s that he let other people know what he wanted.

Speed Racer, my friend, never ever let people know what you want. Because if you do, you might as well send them engraved invitations saying, “Hi, this is what I want you to prevent me from ever having." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182270-after-my-brush-with-the-suicidal-impulse-i-listen-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 15:22:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182270-after-my-brush-with-the-suicidal-impulse-i-listen-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After my brush with the suicidal impulse, I listen with new ears to others when they
speak on the subject. I think there are people who were born with that little door open, and they
have to go through life knowing that they might jump through it at any moment." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265802-it-hit-him-that-his-own-form-of-loneliness-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 15:24:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265802-it-hit-him-that-his-own-form-of-loneliness-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It hit him that his own form of loneliness was a luxury, one as chosen and as paid for as three weeks in Kenya's velds or a cherry red Ferrari. Real loneliness wasn't something an assistant scoped out and got a good price on. Real loneliness was smothering and it stank of hopelessness." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265804-if-he-d-learned-one-thing-while-he-d-been-away-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 15:25:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265804-if-he-d-learned-one-thing-while-he-d-been-away-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If he'd learned one thing while he'd been away, it was that loneliness is the most taboo subject in the world. Forget sex or politics or religion. Or even failure. Loneliness is what clears out a room." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265806-imagine-you-are-sitting-down-in-a-chair-and-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 15:29:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265806-imagine-you-are-sitting-down-in-a-chair-and-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine you are sitting down in a chair and on a screen before you you are shown a bloody, ripping film of yourself undergoing surgery.  The surgery saved your life.  It was pivotal in making you you.  But you don't remember it.  Or do you?  Do we understand the events that make us who we are?  Do we ever understand the factors that make us do the things we do?
    When we sleep at night - when we walk across a field and see a tree full of sleeping birds - when we tell small lies to our friends - when we make love - what acts of surgery are happening to our souls - what damage and healing and shock are we going through that we will never be able to fathom?  What films are generated that we will never be shown?" -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265805-imagine-you-re-a-forty-year-old-richard-hamilton-said-to-me-around</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 15:29:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265805-imagine-you-re-a-forty-year-old-richard-hamilton-said-to-me-around]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine you're a forty-year-old, Richard,&quot; Hamilton said to me around this time, while working as a salesman at a Radio Shack in Lynn Valley,&quot;and suddenly somebody comes up to you saying, 'Hi, I'd like you to meet Kevin.  Kevin is eighteen and will be making all of your career decisions for you.'  I'd be flipped out.  Wouldn't you?  But that's what life is all about - some eighteen-year-old  kid making your big decisions for you that stick for a lifetime.&quot; He shuddered." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265807-maybe-people-with-weird-haircuts-are-like-structures-that-become</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 15:29:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265807-maybe-people-with-weird-haircuts-are-like-structures-that-become]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe people with weird haircuts are like structures that become interesting only after being wrecked - Florida ranch houses half-fallen into sinkholes; bankrupt malls; civilizations after a nuclear war.  I feel a warm tragic glow knowing I may be of interest to the world only once I have been destroyed." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 15:34:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11285-god-does-not-play-dice-with-the-universe-he-plays</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 15:35:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11285-god-does-not-play-dice-with-the-universe-he-plays]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God does not play dice with the universe; He plays an ineffable game of His own devising, which might be compared, from the perspective of any of the other players [i.e. everybody], to being involved in an obscure and complex variant of poker in a pitch-dark room, with blank cards, for infinite stakes, with a Dealer who won't tell you the rules, and who &lt;i&gt;smiles all the time&lt;/i&gt;." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21556-he-had-noticed-that-events-were-cowards-they-didn-t-occur</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 15:36:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21556-he-had-noticed-that-events-were-cowards-they-didn-t-occur]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He had noticed that events were cowards: they didn't occur singly, but instead they would run in packs and leap out at him all at once." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174610-there-are-four-simple-ways-for-the-observant-to-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 15:39:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174610-there-are-four-simple-ways-for-the-observant-to-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are four simple ways for the observant to tell Mr. Croup and Mr. Vandemar apart: first, Mr. Vandemar is two and a half heads taller than Mr. Croup; second, Mr. Croup has eyes of a faded china blue, while Mr. Vandemar's eyes are brown; third, while Mr. Vandemar fashioned the rings he wears on his right hand out of the skulls of four ravens, Mr. Croup has no obvious jewelery; fourth, Mr. Croup likes words, while Mr. Vandemar is always hungry. Also, they look nothing at all alike." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234634-what-should-i-believe-thought-shadow-and-the-voice-came</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 15:45:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234634-what-should-i-believe-thought-shadow-and-the-voice-came]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What should I believe? thought Shadow, and the voice came back to him from somewhere deep beneath the world, in a bass rumble: Believe everything." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223060-some-people-are-like-slinkies-they-aren-t-really-good-for-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 18:39:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Patricia Briggs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223060-some-people-are-like-slinkies-they-aren-t-really-good-for-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people are like Slinkies.They aren't really good for anything, but they still bring a smile to my face when I push them down a flight of stairs." -- Patricia Briggs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83017-i-like-to-see-people-reunited-i-like-to-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 15:32:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83017-i-like-to-see-people-reunited-i-like-to-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like to see people reunited, I like to see people run to each other, I like the kissing and the crying, I like the impatience, the stories that the mouth can't tell fast enough, the ears that aren't big enough, the eyes that can't take in all of the change, I like the hugging, the bringing together, the end of missing someone." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311576-your-personality---the-real-you-inside---was-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 15:32:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Scott Westerfeld]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311576-your-personality---the-real-you-inside---was-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your personality - the real you inside - was the price of beauty." -- Scott Westerfeld]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103252-i-regret-that-it-takes-a-life-to-learn-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 12:58:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103252-i-regret-that-it-takes-a-life-to-learn-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I regret that it takes a life to learn how to live." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43014-it-s-the-tragedy-of-loving-you-can-t-love-anything-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 12:59:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43014-it-s-the-tragedy-of-loving-you-can-t-love-anything-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's the tragedy of loving, you can't love anything more than something you miss." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 19:23:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are bored and disgusted by politics and don't bother to vote, you are in effect voting for the entrenched Establishments of the two major parties, who please rest assured are not dumb, and who are keenly aware that it is in their interests to keep you disgusted and bored and cynical and to give you every possible reason to stay at home doing one-hitters and watching MTV on primary day.  By all means stay home if you want, but don't bullshit yourself that you're not voting.  In reality, there is &lt;i&gt;no such thing as not voting:&lt;/i&gt; you either vote by voting, or you vote by staying home and tacitly doubling the value of some Diehard's vote." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54814-tradition-means-giving-votes-to-the-most-obscure-of-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 19:24:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54814-tradition-means-giving-votes-to-the-most-obscure-of-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tradition means giving votes to the most obscure of all classes, our ancestors. It is the democracy of the dead. Tradition refuses to submit to the small and arrogant oligarchy of those who merely happen to be walking about." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74402-always-vote-for-principle-though-you-may-vote-alone-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 19:27:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by John Quincy Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74402-always-vote-for-principle-though-you-may-vote-alone-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Always vote for principle, though you may vote alone, 
and you may cherish the sweetest reflection that 
your vote is never lost." -- John Quincy Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170148-the-woods-were-my-ritalin-nature-calmed-me-focused-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 17:53:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Richard Louv]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170148-the-woods-were-my-ritalin-nature-calmed-me-focused-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The woods were my Ritalin.  Nature calmed me, focused me, and yet excited my senses." -- Richard Louv]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383634-not-that-there-wasn-t-still-plenty-of-subduing-to-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 18:34:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Sarah Vowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383634-not-that-there-wasn-t-still-plenty-of-subduing-to-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not that there wasn't still plenty of subduing to do here in North America.  &quot;Even within our own limits, the savage still lights his death fires, to appease the wrath of an idol,&quot; he points out.  What's worse, to the &quot;north, there is an immense region of palpable darkness.&quot; (Hi, Canada!)" -- Sarah Vowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706150-the-air-has-that-bracing-autumnal-bite-so-that-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 18:36:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Sarah Vowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706150-the-air-has-that-bracing-autumnal-bite-so-that-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...the air has that bracing autumnal bite so that all you want to do is bob for apples or hang a witch or something." -- Sarah Vowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/591039-i-m-a-slow-walker-but-i-never-walk-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 10:55:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/591039-i-m-a-slow-walker-but-i-never-walk-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm a slow walker but I never walk back." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485442-as-he-read-i-fell-in-love-the-way-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 09:35:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485442-as-he-read-i-fell-in-love-the-way-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As he read, I fell in love the way you fall asleep: slowly, and then all at once." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485711-my-thoughts-are-stars-i-cannot-fathom-into-constellations</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 09:35:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485711-my-thoughts-are-stars-i-cannot-fathom-into-constellations]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My thoughts are stars I cannot fathom into constellations." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
