<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/186853-melody]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/186853-melody" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 03:56:49 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67812-we-use-words-to-understand-each-other-and-even-sometimes</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 03:56:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by José Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67812-we-use-words-to-understand-each-other-and-even-sometimes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We use words to understand each other and even, sometimes, to find each other." -- José Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46362-i-always-advise-people-never-to-give-advice</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 10:30:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46362-i-always-advise-people-never-to-give-advice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I always advise people never to give advice." -- P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28623-read-not-to-contradict-and-confute-nor-to-believe-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 15:44:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by Francis Bacon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28623-read-not-to-contradict-and-confute-nor-to-believe-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Read not to contradict and confute; nor to believe and take for granted; nor to find talk and discourse; but to weigh and consider.  Some books are to be tasted, others to be swallowed, and some few to be chewed and digested: that is, some books are to be read only in parts, others to be read, but not curiously, and some few to be read wholly, and with diligence and attention." -- Francis Bacon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95718-focusing-your-life-solely-on-making-a-buck-shows-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 11:25:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by Barack Obama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95718-focusing-your-life-solely-on-making-a-buck-shows-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Focusing your life solely on making a buck shows a certain poverty of ambition. It asks too little of yourself. Because it's only when you hitch your wagon to something larger than yourself that you realize your true potential." -- Barack Obama]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39612-pierre-was-right-when-he-said-that-one-must-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 09:02:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39612-pierre-was-right-when-he-said-that-one-must-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pierre was right when he said that one must believe in the possibility of happiness in order to be happy, and I now believe in it. Let the dead bury the dead, but while I'm alive, I must live and be happy." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54761-if-you-d-ever-had-a-grown-up-daughter-you-d-know-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2010 03:30:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by William Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54761-if-you-d-ever-had-a-grown-up-daughter-you-d-know-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["if you'd ever had a grown-up daughter you'd know that by comparison a bucking steer is easy to manage.  And as to knowing what goes on inside her - well, it's much better to pretend you're the simple, innocent old fool she almost certainly takes you for." -- William Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103081-people-sometimes-sneer-at-those-who-run-every-day-claiming</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2010 05:36:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103081-people-sometimes-sneer-at-those-who-run-every-day-claiming]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People sometimes sneer at those who run every day, claiming they'll go to any length to live longer. But don't think that's the reason most people run. Most runners run not because they want to live longer, but because they want to live life to the fullest. If you're going to while away the years, it's far better to live them with clear goals and fully alive then in a fog, and I believe running helps you to do that. Exerting yourself to the fullest within your individual limits: that's the essence of running, and a metaphor for life — and for me, for writing as whole. I believe many runners would agree" -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487821-i-ll-tell-you-what-s-wrong-with-dumb-shit-patriotism--it-s-delusional-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 05:09:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487821-i-ll-tell-you-what-s-wrong-with-dumb-shit-patriotism--it-s-delusional-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'll tell you what's wrong with dumb-shit patriotism--it's delusional! It signifies nothing but the American need to win" -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154-isn-t-it-pretty-to-think-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 06:31:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154-isn-t-it-pretty-to-think-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't it pretty to think so." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5539-a-few-light-taps-upon-the-pane-made-him-turn</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 05:06:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5539-a-few-light-taps-upon-the-pane-made-him-turn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A few light taps upon the pane made him turn to the window. It had begun to snow again. He watched sleepily the flakes, silver and dark, falling obliquely against the lamplight. The time had come for him to set out on his journey westward. Yes, the newspapers were right: snow was general all over Ireland. It was falling on every part of the dark central plain, on the treeless hills, falling softly upon the Bog of Allen and, farther westward, softly falling into the dark mutinous Shannon waves. It was falling, too, upon every part of the lonely churchyard on the hill where Michael Furey lay buried. It lay thickly drifted on the crooked crosses and headstones, on the spears of the little gate, on the barren thorns. His soul swooned slowly as he heard the snow falling faintly through the universe and faintly falling, like the descent of their last end, upon all the living and the dead." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237620-i-think-we-ought-to-read-only-the-kind-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 11:50:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237620-i-think-we-ought-to-read-only-the-kind-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think we ought to read only the kind of books that wound or stab us. If the book we're reading doesn't wake us up with a blow to the head, what are we reading for? So that it will make us happy, as you write? Good Lord, we would be happy precisely if we had no books, and the kind of books that make us happy are the kind we could write ourselves if we had to. But we need books that affect us like a disaster, that grieve us deeply, like the death of someone we loved more than ourselves, like being banished into forests far from everyone, like a suicide. A book must be the axe for the frozen sea within us. That is my belief." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243621-we-need-the-books-that-affect-us-like-a-disaster</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 12:12:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243621-we-need-the-books-that-affect-us-like-a-disaster]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We need the books that affect us like a disaster, that grieve us deeply, like the death of someone we loved more than ourselves, like being banished into forests far from everyone, like a suicide. A book must be the axe for the frozen sea inside us." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101502-the-plain-fact-is-that-the-planet-does-not-need</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2013 08:31:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by David W. Orr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101502-the-plain-fact-is-that-the-planet-does-not-need]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The plain fact is that the planet does not need more successful people. But it does desperately need more peacemakers, healers, restorers, storytellers, and lovers of every kind. It needs people who live well in their places. It needs people of moral courage willing to join the fight to make the world habitable and humane. And these qualities have little to do with success as we have defined it." -- David W. Orr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/890183-in-other-words-there-is-something-otherworldly-about-our-existence</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 07:50:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by Guy Murchie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/890183-in-other-words-there-is-something-otherworldly-about-our-existence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In other words there is something otherworldly about our existence here --something more than matter, more than the body and mind we have been discussing -- in short, something fundamentally and profoundly abstract. And I mention this aspect because it is not at all obvious, indeed scarcely notices by the great majority of us as we go about our daily lives." -- Guy Murchie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 23:27:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980938-because-i-don-t-care-what-anyone-says-or-how-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 08:28:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980938-because-i-don-t-care-what-anyone-says-or-how-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because I don’t care what anyone says or how often or winningly they say it: no one will ever, ever be able to persuade me that life is some awesome, rewarding treat. Because, here’s the truth: life is a catastrophe. The basic fact of existence – of walking around trying to feed ourselves and find friends and whatever else we do – is a catastrophe. Forget all this ridiculous ‘Our Town’ nonsense everyone talks: the miracle of a newborn babe, the joy of one simple blossom, Life You Are Too Wonderful To Grasp, &amp;c. For me – and I’ll keep repeating it doggedly till I die, till I fall over on my ungrateful nihilistic face and am too weak to say it: better never born, than born into this cesspool. Sinkhole of hospital beds, coffins, and broken hearts. No release, no appeal, no “do-overs” to employ a favored phrase of Xandra’s, no way forward but age and loss, and no way out but death." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
