<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/187016-will-humphreys]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/187016-will-humphreys" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 18:11:24 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99358-i-therefore-hate-the-corrupt-slaveholding-women-whipping-cradle-plundering-partial-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 18:11:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Will add a quote by Frederick Douglass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99358-i-therefore-hate-the-corrupt-slaveholding-women-whipping-cradle-plundering-partial-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...I therefore hate the corrupt, slaveholding, women-whipping, cradle-plundering, partial and hypocritical Christianity of the land... I look upon it as the climax of all misnomers, the boldest of all frauds, and the grossest of all libels. Never was there a clearer case of 'stealing the livery of the court of heaven to serve the devil in.' I am filled with unutterable loathing when I contemplate the religious pomp and show, together with the horrible inconsistencies, which every where surround me. We have men-stealers for ministers, women-whippers for missionaries, and cradle-plunderers for church members. The man who wields the blood-clotted cowskin during the week fills the pulpit on Sunday, and claims to be a minister of the meek and lowly Jesus. . . . The slave auctioneer’s bell and the church-going bell chime in with each other, and the bitter cries of the heart-broken slave are drowned in the religious shouts of his pious master. Revivals of religion and revivals in the slave-trade go hand in hand together. The slave prison and the church stand near each other. The clanking of fetters and the rattling of chains in the prison, and the pious psalm and solemn prayer in the church, may be heard at the same time. The dealers in the bodies of men erect their stand in the presence of the pulpit, and they mutually help each other. The dealer gives his blood-stained gold to support the pulpit, and the pulpit, in return, covers his infernal business with the garb of Christianity. Here we have religion and robbery the allies of each other—devils dressed in angels’ robes, and hell presenting the semblance of paradise." -- Frederick Douglass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275273-what-are-your-fees-inquired-guyal-cautiously-i-respond-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 02:11:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Will add a quote by Jack Vance]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275273-what-are-your-fees-inquired-guyal-cautiously-i-respond-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What are your fees?&quot; inquired Guyal cautiously. &quot;I respond to three questions,&quot; stated the augur. &quot;For twenty terces I phrase the answer in clear and actionable language; for ten I use the language of cant, which occasionally admits of ambiguity; for five, I speak a parable which you must interpret as you will; and for one terce, I babble in an unknown tongue." -- Jack Vance]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218257-good-music-always-defeats-bad-luck</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 02:11:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Will add a quote by Jack Vance]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218257-good-music-always-defeats-bad-luck]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good music always defeats bad luck." -- Jack Vance]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
