<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/187043-laura]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/187043-laura" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 09:48:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44544-she-waited-for-the-train-to-pass-then-she-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 09:48:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44544-she-waited-for-the-train-to-pass-then-she-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She waited for the train to pass. Then she said, &quot;I sometimes think that people’s hearts are like deep wells. Nobody knows what’s at the bottom. All you can do is imagine by what comes floating to the surface every once in a while." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44904-she-was-good-at-playing-abstract-confusion-in-the-same</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:34:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Clive James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44904-she-was-good-at-playing-abstract-confusion-in-the-same]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was good at playing abstract confusion in the same way that a midget is good at being short." -- Clive James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1146-it-was-about-eleven-o-clock-in-the-morning-mid-october</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 21:10:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Raymond Chandler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1146-it-was-about-eleven-o-clock-in-the-morning-mid-october]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was about eleven o'clock in the morning, mid October, with the sun not shining and a look of hard wet rain in the clearness of the foothills. I was wearing my powder-blue suit, with dark blue shirt, tie and display handkerchief, black brogues, black wool socks with dark little clocks on them. I was neat, clean, shaved and sober, and I didn't care who knew it. I was everything the well-dressed private detective ought to be. I was calling on four million dollars." -- Raymond Chandler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108634-i-really-am-a-pessimist-i-ve-always-felt-that-fascism</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 20:15:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Norman Mailer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108634-i-really-am-a-pessimist-i-ve-always-felt-that-fascism]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I really am a pessimist. I've always felt that fascism is a more natural governmental condition than democracy. Democracy is a grace. It's something essentially splendid because it's not at all routine or automatic. Fascism goes back to our infancy and childhood, where we were always told how to live. We were told, Yes, you may do this; no, you may not do that. So the secret of fascism is that it has this appeal to people whose later lives are not satisfactory." -- Norman Mailer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160756-on-the-girl-s-brown-legs-there-were-many-small-white</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 08:08:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Chris Cleave]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160756-on-the-girl-s-brown-legs-there-were-many-small-white]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the girl's brown legs there were many small white scars. I was thinking, Do those scars cover the whole of you, like the stars and the moons on your dress? I thought that would be pretty too, and I ask you right here please to agree with me that a scar is never ugly. That is what the scar makers want us to think. But you and I, we must make an agreement to defy them. We must see all scars as beauty. Okay? This will be our secret. Because take it from me, a scar does not form on the dying. A scar means, I survived." -- Chris Cleave]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22263-there-is-only-one-way-to-read-which-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2010 20:55:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22263-there-is-only-one-way-to-read-which-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is only one way to read, which is to browse in libraries and bookshops, picking up books that attract you, reading only those, dropping them when they bore you, skipping the parts that drag-and never, never reading anything because you feel you ought, or because it is part of a trend or a movement.  Remember that the book which bores you when you are twenty or thirty will open doors for you when you are forty or fifty-and vise versa.  Don’t read a book out of its right time for you.  " -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70366-i-love-that-name-a-country-named-chad-sounds-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 08:08:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Gary Brecher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70366-i-love-that-name-a-country-named-chad-sounds-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love that name. A country named Chad. Sounds like somebody who lived next door to the Brady Bunch. But if Chad actually lived next door to the Bradys, Greg would be roasting over a slow fire and Marcia would be standing naked on an auction block, because Chad is one of the hungriest, craziest, most desperate places on the planet." -- Gary Brecher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165329-i-love-the-recklessness-of-faith-first-you-leap-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 17:14:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by William Sloane Coffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165329-i-love-the-recklessness-of-faith-first-you-leap-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love the recklessness of faith. First you leap, and then you grow wings." -- William Sloane Coffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22342-men-can-starve-from-a-lack-of-self-realization-as-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2011 14:53:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Richard Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22342-men-can-starve-from-a-lack-of-self-realization-as-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men can starve from a lack of self-realization  as much as they can from a lack of bread." -- Richard Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45103-said-during-a-debate-when-his-opponent-ridiculously-asserted-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 06:59:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45103-said-during-a-debate-when-his-opponent-ridiculously-asserted-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[&lt;i&gt;Said during a debate when his opponent ridiculously asserted that atheism and belief in evolution leads to Nazism&lt;/i&gt;:]

Atheism by itself is of course not a moral position or a political one of any kind, it simply is the refusal to believe in a supernatural dimension. For you to say of Naziism, that it was the implementation of the work of [author:Charles Darwin|12793] is a filthy slander, undeserving of you, and an insult to this audience.  [author:Darwin|12793]’s thought was not taught in Germany; [author:Darwinism|12793] was derided in Germany along with every other form of unbelief that all the great modern atheists, [author:Darwin|12793], [author:Einstein|9810] and [author:Freud|10017] were alike despised by the National Socialist regime.

Now, just to take the most notorious of the 20th century totalitarianisms, the most finished example, the most perfected one, the most ruthless and refined one, that of National Socialism, the one that fortunately allowed the escape of all these great atheists, thinkers and many others, to the United States, a country of separation of church and state, that gave them welcome, if it’s an atheistic regime, then how come that in the first chapter of Mein Kampf, that [author:Hitler|30691] says that he’s doing God’s work and executing God’s will in destroying the Jewish people?  How come the fuhrer oath that every officer of the Party and the Army had to take, making [author:Hitler|30691] into a minor god, begins “I swear in the name of almighty God, my loyalty to the Fuhrer?” How come that on the belt buckle of every Nazi soldier it says Gott mit uns, God on our side? How come that the first treaty made by the Nationalist Socialist dictatorship, the very first is with the Vatican? It’s exchanging political control of Germany for Catholic control of German education. How come that the church has celebrated the birthday of the Fuhrer every year, on that day until democracy put an end to this filthy, quasi-religious, superstitious, barbarous, reactionary system. Again, this is not a difference of emphasis between us to suggest that there’s something fascistic about me and about my beliefs is something I won't hear said and you shouldn't believe." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
