<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/187052-nick]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/187052-nick" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 07:34:18 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/428808-but-mdash-let-me-tell-you-my-cat-joke-it-s-very-short</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 07:34:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Philip K. Dick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/428808-but-mdash-let-me-tell-you-my-cat-joke-it-s-very-short]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But&amp;mdash;let me tell you my cat joke. It's very short and simple. A hostess is giving a dinner party and she's got a lovely five-pound T-bone steak sitting on the sideboard in the kitchen waiting to be cooked while she chats with the guests in the living room&amp;mdash;has a few drinks and whatnot. But then she excuses herself to go into the kitchen to cook the steak&amp;mdash;and it's gone. And there's the family cat, in the corner, sedately washing it's face.&quot;

&quot;The cat got the steak,&quot; Barney said.

&quot;Did it? The guests are called in; they argue about it. The steak is gone, all five pounds of it; there sits the cat, looking well-fed and cheerful. &quot;Weigh the cat,&quot; someone says. They've had a few drinks; it looks like a good idea. So they go into the bathroom and weigh the cat on the scales. It reads exactly five pounds. They all perceive this reading and a guest says, &quot;okay, that's it. There's the steak.&quot; They're satisfied that they know what happened, now; they've got empirical proof. Then a qualm comes to one of them and he says, puzzled, &quot;But where's the cat?" -- Philip K. Dick]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
