<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/187297-lavinia]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/187297-lavinia" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 00:11:56 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/751872-don-t-ever-live-vicariously-this-is-your-life-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 00:11:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lavinia add a quote by Lavinia Spalding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/751872-don-t-ever-live-vicariously-this-is-your-life-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't ever live vicariously. This is your life. Live." -- Lavinia Spalding]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/531103-that-s-because-true-travel-the-kind-with-no-predetermined-end</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 02:37:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lavinia add a quote by Stephanie Elizondo Griest]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/531103-that-s-because-true-travel-the-kind-with-no-predetermined-end]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's because true travel, the kind with no predetermined end, is one of the most selfish endeavors we can possibly undertake-an act in which we focus solely on our own fulfillment, with little regard to those we leave behind. After all, we're the ones venturing out into the big crazy world, filling up journals, growing like weeds. And we have the gall to think they're just sitting at home, soaking in security and stability.
It is only when we reopen these wrapped and ribboned boxes, upon our triumphant return home, that we discover nothing is the way we had left it before." -- Stephanie Elizondo Griest]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1213547-there-s-something-profoundly-intense-and-intoxicating-about-friendship-found-en</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2014 15:20:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lavinia add a quote by Lavinia Spalding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1213547-there-s-something-profoundly-intense-and-intoxicating-about-friendship-found-en]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There’s something profoundly intense and intoxicating about friendship found en route. It’s the bond that arises from being thrust into uncomfortable circumstances, and the vulnerability of trusting others to navigate those situations. It’s the exhilaration of meeting someone when we are our most alive selves, breathing new air, high on life-altering moments. It’s the discovery of the commonality of the world’s people and the attendant rejection of prejudices. It’s the humbling experience of being suspicious of a stranger who then extends a great kindness. It’s the astonishment of learning from those we set out to teach. It’s the intimacy of sharing small spaces, the recognition of a kindred spirit across the globe.

It’s the travel relationship, and it can only call itself family." -- Lavinia Spalding]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
