<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/188545-victoria]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/188545-victoria" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 08:39:58 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236085-if-you-reveal-everything-bare-every-feeling-ask-for-understanding</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 08:39:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236085-if-you-reveal-everything-bare-every-feeling-ask-for-understanding]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you reveal everything, bare every feeling, ask for understanding, you lose something crucial to your sense of yourself. You need to know things that others don't know. It's what no one knows about you that allows you to know yourself." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292356-now-we-re-in-that-sweet-period-where-everyone-agrees-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 13:29:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292356-now-we-re-in-that-sweet-period-where-everyone-agrees-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now we're in that sweet period where everyone agrees that our recent horrors should never be repeated. But collective thinking is usually short-lived. We're fickle, stupid beings with poor memories and a great gift for self-destruction." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/451035-but-love-doesn-t-always-generate-hope-anyone-who-has-ever</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 05:28:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Kevin Brockmeier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/451035-but-love-doesn-t-always-generate-hope-anyone-who-has-ever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But love doesn't always generate hope. Anyone who has ever experienced love knows that you can have too much love or too little. You can have love that parches, love that defeats. You can have love measured out in the wrong proportions. It's like your sunlight and water--the wrong kind of love is just as likely to stifle hope as it is to nourish it." -- Kevin Brockmeier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2532-great-heroes-need-great-sorrows-and-burdens-or-half-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 11:31:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2532-great-heroes-need-great-sorrows-and-burdens-or-half-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Great heroes need great sorrows and burdens, or half their greatness goes unnoticed. It is all part of the fairy tale." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14404-real-magic-can-never-be-made-by-offering-someone-else-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 11:31:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14404-real-magic-can-never-be-made-by-offering-someone-else-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Real magic can never be made by offering someone else's liver. You must tear out your own, and not expect to get it back." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22331-we-are-not-always-what-we-seem-and-hardly-ever</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 11:31:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22331-we-are-not-always-what-we-seem-and-hardly-ever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are not always what we seem, and hardly ever what we dream." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34244-when-i-was-alive-i-believed-as-you-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 11:31:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34244-when-i-was-alive-i-believed-as-you-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was alive, I believed — as you do — that time was at least as real and solid as myself, and probably more so. I said 'one o'clock' as though I could see it, and 'Monday' as though I could find it on the map; and I let myself be hurried along from minute to minute, day to day, year to year, as though I were actually moving from one place to another. Like everyone else, I lived in a house bricked up with seconds and minutes, weekends and New Year's Days, and I never went outside until I died, because there was no other door. Now I know that I could have walked through the walls. (...) You can strike your own time, and start the count anywhere. When you understand that — then any time at all will be the right time for you." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61590-the-truly-free-man-is-the-one-who-can-turn</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 08:13:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Jules Renard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61590-the-truly-free-man-is-the-one-who-can-turn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truly free man is the one who can turn down an invitation to dinner without giving an excuse." -- Jules Renard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508780-in-his-view-we-were-already-a-success-because-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 09:36:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Kristin Kimball]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/508780-in-his-view-we-were-already-a-success-because-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In his view, we were already a success, because we were doing something hard and it was something that mattered to us. You don't measure things like that with words like success or failure, he said. Satisfaction comes from trying hard things and then going on to the next hard thing, regardless of the outcome. What mattered was whether or not you were moving in a direction you thought was right." -- Kristin Kimball]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100776-every-spirit-passing-through-the-world-fingers-the-tangible-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 07:29:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100776-every-spirit-passing-through-the-world-fingers-the-tangible-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every spirit passing through the world fingers the tangible and mars the mutable, and finally has come to look and not to buy." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606499-to-crave-and-to-have-are-as-like-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 05:43:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606499-to-crave-and-to-have-are-as-like-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To crave and to have are as like as a thing and its shadow. For when does a berry break upon the tongue as sweetly as when one longs to taste it, and when is the taste refracted into it so many hues and savors of ripeness and earth, and when do our senses know any thing so utterly as when we lack it?" -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/579233-the-dead-are-celebrated-the-dead-are-loved-they-give</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 11:56:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Téa Obreht]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/579233-the-dead-are-celebrated-the-dead-are-loved-they-give]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The dead are celebrated. The dead are loved. They give something to the living. Once you put something into the ground, Doctor, you always know where to find it." -- Téa Obreht]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431910-that-was-true-iris-would-sometimes-think-about-marriage-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 12:00:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Ayelet Waldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431910-that-was-true-iris-would-sometimes-think-about-marriage-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That was true, Iris would sometimes think, about marriage: it was only a boat, too. A wooden boat, difficult to build, even more difficult to maintain, whose beauty derived at least in part from its unlikelihood. Long ago the pragmatic justifications for both marriage and wooden-boat building had been lost or superseded. Why invest countless hours, years, and dollars in planing and carving, gluing and fastening, caulking and fairing, when a fiberglass boat can be had at a fraction of the cost? Why struggle to maintain love and commitment over decades when there were far easier ways to live, ones that required no effort or attention to prevent corrosion and rot? Why continue to pour your heart into these obsolete arts? Because their beauty, the way they connect you to your history and to the living world, justifies your efforts. A long marriage, like a classic wooden boat, could be a thing of grace, but only if great effort was devoted to its maintenance. At first your notions of your life with another were no more substantial than a pattern laid down in plywood. Then year by year you constructed the frame around the form, and began layering memories, griefs, and small triumphs like strips of veneer planking bent around the hull of everyday routine. You sanded down the rough edges, patched the misunderstandings, faired the petty betrayals. Sometimes you sprung a leak. You fell apart in rough weather or were smashed on devouring rocks. But then, as now, in the teeth of a storm, when it seemed like all was lost, the timber swelled, the leak sealed up, and you found that your craft was, after all, sea-kindly." -- Ayelet Waldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629924-some-mornings-she-d-wake-and-vow-today-i-will-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 08:51:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629924-some-mornings-she-d-wake-and-vow-today-i-will-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some mornings, she’d wake and vow, &lt;i&gt;Today, I will get it right. I won’t be such an awful mess of a girl. I won’t lose my temper or make unkind remarks. I won’t go too far with a joke and feel the room go quiet with disapproval. I’ll be good and kind and sensible and patient. The sort everyone loves&lt;/i&gt;. But by evening, her good intentions would have unraveled. She’d say the wrong thing or talk a little too loudly. She’d take a dare she shouldn’t, just to be noticed. Perhaps Mabel was right, and she was selfish. But what was the point of living so quietly you made no noise at all? “Oh, Evie, you’re too much,” people said, and it wasn’t complimentary. Yes, she was too much. She felt like too much inside all the time. So why wasn’t she ever enough?" -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/871535-age-doesn-t-arrive-slowly-it-comes-in-a-rush-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 12:26:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by James Salter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/871535-age-doesn-t-arrive-slowly-it-comes-in-a-rush-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Age doesn't arrive slowly, it comes in a rush. One day nothing has changed, a week later, everything has. A week may be too long a time, it can happen overnight. You are the same and still the same and suddenly one morning two distinct lines, ineradicable, have appeared at the corners of your mouth." -- James Salter]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
