<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/189460-ciona]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/189460-ciona" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 19:04:08 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218735-i-have-made-it-a-rule-of-my-life-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 19:04:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ciona add a quote by Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218735-i-have-made-it-a-rule-of-my-life-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have made it a rule of my life never to regret and never to look back. Regret is an appalling waste of energy... you can't build on it; it's only good for wallowing in." -- Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30765-i-imagine-i-was-always-writing-twaddle-it-was-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 19:04:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ciona add a quote by Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30765-i-imagine-i-was-always-writing-twaddle-it-was-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I imagine I was always writing. Twaddle it was, too. But better far write twaddle or anything, anything, than nothing at all." -- Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36884-anyone-who-says-here-s-my-address-write-me-a-poem</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 19:05:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ciona add a quote by Naomi Shihab Nye]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36884-anyone-who-says-here-s-my-address-write-me-a-poem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who says, “Here’s my address, write me a poem,” deserves something in reply. So I’ll tell you a secret instead: poems hide. In the bottoms of our shoes, they are sleeping. They are the shadows drifting across our ceilings the moment before we wake up. What we have to do is live in a way that lets us find them." -- Naomi Shihab Nye]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226819-i-adore-life-what-do-all-the-fools-matter-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 19:07:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ciona add a quote by Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226819-i-adore-life-what-do-all-the-fools-matter-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I adore Life. What do all the fools matter and all the stupidity. They do matter but somehow for me they cannot touch the body of Life. Life is marvellous. I want to be deeply rooted in it - to live - to expand - to breathe in it - to rejoice - to share it. To give and to be asked for Love." -- Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36609-as-a-writer-you-should-not-judge-you-should-understand</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 13:39:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ciona add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36609-as-a-writer-you-should-not-judge-you-should-understand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As a writer, you should not judge, you should understand." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5521-everything-you-can-imagine-is-real</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:20:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ciona add a quote by Pablo Picasso]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5521-everything-you-can-imagine-is-real]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything you can imagine is real." -- Pablo Picasso]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4673-art-washes-away-from-the-soul-the-dust-of-everyday</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:22:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ciona add a quote by Pablo Picasso]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4673-art-washes-away-from-the-soul-the-dust-of-everyday]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Art washes away from the soul the dust of everyday life." -- Pablo Picasso]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47367-to-draw-you-must-close-your-eyes-and-sing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:23:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ciona add a quote by Pablo Picasso]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47367-to-draw-you-must-close-your-eyes-and-sing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To draw, you must close your eyes and sing" -- Pablo Picasso]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34202-many-people-hear-voices-when-no-one-is-there-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 09:21:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ciona add a quote by Margaret Chittenden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34202-many-people-hear-voices-when-no-one-is-there-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many people hear voices when no one is there. Some of them are called mad and are shut up in rooms where they stare at the walls all day. Others are called writers and they do pretty much the same thing." -- Margaret Chittenden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484257-it-s-decidedly-bizzare-when-the-worst-thing-hppens-and-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 13:39:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ciona add a quote by Elisa Albert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484257-it-s-decidedly-bizzare-when-the-worst-thing-hppens-and-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's decidedly bizzare, when the Worst Thing hppens and you find yourself still conscious, still breathing." -- Elisa Albert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 08:36:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ciona add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
