<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/189861-jennifer-didik]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/189861-jennifer-didik" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 17:19:39 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/345392-she-sank-with-an-enormous-sigh-that-carried-all-rigidity</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 17:19:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/345392-she-sank-with-an-enormous-sigh-that-carried-all-rigidity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She sank with an enormous sigh that carried all rigidity like a mythical fluid from her, down next to him; so weak she couldn't help him undress her; it took him 20 minutes, rolling, arranging her this way and that, as if she thought, he were some scaled-up, short-haired, poker-faced little girl with a Barbie doll. She may have fallen asleep once or twice. She awoke at last to find herself getting laid; she'd come in on a sexual crescendo in progress, like a cut to a scene where the camera's already moving. Outside a fugue of guitars had begun, and she counted each electronic voice as it came in, till she reached six or so and recalled only three of the Paranoids played guitars; so others must be plugging in." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371658-did-i-read-the-new-yorker-this-question-had-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 19:03:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Jonathan Lethem]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371658-did-i-read-the-new-yorker-this-question-had-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did I read The New Yorker? This question had a dangerous urgency. It wasn't any one writer or article he was worried about, but the font. The meaning embedded, at a preconscious level, by the look of the magazine; the seal, as he described it, that the typography and layout put on dialectical thought. According to Perkus, to read The New Yorker was to find that you always already agreed, not with The New Yorker but, much more dismayingly, with yourself. I tried hard to understand. Apparently here was the paranoia Susan Eldred had warned me of: The New Yorker's font was controlling, perhaps assailing, Perkus Tooth's mind. To defend himself he frequently retyped their articles and printed them out in simple Courier, an attempt to dissolve the magazine's oppressive context. Once I'd enter his apartment to find him on his carpet with a pair of scissors, furiously slicing up and rearranging an issue of the magazine, trying to shatter its spell on his brain." -- Jonathan Lethem]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371670-it-took-almost-an-hour-to-get-to-bernard-s-house</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 19:17:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371670-it-took-almost-an-hour-to-get-to-bernard-s-house]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It took almost an hour to get to Bernard's house. Somewhere in Long Island. Beautiful trees. I'd never seen such beautiful trees. Out in the driveway, one of Bernard's nephews had slit his pants legs to the knee and was running up and down in the sunlight, watching how they caught the breeze. Inside the house, people stood around a table piled with food talking about Isaac. I knew I didn't belong there. I felt like a fool and an imposter. I stood by the window, making myself invisible. I didn't think it would be so painful. And yet. To hear people talk about the son I'd only been able to imagine as if he were as familiar to them as a relative was almost too much to bear. So I slipped away. I wandered through the rooms of Isaac's half-brother's house. I thought: My son walked on this carpet. I came to a guest bedroom. I thought: From time to time, he slept in this bed. This very bed! His head on these pillows. I lay down. I was tired, I couldn't help myself. The pillow sank under my cheek. And as he lay here, I thought, he looked out this very window, at that very tree." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/428374-her-son-lives-he-has-her-eyes-precisely-her-eyes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 20:02:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/428374-her-son-lives-he-has-her-eyes-precisely-her-eyes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her son lives. He has her eyes, precisely her eyes. You remember the shape and color of Lily Evans's eyes, I am sure?" -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/517832-before-i-opened-my-computer-in-the-parking-lot-today</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 20:02:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Diane Keaton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/517832-before-i-opened-my-computer-in-the-parking-lot-today]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Before I opened my computer in the parking lot today, I relived one of my favorite memories. It's the one with Woody and me sitting on the steps of the Metropolitan Museum after it's closed. We're watching people parade out of the museum in summer shorts and sandals. The trees to the south are planted in parallel lines. The water in the fountain shoots up with a mist that almost reaches the steps we sit on. We look at silver-haired ladies in red-and-white-print dresses. We separate the mice from the men, the tourists from the New Yorkers, the Upper East Siders from the West Siders. The hot-pretzel vendor sells us a wad of dough in knots with clumps of salt stuck on top. We make our usual remarks about the crazies and wonder what it would be like to live in a penthouse apartment on Fifth Avenue overlooking the Met. We laugh and say the same things we always say. We hold hands and keep sitting, just sitting, as the sun beings to set. It's a perfect afternoon." -- Diane Keaton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64394-look-at-me-he-whispered-the-green-eyes-found-the-black-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 20:02:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64394-look-at-me-he-whispered-the-green-eyes-found-the-black-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look...at...me...&quot; he whispered. The green eyes found the black, but after a second, something in the depths of the dark pair seemed to vanish, leaving them fixed, blank, and empty. The hand holding Harry thudded to the floor, and Snape moved no more." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/454285-emptiness-was-an-index-it-recorded-the-incomprehensible-chronicle-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 20:02:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Colson Whitehead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/454285-emptiness-was-an-index-it-recorded-the-incomprehensible-chronicle-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Emptiness was an index. It recorded the incomprehensible chronicle of the metropolis, the demographic realities, how money worked, the cobbled-together lifestyles and roosting habits. The population remained at a miraculous density, it seemed to him, for the empty rooms brimmed with evidence, in the stragglers they did or did not contain, in the busted barricades, in the expired relatives on the futon beds, arms crossed over their chests in ad hoc rites. The rooms stored anthropological clues re: kinship rituals and taboos. How they treated their dead.

The rich tended to escape. Entire white-glove buildings were devoid, as Omega discovered after they worried the seams of and then shattered the glass doors to the lobby (no choice, despite the No-No Cards). The rich fled during the convulsions of the great evacuation, dragging their distilled possessions in wheeled luggage of European manufacture, leaving their thousand-dollar floor lamps to attract dust to their silver surfaces and recount luxury to later visitors, bowing like weeping willows over imported pile rugs. A larger percentage of the poor tended to stay, shoving layaway bureaus and media consoles up against the doors. There were those who decided to stay, willfully uncomprehending or stupid or incapacitated by the scope of the disaster, and those who could not leave for a hundred other reasons - because they were waiting for their girlfriend or mother or soul mate to make it home first, because their mobility was compromised or a relative was debilitated, crutched, too young. Because it was too impossible, the enormity of the thought: This is the end. He knew them all from their absences." -- Colson Whitehead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/495049-buster-closed-his-eyes-held-his-breath-and-before-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 20:02:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Kevin Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/495049-buster-closed-his-eyes-held-his-breath-and-before-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Buster closed his eyes, held his breath, and, before he realized that the gun had been fired, a gust of heat and wind passed over him and deconstructed the beer can atop his head, the sound of something irrevocably giving up its shape and becoming, in an instant, something new." -- Kevin Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526448-did-the-rhythm-of-the-train-on-the-tracks-somehow</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2012 18:54:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526448-did-the-rhythm-of-the-train-on-the-tracks-somehow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did the rhythm of the train on the tracks somehow unravel her and make her behave out of character? Was she altered in transit, when her feet were not upon the ground?" -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329791-he-is-thinking-about-asymmetry-this-is-a-world-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 06:34:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Paul Murray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329791-he-is-thinking-about-asymmetry-this-is-a-world-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He is thinking about asymmetry. This is a world, he is thinking, where you can lie in bed, listening to a song as you dream about someone you love, and your feelings and the music will resonate so powerfully and completely that it seems impossible that the beloved, whoever and wherever he or she might be, should not know, should not pick up this signal as it pulsates from your heart, as if you and the music and the love and the whole universe have merged into one force that can be chanelled out into the darkness to bring them this message. But, in actuality, not only will he or she not know, there is nothing to stop that other person from lying on his or her bed at the exact moment listening to the exact same song and thinking about someone else entirely-from aiming those identical feelings in some completely opposite direction, at some totally other person, who may in turn be lying in the dark thinking of another person still, a fourth, who is thinking of a fifth, and so on, and so on, so that rather than a universe of neatly reciprocating pairs, love and love-returned fluttering through space nicely and symmetrically like so many pairs of butterfly wings, instead we get chains of yearning, which sprawl and meander and culminate in an infinite number of dead ends." -- Paul Murray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674495-i-just-believed-it-easily-the-way-you-might-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 11:16:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Alice Munro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674495-i-just-believed-it-easily-the-way-you-might-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I just believed it easily, the way you might believe and in fact remember that you once had another set of teeth, now vanished but real in spite of that. Until one day, one day when I may even have been in my teens, I knew with a dim sort of hole in my insides that now I didn't believe it anymore." -- Alice Munro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706890-somehow-molly-he-heard-her-in-the-entryway-mol-molly</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 17:31:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706890-somehow-molly-he-heard-her-in-the-entryway-mol-molly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Somehow: Molly.
He heard her in the entryway. Mol, Molly, oh boy. When they were first married they used to fight. Say the most insane things. Afterward, sometimes there would be tears. Tears in bed? And then they would - Molly pressing her hot wet face against his hot wet face. They were sorry, they were saying with their bodies, they were accepting each other back, and that feeling, that feeling of being accepted back again and again, of someone's affection for you expanding to encompass whatever new flawed thing had just manifested in you, that was the deepest, dearest thing he'd ever -
She came in flustered and apologetic, a touch of anger in her face. He'd embarrassed her. He saw that. He'd embarrassed her by doing something that showed she hadn't sufficiently noticed him needing her. She'd been too busy nursing him to notice how scared he was. She was angry at him for pulling this stunt and ashamed of herself for feeling angry at him in his hour of need, and was trying to put the shame and anger behind her now so she could do what might be needed.
All of this was in her face. He knew her so well.
Also concern.
Overriding everything else in that lovely face was concern.
She came to him now, stumbling a bit on a swell in the floor of this stranger's house." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/912685-indoors-the-evening-gets-you-d-say-festive-with-maxine-riding</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 13:02:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/912685-indoors-the-evening-gets-you-d-say-festive-with-maxine-riding]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Indoors, the evening gets you’d say festive, with Maxine riding Horst for the better part of an hour, not that it’s anybody’s business of course, and coming a number of times, at last fiercely in sync with Horst, not long after which, owing to some extrasensory cue from the television, whose mute feature has been engaged, they surface from their post-orgy daze in time to witness Derek Jeter’s clutch tenth-inning homer and another trademark Yankee win. “Yes!” Horst beginning to scream in delighted disbelief. “And it better be Keanu Reeves in the biopic!" -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/951763-outside-it-dawned-on-me-that-my-mother-hadn-t-specified</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 18:18:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Scott Hutchins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/951763-outside-it-dawned-on-me-that-my-mother-hadn-t-specified]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Outside it dawned on me that my mother hadn't specified the method of my father's suicide. She'd just said he'd committed suicide. It seemed horrible to me that I hadn't thought to ask. I decided not to pack. I had clothes in my bedroom at home. I still lived there, in a sense. I hadn't planned on coming home for the summer. He'd been mad about that, I thought. Or had he? I'd reached a point where I couldn't tell if he was mad about everything, or nothing, or wasn't mad at all." -- Scott Hutchins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/964907-the-woman-in-the-film-drinks-in-a-bar-she-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 10:49:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Rachel Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/964907-the-woman-in-the-film-drinks-in-a-bar-she-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The woman in the film drinks in a bar. She's in hair curlers, a chiffon headscarf tied over them like a tarp over a log pile. The hollows of the curlers, spaces for hope: something good might happen.

There was no sign of Sandro. I watched the film to keep myself awake while I waited.

A man bought the woman a beer. She took dainty sips in her hair curlers, in preparation for no specific occasion. Curler time seemed almost religious, a waiting that was more important than what the waiting was for. Curler time was about living the now with a belief that a future, an occasion for set hair, existed." -- Rachel Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1263784-in-his-pocket-the-mobile-phone-beeped-and-wriggled-they-d</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 18:32:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Tom Rachman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1263784-in-his-pocket-the-mobile-phone-beeped-and-wriggled-they-d]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In his pocket, the mobile phone beeped and wriggled. They'd said on the radio that the entirety of human knowledge was available on these handsets, that smartphones had outsmarted their owners. But, for now, he was in control, and the nagging gadget had to wait. He took only a glance at the little screen, enough to see that the text came from Tooly. He pocketed the phone and finished tidying up the Honesty Barrel. Soon he'd read her message and he would know. But not yet. That present had not arrived yet. This one lingered." -- Tom Rachman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1263791-four-years-ago-he-d-nearly-married-but-his-girlfriend-went</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 18:37:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Tom Rachman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1263791-four-years-ago-he-d-nearly-married-but-his-girlfriend-went]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Four years ago, he'd nearly married. But his girlfriend went to do theater in London and met a new man there. They'd stayed friends, till she sent photos of her newborn. &quot;When you open the baby-photo email,&quot; Fogg said, &quot;it's like your friends waving goodbye." -- Tom Rachman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
