<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/190514-carlton]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/190514-carlton" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 14:34:45 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/613714-conservatives-and-those-on-the-right-are-usually-willing-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 14:34:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carlton add a quote by Joseph Epstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/613714-conservatives-and-those-on-the-right-are-usually-willing-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Conservatives and those on the right are usually willing to settle for thinking themselves correct on political issues; those on the left have always needed to feel not so much that they are correct but that they are also good. Disagree with someone on the right and he is likely to think you obtuse, wrong, sentimental, foolish, a dope; disagree with someone one the left and he is more likely to think you selfish, cold-hearted, a sellout, evil-in league with the devil, he might say, if he didn't think religious terminology too coarse for our secular age. To this day one will hear of people who fell for Communism in a big way let off the hook because they were sincere; if one's heart is in the right place, nothing else matters, even if one's naive opinions made it easier for tyrants to murder millions." -- Joseph Epstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/634906-did-i-request-thee-maker-from-my-clay-to-mould</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 09:49:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carlton add a quote by John Milton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/634906-did-i-request-thee-maker-from-my-clay-to-mould]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did I request thee, Maker, from my clay
To mould me man? Did I solicit thee
From darkness to promote me?" -- John Milton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630802-i-am-a-conservative-barack-obama-is-the-hans-gruber</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 09:45:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carlton add a quote by Kurt Schlichter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630802-i-am-a-conservative-barack-obama-is-the-hans-gruber]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am a Conservative: Barack Obama is the Hans Gruber of American politics. #caring" -- Kurt Schlichter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292634-i-ve-come-to-believe-that-there-exists-in-the-universe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 11:27:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carlton add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292634-i-ve-come-to-believe-that-there-exists-in-the-universe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've come to believe that there exists in the universe something I call &quot;The Physics of The Quest&quot; — a force of nature governed by laws as real as the laws of gravity or momentum. And the rule of Quest Physics maybe goes like this: &quot;If you are brave enough to leave behind everything familiar and comforting (which can be anything from your house to your bitter old resentments) and set out on a truth-seeking journey (either externally or internally), and if you are truly willing to regard everything that happens to you on that journey as a clue, and if you accept everyone you meet along the way as a teacher, and if you are prepared – most of all – to face (and forgive) some very difficult realities about yourself... then truth will not be withheld from you.&quot; Or so I've come to believe." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
