<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/19167-chris-cyr]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/19167-chris-cyr" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 14:16:15 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19020-you-can-always-count-on-a-murderer-for-a-fancy</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 14:16:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19020-you-can-always-count-on-a-murderer-for-a-fancy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can always count on a murderer for a fancy prose style." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19036-the-word-we-is-as-lime-poured-over-men-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 14:39:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19036-the-word-we-is-as-lime-poured-over-men-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The word &quot;We&quot; is as lime poured over men, which sets and hardens to stone, and crushes all beneath it, and that which is white and that which is black are lost equally in the grey of it. It is the word by which the depraved steal the virtue of the good, by which the weak steal the might of the strong, by which the fools steal the wisdom of the sages. 

What is my joy if all hands, even the unclean, can reach into it? What is my wisdom, if even the fools can dictate to me? What is my freedom, if all creatures, even the botched and impotent, are my masters? What is my life, if I am but to bow, to agree and to obey? 

But I am done with this creed of corruption. 

I am done with the monster of &quot;We,&quot; the word of serfdom, of plunder, of misery, falsehood and shame. 

And now I see the face of god, and I raise this god over the earth, this god whom men have sought since men came into being, this god who will grant them joy and peace and pride. 

This god, this one word: 

&quot;I." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19037-we-wanted-to-blast-the-world-free-of-history-picture</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 14:44:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19037-we-wanted-to-blast-the-world-free-of-history-picture]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We wanted to blast the world free of history.... picture yourself planting radishes and seed potatoes on the fifteenth green of a forgotten golf course. You'll hunt elk through the damp canyon forests around the ruins of Rockefeller Center, and dig clams next to the skeleton of the Space Needle leaning at a forty-five degree angle. We'll paint the skyscrapers with huge totem faces and goblin tikis, and every evening what's left of mankind will retreat to empty zoos and lock itself in cages as protection against the bears and big cats and wolves that pace and watch us from outside the cage bars at night." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19038-and-some-of-your-elders-remember-pleasures-with-regret-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 14:49:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19038-and-some-of-your-elders-remember-pleasures-with-regret-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And some of your elders remember pleasures with regret like wrongs committed in drunkenness.

But regret is the beclouding of the mind and not its chastisement. 

They should remember their pleasures with gratitude, as they would the harvest of a summer." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6350-happiness-is-but-a-mere-episode-in-the-general-drama</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 22:15:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Thomas Hardy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6350-happiness-is-but-a-mere-episode-in-the-general-drama]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is but a mere episode in the general drama of pain." -- Thomas Hardy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
