<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/191869-patti]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/191869-patti" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 11:00:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 11:00:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 16:21:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that everything happens for a reason. People change so that you can learn to let go, things go wrong so that you appreciate them when they're right, you believe lies so you eventually learn to trust no one but yourself, and sometimes good things fall apart so better things can fall together." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 16:24:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 16:28:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We accept the love we think we deserve." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6708-the-statistics-on-sanity-are-that-one-out-of-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 16:25:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Rita Mae Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6708-the-statistics-on-sanity-are-that-one-out-of-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The statistics on sanity are that one out of every four people is suffering from a mental illness. Look at your 3 best friends. If they're ok, then it's you." -- Rita Mae Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208546-the-truth-is-everyone-is-going-to-hurt-you-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 16:25:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208546-the-truth-is-everyone-is-going-to-hurt-you-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is, everyone is going to hurt you. You just got to find the ones worth suffering for." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/652-i-became-insane-with-long-intervals-of-horrible-sanity</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 16:25:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/652-i-became-insane-with-long-intervals-of-horrible-sanity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I became insane, with long intervals of horrible sanity." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 16:25:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 16:47:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I can hear my bones straining under the weight of all the lives I'm not living." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4852-so-this-is-my-life-and-i-want-you-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 16:49:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4852-so-this-is-my-life-and-i-want-you-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So, this is my life. And I want you to know that I am both happy and sad and I'm still trying to figure out how that could be." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76393-i-have-a-history-of-making-decisions-very-quickly-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 11:00:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76393-i-have-a-history-of-making-decisions-very-quickly-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have a history of making decisions very quickly about men.  I have always fallen in love fast and without measuring risks.  I have a tendency not only to see the best in everyone, but to assume that everyone is emotionally capable of reaching his highest potential.  I have fallen in love more times than I care to count with the highest potential of a man, rather than with the man himself, and I have hung on to the relationship for a long time (sometimes far too long) waiting for the man to ascend to his own greatness.  Many times in romance I have been a victim of my own optimism." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31921-sometimes-we-can-choose-the-paths-we-follow-sometimes-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 11:11:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31921-sometimes-we-can-choose-the-paths-we-follow-sometimes-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes we can choose the paths we follow. Sometimes our choices are made for us. And sometimes we have no choice at all." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21657-it-s-not-the-load-that-breaks-you-down-it-s-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 15:52:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Lou Holtz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21657-it-s-not-the-load-that-breaks-you-down-it-s-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not the load that breaks you down, it's the way you carry it." -- Lou Holtz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18271-there-is-always-some-madness-in-love-but-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 15:52:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18271-there-is-always-some-madness-in-love-but-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is always some madness in love. But there is also always some reason in madness." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67443-what-i-want-is-to-be-needed-what-i-need</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 16:04:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67443-what-i-want-is-to-be-needed-what-i-need]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I want is to be needed. What I need is to be indispensable to somebody. Who I need is somebody that will eat up all my free time, my ego, my attention. Somebody addicted to me. A mutual addiction." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8178-nobody-realizes-that-some-people-expend-tremendous-energy-merely-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 16:04:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8178-nobody-realizes-that-some-people-expend-tremendous-energy-merely-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody realizes that some people expend tremendous energy merely to be normal." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158856-don-t-be-reckless-with-other-people-s-hearts-and-don-t-put</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 16:16:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Mary Schmich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158856-don-t-be-reckless-with-other-people-s-hearts-and-don-t-put]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't be reckless with other people's hearts, and don't put up with people that are reckless with yours." -- Mary Schmich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40848-i-mean-maybe-i-am-crazy-i-mean-maybe-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 16:22:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40848-i-mean-maybe-i-am-crazy-i-mean-maybe-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I mean, maybe I am crazy. I mean, maybe. But if this is all there is, then I don't want to be sane." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271881-it-s-much-easier-to-not-know-things-sometimes-things-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 16:19:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271881-it-s-much-easier-to-not-know-things-sometimes-things-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's much easier to not know things sometimes. Things change and friends leave. And life doesn't stop for anybody. I wanted to laugh. Or maybe get mad. Or maybe shrug at how strange everybody was, especially me. I think the idea is that every person has to live for his or her own life and than make the choice to share it with other people. You can't just sit their and put everybody's lives ahead of yours and think that counts as love. You just can't. You have to do things. I'm going to do what I want to do. I'm going to be who I really am. And I'm going to figure out what that is. And we could all sit around and wonder and feel bad about each other and blame a lot of people for what they did or didn't do or what they didn't know. I don't know. I guess there could always be someone to blame. It's just different. Maybe it's good to put things in perspective, but sometimes, I think that the only perspective is to really be there. Because it's okay to feel things. I was really there. And that was enough to make me feel infinite. I feel infinite." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30858-every-woman-is-a-rebel</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 15:50:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30858-every-woman-is-a-rebel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every woman is a rebel." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48296-ok-you-fuck-me-then-snub-me-you-love-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 15:55:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48296-ok-you-fuck-me-then-snub-me-you-love-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ok. You fuck me, then snub me. You love me, you hate me. You show me a sensitive side, then you turn into a total asshole. Is this a pretty accurate description of our relationship." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361858-he-s-not-perfect-you-aren-t-either-and-the-two-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 16:16:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361858-he-s-not-perfect-you-aren-t-either-and-the-two-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He’s not perfect. You aren’t either, and the two of you will never be perfect. But if he can make you laugh at least once, causes you to think twice, and if he admits to being human and making mistakes, hold onto him and give him the most you can. He isn’t going to quote poetry, he’s not thinking about you every moment, but he will give you a part of him that he knows you could break. Don’t hurt him, don’t change him, and don’t expect for more than he can give. Don’t analyze. Smile when he makes you happy, yell when he makes you mad, and miss him when he’s not there. Love hard when there is love to be had. Because perfect guys don’t exist, but there’s always one guy that is perfect for you." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12278-i-think-and-think-and-think-i-ve-thought-myself-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 16:25:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12278-i-think-and-think-and-think-i-ve-thought-myself-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think and think and think, I‘ve thought myself out of happiness one million times, but never once into it." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118255-i-think-i-deserve-something-beautiful</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 16:26:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118255-i-think-i-deserve-something-beautiful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think I deserve something beautiful." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6384-imperfection-is-beauty-madness-is-genius-and-it-s-better-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 16:28:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6384-imperfection-is-beauty-madness-is-genius-and-it-s-better-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imperfection is beauty, madness is genius and it's better to be absolutely ridiculous than absolutely boring." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 16:30:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72139-i-think-that-we-re-all-mentally-ill-those-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 16:36:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72139-i-think-that-we-re-all-mentally-ill-those-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think that we're all mentally ill.  Those of us outside the asylums only hide it a little better - and maybe not all that much better after all." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105031-i-also-believe-that-parents-if-they-love-you-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 13:59:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105031-i-also-believe-that-parents-if-they-love-you-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I also believe that parents, if they love you, will hold you up safely, above their swirling waters, and sometimes that means you'll never know what they endured, and you may treat them unkindly, in a way you otherwise wouldn't." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68276-and-no-matter-what-anybody-says-about-grief-and-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 14:01:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68276-and-no-matter-what-anybody-says-about-grief-and-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And no matter what anybody says about grief and about time healing all wounds, the truth is, there are certain sorrows that never fade away until the heart stops beating and the last breath is taken." -- Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 14:15:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patti add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May your coming year be filled with magic and dreams and good madness. I hope you read some fine books and kiss someone who thinks you're wonderful, and don't forget to make some art -- write or draw or build or sing or live as only you can. And I hope, somewhere in the next year, you surprise yourself." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
