<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/191959-susan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/191959-susan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 13:22:05 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53166-the-best-fantasy-is-written-in-the-language-of-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 13:22:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53166-the-best-fantasy-is-written-in-the-language-of-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best fantasy is written in the language of dreams. It is alive as dreams are alive, more real than real ... for a moment at least ... that long magic moment before we wake.

     Fantasy is silver and scarlet, indigo and azure, obsidian veined with gold and lapis lazuli. Reality is plywood and plastic, done up in mud brown and olive drab. Fantasy tastes of habaneros and honey, cinnamon and cloves, rare red meat and wines as sweet as summer. Reality is beans and tofu, and ashes at the end. Reality is the strip malls of Burbank, the smokestacks of Cleveland, a parking garage in Newark. Fantasy is the towers of Minas Tirith, the ancient stones of Gormenghast, the halls of Camelot. Fantasy flies on the wings of Icarus, reality on Southwest Airlines. Why do our dreams become so much smaller when they finally come true?

     We read fantasy to find the colors again, I think. To taste strong spices and hear the songs the sirens sang. There is something old and true in fantasy that speaks to something deep within us, to the child who dreamt that one day he would hunt the forests of the night, and feast beneath the hollow hills, and find a love to last forever somewhere south of Oz and north of Shangri-La.

     They can keep their heaven. When I die, I'd sooner go to middle Earth." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/438396-oh-how-i-regret-not-having-worn-a-bikini-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2012 18:16:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Nora Ephron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/438396-oh-how-i-regret-not-having-worn-a-bikini-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh, how I regret not having worn a bikini for the entire year I was twenty-six. If anyone young is reading this, go, right this minute, put on a bikini, and don't take it off until you're thirty-four." -- Nora Ephron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95950-only-yesterday-i-was-no-different-than-them-yet-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 20:33:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95950-only-yesterday-i-was-no-different-than-them-yet-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only yesterday I was no different than them, yet I was saved. I am explaining to you the way of life of a people who say every sort of wicked thing about me because I sacrificed their friendship to gain my own soul. I left the dark paths of their duplicity and turned my eyes toward the light where there is salvation, truth, and justice. They have exiled me now from their society, yet I am content. Mankind only exiles the one whose large spirit rebels against injustice and tyranny. He who does not prefer exile to servility is not free in the true and necessary sense of freedom." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/794061-betrayal-is-an-ironic-thing-he-or-she-betrays-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 20:49:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Shannon L. Alder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/794061-betrayal-is-an-ironic-thing-he-or-she-betrays-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Betrayal is an ironic thing. He or she betrays you then you betray yourself. You think you’re showing strength with your anger, but in reality you’re showing how much you still care." -- Shannon L. Alder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/735038-our-faith-in-others-betrays-that-we-would-rather-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 20:49:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/735038-our-faith-in-others-betrays-that-we-would-rather-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our faith in others betrays that we would rather have faith in ourselves. Our longing for a friend is our betrayer. And often with our love we want merely to overcome envy. And often we attack and make ourselves enemies, to conceal that we are vulnerable." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/845-the-individual-has-always-had-to-struggle-to-keep-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 23:00:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/845-the-individual-has-always-had-to-struggle-to-keep-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The individual has always had to struggle to keep from being overwhelmed by the tribe. If you try it, you will be lonely often, and sometimes frightened. But no price is too high to pay for the privilege of owning yourself." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18645-the-surest-way-to-corrupt-a-youth-is-to-instruct</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 23:00:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18645-the-surest-way-to-corrupt-a-youth-is-to-instruct]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The surest way to corrupt a youth is to instruct him to hold in higher esteem those who think alike than those who think differently." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/415597-youth-is-easily-deceived-because-it-is-quick-to-hope</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 23:06:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Aristotle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/415597-youth-is-easily-deceived-because-it-is-quick-to-hope]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["youth is easily deceived because it is quick to hope." -- Aristotle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118286-there-are-some-things-in-this-world-you-rely-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 05:22:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118286-there-are-some-things-in-this-world-you-rely-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are some things in this world you rely on, like a sure bet. And when they let you down, shifting from where you've carefully placed them, it shakes your faith, right where you stand." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
