<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/193515-christopher]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/193515-christopher" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 05:01:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406827-what-struck-me-on-the-beach-and-it-struck-me-indeed</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 05:01:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Gene Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406827-what-struck-me-on-the-beach-and-it-struck-me-indeed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What struck me on the beach–and it struck me indeed, so that I staggered as at a blow–was that if the Eternal Principle had rested in that curved thorn I had carried about my neck across so many leagues, and if it now rested in the new thorn (perhaps the same thorn) I had only now put there, then it might rest in everything, in every thorn in every bush, in every drop of water in the sea. The thorn was a sacred Claw because all thorns were sacred Claws; the sand in my boots was sacred sand because it came from a beach of sacred sand. The cenobites treasured up the relics of the sannyasins because the sannyasins had approached the Pancreator. But everything had approached and even touched the Pancreator, because everything had dropped from his hand. Everything was a relic. All the world was a relic. I drew off my boots, that had traveled with me so far, and threw them into the waves that I might not walk shod on holy ground." -- Gene Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/481598-i-began-as-most-young-people-do-by-reading-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2012 07:25:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Gene Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/481598-i-began-as-most-young-people-do-by-reading-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I began, as most  young  people  do, by reading the books I enjoyed. But I found that narrowed  my  pleasure,  in time, until I spent most of my  hours  searching  for  such  books.  Then  I devised a plan of study for myself,  tracing  obscure  sciences,  one  after another, from the dawn of knowledge to the present. Eventually  I  exhausted even that, and beginning at the great ebony case that stands in  the  center of the room we of the  library  have  maintained  for  three  hundred  years against  the  return  of  the  Autarch Sulpicius  (and   into   which,   in consequence, no one ever comes) I read outward  for  a  period  of  fifteen years, often finishing two books in one day." -- Gene Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/493624-that-s-why-people-require-travel-books-on-the-1960s-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 00:46:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Roger Hutchinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/493624-that-s-why-people-require-travel-books-on-the-1960s-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That’s why people require travel books on the 1960s, I thought. They want to go there. They want to feel that sun on their backs." -- Roger Hutchinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/502600-the-issues-the-underground-press-raised-have-not-been-settled</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 22:51:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Nigel Fountain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/502600-the-issues-the-underground-press-raised-have-not-been-settled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The issues the underground press raised have not been settled. In colder times they may have frosted over, but as long as individuals and groups seek to take control of their own lives the experiences of those times contain information that can and must be used." -- Nigel Fountain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522469-it-may-be-that-the-only-reason-childhood-memories-act</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 20:19:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Gene Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522469-it-may-be-that-the-only-reason-childhood-memories-act]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It may be that the only reason childhood memories act on us so strongly is that, being the most remote we possess, they are the worst remembered and so offer the least resistance to that process by which we mold them nearer and nearer to an ideal which is fundamentally artistic, or at least nonfactual." -- Gene Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674955-the-people-who-hitched-to-katmandu-and-are-doubtlessly-still</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 04:55:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Patrick Marnham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674955-the-people-who-hitched-to-katmandu-and-are-doubtlessly-still]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The people who hitched to Katmandu (and are doubtlessly still doing so, despite the usual reports of official prohibitions) seem to me to be of this sort, displaced persons, aimless couples without papers. They are ill-suited to play the role which they are conventionally given; that of proletarian playboys, outriders of a modern sub-culture, who intend, mainly through will-power, to end injustice and rule the world. For the most part they have chosen to be the sole inhabitants of private worlds, and their aspirations will not be found in the bazaars of the international youth movement, or of the global underground or any other such tentative organizations." -- Patrick Marnham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004761-that-was-the-choice-that-father-dmitri-was-given-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 03:23:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Oliver Bullough]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004761-that-was-the-choice-that-father-dmitri-was-given-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That was the choice that Father Dmitri was given. As a Russian, he wanted to support Russia. As a Christian, he wanted to the oppose the Soviet Union. But, if he opposed the Soviet Union, he was allying with foreigners and thus fighting against Russia. He had to choose, therefore, between his religion and his country and he chose his country. That was how he himself justified his choice." -- Oliver Bullough]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
