<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/196704-pablo]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/196704-pablo" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 09:00:20 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320551-the-despising-without-remission-that-constitutes-being-a-conscientious-citizen</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 09:00:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pablo add a quote by Nathan Zuckerman via Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320551-the-despising-without-remission-that-constitutes-being-a-conscientious-citizen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The despising without remission that constitutes being a conscientious citizen in the reign of George W Bush was not for one who had developed a strong interest in surviving as reasonably serene." -- Nathan Zuckerman via Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328033-a-legion-of-horribles-hundreds-in-number-half-naked-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 06:46:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pablo add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328033-a-legion-of-horribles-hundreds-in-number-half-naked-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A legion of horribles, hundreds in number, half naked or clad in costumes attic or biblical or wardrobed out of a fevered dream with the skins of animals and silk finery and pieces of uniform still tracked with the blood of prior owners, coats of slain dragoons, frogged and braided cavalry jackets, one in a stovepipe hat and one with an umbrella and one in white stockings and a bloodstained wedding veil and some in headgear or cranefeathers or rawhide helmets that bore the horns of bull or buffalo and one in a pigeontailed coat worn backwards and otherwise naked and one in the armor of a Spanish conquistador, the breastplate and pauldrons deeply dented with old blows of mace or sabre done in another country by men whose very bones were dust and many with their braids spliced up with the hair of other beasts until they trailed upon the ground and their horses' ears and tails worked with bits of brightly colored cloth and one whose horse's whole head was painted crimson red and all the horsemen's faces gaudy and grotesque with daubings like a company of mounted clowns, death hilarious, all howling in a barbarous tongue and riding down upon them like a horde from a hell more horrible yet than the brimstone land of Christian reckoning, screeching and yammering and clothed in smoke like those vaporous beings in regions beyond right knowing where the eye wanders and the lip jerks and drools." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12042-that-which-can-be-asserted-without-evidence-can-be-dismissed</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 10:44:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pablo add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12042-that-which-can-be-asserted-without-evidence-can-be-dismissed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That which can be asserted without evidence, can be dismissed without evidence." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83838-if-you-can-t-fix-it-you-have-to-stand-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 07:08:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pablo add a quote by Annie Proulx (Brokeback Mountain)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83838-if-you-can-t-fix-it-you-have-to-stand-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can't fix it, you have to stand it." -- Annie Proulx (Brokeback Mountain)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52073-the-first-draft-of-anything-is-shit</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 19:37:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pablo add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52073-the-first-draft-of-anything-is-shit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first draft of anything is shit." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4808-success-is-getting-what-you-want-happiness-is-wanting-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2013 07:07:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pablo add a quote by W. P. Kinsella]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4808-success-is-getting-what-you-want-happiness-is-wanting-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Success is getting what you want, happiness is wanting what you get" -- W. P. Kinsella]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/424978-there-can-be-no-progress-without-head-on-confrontation</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 09:57:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pablo add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/424978-there-can-be-no-progress-without-head-on-confrontation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There can be no progress without head-on confrontation." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/168930-the-world-soon-to-be-largely-populated-by-men-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 11:35:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pablo add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/168930-the-world-soon-to-be-largely-populated-by-men-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world soon to be largely populated by men who would eat your children in front of your eyes and the cities themselves held by cores of blackened looters who tunneled among the ruins and crawled from the rubble white of tooth and eye carrying charred and anynymous tins of food in nylon nets like shoppers in the commissaries of hell. The soft black talc blew through the streets like squid ink uncoiling along a sea floor and the cold crept down and the dark came early and the scavengers passing down the steep canyons with their torches trod silky holes in the drifted ash that closed behind them silently as eyes. Out on the roads the pilgrims sank down and fell over and died and the bleak and shrouded earth went trundling past the sun and returned again as trackless and as unremarked as the path of any nameless sisterworld in the ancient dark beyond." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5539-a-few-light-taps-upon-the-pane-made-him-turn</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 07:08:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pablo add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5539-a-few-light-taps-upon-the-pane-made-him-turn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A few light taps upon the pane made him turn to the window. It had begun to snow again. He watched sleepily the flakes, silver and dark, falling obliquely against the lamplight. The time had come for him to set out on his journey westward. Yes, the newspapers were right: snow was general all over Ireland. It was falling on every part of the dark central plain, on the treeless hills, falling softly upon the Bog of Allen and, farther westward, softly falling into the dark mutinous Shannon waves. It was falling, too, upon every part of the lonely churchyard on the hill where Michael Furey lay buried. It lay thickly drifted on the crooked crosses and headstones, on the spears of the little gate, on the barren thorns. His soul swooned slowly as he heard the snow falling faintly through the universe and faintly falling, like the descent of their last end, upon all the living and the dead." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525471-man-surprised-me-most-about-humanity-because-he-sacrifices-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 12:42:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pablo add a quote by James J. Lachard (Jim Brown)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525471-man-surprised-me-most-about-humanity-because-he-sacrifices-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man surprised me most about humanity. Because he sacrifices his health in order to make money.
Then he sacrifices money to recuperate his health. And then he is so anxious about the future that he does not enjoy the present; the result being that he does not live in the present or the future; he lives as if he is never going to die, and then dies having never really lived." -- James J. Lachard (Jim Brown)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24141-ignorance-more-frequently-begets-confidence-than-does-knowledge-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 08:54:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pablo add a quote by Charles Darwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24141-ignorance-more-frequently-begets-confidence-than-does-knowledge-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ignorance more frequently begets confidence than does knowledge: it is those who know little, not those who know much, who so positively assert that this or that problem will never be solved by science." -- Charles Darwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/535702-religion-was-invented-when-the-first-con-man-met-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 10:12:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pablo add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/535702-religion-was-invented-when-the-first-con-man-met-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Religion was invented when the first con man met the first fool." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
