<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/198484-harold-ogle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/198484-harold-ogle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 09:55:36 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297335-her-eyes-were-glittering-like-the-eyes-of-a-child</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 09:55:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297335-her-eyes-were-glittering-like-the-eyes-of-a-child]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her eyes were glittering like the eyes of a child when you give a  nice surprise, and she laughed with a sudden throaty, tingling way.  It is the way a woman laughs for happiness.  They never laugh that way just when they are being polite or at a joke.  A woman only laughs that way a few times in her life.  A woman only laughs that way when something has touched her way down in the very quick of her being and the happiness just wells out as natural as breath and the first jonquils and mountain brooks.  When a woman laughs that way it always does something to you.  It does not matter what kind of a face she has got either.  You hear that laugh and feel that you have grasped a clean and beautiful truth.  You feel that way because that laugh is a revelation.  It is a great impersonal sincerity.  It is a spray of dewy blossom from the great central stalk of All Being, and the woman’s name and address hasn’t got a damn thing to do with it.  Therefore, the laugh cannot be faked.  If a woman could learn to fake it she would make Nell Gwyn and Pompadour look like a couple of Campfire Girls wearing bifocals and ground-gripper shoes with bands on their teeth.  She could get all society by the ears.  For all any man really wants is to hear a woman laugh like that." -- Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2887-if-you-judge-people-you-have-no-time-to-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 10:09:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2887-if-you-judge-people-you-have-no-time-to-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you judge people, you have no time to love them." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99885-happiness-quite-unshared-can-scarcely-be-called-happiness-it-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 07:33:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99885-happiness-quite-unshared-can-scarcely-be-called-happiness-it-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness quite unshared can scarcely be called happiness; it has no taste." -- Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119085-who-hears-music-feels-his-solitude-peopled-at-once</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 07:27:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Robert Browning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119085-who-hears-music-feels-his-solitude-peopled-at-once]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who hears music, feels his solitude
Peopled at once." -- Robert Browning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1227-of-all-forms-of-caution-caution-in-love-is-perhaps</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 19:50:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1227-of-all-forms-of-caution-caution-in-love-is-perhaps]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of all forms of caution, caution in love is perhaps the most fatal to true happiness." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 13:18:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5-an-expert-is-a-person-who-has-made-all-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 13:18:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Niels Bohr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5-an-expert-is-a-person-who-has-made-all-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An expert is a person who has made all the mistakes that can be made in a very narrow field." -- Niels Bohr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188928-the-true-alchemists-do-not-change-lead-into-gold-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 08:02:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by William H. Gass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188928-the-true-alchemists-do-not-change-lead-into-gold-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The true alchemists do not change lead into gold; they change the world into words." -- William H. Gass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81428-d-on-t-ever-apologize-to-an-author-for-buying-something-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 08:09:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81428-d-on-t-ever-apologize-to-an-author-for-buying-something-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[D]on't ever apologize to an author for buying something in paperback, or taking it out from a library (that's what they're there for. Use your library). Don't apologize to this author for buying books second hand, or getting them from bookcrossing or borrowing a friend's copy. What's important to me is that people read the books and enjoy them, and that, at some point in there, the book was bought by someone. And that people who like things, tell other people. The most important thing is that people read... " -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138266-no-mockery-in-this-world-ever-sounds-to-me-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 08:09:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138266-no-mockery-in-this-world-ever-sounds-to-me-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No mockery in this world ever sounds to me so hollow as that of being told to cultivate happiness. What does such advice mean? Happiness is not a potato, to be planted in mould, and tilled with manure. Happiness is a glory shining far down upon us out of Heaven. She is a divine dew which the soul, on certain of its summer mornings, feels dropping upon it from the amaranth bloom and golden fruitage of Paradise." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13146-never-trust-anyone-who-has-not-brought-a-book-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 15:44:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13146-never-trust-anyone-who-has-not-brought-a-book-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never trust anyone who has not brought a book with them." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244101-break-the-spine-of-one-of-my-books-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 15:44:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Mia James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244101-break-the-spine-of-one-of-my-books-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Break the spine of one of my books and I break yours." -- Mia James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 15:44:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened." -- Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3356-i-like-nonsense-it-wakes-up-the-brain-cells-fantasy</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 15:51:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3356-i-like-nonsense-it-wakes-up-the-brain-cells-fantasy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like nonsense, it wakes up the brain cells. Fantasy is a necessary ingredient in living." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20171-there-are-three-rules-for-writing-a-novel-unfortunately-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 16:04:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20171-there-are-three-rules-for-writing-a-novel-unfortunately-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are three rules for writing a novel. Unfortunately, no one knows what they are." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335887-now-i-am-in-control-he-followed-this-statement-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 08:39:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Phil Foglio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335887-now-i-am-in-control-he-followed-this-statement-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now I am in control!&quot; He followed this statement with a burst of laughter that showed the owner had done a fair share of gloating in his time, and had the basics down pat." -- Phil Foglio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1268-however-many-holy-words-you-read-however-many-you-speak</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 15:59:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Buddha Siddhartha Guatama Shakyamuni]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1268-however-many-holy-words-you-read-however-many-you-speak]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["However many holy words you read, however many you speak, what good will they do you if you do not act on upon them?" -- Buddha Siddhartha Guatama Shakyamuni]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53152-if-you-want-to-convince-children-of-the-power-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 16:15:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Roger Sutton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53152-if-you-want-to-convince-children-of-the-power-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["if you want to convince children of the power of books, don’t tell them stories are good. Tell them a good story." -- Roger Sutton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1139-she-generally-gave-herself-very-good-advice-though-she-very</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 16:51:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1139-she-generally-gave-herself-very-good-advice-though-she-very]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She generally gave herself very good advice, (though she very seldom followed it)." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17335-perhaps-it-s-impossible-to-wear-an-identity-without-becoming-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 11:14:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Orson Scott Card]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17335-perhaps-it-s-impossible-to-wear-an-identity-without-becoming-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps it's impossible to wear an identity without becoming what you pretend to be." -- Orson Scott Card]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437516-you-should-date-a-girl-who-reads-date-a-girl</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 15:59:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Rosemarie Urquico]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437516-you-should-date-a-girl-who-reads-date-a-girl]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You should date a girl who reads.
Date a girl who reads. Date a girl who spends her money on books instead of clothes, who has problems with closet space because she has too many books. Date a girl who has a list of books she wants to read, who has had a library card since she was twelve.

Find a girl who reads. You’ll know that she does because she will always have an unread book in her bag. She’s the one lovingly looking over the shelves in the bookstore, the one who quietly cries out when she has found the book she wants. You see that weird chick sniffing the pages of an old book in a secondhand book shop? That’s the reader. They can never resist smelling the pages, especially when they are yellow and worn.

She’s the girl reading while waiting in that coffee shop down the street. If you take a peek at her mug, the non-dairy creamer is floating on top because she’s kind of engrossed already. Lost in a world of the author’s making. Sit down. She might give you a glare, as most girls who read do not like to be interrupted. Ask her if she likes the book.

Buy her another cup of coffee.

Let her know what you really think of Murakami. See if she got through the first chapter of Fellowship. Understand that if she says she understood James Joyce’s Ulysses she’s just saying that to sound intelligent.  Ask her if she loves Alice or she would like to be Alice.

It’s easy to date a girl who reads. Give her books for her birthday, for Christmas, for anniversaries. Give her the gift of words, in poetry and in song. Give her Neruda, Pound, Sexton, Cummings. Let her know that you understand that words are love. Understand that she knows the difference between books and reality but by god, she’s going to try to make her life a little like her favorite book. It will never be your fault if she does.

She has to give it a shot somehow.

Lie to her. If she understands syntax, she will understand your need to lie. Behind words are other things: motivation, value, nuance, dialogue. It will not be the end of the world.

Fail her. Because a girl who reads knows that failure always leads up to the climax. Because girls who read understand that all things must come to end, but that you can always write a sequel. That you can begin again and again and still be the hero. That life is meant to have a villain or two.

Why be frightened of everything that you are not? Girls who read understand that people, like characters, develop. Except in the Twilight series.

If you find a girl who reads, keep her close. When you find her up at 2 AM clutching a book to her chest and weeping, make her a cup of tea and hold her. You may lose her for a couple of hours but she will always come back to you. She’ll talk as if the characters in the book are real, because for a while, they always are.

You will propose on a hot air balloon. Or during a rock concert. Or very casually next time she’s sick. Over Skype.

You will smile so hard you will wonder why your heart hasn’t burst and bled out all over your chest yet. You will write the story of your lives, have kids with strange names and even stranger tastes. She will introduce your children to the Cat in the Hat and Aslan, maybe in the same day. You will walk the winters of your old age together and she will recite Keats under her breath while you shake the snow off your boots.

Date a girl who reads because you deserve it. You deserve a girl who can give you the most colorful life imaginable. If you can only give her monotony, and stale hours and half-baked proposals, then you’re better off alone. If you want the world and the worlds beyond it, date a girl who reads.

Or better yet, date a girl who writes." -- Rosemarie Urquico]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1194-life-s-hard-it-s-even-harder-when-you-re-stupid</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 15:23:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by John Wayne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1194-life-s-hard-it-s-even-harder-when-you-re-stupid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life's hard. It's even harder when you're stupid." -- John Wayne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228974-write-what-you-know-that-should-leave-you-with-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 18:45:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Howard Nemerov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228974-write-what-you-know-that-should-leave-you-with-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Write what you know. That should leave you with a lot of free time." -- Howard Nemerov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75457-humor-keeps-us-alive-humor-and-food-don-t-forget-food</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 18:51:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75457-humor-keeps-us-alive-humor-and-food-don-t-forget-food]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humor keeps us alive. Humor and food. Don't forget food. You can go a week without laughing." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9654-live-in-such-a-way-that-you-would-not-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 18:56:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Will Rogers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9654-live-in-such-a-way-that-you-would-not-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Live in such a way that you would not be ashamed to sell your parrot to the town gossip." -- Will Rogers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47409-don-t-let-yesterday-take-up-too-much-of-today</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 18:58:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Will Rogers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47409-don-t-let-yesterday-take-up-too-much-of-today]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't let yesterday take up too much of today" -- Will Rogers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14365-i-am-not-a-member-of-any-organized-political-party</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 18:59:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Will Rogers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14365-i-am-not-a-member-of-any-organized-political-party]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am not a member of any organized political party — I am a Democrat. " -- Will Rogers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/466354-when-i-die-i-want-to-die-like-my-grandfather</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 19:00:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Will Rogers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/466354-when-i-die-i-want-to-die-like-my-grandfather]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I die, I want to die like my grandfather who died peacefully in his sleep. Not screaming like all the passengers in his car." -- Will Rogers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/605563-good-judgment-comes-from-experience-and-a-lot-of-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 19:02:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Will Rogers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/605563-good-judgment-comes-from-experience-and-a-lot-of-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good judgment comes from experience, and a lot of that comes from bad judgment." -- Will Rogers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6805-sometimes-the-questions-are-complicated-and-the-answers-are-simple</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 08:47:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harold add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6805-sometimes-the-questions-are-complicated-and-the-answers-are-simple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes the questions are complicated and the answers are simple." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
