<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/199183-ian]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/199183-ian" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 14:45:01 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7079-after-all-what-was-the-whole-wide-world-but-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 14:45:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by Richard Russo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7079-after-all-what-was-the-whole-wide-world-but-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After all, what was the whole wide world but a place for people to yearn for their heart's impossible desires, for those desires to become entrenched in defiance of logic, plausibility, and even the passage of time, as eternal as polished marble.                              " -- Richard Russo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246003-philosophy-i-studied-philosophy-for-four-years-but-i-d-trade</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 15:09:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by A.J. Jacobs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246003-philosophy-i-studied-philosophy-for-four-years-but-i-d-trade]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["philosophy
I studied philosophy for four years. But I'd trade everything I learned for this passage... quoted in the Britannica:
'But we were born of risen apes, not fallen angels, and the apes were armed killers besides. And so what shall we wonder at? Our murders and massacres and missiles, and our irreconcilable regiments? Or our treaties whatever they may be worth; our symphonies however seldom they may be played; our peaceful acres, however frequently they may be converted into battlefields; our dreams however rarely they may be accomplished. The miracle of man is not how far he has sunk but how magnificently he has risen. We are known among the stars by our poems, not our corpses.'
Amen." -- A.J. Jacobs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8776-maybe-we-all-live-life-at-too-high-a-pitch</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 10:49:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8776-maybe-we-all-live-life-at-too-high-a-pitch]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe we all live life at too high a pitch, those of us who absorb emotional things all day, and as mere consequence we can never feel merely content: we have to be unhappy, or ecstatically, head-over-heels happy, and those states are difficult to achieve within a stable, solid relationship." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
