<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/199238-john]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/199238-john" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 10:26:08 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 10:26:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/356-i-learned-this-at-least-by-my-experiment-that-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 10:26:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/356-i-learned-this-at-least-by-my-experiment-that-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I learned this, at least, by my experiment: that if one advances confidently in the direction of his dreams, and endeavors to live the life which he has imagined, he will meet with a success unexpected in common hours." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3124-our-truest-life-is-when-we-are-in-dreams-awake</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 10:27:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3124-our-truest-life-is-when-we-are-in-dreams-awake]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our truest life is when we are in dreams awake." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2021-do-not-be-too-moral-you-may-cheat-yourself-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 10:27:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2021-do-not-be-too-moral-you-may-cheat-yourself-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not be too moral. You may cheat yourself out of much life so. Aim above morality. Be not simply good, be good for something." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5892-our-life-is-frittered-away-by-detail-simplify-simplify</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 10:27:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5892-our-life-is-frittered-away-by-detail-simplify-simplify]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our life is frittered away by detail. Simplify, simplify." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5998-we-must-learn-to-reawaken-and-keep-ourselves-awake-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 10:27:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5998-we-must-learn-to-reawaken-and-keep-ourselves-awake-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must learn to reawaken and keep ourselves awake, not by mechanical aids, but by an infinite expectation of the dawn, which does not forsake us even in our soundest sleep. I know of no more encouraging fact than the unquestionable ability of man to elevate his life by a conscious endeavour. It is something to be able to paint a particular picture, or to carve a statue, and so to make a few objects beautiful; but it is far more glorious to carve and paint the very atmosphere and medium through which we look, which morally we can do. To affect the quality of the day, that is the highest of arts." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11123-there-is-no-remedy-for-love-but-to-love-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 10:27:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11123-there-is-no-remedy-for-love-but-to-love-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no remedy for love, but to love more." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120243-long-before-i-became-a-feminist-in-any-explicit-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 18:25:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Joanna Russ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120243-long-before-i-became-a-feminist-in-any-explicit-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Long before I became a feminist in any explicit way, I had turned from writing love stories about women in which women were losers, and adventure stories about men in which the men were winners, to writing adventure stories about a woman in which the woman won. It was one of the hardest things I ever did in my life." -- Joanna Russ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/779-love-doesn-t-just-sit-there-like-a-stone-it-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 19:33:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/779-love-doesn-t-just-sit-there-like-a-stone-it-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love doesn't just sit there, like a stone, it has to be made, like bread; remade all the time, made new." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4031-what-sane-person-could-live-in-this-world-and-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 19:33:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ursula K. LeGuin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4031-what-sane-person-could-live-in-this-world-and-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What sane person could live in this world and not be crazy?" -- Ursula K. LeGuin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18936-we-read-books-to-find-out-who-we-are-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 19:33:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ursula K. LeGuin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18936-we-read-books-to-find-out-who-we-are-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We read books to find out who we are.  What other people, real or imaginary, do and think and feel... is an essential guide to our understanding of what we ourselves are and may become." -- Ursula K. LeGuin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24392-the-book-itself-is-a-curious-artifact-not-showy-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 19:33:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24392-the-book-itself-is-a-curious-artifact-not-showy-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The book itself is a curious artifact, not showy in its technology but complex and extremely efficient: a really neat little device, compact, often very pleasant to look at and handle, that can last decades, even centuries. It doesn't have to be plugged in, activated, or performed by a machine; all it needs is light, a human eye, and a human mind. It is not one of a kind, and it is not ephemeral. It lasts. It is reliable. If a book told you something when you were fifteen, it will tell it to you again when you're fifty, though you may understand it so differently that it seems you're reading a whole new book.&quot;

(&lt;i&gt;Staying Awake: Notes on the alleged decline of reading&lt;/i&gt;, Harper's Magazine, February 2008)" -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99607-as-you-read-a-book-word-by-word-and-page</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 19:34:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99607-as-you-read-a-book-word-by-word-and-page]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As you read a book word by word and page by page, you participate in its creation, just as a cellist playing a Bach suite participates, note by note, in the creation, the coming-to-be, the existence, of the music. And, as you read and re-read, the book of course participates in the creation of you, your thoughts and feelings, the size and temper of your soul." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39653-this-is-and-thou-art-there-is-no-safety-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 19:34:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ursula K. LeGuin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39653-this-is-and-thou-art-there-is-no-safety-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is. And thou art. There is no safety. There is no end. The word must be heard in silence. There must be darkness to see the stars. The dance is always danced above the hollow place, above the terrible abyss." -- Ursula K. LeGuin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129860-while-we-read-a-novel-we-are-insane-bonkers-we-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 19:34:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129860-while-we-read-a-novel-we-are-insane-bonkers-we-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["While we read a novel, we are insane—bonkers. We believe in the existence of people who aren't there, we hear their voices... Sanity returns (in most cases) when the book is closed." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166432-it-is-our-suffering-that-brings-us-together-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 19:35:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166432-it-is-our-suffering-that-brings-us-together-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is our suffering that brings us together. It is not love. Love does not obey the mind, and turns to hate when forced. The bond that binds us is beyond choice. We are brothers. We are brothers in what we share. In pain, which each of us must suffer alone, in hunger, in poverty, in hope, we know our brotherhood. We know it, because we have had to learn it. We know that there is no help for us but from one another, that no hand will save us if we do not reach out our hand. And the hand that you reach out is empty, as mine is. You have nothing. You possess nothing. You own nothing. You are free. All you have is what you are, and what you give." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58660-what-is-an-anarchist-one-who-choosing-accepts-the-responsibility</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 19:35:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58660-what-is-an-anarchist-one-who-choosing-accepts-the-responsibility]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is an anarchist? One who, choosing, accepts the responsibility of choice." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102895-they-have-nothing-to-give-they-have-no-power-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 19:44:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102895-they-have-nothing-to-give-they-have-no-power-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They have nothing to give. They have no power of making. All their power is to darken and destroy. They cannot leave this place; they are this place; and it should be left to them. They should not be denied nor forgotten, but neither should they be worshiped. The Earth is beautiful, and bright, and kindly, but that is not all. The Earth is also terrible, and dark, and cruel. The rabbit shrieks dying in the green meadows. The mountains clench their great hands full of hidden fire. There are sharks in the sea, and there is cruelty in men’s eyes. And where men worship these things and abase themselves before them, there evil breeds; there places are made in the world where darkness gathers, places given over wholly to the Ones whom we call Nameless, the ancient and holy Powers of the Earth before the Light, the powers of the dark, of ruin, of madness… I think they drove your priestess Kossil mad a long time ago; I think she has prowled these caverns as she prowls the labyrinth of her own self, and now she cannot see the daylight any more. She tells you that the Nameless Ones are dead; only a lost soul, lost to truth, could believe that. They exist. But they are not your Masters. They never were. You are free, Tenar. You were taught to be a slave, but you have broken free." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190716-if-a-book-told-you-something-when-you-were-fifteen</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 19:46:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190716-if-a-book-told-you-something-when-you-were-fifteen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a book told you something when you were fifteen, it will tell you it again when you're fifty, though you may understand it so differently that it seems you're reading a whole new book." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24729-there-are-it-seems-two-muses-the-muse-of-inspiration</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 20:41:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24729-there-are-it-seems-two-muses-the-muse-of-inspiration]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are, it seems, two muses: the Muse of Inspiration, who gives us inarticulate visions and desires, and the Muse of Realization, who returns again and again to say &quot;It is yet more difficult than you thought.&quot; This is the muse of form. It may be then that form serves us best when it works as an obstruction, to baffle us and deflect our intended course. It may be that when we no longer know what to do, we have come to our real work and when we no longer know which way to go, we have begun our real journey. The mind that is not baffled is not employed. The impeded stream is the one that sings." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129307-we-have-lived-our-lives-by-the-assumption-that-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 20:43:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129307-we-have-lived-our-lives-by-the-assumption-that-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have lived our lives by the assumption that what was good for us would be good for the world. We have been wrong. We must change our lives so that it will be possible to live by the contrary assumption, that what is good for the world will be good for us. And that requires that we make the effort to know the world and learn what is good for it." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12198-better-than-any-argument-is-to-rise-at-dawn-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 20:43:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12198-better-than-any-argument-is-to-rise-at-dawn-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Better than any argument is to rise at dawn and pick dew-wet red berries in a cup." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169385-nobody-can-discover-the-world-for-somebody-else-only-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 20:43:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169385-nobody-can-discover-the-world-for-somebody-else-only-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody can discover the world for somebody else.  Only when we discover it for ourselves does it become common ground and a common bond and we cease to be alone." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261818-in-a-society-in-which-nearly-everybody-is-dominated-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 20:45:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261818-in-a-society-in-which-nearly-everybody-is-dominated-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a society in which nearly everybody is dominated by somebody else's mind or by a disembodied mind, it becomes increasingly difficult to learn the truth about the activities of governments and corporations, about the quality or value of products, or about the health of one's own place and economy.
In such a society, also, our private economies will depend less and less upon the private ownership of real, usable property, and more and more upon property that is institutional and abstract, beyond individual control, such as money, insurance policies, certificates of deposit, stocks, and shares. And as our private economies become more abstract, the mutual, free helps and pleasures of family and community life will be supplanted by a kind of displaced or placeless citizenship and by commerce with impersonal and self-interested suppliers...
Thus, although we are not slaves in name, and cannot be carried to market and sold as somebody else's legal chattels, we are free only within narrow limits.  For all our talk about liberation and personal autonomy, there are few choices that we are free to make.  What would be the point, for example, if a majority of our people decided to be self-employed?
The great enemy of freedom is the alignment of political power with wealth.  This alignment destroys the commonwealth - that is, the natural wealth of localities and the local economies of household, neighborhood, and community - and so destroys democracy, of which the commonwealth is the foundation and practical means." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21311-i-see-that-the-life-of-this-place-is-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 20:46:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21311-i-see-that-the-life-of-this-place-is-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I see that the life of this place is always emerging beyond expectation or prediction or typicality, that it is unique, given to the world minute by minute, only once, never to be repeated. And this is when I see that this life is a miracle, absolutely worth having, absolutely worth saving.  We are alive within mystery, by miracle." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104206-i-took-her-into-bed-with-me-and-propped-myself</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 20:47:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104206-i-took-her-into-bed-with-me-and-propped-myself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I took her into bed with me and propped myself up with pillows against the headboard to let her nurse. As she nursed and the milk came, she began a little low contented sort of singing. I would feel milk and love flowing from me to her as once it had flowed to me. It emptied me. As the baby fed, I seemed slowly to grow empty of myself, as if in the presence of that long flow of love even grief could not stand." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83945-the-world-is-indeed-comic-but-the-joke-is-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 05:39:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by H. P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83945-the-world-is-indeed-comic-but-the-joke-is-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is indeed comic, but the joke is on mankind." -- H. P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23101-pleasure-to-me-is-wonder-the-unexplored-the-unexpected-the-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 05:40:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23101-pleasure-to-me-is-wonder-the-unexplored-the-unexpected-the-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pleasure to me is wonder—the unexplored, the unexpected, the thing that is hidden and the changeless thing that lurks behind superficial mutability. To trace the remote in the immediate; the eternal in the ephemeral; the past in the present; the infinite in the finite; these are to me the springs of delight and beauty." -- H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167404-never-explain-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 05:40:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167404-never-explain-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never Explain Anything" -- H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211741-if-i-am-mad-it-is-mercy-may-the-gods</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 05:40:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211741-if-i-am-mad-it-is-mercy-may-the-gods]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I am mad, it is mercy! May the gods pity the man who in his callousness can remain sane to the hideous end!" -- H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
