<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/200718-tracy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/200718-tracy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 16:28:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4772-i-am-tomorrow-or-some-future-day-what-i-establish</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 16:28:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4772-i-am-tomorrow-or-some-future-day-what-i-establish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am tomorrow, or some future day, what I establish today. I am today what I established yesterday or some previous day." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/651-all-that-we-see-or-seem-is-but-a-dream</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 16:19:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/651-all-that-we-see-or-seem-is-but-a-dream]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that we see or seem is but a dream within a dream." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48648-once-upon-a-midnight-dreary-while-i-pondered-weak-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 17:33:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48648-once-upon-a-midnight-dreary-while-i-pondered-weak-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a midnight dreary, while I pondered, weak and weary,
Over many a quaint and curious volume of forgotten lore,
While I nodded, nearly napping, suddenly there came a tapping,
As of some one gently rapping, rapping at my chamber door.
Tis some visitor,&quot; I muttered, &quot;tapping at my chamber door —
      Only this, and nothing more.&quot;

Ah, distinctly I remember it was in the bleak December,
And each separate dying ember wrought its ghost upon the floor.
Eagerly I wished the morrow; — vainly I had sought to borrow
From my books surcease of sorrow — sorrow for the lost Lenore —
For the rare and radiant maiden whom the angels name Lenore —
      Nameless here for evermore.

And the silken sad uncertain rustling of each purple curtain
Thrilled me — filled me with fantastic terrors never felt before;
So that now, to still the beating of my heart, I stood repeating,
Tis some visitor entreating entrance at my chamber door —
Some late visitor entreating entrance at my chamber door; —
    This it is, and nothing more.&quot;

Presently my soul grew stronger; hesitating then no longer,
Sir,&quot; said I, &quot;or Madam, truly your forgiveness I implore;
But the fact is I was napping, and so gently you came rapping,
And so faintly you came tapping, tapping at my chamber door,
That I scarce was sure I heard you&quot;— here I opened wide the door; —
    Darkness there, and nothing more.

Deep into that darkness peering, long I stood there wondering, fearing,
Doubting, dreaming dreams no mortals ever dared to dream before;
But the silence was unbroken, and the stillness gave no token,
And the only word there spoken was the whispered word, &quot;Lenore?&quot;
This I whispered, and an echo murmured back the word, &quot;Lenore!&quot; —
      Merely this, and nothing more.

Back into the chamber turning, all my soul within me burning,
Soon again I heard a tapping somewhat louder than before.
Surely,&quot; said I, &quot;surely that is something at my window lattice:
Let me see, then, what thereat is, and this mystery explore —
Let my heart be still a moment and this mystery explore; —
    'Tis the wind and nothing more.&quot;

Open here I flung the shutter, when, with many a flirt and flutter,
In there stepped a stately raven of the saintly days of yore;
Not the least obeisance made he; not a minute stopped or stayed he;
But, with mien of lord or lady, perched above my chamber door —
Perched upon a bust of Pallas just above my chamber door —
    Perched, and sat, and nothing more.

Then this ebony bird beguiling my sad fancy into smiling,
By the grave and stern decorum of the countenance it wore.
Though thy crest be shorn and shaven, thou,&quot; I said, &quot;art sure no craven,
Ghastly grim and ancient raven wandering from the Nightly shore —
Tell me what thy lordly name is on the Night's Plutonian shore!&quot;
      Quoth the Raven, &quot;Nevermore.&quot;

Much I marveled this ungainly fowl to hear discourse so plainly,
Though its answer little meaning— little relevancy bore;
For we cannot help agreeing that no living human being
Ever yet was blest with seeing bird above his chamber door —
Bird or beast upon the sculptured bust above his chamber door,
      With such name as &quot;Nevermore." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 17:33:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one can make you feel inferior without your consent." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1944-a-woman-is-like-a-tea-bag-you-never-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 17:33:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1944-a-woman-is-like-a-tea-bag-you-never-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A woman is like a tea bag; you never know how strong it is until it's in hot water." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3929-yesterday-is-history-tomorrow-is-a-mystery-today-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 17:33:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Bill Keane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3929-yesterday-is-history-tomorrow-is-a-mystery-today-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yesterday is history, tomorrow is a mystery, today is a gift of God, which is why we call it the present." -- Bill Keane]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
