<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/201127-julia]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/201127-julia" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2008 15:58:21 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27180-right-i-look-fine-except-i-don-t-said-zora-tugging</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2008 15:58:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27180-right-i-look-fine-except-i-don-t-said-zora-tugging]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Right.  I look fine. Except I don't,' said Zora, tugging sadly at her man's nightshirt.  This was why Kiki had dreaded having girls: she knew she wouldn't be able to protect them from self-disgust.  To that end she had tried banning television in the early years, and never had a lipstick or a woman's magazine crossed the threshold of the Belsey home to Kiki's knowledge, but these and other precautionary measures had made no difference.  It was in the air, or so it seemed to Kiki, this hatred of women and their bodies-- it seeped in with every draught in the house; people brought it home on their shoes, they breathed it in off their newspapers.  There was no way to control it." -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27185-people-often-ask-me-why-my-style-is-so-simple</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2008 16:01:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Ruskin Bond]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27185-people-often-ask-me-why-my-style-is-so-simple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People often ask me why my style is so simple.  It is, in fact, deceptively simple, for no two sentences are alike.  It is clarity that I am striving to attain, not simplicity.

Of course, some people want literature to be difficult and there are writers who like to make their readers toil and sweat.  They hope to be taken more seriously that way.  I have always tried to achieve a prose that is easy and conversational.  And those who think this is simple should try it for themselves." -- Ruskin Bond]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24015-you-do-not-have-to-be-good-you-do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2008 17:49:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24015-you-do-not-have-to-be-good-you-do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You do not have to be good.
You do not have to walk on your knees
for a hundred miles through the desert, repenting.
You only have to let the soft animal of your body 
love what it loves.
Tell me about despair, yours, and I will tell you mine.
Meanwhile the world goes on.
Meanwhile the sun and the clear pebbles of the rain
are moving across the landscapes,
over the prairies and the deep trees,
the mountains and the rivers.
Meanwhile the wild geese, high in the clean blue air,
are heading home again.
Whoever you are, no matter how lonely,
the world offers itself to your imagination,
calls to you like the wild geese, harsh and exciting –
over and over announcing your place
in the family of things." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21364-hello-sun-in-my-face-hello-you-who-made-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2008 17:49:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21364-hello-sun-in-my-face-hello-you-who-made-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hello, sun in my face. Hello you who made the morning and spread it over the fields...Watch, now, how I start the day in happiness, in kindness." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160756-on-the-girl-s-brown-legs-there-were-many-small-white</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2010 13:32:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Chris Cleave]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160756-on-the-girl-s-brown-legs-there-were-many-small-white]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the girl's brown legs there were many small white scars. I was thinking, Do those scars cover the whole of you, like the stars and the moons on your dress? I thought that would be pretty too, and I ask you right here please to agree with me that a scar is never ugly. That is what the scar makers want us to think. But you and I, we must make an agreement to defy them. We must see all scars as beauty. Okay? This will be our secret. Because take it from me, a scar does not form on the dying. A scar means, I survived." -- Chris Cleave]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
