<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/201275-richard]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/201275-richard" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 05:48:46 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318191-sometimes-when-i-get-up-and-emerge-from-the-mists</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 05:48:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Bohumil Hrabal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318191-sometimes-when-i-get-up-and-emerge-from-the-mists]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes when I get up and emerge from the mists of slumber, my whole room hurts, my whole bedroom, the view from the window hurts, kids go to school, people go shopping, everybody knows where to go, only I don't know where I want to go, I get dressed, blearily, stumbling, hopping about to pull on my trousers, I go and shave with my electric razor - for years now, whenever I shave, I've avoided looking at myself in the mirror, I shave in the dark or round the corner, sitting on a chair in the passage, with the socket in the bathroom,  I don't like looking at myself any more, I'm scared by my own face in the bathroom, I'm hurt even by my own appearance, I see yesterday's drunkenness in my eyes, I don't even have breakfast any more, or if I do, only coffee and a cigarette, I sit at the table, sometimes my hands give way under me and several times I repeat to myself, Hrabal, Hrabal, Bohumil Hrabal, you've victoried yourself away, you've reached the peak of emptiness, as my Lao Tzu taught me, I've reached the peak of emptiness and everything hurts, even the walk to the bus-stop hurts, and the whole bus hurts as well, I lower my guilty-looking eyes, I'm afraid of looking people in the eye, sometimes I cross my palms and extend my wrists, I hold out my hands so that people can arrest me and hand me over to the cops, because I feel guilty even about this once too loud a solitude which isn't loud any longer, because I'm hurt not only by the escalator which takes me down to the infernal regions below, I'm hurt even by the looks of the people travelling up, each of them has somewhere to go, while I've reached the peak of emptiness and don't know where I want to go." -- Bohumil Hrabal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183722-because-real-thoughts-come-from-outside-and-travel-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 05:51:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Bohumil Hrabal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183722-because-real-thoughts-come-from-outside-and-travel-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["... because real thoughts come from outside and travel with us like the noodle soup we take to work; in other words, inquisitors burn books in vain. If a book has anything to say, it burns with a quiet laugh, because any book worth its salt points up and out of itself." -- Bohumil Hrabal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1276896-adapt-yourself-to-the-things-among-which-your-lot-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 13:24:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1276896-adapt-yourself-to-the-things-among-which-your-lot-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Adapt yourself to the things among which your lot has been cast and love sincerely the fellow creatures with whom destiny has ordained that you shall live." -- Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
