<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/203765-shanthanu]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/203765-shanthanu" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 13:34:01 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22562-faith-is-at-one-and-the-same-time-absolutely-necessary</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 13:34:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Stanislaw Lem]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22562-faith-is-at-one-and-the-same-time-absolutely-necessary]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Faith is, at one and the same time, absolutely necessary and altogether impossible." -- Stanislaw Lem]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 13:34:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always imagined that Paradise will be a kind of library." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 07:59:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2579-do-not-read-as-children-do-to-amuse-yourself-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 23:34:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2579-do-not-read-as-children-do-to-amuse-yourself-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not read, as children do, to amuse yourself, or like the ambitious, for the purpose of instruction. No, read in order to live." -- Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15622-where-do-i-get-my-ideas-from-you-might-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2011 17:02:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15622-where-do-i-get-my-ideas-from-you-might-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where do I get my ideas from? You might as well have asked that of Beethoven. He was goofing around in Germany like everybody else, and all of a sudden this stuff came gushing out of him. It was music. I was goofing around like everybody else in Indiana, and all of a sudden stuff came gushing out. It was disgust with civilization." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171748-to-be-is-to-do---socrates-to-do-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2011 17:02:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171748-to-be-is-to-do---socrates-to-do-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be is to do - Socrates

To do is to be - Sartre

Do Be Do Be Do - Sinatra" -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39987-men-of-god-and-men-of-war-have-strange-affinities</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2011 00:07:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39987-men-of-god-and-men-of-war-have-strange-affinities]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men of God and men of war have strange affinities." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322035-many-a-book-is-like-a-key-to-unknown-chambers</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 23:16:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322035-many-a-book-is-like-a-key-to-unknown-chambers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many a book is like a key to unknown chambers within the castle of one’s own self." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7810-let-us-be-grateful-to-the-people-who-make-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 15:52:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7810-let-us-be-grateful-to-the-people-who-make-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let us be grateful to the people who make us happy; they are the charming gardeners who make our souls blossom." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430357-of-all-man-s-instruments-the-most-wondrous-no-doubt-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 12:58:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430357-of-all-man-s-instruments-the-most-wondrous-no-doubt-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of all man’s instruments, the most wondrous, no doubt, is the book. The other instruments are extensions of his body. The microscope, the telescope, are extensions of his sight; the telephone is the extension of his voice; then we have the plow and the sword, extensions of the arm. But the book is something else altogether: the book is an extension of memory and imagination." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1025-happiness-is-a-warm-puppy</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 14:52:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1025-happiness-is-a-warm-puppy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is a warm puppy." -- Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/507424-strange-department-this-their-motto-was-the-comprehension-of-infinity</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2013 14:19:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Arkady Strugatsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/507424-strange-department-this-their-motto-was-the-comprehension-of-infinity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Strange department, this. Their motto was: &quot;The comprehension of Infinity requires infinite time.&quot; I did not argue with that, but then they derived an unexpected conclusion from it: Therefore work or not, it´s all the same.&quot;
 In the interests of not increasing the entropy of the universe, they did not work." -- Arkady Strugatsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7570-if-you-have-a-garden-and-a-library-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 07:35:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7570-if-you-have-a-garden-and-a-library-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you have a garden and a library, you have everything you need." -- Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111898-this-life-of-ours-human-life-is-like-a-flower-gloriously</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2013 15:29:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Anton Chekhov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111898-this-life-of-ours-human-life-is-like-a-flower-gloriously]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This life of ours...human life is like a flower gloriously blooming in a meadow: along comes a goat, eats it up---no more flower." -- Anton Chekhov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/666051-there-is-something-strikingly-different-about-the-quality-of-photographs</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2013 15:31:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Amitav Ghosh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/666051-there-is-something-strikingly-different-about-the-quality-of-photographs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is something strikingly different about the quality of photographs of that time. It has nothing to do with age or colour, or the feel of paper. . . . In modern family photographs the camera pretends to circulate like a friend, clicking its shutters at those moments when its subjects have disarranged themselves to present to it those postures which they would like to think of as informal. But in pictures of that time, the camera is still a public and alien eye, faced with which people feel bound either to challenge the intrusion by striking postures of defiant hilarity, or else to compose their faces, and straighten their shoulders, not always formally, but usually with just that hint of stiffness which suggests a public face." -- Amitav Ghosh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/645950-i-hadn-t-known-there-were-so-many-idiots-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 18:53:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Stanislaw Lem]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/645950-i-hadn-t-known-there-were-so-many-idiots-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hadn't known there were so many idiots in the world until I started using the Internet." -- Stanislaw Lem]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192769-the-two-most-common-elements-in-the-world-are-hydrogen</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 05:33:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Arthur Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192769-the-two-most-common-elements-in-the-world-are-hydrogen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The two most common elements in the world are hydrogen and stupidity. 
" -- Arthur Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7763-preach-the-gospel-at-all-times-and-when-necessary-use</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2013 10:48:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by St. Francis of Assisi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7763-preach-the-gospel-at-all-times-and-when-necessary-use]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Preach the Gospel at all times, and when necessary, use words." -- St. Francis of Assisi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34560-the-devil-can-cite-scripture-for-his-purpose</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2013 10:48:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34560-the-devil-can-cite-scripture-for-his-purpose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The devil can cite Scripture for his purpose." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/858528-moreover-man-carries-in-his-heart-the-desire-always-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 18:10:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Jacques Tardi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/858528-moreover-man-carries-in-his-heart-the-desire-always-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Moreover, man carries in his heart the desire always to wield his scientific knowledge in service of the greater good. He would of course never use it for destructive purposes. Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha! ..." -- Jacques Tardi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/877641-it-was-easy-to-share-when-there-was-enough-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 10:06:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shanthanu add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/877641-it-was-easy-to-share-when-there-was-enough-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was easy to share when there was enough, even barely enough, to go round. But when there was not enough? Then force entered in; might making right; power, and its tool, violence, and its most devoted ally, the averted eye." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
