<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/204436-rjhall]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/204436-rjhall" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 02:39:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148724-i-love-books-if-they-are-good-books-i-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 02:39:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Hugo Chavez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148724-i-love-books-if-they-are-good-books-i-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love books.  If they are good books, I love them even more.  But even if they are bad books, I still love them." -- Hugo Chavez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148725-i-m-a-reading-addict-i-can-t-live-without-it-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 02:41:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Hugo Chavez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148725-i-m-a-reading-addict-i-can-t-live-without-it-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm a reading addict.  I can't live without it, like someone who is addicted to drugs." -- Hugo Chavez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145140-a-book-is-made-from-a-tree-it-is-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2009 06:36:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145140-a-book-is-made-from-a-tree-it-is-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book is made from a tree. It is an assemblage of flat, flexible parts (still called &quot;leaves&quot;) imprinted with dark pigmented squiggles. One glance at it and you hear the voice of another person, perhaps someone dead for thousands of years. Across the millennia, the author is speaking, clearly and silently, inside your head, directly to you. Writing is perhaps the greatest of human inventions, binding together people, citizens of distant epochs, who never knew one another. Books break the shackles of time ― proof that humans can work magic." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220708-they-will-also-tell-you-how-far-along-we-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 00:03:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Dmitry Orlov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220708-they-will-also-tell-you-how-far-along-we-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They will also tell you how far along we are along the depletion curve; the optimists among them will even claim that there is nothing to worry about, because we have two or three decades of production left at the current level. It is to be expected that we will run out of fossil fuels before we run out of optimists, who are, along with fools and madmen, a renewable resource." -- Dmitry Orlov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82060-but-life-is-glorious-when-it-is-happy-days-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 00:07:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Isaac Asimov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82060-but-life-is-glorious-when-it-is-happy-days-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But life is glorious when it is happy; days are carefree when they are happy; the interplay of thought and imagination is far and superior to that of muscle and sinew. Let me tell you, if you don't know it from your own experience, that reading a good book, losing yourself in the interest of words and thoughts, is for some people (me, for instance) an incredible intensity of happiness." -- Isaac Asimov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54055-freiheit-ist-immer-die-freiheit-des-andersdenkenden-freedom-is-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2010 06:57:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Rosa Luxemburg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54055-freiheit-ist-immer-die-freiheit-des-andersdenkenden-freedom-is-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Freiheit ist immer die Freiheit des Andersdenkenden

Freedom is always, and exclusively, freedom for the one who thinks differently." -- Rosa Luxemburg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102430-books-are-the-treasured-wealth-of-the-world-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 03:07:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102430-books-are-the-treasured-wealth-of-the-world-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are the treasured wealth of the world and the fit inheritance of generations and nations. Books, the oldest and the best, stand naturally and rightfully on the shelves of every cottage. They have no cause of their own to plead, but while they enlighten and sustain the reader his common sense will not refuse them. Their authors are a natural and irresistible aristocracy in every society, and, more than kings or emperors, exert an influence on mankind." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/388617-depression-is-the-most-unpleasant-thing-i-have-ever-experienced</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 23:50:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/388617-depression-is-the-most-unpleasant-thing-i-have-ever-experienced]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Depression is the most unpleasant thing I have ever experienced. . . .  It is that absence of being able to envisage that you will ever be cheerful again.  The absence of hope.  That very deadened feeling, which is so very different from feeling sad.  Sad hurts but it's a healthy feeling.  It is a necessary thing to feel.  Depression is very different." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83262-m-mabeuf-s-political-opinion-was-a-passionate-fondness-for-plants</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 23:51:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Victor Hugo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83262-m-mabeuf-s-political-opinion-was-a-passionate-fondness-for-plants]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["M. Mabeuf’s political opinion was a passionate fondness for plants, and a still greater one for books. He had, like everybody else, his termination in ist, without which nobody could have lived in those times, but he was neither a royalist, nor a Bonapartist, nor a chartist, nor an Orleanist, nor an anarchist; he was an old-bookist." -- Victor Hugo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141465-she-let-her-head-fall-back-upon-marius-knees-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 23:52:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Victor Hugo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141465-she-let-her-head-fall-back-upon-marius-knees-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She let her head fall back upon Marius' knees and her eyelids closed. He thought that poor soul had gone. Eponine lay motionless; but just when Marius supposed her for ever asleep, she slowly opened her eyes in which the gloomy deepness of death appeared, and said to him with an accent the sweetness on which already seemed to come from another world:

&quot;And then, do you know, Monsieur Marius, I believe I was a little in love with you.&quot;

She essayed to smile again and expired." -- Victor Hugo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/463155-my-mind-has-touched-the-farthest-horizons-of-mortal-imagination</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 23:44:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Susan Kay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/463155-my-mind-has-touched-the-farthest-horizons-of-mortal-imagination]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My mind has touched the farthest horizons of mortal imagination and reaches ever outward to embrace infinity. There is no knowledge beyond my comprehension, no art or skill upon this entire planet that lies beyond the mastery of my hand. And yet, like Faust, I look in vain, I learn in vain. . . . For as long as I live, no woman will ever look on me in love." -- Susan Kay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/479663-it-wont-be-long-now-it-wont-be-long-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2011 05:04:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Don Marquis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/479663-it-wont-be-long-now-it-wont-be-long-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["it wont be long now it wont be long
man is making deserts of the earth
it wont be long now
before man will have used it up
so that nothing but ants
and centipedes and scorpions
can find a living on it
....
what man calls civilization
always results in deserts
....
men talk of money and industry
of hard times and recoveries
of finance and economics
but the ants wait and the scorpions wait
for while men talk they are making deserts all the time
getting the world ready for the conquering ant
drought and erosion and desert
because men cannot learn
....
it wont be long now it wont be long
till earth is barren as the moon
and sapless as a mumbled bone" -- Don Marquis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480441-he-tried-to-read-an-elementary-economics-text-it-bored</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 02:11:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480441-he-tried-to-read-an-elementary-economics-text-it-bored]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He tried to read an elementary economics text; it bored him past endurance, it was like listening to somebody interminably recounting a long and stupid dream. He could not force himself to understand how banks functioned and so forth, because all the operations of capitalism were as meaningless to him as the rites of a primitive religion, as barbaric, as elaborate, and as unnecessary. In a human sacrifice to deity there might be at least a mistaken and terrible beauty; in the rites of the moneychangers, where greed, laziness, and envy were assumed to move all men's acts, even the terrible became banal." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480472-europe-it-is-true-is-a-geographical-and-within-certain</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 03:37:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Rosa Luxemburg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480472-europe-it-is-true-is-a-geographical-and-within-certain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Europe, it is true, is a geographical and, within certain limits, an historical cultural conception. But the idea of Europe as an economic unit contradicts capitalist development in two ways. First of all there exist within Europe among the capitalist States – and will so long as these exist – the most violent struggles of competition and antagonisms, and secondly the European States can no longer get along economically without the non-European countries. ... At the present stage of development of the world market and of world economy, the conception of Europe as an isolated economic unit is a sterile concoction of the brain. ...
And if the idea of a European union in the economic sense has long been outstripped, this is no less the case in the political sense.
....
Only were one suddenly to lose sight of all these happenings and manoeuvres, and to transfer oneself back to the blissful times of the European concert of powers, could one say, for instance, that for forty years we have had uninterrupted peace. This conception, which considers only events on the European continent, does not notice that the very reason why we have had no war in Europe for decades is the fact that international antagonisms have grown infinitely beyond the narrow confines of the European continent, and that European problems and interests are now fought out on the world seas and in the by-corners of Europe." -- Rosa Luxemburg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/482427-happiness-is-an-illusion-natalie-it-doesn-t-actually-exist-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 00:13:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Lee Goldberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/482427-happiness-is-an-illusion-natalie-it-doesn-t-actually-exist-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is an illusion, Natalie. It doesn't actually exist.&quot;

&quot;Of course it does,&quot; I said. &quot;It's what you feel when you're not sad.&quot;

&quot;That's unconsciousness. And I'm pretty sure that I'm miserable when I am unconscious, too." -- Lee Goldberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492355-had-martha-foley-returned-william-james-sidis-s-passion-as-margaret</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 09:38:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Amy Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492355-had-martha-foley-returned-william-james-sidis-s-passion-as-margaret]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Had Martha Foley returned William  [James Sidis]'s passion as Margaret [Engemann] did Norbert [Wiener]'s, perhaps the two prodigies would have had more in common in the long run. ... In the life of a prodigy, perhaps more than in the average life, a marriage or a requited love is the greatest single factor that can heal the old childhood wounds. William and Norbert's response to their childhood and teenage rejections and humiliations was to retreat into the painless world of ideas, where successes and satisfactions abounded. A successful love affair could be the key to reentry into the world of feeling, bridging the gap between the cerebral and the emotional lives." -- Amy Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/493122-all-julie-has-to-do-is-explain-to-her-friends</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 00:10:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Lee Goldberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/493122-all-julie-has-to-do-is-explain-to-her-friends]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All Julie has to do is explain to her friends that she's using it to individually seal each item that she throws out.&quot;
&quot;Then they'd think she was a geek,&quot; I said.
&quot;She will thank me later,&quot; Monk said.
&quot;Why would she thank you for being considered a geek?&quot;
&quot;Don't you know anything about teenage life?&quot; Monk said. &quot;It's a badge of respect.&quot;
&quot;It is?&quot;
&quot;I was one,&quot; he said.
&quot;You don't say.&quot;
&quot;A very special one. I was crowned King of the Geeks, not once, but every single year of high school,&quot; Monk said. &quot;It's a record that remains unbroken in my school to this day.&quot;
&quot;Were there a lot of students who wanted to be King of the Geeks?&quot;
&quot;It's like being homecoming king, only better. You don't have to go to any dances,&quot; Monk said. &quot;You aren't even invited." -- Lee Goldberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5324-what-i-will-be-remembered-for-are-the-foundation-trilogy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 02:24:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Isaac Asimov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5324-what-i-will-be-remembered-for-are-the-foundation-trilogy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I will be remembered for are the Foundation Trilogy and the Three Laws of Robotics. What I want to be remembered for is no one book, or no dozen books. Any single thing I have written can be paralleled or even surpassed by something someone else has done. However, my total corpus for quantity, quality and variety can be duplicated by no one else. That is what I want to be remembered for." -- Isaac Asimov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317005-let-her-destroy-me-if-she-will-better-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 02:25:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Paisley Swan Stewart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317005-let-her-destroy-me-if-she-will-better-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let her destroy me if she will.  Better to be destroyed by her love than to never have known it. Erik

Book 2~Chanson de l'Ange: The Angel's Song" -- Paisley Swan Stewart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/632171-nothing-eases-suffering-like-human-touch</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 02:26:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Bobby Fischer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/632171-nothing-eases-suffering-like-human-touch]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing eases suffering like human touch." -- Bobby Fischer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280276-angel-men-die-for-honor-riches-and-glory-saints-and-women</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 02:26:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Paisley Swan Stewart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280276-angel-men-die-for-honor-riches-and-glory-saints-and-women]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Angel, men die for honor, riches and glory…saints and women die for love." -- Paisley Swan Stewart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266630-if-a-man-walks-in-the-woods-for-love-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 02:28:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266630-if-a-man-walks-in-the-woods-for-love-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a man walks in the woods for love of them half of each day, he is in danger of being regarded as a loafer; but if he spends his whole day as a spectulator, shearing off those woods and making the earth bald before her time, he is esteemed an industrious and enterprising citizen." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27023-free-love-as-if-love-is-anything-but-free</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 02:28:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Emma Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27023-free-love-as-if-love-is-anything-but-free]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[" Free love? As if love is anything but free! Man has bought brains, but all the millions in the world have failed to buy love. Man has subdued bodies, but all the power on earth has been unable to subdue love. Man has conquered whole nations, but all his armies could not conquer love. Man has chained and fettered the spirit, but he has been utterly helpless before love. High on a throne, with all the splendor and pomp his gold can command, man is yet poor and desolate, if love passes him by. And if it stays, the poorest hovel is radiant with warmth, with life and color. Thus love has the magic power to make of a beggar a king. Yes, love is free; it can dwell in no other atmosphere. In freedom it gives itself unreservedly, abundantly, completely. All the laws on the statutes, all the courts in the universe, cannot tear it from the soil, once love has taken root." -- Emma Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/733190-such-are-the-limitations-of-the-human-mind-and-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 01:19:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Frederick Douglass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/733190-such-are-the-limitations-of-the-human-mind-and-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Such are the limitations of the human mind, and so thoroughly engrossing are the cares of common life, that only the few among men can discern through the glitter and dazzle of present prosperity the dark outlines of approaching disasters, even though they may have come up to our very gates, and are already within striking distance.  The yawning seam and corroded bolt conceal their defects from the mariner until the storm calls all hands to the pumps.  Prophets, indeed, were abundant before the war; but who cares for prophets while their predictions remain unfulfilled, and the calamities of which they tell are masked behind a blinding blaze of national prosperity?" -- Frederick Douglass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/784927-however-robust-evidence-shows-that-people-systematically-overestimate-the-probability</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 00:19:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[RJHall add a quote by Daniel Nettle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/784927-however-robust-evidence-shows-that-people-systematically-overestimate-the-probability]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["However, robust evidence shows that people systematically overestimate the probability of positive future contingencies, and underestimate the probability of negative ones — only those who are depressed or dysphoric come to accurate assessments." -- Daniel Nettle]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
