<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/205738-alpha]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/205738-alpha" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 13:15:40 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32832-if-you-re-50-years-old-or-younger-give-every-book</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 13:15:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alpha add a quote by Nancy Pearl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32832-if-you-re-50-years-old-or-younger-give-every-book]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're 50 years old or younger, give every book about 50 pages before you decide to commit yourself to reading it, or give it up.

If you're over 50, which is when time gets shorter, subtract your age from 100 - the result is the number of pages you should read before deciding whether or not to quit. If you're 100 or over you get to judge the book by its cover, despite the dangers in doing so." -- Nancy Pearl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/389100-her-only-thought-was-of-getting-away-as-if-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 15:15:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alpha add a quote by Jennifer Egan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/389100-her-only-thought-was-of-getting-away-as-if-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her only thought was of getting away, as if she were carrying a live grenade from inside the house, so that when it exploded, it would destroy just herself." -- Jennifer Egan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176781-a-story-is-not-like-a-road-to-follow</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 21:57:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alpha add a quote by Alice Munro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176781-a-story-is-not-like-a-road-to-follow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A story is not like a road to follow …  it's more like a house. You go inside and stay there for a while, wandering back and forth and settling where you like and discovering how the room and corridors relate to each other, how the world outside is altered by being viewed from these windows. And you, the visitor, the reader, are altered as well by being in this enclosed space, whether it is ample and easy or full of crooked turns, or sparsely or opulently furnished. You can go back again and again, and the house, the story, always contains more than you saw the last time. It also has a sturdy sense of itself of being built out of its own necessity, not just to shelter or beguile you." -- Alice Munro]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
