<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/206536-tanish]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/206536-tanish" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2008 03:48:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21075-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-volcanoes-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2008 03:48:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanish add a quote by Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21075-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-volcanoes-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a temporary madness, it erupts like volcanoes and then subsides.  And when it subsides, you have to make a decision.  You have to work out whether your roots have so entwined together that it is inconceivable that you should ever part.  Because this is what love is.  Love is not breathlessness, it is not excitement, it is not the promulgation of promises of eternal passion, it is not the desire to mate every second minute of the day, it is not lying awake at night imagining that he is kissing every cranny of your body.  No, don't blush, I am telling you some truths.  That is just being &quot;in love&quot;, which any fool can do.  Love itself is what is left over when being in love has burned away, and this is both an art and a fortunate accident." -- Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66653-where-does-it-all-begin-history-has-no-beginnings-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2008 03:48:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanish add a quote by Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66653-where-does-it-all-begin-history-has-no-beginnings-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where does it all begin?  History has no beginnings, for everything that happens becomes the cause or pretext for what occurs afterwards, and this chain of cause and pretext stretches back to the Palaeolithic age, when the first Cain of one tribe murdered the first Abel of another. All war is fratricide, and there is therefore an infinite chain of blame that winds its circuitous route back and forth across the path and under the feet of every people and every nation, so that a people who are the victims of one time become the victimisers a generation later, and newly liberated nations resort immediately to the means of their former oppressors. The triple contagions of nationalism, utopianism and religious absolutism effervesce together into an acid that corrodes the moral metal of a race, and it shamelessly and even proudly performs deeds that it would deem vile if they were done by any other." -- Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66652-so-many-nominal-christians-throughout-history-took-no-notice</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2008 03:48:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tanish add a quote by Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66652-so-many-nominal-christians-throughout-history-took-no-notice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["... so many nominal Christians throughout history,  took no notice whatsoever of the key parable of Jesus Christ himself, which taught that you shall love your neighbour as you love yourself, and even those that you have despised and hated are your neighbours. This never made any difference to Christians, since the primary epiphenomena of any religion’s foundation are the production and flourishment of hypocrisy, megalomania and psychopathy, and the first casualties of a religion’s establishment are the intensions of its founders. One can imagine Jesus and Mohammed glumly comparing notes in paradise, scratching their heads and bemoaning their vain expense of effort and suffering, which resulted only in the construction of two monumental whited sepulchres. ..." -- Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
