<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/20698-larissa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/20698-larissa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 16:23:43 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/428880-she-wasn-t-a-person-to-whom-things-happen-she-did</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 16:23:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Larissa add a quote by Muriel Spark]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/428880-she-wasn-t-a-person-to-whom-things-happen-she-did]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She wasn't a person to whom things happen. She did all the happenings." -- Muriel Spark]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/922831-strange-it-is-a-huge-nothing-that-we-fear</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 12:16:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Larissa add a quote by Seamus Heaney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/922831-strange-it-is-a-huge-nothing-that-we-fear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Strange, it is a huge nothing that we fear." -- Seamus Heaney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275913-remember-any-lie-you-are-told-even-deliberately-is-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 16:24:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Larissa add a quote by Halldór Laxness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275913-remember-any-lie-you-are-told-even-deliberately-is-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember, any lie you are told, even deliberately, is often a more significant fact than a truth told in all sincerity." -- Halldór Laxness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522798-my-thoughts-are-an-ocean-they-wash-woefully-up-against</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 14:27:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Larissa add a quote by Nescio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522798-my-thoughts-are-an-ocean-they-wash-woefully-up-against]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My thoughts are an ocean, they wash woefully up against their limits." -- Nescio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/301729-every-reader-his-or-her-book-every-book-its-reader</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 16:23:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Larissa add a quote by S.R. Ranganathan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/301729-every-reader-his-or-her-book-every-book-its-reader]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every reader his or her book.
Every book its reader." -- S.R. Ranganathan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121796-now-here-s-the-heavy-irony-so-i-went-back-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 16:23:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Larissa add a quote by Elaine Dundy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121796-now-here-s-the-heavy-irony-so-i-went-back-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now here's the heavy irony. So I went back to New York to become a librarian. To actually &lt;i&gt;seek out&lt;/i&gt; this thing I've been fleeing all my life. and (here it comes): a librarian is just not that easy to become...Apparently there's a whole filing system and annotating system and stamping system and God knows what you have to learn before you qualify." -- Elaine Dundy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/482162-orm-always-afterwards-used-to-say-that-after-good-luck</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 12:02:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Larissa add a quote by Frans G. Bengtsson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/482162-orm-always-afterwards-used-to-say-that-after-good-luck]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...Orm always afterwards used to say that, after good luck, strength, and skill at arms, nothing was so useful to a man who found himself among foreigners as the ability to learn a language." -- Frans G. Bengtsson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/457767-can-a-person-who-has-been-brought-up-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 16:24:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Larissa add a quote by Audur Ava Olafsdottir]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/457767-can-a-person-who-has-been-brought-up-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Can a person who has been brought up in the heart of a thick dark forest, where one has to beat a path through multiple layers of trees just to take a letter to the post office, have any conception of what it’s like to spend one’s entire childhood waiting for a single tree to grow?" -- Audur Ava Olafsdottir]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174977-corliss-wondered-what-happens-to-a-book-that-sits-unread</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 16:23:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Larissa add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174977-corliss-wondered-what-happens-to-a-book-that-sits-unread]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Corliss wondered what happens to a book that sits unread on a library shelf for thirty years. Can a book rightfully be called a book if it never gets read?...

'How many books never get checked out,&quot; Corliss asked the librarian. 

'Most of them,' she said.

Corliss never once considered the fate of library books. She loved books. How could she not worry about the unread? She felt like a disorganized scholar, an abusive mother, and a cowardly soldier.

'Are you serious?' Corliss asked. 'What are we talking about here? If you were guessing, what is the percentage of books in this library that never get checked out?' 

'We're talking sixty percent of them. Seriously. Maybe seventy percent. And I'm being optimistic. It's probably more like eighty or ninety percent. This isn't a library, it's an orphanage.'

The librarian talked in a reverential whisper. Corliss knew she'd misjudged this passionate woman. Maybe she dressed poorly, but she was probably great in bed, certainly believed in God and goodness, and kept an illicit collection of overdue library books on her shelves." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/586188-he-d-always-had-a-quickening-of-the-heart-when-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2012 10:21:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Larissa add a quote by Dorothy B. Hughes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/586188-he-d-always-had-a-quickening-of-the-heart-when-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He'd always had a quickening of the heart when he crossed into Arizona and beheld the cactus country. This was as the desert should be, this was the desert of the picture books, with the land unrolled to the farthest distant horizon hills, with saguaro standing sentinel in their strange chessboard pattern, towering supinely above the fans of ocotillo and brushy mesquite." -- Dorothy B. Hughes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521623-i-think-you-re-more-an-archivist-than-a-librarian-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2012 13:24:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Larissa add a quote by Avi Steinberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521623-i-think-you-re-more-an-archivist-than-a-librarian-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think you’re more an archivist than a librarian,” he said.

He told me that archivists and librarians were opposite personas. True librarians are unsentimental. They’re pragmatic, concerned with the newest, cleanest, most popular books. Archivists, on the other hand, are only peripherally interested in what other people like, and much prefer the rare to the useful.

”They like everything,” he said, “gum wrappers as much as books.” He said this with a hint of disdain.

”Librarians like throwing away garbage to make space, but archivists,” he said, “they’re too crazy to throw anything out.”

”You’re right,” I said. ”I’m more of an archivist.”

”And I’m more of a librarian,” he said.

”Can we still be friends?" -- Avi Steinberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/971610-i-never-saw-such-a-bunch-of-apple-eaters</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 05:30:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Larissa add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/971610-i-never-saw-such-a-bunch-of-apple-eaters]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I never saw such a bunch of apple-eaters." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1194379-everything-that-happens-to-us-everything-that-we-say-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 05:03:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Larissa add a quote by Javier Marías]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1194379-everything-that-happens-to-us-everything-that-we-say-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything that happens to us, everything that we say or hear, everything that we see with our own eyes or we articulate with our tongue, everything that enters through our ears, everything we are witness to (and for which we are therefore partially responsible) must find a recipient outside ourselves and we choose that recipient according to what happens, or what we are told or even according to what we ourselves say. Each thing must be told to someone—though not necessarily to the same person—and each thing will undergo a selection process, the way someone out shopping might scrutinize, set aside, and assess presents for the season to come. Everything must be told at least once, although...it must be told when the time is right, or, which comes to the same thing, at the right moment, and sometimes, if you fail to recognize that right moment or deliberately let it pass, there will never again be another." -- Javier Marías]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1245446-he-read-as-others-pray-as-gamblers-follow-the-spinning</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 04:32:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Larissa add a quote by Stefan Zweig]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1245446-he-read-as-others-pray-as-gamblers-follow-the-spinning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He read as others pray, as gamblers follow the spinning of the roulette wheel, as drunkards stare into vacancy; he read with such profound absorption that ever since I first watched him the reading of ordinary mortals seemed a pastime." -- Stefan Zweig]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
