<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/207683-philitsa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/207683-philitsa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 19:19:02 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525375-beware-the-irrational-however-seductive-shun-the-transcendent-and-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 19:19:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philitsa add a quote by Christopher Hitchens ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525375-beware-the-irrational-however-seductive-shun-the-transcendent-and-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beware the irrational, however seductive. Shun the ‘transcendent’ and all who invite you to subordinate or annihilate yourself. Don’t be afraid to be thought arrogant or selfish. Picture all experts as if they were mammals. Never be a spectator of unfairness or stupidity. Seek out argument and disputation for their own sake; the grave will provide plenty of time for silence." -- Christopher Hitchens ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/469537-another-day-another-dolor</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2014 10:11:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philitsa add a quote by Colum McCann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/469537-another-day-another-dolor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Another day, another dolor." -- Colum McCann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1243967-your-cold-mornings-are-filled-with-the-heartache-about-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 23:19:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philitsa add a quote by Paul Harding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1243967-your-cold-mornings-are-filled-with-the-heartache-about-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your cold mornings are filled with the heartache about the fact that although we are not at ease in this world, it is all we have, that it is ours but that it is full of strife, so that all we can call our own is strife; but even that is better than nothing at all, isn't it? And as you split frost-laced wood with numb hands, rejoice that your uncertainty is God's will and His grace toward you and that that is beautiful, and part of a greater certainty, as your own father always said in his sermons and to you at home. And as the ax bites into the wood, be comforted in the fact that the ache in your heart and the confusion in your soul means that you are still alive, still human, and still open to the beauty of the world, even though you have done nothing to deserve it. And when you resent the ache in your heart, remember: You will be dead and buried soon enough." -- Paul Harding]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1254488-that-she-made-a-point-to-eat-only-the-gristliest</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 20:14:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philitsa add a quote by Paul Harding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1254488-that-she-made-a-point-to-eat-only-the-gristliest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That she made a point to eat only the gristliest chicken bits, the burned biscuits, the mealiest potatoes, while she complained that his children were, variously, weak-minded, hysterical or sickly, and seemed to imply that such afflictions were the result of the lack of a good piece of steak or a new bonnet, was only circumstance; were she installed on a throne at a twelve-course banquet table teaming with all of God's creatures brought from both air and field, trussed and roasted and swimming in their own succulent juices, she would heap her plate with the most exquisite victuals and lament that his feeble offspring were the way they were because they had it too well and what they really needed was a vat of cold porridge and a tureen full of dirt." -- Paul Harding]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1254543-hope-is-a-horrible-thing-you-know-i-don-t-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 21:01:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philitsa add a quote by Ann Patchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1254543-hope-is-a-horrible-thing-you-know-i-don-t-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hope is a horrible thing, you know. I don’t know who decided to package hope as a virtue because it’s not. It’s a plague. Hope is like walking around with a fishhook in your mouth and somebody just keeps pulling it and pulling it." -- Ann Patchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
