<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/208782-moonbean]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/208782-moonbean" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 10:13:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13641-imagine-yourself-as-a-living-house-god-comes-in-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 10:13:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Moonbean add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13641-imagine-yourself-as-a-living-house-god-comes-in-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine yourself as a living house. God comes in to rebuild that house. At first, perhaps, you can understand what He is doing. He is getting the drains right and stopping the leaks in the roof and so on; you knew that those jobs needed doing and so you are not surprised. But presently He starts knocking the house about in a way that hurts abominably and does not seem to make any sense. What on earth is He up to? The explanation is that He is building quite a different house from the one you thought of - throwing out a new wing here, putting on an extra floor there, running up towers, making courtyards. You thought you were being made into a decent little cottage: but He is building a palace. He intends to come and live in it Himself." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40099-to-have-faith-in-christ-means-of-course-trying-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 10:13:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Moonbean add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40099-to-have-faith-in-christ-means-of-course-trying-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[To have Faith in Christ] means, of course, trying to do all that He says.  There would be no sense in saying you trusted a person if you would not take his advice. Thus if you have really handed yourself over to Him, it must follow that you are trying to obey Him. But trying in a new way, a less worried way. Not doing these things in order to be saved, but because He has begun to save you already. Not hoping to get to Heaven as a reward for your actions, but inevitably wanting to act in a certain way because a first faint gleam of Heaven is already inside you." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9707-a-proud-man-is-always-looking-down-on-things-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 10:13:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Moonbean add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9707-a-proud-man-is-always-looking-down-on-things-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A proud man is always looking down on things and people; and, of course, as long as you are looking down, you cannot see something that is above you." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33128-and-out-of-that-hopeless-attempt-has-come-nearly-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 10:13:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Moonbean add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33128-and-out-of-that-hopeless-attempt-has-come-nearly-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And out of that hopeless attempt has come nearly all that we call human history—money, poverty, ambition, war, prostitution, classes, empires, slavery—the long terrible story of man trying to find something other than God which will make him happy." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/586921-god-has-infinite-attention-infinite-leisure-to-spare-for-each</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 10:35:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Moonbean add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/586921-god-has-infinite-attention-infinite-leisure-to-spare-for-each]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God has infinite attention, infinite leisure to spare for each one of us. He doesn't have to take us in the line. You're as much alone with Him as if you were the only thing He'd ever created." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1232872-god-is-not-hurried-along-in-the-time-stream-of-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 10:41:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Moonbean add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1232872-god-is-not-hurried-along-in-the-time-stream-of-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God is not hurried along in the Time-stream of this universe any more than an author is hurried along in the imaginary time of his own novel. He has infinite attention to spare for each one of us. He does not have to deal with us in the mass. You are as much alone with him as if you were the only being He had ever created. When Christ died, he died for you individually just as much as if you had been the only man in the world. - Mere Christianity, pg. 131" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
