<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/209077-sara-kearns]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/209077-sara-kearns" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:32:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27047-let-me-live-love-and-say-it-well-in-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:32:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27047-let-me-live-love-and-say-it-well-in-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["let me live, love, and say it well in good sentences" -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287385-i-was-going-to-die-sooner-or-later-whether-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:33:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287385-i-was-going-to-die-sooner-or-later-whether-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was going to die, sooner or later, whether or not I had even spoken myself. My silences had not protected me. Your silences will not protect you.... What are the words you do not yet have? What are the tyrannies you swallow day by day and attempt to make your own, until you will sicken and die of them, still in silence? We have been socialized to respect fear more than our own need for language.&quot;

I began to ask each time: &quot;What's the worst that could happen to me if I tell this truth?&quot; Unlike women in other countries, our breaking silence is unlikely to have us jailed, &quot;disappeared&quot; or run off the road at night. Our speaking out will irritate some people, get us called bitchy or hypersensitive and disrupt some dinner parties. And then our speaking out will permit other women to speak, until laws are changed and lives are saved and the world is altered forever.

Next time, ask: What's the worst that will happen? Then push yourself a little further than you dare. Once you start to speak, people will yell at you. They will interrupt you, put you down and suggest it's personal. And the world won't end.

And the speaking will get easier and easier. And you will find you have fallen in love with your own vision, which you may never have realized you had. And you will lose some friends and lovers, and realize you don't miss them. And new ones will find you and cherish you. And you will still flirt and paint your nails, dress up and party, because, as I think Emma Goldman said, &quot;If I can't dance, I don't want to be part of your revolution.&quot; And at last you'll know with surpassing certainty that only one thing is more frightening than speaking your truth. And that is not speaking." -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:39:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what you shall do; Love the earth and sun and the animals, despise riches, give alms to every one that asks, stand up for the stupid and crazy, devote your income and labor to others, hate tyrants, argue not concerning God, have patience and indulgence toward the people, take off your hat to nothing known or unknown or to any man or number of men, go freely with powerful uneducated persons and with the young and with the mothers of families, read these leaves in the open air every season of every year of your life, re-examine all you have been told at school or church or in any book, dismiss whatever insults your own soul, and your very flesh shall be a great poem and have the richest fluency not only in its words but in the silent lines of its lips and face and between the lashes of your eyes and in every motion and joint of your body." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55425-i-prefer-men-to-cauliflowers</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 13:16:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55425-i-prefer-men-to-cauliflowers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I prefer men to cauliflowers" -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7038-kiss-me-and-you-will-see-how-important-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:39:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7038-kiss-me-and-you-will-see-how-important-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kiss me, and you will see how important I am." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1452-saints-have-no-moderation-nor-do-poets-just-exuberance</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by anne sexton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1452-saints-have-no-moderation-nor-do-poets-just-exuberance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Saints have no moderation, nor do poets, just exuberance." -- anne sexton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23328-when-they-asked-me-what-i-wanted-to-be-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 13:22:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23328-when-they-asked-me-what-i-wanted-to-be-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When they asked me what I wanted to be I said I didn’t know.
&quot;Oh, sure you know,&quot; the photographer said.
&quot;She wants,&quot; said Jay Cee wittily, &quot;to be everything." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20384-i-think-i-could-turn-and-live-with-the-animals</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:38:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20384-i-think-i-could-turn-and-live-with-the-animals]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think I could turn and live with the animals, they are so placid and self contained;
I stand and look at them long and long.
They do not sweat and whine about their condition;
They do not lie awake in the dark and weep for their sins;
They do not make me sick discussing their duty to God;
Not one is dissatisfied-not one is demented with the mania of owning things;
Not one kneels to another, nor his kind that lived thousands of years ago;
Not one is responsible or industrious over the whole earth." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9565-it-is-difficult-to-get-the-news-from-poems-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:38:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by William Carlos Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9565-it-is-difficult-to-get-the-news-from-poems-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is difficult to get the news from poems, yet men die miserably every day for lack of what is found there." -- William Carlos Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98253-be-curious-not-judgmental</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:09:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Walt Whitman ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98253-be-curious-not-judgmental]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be curious, not judgmental." -- Walt Whitman ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25336-i-am-ashamed-of-my-century-but-i-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:35:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Frank O'Hara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25336-i-am-ashamed-of-my-century-but-i-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am ashamed of my century, but I have to smile." -- Frank O'Hara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1922-resist-much-obey-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:12:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1922-resist-much-obey-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Resist much, obey little." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166635-poetry-is-not-a-luxury-it-is-a-vital</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:36:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166635-poetry-is-not-a-luxury-it-is-a-vital]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["... poetry is not a luxury. It is a vital necessity of our existence. It forms the quality of the light within which we predicate our hopes and dreams toward survival and change, first made into language, then into idea, then into more tangible action. Poetry is the way we help give name to the nameless so it can be thought. The farthest horizons of our hopes and fears are cobbled by our poems, carved from the rock experiences of our daily lives." -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61907-note-to-day-an-instructive-curious-spectacle-and-conflict-science-twin</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:36:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61907-note-to-day-an-instructive-curious-spectacle-and-conflict-science-twin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Note, to-day, an instructive, curious spectacle and conflict. Science, (twin, in its fields, of Democracy in its)—Science, testing absolutely all thoughts, all works, has already burst well upon the world—a sun, mounting, most illuminating, most glorious—surely never again to set. But against it, deeply entrench'd, holding possession, yet remains, (not only through the churches and schools, but by imaginative literature, and unregenerate poetry,) the fossil theology of the mythic-materialistic, superstitious, untaught and credulous, fable-loving, primitive ages of humanity." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125120-sometimes-we-are-blessed-with-being-able-to-choose-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:19:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125120-sometimes-we-are-blessed-with-being-able-to-choose-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes we are blessed with being able to choose
the time, and the arena, and the manner of our revolution,
but more usually
we must do battle where we are standing." -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192214-because-the-machine-will-try-to-grind-you-into-dust</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:24:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192214-because-the-machine-will-try-to-grind-you-into-dust]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because the machine will try to grind you into dust anyway, whether or not we speak." -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10895-unless-one-lives-and-loves-in-the-trenches-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:35:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10895-unless-one-lives-and-loves-in-the-trenches-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Unless one lives and loves in the trenches, it is difficult to remember that the war against dehumanization is ceaseless." -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100149-where-is-it-written-that-if-you-don-t-like-religion</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:49:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Hendrik Hertzberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100149-where-is-it-written-that-if-you-don-t-like-religion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where is it written that if you don't like religion you are somehow disqualified from being a legitimate American? What was Mark Twain, a Russian?" -- Hendrik Hertzberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
