<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/210336-eva]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/210336-eva" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 14:40:52 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9535-certainly-my-inner-world-will-never-be-a-peaceful-place</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 14:40:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[eva add a quote by James Tiptree Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9535-certainly-my-inner-world-will-never-be-a-peaceful-place]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Certainly my inner world will never be a peaceful place of bloom; it will have some peace, and occasional riots of bloom, but always a little fight going on too. There is no way I can be peacefully happy in this society and in this skin. I am committed to Uneasy Street. I like it; it is my idea that this street leads to the future, and that I am being true to a way of life which is not here yet, but is more real than what is here." -- James Tiptree Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9538-my-mother-said-i-broke-her-heart-but-it-was-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 14:46:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[eva add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9538-my-mother-said-i-broke-her-heart-but-it-was-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My mother said I broke her heart...but it was my integrity that was important. Is that so selfish? It sells for so little, but it's all we have left in this place. It is the very last inch of us...but within that inch we are free." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19483-on-ne-voit-bien-qu-avec-le-c-ur-l-essentiel-est-invisible</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2008 19:18:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[eva add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19483-on-ne-voit-bien-qu-avec-le-c-ur-l-essentiel-est-invisible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On ne voit bien qu'avec le cœur. L'essentiel est invisible pour les yeux." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114785-on-the-outside-oscar-simply-looked-tired-no-taller-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 15:39:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[eva add a quote by Junot Díaz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114785-on-the-outside-oscar-simply-looked-tired-no-taller-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the outside, Oscar simply looked tired, no taller, no fatter, only the skin under his eyes, pouched from years of quiet desperation, had changed. Inside, he was in a world of hurt. He saw black flashes before his eyes. He saw himself falling through the air. He knew what he was turning into. He was turning into the worst kind of human on the planet: an old bitter dork. Saw himself at the Game Room, picking through the miniatures for the rest of his life. He didn't want this future but he couldn't see how it could be avoided, couldn't figure his way out of it.

Fukú." -- Junot Díaz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123873-since-he-was-very-young-he-had-known-that-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 15:16:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[eva add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123873-since-he-was-very-young-he-had-known-that-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Since he was very young he had known that in certain ways he was unlike anyone else he knew. For a child the consciousness of such difference is very painful, since, having done nothing yet and being incapable of doing anything, he cannot justify it. The reliable and affectionate presence of adults who are also, in their own way, different, is the only reassurance such a child can have; and Shevek had not had it. His father had indeed been utterly reliable and affectionate. Whatever Shevek was and whatever he did, Palat approved and was loyal. But Palat had not had this curse of difference. He was like the others, like all the others to whom community came so easy. He loved Shevek, but he could not show him what freedom is, that recognition of each person's solitude which alone transcends it." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123874-so-he-worked-he-lost-weight-he-walked-light-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 15:20:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[eva add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123874-so-he-worked-he-lost-weight-he-walked-light-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So he worked.

He lost weight; he walked light on the earth. Lack of physical labor, lack of variety of occupation, lack of social and sexual intercourse, none of these appeared to him as lacks, but as freedom. He was the free man: he could do what he wanted to do when he wanted to do it for as long as he wanted to do it. And he did. He worked. He work/played." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123952-gvarab-was-old-enough-that-she-often-wandered-and-maundered</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 22:46:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[eva add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123952-gvarab-was-old-enough-that-she-often-wandered-and-maundered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Gvarab was old enough that she often wandered and maundered. Attendance at her lectures was small and uneven. She soon picked out the thin boy with big ears as her one constant auditor. She began to lecture for him. The light, steady, intelligent eyes met hers, steadied her, woke her, she flashed to brilliance, regained the vision lost. She soared, and the other students in the room looked up confused or startled, even scared if they had the wits to be scared. Gvarab saw a much larger universe than most people were capable of seeing, and it made them blink. The light-eyed boy watched her steadily. In his face she saw her joy. What she offered, what she had offered for a whole lifetime, what no one had ever shared with her, he shared. He was her brother, across the gulf of fifty years, and her redemption." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126050-for-we-each-of-us-deserve-everything-every-luxury-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 21:36:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[eva add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126050-for-we-each-of-us-deserve-everything-every-luxury-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For we each of us deserve everything, every luxury that was ever piled in the tombs of the dead kings, and we each of us deserve nothing, not a mouthful of bread in hunger. Have we not eaten while another starved? Will you punish us for that? Will you reward us for the virtue of starving while others ate? No man earns punishment, no man earns reward. Free your mind of the idea of deserving, the idea of earning, and you will begin to be able to think." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140455-yes-there-s-really-only-one-question-that-can-be-answered</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 23:46:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[eva add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140455-yes-there-s-really-only-one-question-that-can-be-answered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yes. There's really only one question that can be answered, Genry, and we already know the answer....The only thing that makes life possible is permanent, intolerable uncertainty: not knowing what comes next." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163919-i-certainly-wasn-t-happy-happiness-has-to-do-with-reason</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 23:48:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[eva add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163919-i-certainly-wasn-t-happy-happiness-has-to-do-with-reason]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I certainly wasn't happy. Happiness has to do with reason, and only reason earns it. What I was given was the thing you can't earn, and can't keep, and often don't even recognize at the time; I mean joy." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196672-in-hospitals-i-feel-palpable-comfort-i-feel-the-competence</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2009 07:43:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[eva add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196672-in-hospitals-i-feel-palpable-comfort-i-feel-the-competence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In hospitals I feel palpable comfort. I feel the competence, the expertise, so much education and money, all of the supplies sterile, everything packaged, sealed tight. My fears evaporate when the automatic doors shush open." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943816-the-spoken-word-converts-individual-knowledge-into-mutual-knowledge-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 09:45:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[eva add a quote by Karen Joy Fowler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943816-the-spoken-word-converts-individual-knowledge-into-mutual-knowledge-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The spoken word converts individual knowledge into mutual knowledge, and there is no way back once you've gone over that cliff. Saying nothing was more amendable, and over time I'd come to see that it was usually your best course of action." -- Karen Joy Fowler]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
