<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/210650-keri]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/210650-keri" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 12:47:36 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/775439-i-m-a-cancer-you-know-i-tell-her-so-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 12:47:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Adam Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/775439-i-m-a-cancer-you-know-i-tell-her-so-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm a Cancer, you know,&quot; I tell her. &quot;So it's hard for me to talk. And I have all these weird dreams, not the ones with the Sony Girls - ha-ha - but mostly where I mow the lawn. Sometimes I just wash the car, like Gupta! But there's this voice in my head, and Lt. Kim thinks that once we get it to go away, I'll stop worrying that the good things in life are destined to fail, like you and me. But I'm up in this satellite dish, and I'm thinking: what if this is the voice that still believes things can be okay, that believes in good and warns me from bad? It wants to protect me, just like the United Nations." -- Adam Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209729-lo-cried-the-demon-i-am-here-what-dost-thou</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2010 20:23:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Jonathan L. Howard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209729-lo-cried-the-demon-i-am-here-what-dost-thou]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lo!&quot; cried the demon. &quot;I am here! What dost thou seek of me? Why dost thou disturb my repose? Smite me no more with that dread rod!&quot; He looked at Cabal. &quot;Where's your dread rod?&quot;
&quot;I left it at home,&quot; replied Cabal. &quot;Didn't think I really needed it.&quot;
&quot;You can't summon me without a dread rod!&quot; said Lucifuge, appalled.
&quot;You're here, aren't you?&quot;
&quot;Well, yes, but under false pretences. You haven't got a goatskin or two vervain crowns or two candles of virgin wax made by a virgin girl and duly blessed. Have you got the stone called Ematille?&quot;
&quot;I don't even know what Ematille is.&quot;
Neither did the demon. He dropped the subject and moved on. &quot;Four nails from the coffin of a dead child?&quot;
&quot;Don't be fatuous.&quot;
&quot;Half a bottle of brandy?&quot;
&quot;I don't drink brandy.&quot;
&quot;It's not for you.&quot;
&quot;I have a hip flask,&quot; said Cabal, and threw it to him. The demon caught it and took a dram.
&quot;Cheers,&quot; said Lucifuge, and threw it back. They regarded each other for a long moment. &quot;This really is a shambles,&quot; the demon added finally. &quot;What did you summon me for, anyway?" -- Jonathan L. Howard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/448332-owen-henry-said-excitedly-i-think-coach-wants-you-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 18:31:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Chad Harbach]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/448332-owen-henry-said-excitedly-i-think-coach-wants-you-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Owen,&quot; Henry said excitedly, &quot;I think Coach wants you to hit for Meccini.&quot;

Owen closed &lt;i&gt;The Voyage of the Beagle&lt;/i&gt;, on which he had recently embarked. &quot;Really?&quot;

&quot;Runners on first and second,&quot; Rick said. &quot;I bet he wants you to bunt.&quot;

&quot;What's the bunt sign?&quot;

&quot;Two tugs on the left earlobe,&quot; Henry told him. &quot;But first he has to give the indicator, which is squeeze the belt. But if he goes to his cap with either hand or says your first name, that's the wipe-off, and then you have to wait and see whether--&quot;

&quot;Forget it,&quot; Owen said. &quot;I'll just bunt." -- Chad Harbach]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/493534-wagstaff-was-a-trim-little-man-in-a-dark-blue-uniform</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 19:36:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Mal Peet]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/493534-wagstaff-was-a-trim-little-man-in-a-dark-blue-uniform]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wagstaff was a trim little man in a dark-blue uniform with an armband embroidered with the words CIVIL DEFENSE.

&quot;Thank you, Headmaster, and good morning, young gentlemen. Yesterday, as I'm sure you'll remember, I spoke to you about the ways you can help your parents prepare their homes against the possibility of nuclear attack.&quot;

Clem grinned, noting Tash Harmsworth's scowl. Tash was a bugger for an incorrect proposition." -- Mal Peet]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/578795-i-don-t-think-it-should-be-socially-acceptable-for-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 17:46:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Mindy Kaling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/578795-i-don-t-think-it-should-be-socially-acceptable-for-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don’t think it should be socially acceptable for people to say they are “bad with names.” No one is bad with names. That is not a real thing. Not knowing people’s names isn’t a neurological condition; it’s a choice. You choose not to make learning people’s names a priority. It’s like saying, “Hey, a disclaimer about me: I’m rude." -- Mindy Kaling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/545710-zen-cuts-straight-through-the-quidditch-match-in-progress-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 15:53:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Megan McCafferty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/545710-zen-cuts-straight-through-the-quidditch-match-in-progress-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Zen cuts straight through the Quidditch match in progress and almost gets taken down by a Beater hurling a Nerf quaffle right at his machopartes." -- Megan McCafferty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287616-hormones-are-nature-s-three-bottles-of-beer</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 14:32:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Mary Roach]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287616-hormones-are-nature-s-three-bottles-of-beer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hormones are nature's three bottles of beer." -- Mary Roach]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117407-people-like-it-when-you-tell-them-things-in-suitable</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2012 21:58:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Per Petterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117407-people-like-it-when-you-tell-them-things-in-suitable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People like it when you tell them things, in suitable portions, in a modest, intimate tone, and they think they know you, but they do not, they know _about_ you, for what they are let in on are facts, not feelings, not what your opinion is about anything at all, not how what has happened to you and how all the decisions you have made have turned you into who you are. What they do is they fill in with their own feelings and opinions and assumptions, and they compose a new life which has precious little to do with yours, and that lets you off the hook. No-one can touch you unless you yourself want them to." -- Per Petterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/591951-i-wanted-then-to-become-what-i-most-admired-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 18:41:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Megan Mayhew Bergman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/591951-i-wanted-then-to-become-what-i-most-admired-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted, then, to become what I most admired, what now seemed most real to me. I wanted to be that exalted, complicated presence in someone's life, the familiar body, the source of another's existence. But I knew what I wanted was not always what I needed." -- Megan Mayhew Bergman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183361-i-still-have-everything-you-gave-me-it-is-dusty</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2012 21:09:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Naomi Shihab Nye]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183361-i-still-have-everything-you-gave-me-it-is-dusty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I Still Have Everything You Gave Me

It is dusty on the edges.

It is slightly rotten.

I guard it without thinking.

I focus on it once a year
when I shake it out in the wind.

I do not ache.

I would not trade." -- Naomi Shihab Nye]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/600318-amal-you-look-stunned-said-mrs-melchor-have-you-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2012 21:12:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Naomi Shihab Nye]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/600318-amal-you-look-stunned-said-mrs-melchor-have-you-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Amal, you look stunned,&quot; said Mrs. Melchor. &quot;Have you been struck by lightning between classes?&quot;

&quot;Yes,&quot; she said. &quot;The lightning of ignorance.&quot;

Mrs. Melchor raised her eyebrows." -- Naomi Shihab Nye]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497248-i-personally-have-a-cunt-sometimes-it-s-flaps-or-twat</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 20:36:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Caitlin Moran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497248-i-personally-have-a-cunt-sometimes-it-s-flaps-or-twat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I personally have a cunt. Sometimes it's 'flaps' or 'twat', but most of the time, it's my cunt. Cunt is a proper, old, historic, strong word. I like that my fire escape also doubles up as the most potent swearword in the English language. Yeah. That's how powerful it is, guys. If I tell you what I've got down there, old ladies and clerics might faint. I like how shocked people are when you say 'cunt'. It's like I have a nuclear bomb in my pants, or a tiger, or a gun.

  Compared to this the most powerful swearword men have got out of their privates is 'dick', which is frankly vanilla, and I believe you're allowed to use on, like, Blue Peter if something goes wrong. In a culture where nearly everything female is still seen as squeam-inducing, and/or weak - menstruation, menopause, just the sheer simple act of calling someone 'a girl' - I love that 'cunt' stands, on its own, as the supreme unvanquishable word. It has almost mystic resonance. It is a cunt - we all know it's a cunt - but we can't call it a cunt. We can't say the actual word. It's too powerful. Like Jews can never utter the Tetragrammaton - an must make do with 'Jehovah', instead." -- Caitlin Moran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/471825-actually-that-s-my-secret-i-can-t-even-talk-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 16:02:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/471825-actually-that-s-my-secret-i-can-t-even-talk-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Actually that’s my secret — I can’t even talk about you to anybody because I don’t want any more people to know how wonderful you are." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629633-ramon-looked-closely-at-the-little-guy-as-he-ate</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 20:18:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Lish McBride]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629633-ramon-looked-closely-at-the-little-guy-as-he-ate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ramon looked closely at the little guy as he ate. &quot;Maybe he's Jewish. I mean, if Sammy Davis Jr. could convert to Judaism, why not a chupacabra? We should name him Harry Mendelbaum.&quot;

I held up my arms in protest. &quot;You're all racist. Now shut up. We'll call him Taco von Precious of Svenenstein. There, everybody happy?&quot;

&quot;Isn't &lt;em&gt;von&lt;/em&gt; the same thing as &lt;em&gt;of&lt;/em&gt;?&quot; Frank asked. &quot;Wouldn't that be kind of redundant?&quot;

&quot;You're redundant,&quot; I said." -- Lish McBride]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644198-before-long-everyone-was-giving-him-answers-and-feeling-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 17:41:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Diana Wynne Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644198-before-long-everyone-was-giving-him-answers-and-feeling-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Before long, everyone was giving him answers, and feeling a little superior, because it was really remarkable the number of things Chrestomanci seemed not to know. He had heard of Hitler, though he asked Brian to refresh his memory about him, but he had only the haziest notion about Gandhi or Einstein, and he had never heard of Walt Disney or reggae." -- Diana Wynne Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644725-now-granted-howard-doesn-t-fit-the-conventional-psychological-profile-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2012 15:08:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Chris Ballard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644725-now-granted-howard-doesn-t-fit-the-conventional-psychological-profile-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now, granted, Howard doesn't fit the conventional psychological profile of a rebounder - that of the no-nonsense, utilitarian &quot;dirty work&quot; specialist. Rather, this is a guy who sings Beyoncé at the free throw line, who quotes not &lt;em&gt;Scarface&lt;/em&gt; but &lt;em&gt;Finding Nemo&lt;/em&gt;, whose idea of humor is ordering 10 pizzas to be delivered to another player's hotel room, or knocking on teammates' doors and sprinting off down the hall, giggling. He goofs around during practice, during press conferences and during team shootarounds, for which Magic coach Stan Van Gundy has had to institute a no-flatulence rule because, as teammate Rashard Lewis says, &quot;Dwight really likes to cut the cheese." -- Chris Ballard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/700553-you-can-t-keep-acting-like-this-lillian-says-and-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 20:05:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Brenna Yovanoff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/700553-you-can-t-keep-acting-like-this-lillian-says-and-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can't keep acting like this,&quot; Lillian says, and for the first time in months, it's like she's actually trying to be nice. &quot;Tragedy isn't this evil thing that came from outer space. It's just there, you know. Along with everything else." -- Brenna Yovanoff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226436-remember-you-are-not-you-now-you-are-you-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 10:40:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Marty McConnell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226436-remember-you-are-not-you-now-you-are-you-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["remember you
are not you, now. you are you
a year from now. how does that
woman walk? she is not sick or sad.
doesn’t even remember today.
has been to Europe. what song
is she humming? now. right now.
that’s it." -- Marty McConnell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/495172-kiss-me-hardy-kiss-me-quick</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 13:33:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Elizabeth Wein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/495172-kiss-me-hardy-kiss-me-quick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["KISS ME, HARDY! Kiss me, QUICK!" -- Elizabeth Wein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/454767-dearest-alexia-oh-please-absolve-me-of-this-guilt-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 17:45:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Gail Carriger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/454767-dearest-alexia-oh-please-absolve-me-of-this-guilt-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dearest Alexia,
 Oh, please absolve me of this guilt I already feel squishing on my very soul! My troubled heart weeps! Oh dear, Ivy was getting flowery. My bones ache with the sin that I am about to commit. Oh, why must I have bones? I have lost myself to this transplanting love. You could not possibly understand how this feels! Yet try to comprehend, dearest Alexia, I am like a delicate bloom. Marriage without love is all very well for people like you, but I should wilt and wither. I need a man possessed of a poet’s soul! I am simply not so stoic as you. I cannot stand to be apart from him one moment longer! The caboose of my love has derailed, and I must sacrifice all for the man I adore! Please do not judge me harshly! It was all for love! 
~ Ivy." -- Gail Carriger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/455530-she-moved-with-such-purpose-it-was-as-though-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 17:45:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Gail Carriger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/455530-she-moved-with-such-purpose-it-was-as-though-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She moved with such purpose it was as though she walked with exclamation marks." -- Gail Carriger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/600877-one-should-do-what-one-is-best-at-on-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 16:26:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Gail Carriger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/600877-one-should-do-what-one-is-best-at-on-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One should do what one is best at on as large a scale as possible." -- Gail Carriger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/653838-how-do-you-know-i-wouldn-t-have-just-been-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 19:14:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Maggie Stiefvater]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/653838-how-do-you-know-i-wouldn-t-have-just-been-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How do you know I wouldn't have just been happy with the truth? I don’t care if my father was a deadbeat named Butternut. It doesn't change anything right now.”
“His name wasn't really Butternut, was it?” Gansey asked Adam in a low voice." -- Maggie Stiefvater]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/752108-we-have-to-be-back-in-three-hours-ronan-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 19:17:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Maggie Stiefvater]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/752108-we-have-to-be-back-in-three-hours-ronan-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have to be back in three hours,&quot; Ronan said. &quot;I just fed Chainsaw but she'll need it again.&quot;

&quot;This,&quot; Gansey replied &quot;is precisely why I didn't want to have a baby with you." -- Maggie Stiefvater]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/763041-gansey-turned-the-key-the-engine-turned-over-once-paused</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 19:35:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Maggie Stiefvater]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/763041-gansey-turned-the-key-the-engine-turned-over-once-paused]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Gansey turned the key. The engine turned over once, paused for the briefest of moments - and then roared to deafening life. The Camaro lived to fight another day. The radio was even working, playing the Stevie Nicks song that always sounded to Gansey like it was about a one-winged dove." -- Maggie Stiefvater]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/809355-she-was-fluent-in-four-languages-and-yet-her-fists</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2013 18:19:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Anthony Marra]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/809355-she-was-fluent-in-four-languages-and-yet-her-fists]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was fluent in four languages and yet her fists against the rusted hood were the fullest articulation of her defeat." -- Anthony Marra]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309625-we-had-a-bishop-this-morning-and-what-do-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 22:25:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Jean Webster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309625-we-had-a-bishop-this-morning-and-what-do-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We had a bishop this morning and &lt;i&gt;what do you think he said?&lt;/i&gt;
&quot;The most beneficent promise made us in the Bible is this,'The poor ye have always with you.' They were put here in order to keep us charitable.&quot;
The poor, please observe, being a sort of useful domestic animal. If I hadn't grown into such a perfect lady, I should have gone up after service and told him what I thought." -- Jean Webster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209726-well-it-s-simple-to-love-someone-she-said-but-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2013 17:36:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Rebecca Stead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209726-well-it-s-simple-to-love-someone-she-said-but-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, it's simple to love someone,&quot; she said. &quot;But it's hard to know when you need  to say it out loud." -- Rebecca Stead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/645309-her-name-s-chainsaw-replied-ronan-without-looking-up-then-noah</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 16:52:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Maggie Stiefvater]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/645309-her-name-s-chainsaw-replied-ronan-without-looking-up-then-noah]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her name's Chainsaw,&quot; replied Ronan, without looking up. Then: &quot;Noah. You're creepy as hell back there." -- Maggie Stiefvater]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/976929-brew-is-mainly-a-run-blocking-coach-he-has-only-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 23:12:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[keri. add a quote by Nate Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/976929-brew-is-mainly-a-run-blocking-coach-he-has-only-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Brew is mainly a run-blocking coach. He has only a nominal interest in the passing game. His bailiwick is biting someone in the fucking neck! He likes to get dirty. By that I mean that he likes for us to get dirty." -- Nate Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
