<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/211278-simon]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/211278-simon" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 12:20:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259954-sections-in-the-bookstore---books-you-haven-t-read--</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 12:20:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Simon add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259954-sections-in-the-bookstore---books-you-haven-t-read--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sections in the bookstore

- Books You Haven't Read
- Books You Needn't Read
- Books Made for Purposes Other Than       Reading
- Books Read Even Before You Open Them Since They Belong to the Category of Books Read Before Being Written
- Books That If You Had More Than One Life You Would Certainly Also Read But Unfortunately Your Days Are Numbered
- Books You Mean to Read But There Are Others You Must Read First
- Books Too Expensive Now and You'll Wait 'Til They're Remaindered
- Books ditto When They Come Out in Paperback
- Books You Can Borrow from Somebody
- Books That Everybody's Read So It's As If You Had Read Them, Too
- Books You've Been Planning to Read for Ages
- Books You've Been Hunting for Years Without Success
- Books Dealing with Something You're Working on at the Moment
- Books You Want to Own So They'll Be Handy Just in Case
- Books You Could Put Aside Maybe to Read This Summer
- Books You Need to Go with Other Books on Your Shelves
- Books That Fill You with Sudden, Inexplicable Curiosity, Not Easily Justified
- Books Read Long Ago Which It's Now Time to Re-read
- Books You've Always Pretended to Have Read and Now It's Time to Sit Down and Really Read Them" -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/944654-anyone-can-be-a-barbarian-it-requires-a-terrible-effort</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 19:41:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Simon add a quote by Leonard Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/944654-anyone-can-be-a-barbarian-it-requires-a-terrible-effort]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone can be a barbarian; it requires a terrible effort to remain a civilized man." -- Leonard Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198144-coming-at-us-like-this--in-waves-massed-and-unbreachable--knowledge-becomes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2014 07:50:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Simon add a quote by Ruth Ozeki]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198144-coming-at-us-like-this--in-waves-massed-and-unbreachable--knowledge-becomes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Coming at us like this--in waves, massed and unbreachable--knowledge becomes symbolic of our disempowerment--becomes bad knowledge--so we deny it, riding its crest until it subsides from consciousness... &quot;Ignorance.&quot; In this root sense, ignorance is an act of will, a choice that one makes over and over again, especially when information overwhelms and knowledge has become synonymous with impotence... If we can't act on knowledge, then we can't survive without ignorance... Ignorance becomes empowering because it enables people to live. Stupidity becomes proactive, a political statement." -- Ruth Ozeki]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
