<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/211919-ariel-aj-vanderhorst]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/211919-ariel-aj-vanderhorst" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 19:50:10 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/660-i-believe-in-christianity-as-i-believe-that-the-sun</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 19:50:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ariel (AJ) add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/660-i-believe-in-christianity-as-i-believe-that-the-sun]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in Christianity as I believe that the sun has risen: not only because I see it, but because by it I see everything else." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374121-in-the-midst-of-a-world-of-light-and-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 19:50:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ariel (AJ) add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374121-in-the-midst-of-a-world-of-light-and-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the midst of a world of light and love, of song and feast and dance, [Lucifer] could find nothing to think of more interesting than his own prestige." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/659780-but-god-will-look-to-every-soul-like-its-first</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 10:03:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ariel (AJ) add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/659780-but-god-will-look-to-every-soul-like-its-first]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But God will look to every soul like its first love because He is its first love. Your place in heaven will seem to be made for you and you alone, because you were made for it--made for it stitch by stitch as a glove is made for a hand.

It is from this point of view that we can understand hell in its aspect of privation. All your life an unattainable ecstasy has hovered just beyond the grasp of your consciousness. The day is coming when you will wake to find, beyond all hope, that you have attained it, or else, that it was within your reach and you have lost it forever." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33277-whatever-you-do-he-will-make-good-of-it-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 19:53:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ariel (AJ) add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33277-whatever-you-do-he-will-make-good-of-it-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever you do, He will make good of it. But not the good He had prepared for you if you had obeyed him." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167978-in-speaking-of-this-desire-for-our-own-far-off</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 06:51:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ariel (AJ) add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167978-in-speaking-of-this-desire-for-our-own-far-off]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In speaking of this desire for our own far off country, which we find in ourselves even now, I feel a certain shyness. I am almost committing an indecency. I am trying to rip open the inconsolable secret in each one of you—the secret which hurts so much that you take your revenge on it by calling it names like Nostalgia and Romanticism and Adolescence; the secret also which pierces with such sweetness that when, in very intimate conversation, the mention of it becomes imminent, we grow awkward and affect to laugh at ourselves; the secret we cannot hide and cannot tell, though we desire to do both. We cannot tell it because it is a desire for something that has never actually appeared in our experience. We cannot hide it because our experience is constantly suggesting it, and we betray ourselves like lovers at the mention of a name. Our commonest expedient is to call it beauty and behave as if that had settled the matter. Wordsworth’s expedient was to identify it with certain moments in his own past. But all this is a cheat. If Wordsworth had gone back to those moments in the past, he would not have found the thing itself, but only the reminder of it; what he remembered would turn out to be itself a remembering. The books or the music in which we thought the beauty was located will betray us if we trust to them; it was not in them, it only came through them, and what came through them was longing. These things—the beauty, the memory of our own past—are good images of what we really desire; but if they are mistaken for the thing itself they turn into dumb idols, breaking the hearts of their worshipers. For they are not the thing itself; they are only the scent of a flower we have not found, the echo of a tune we have not heard, news from a country we have never yet visited." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
