<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/21271-azadeh]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/21271-azadeh" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 05:31:24 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/452507-just-because-you-made-it-warm-doesn-t-make-it-yours</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 05:31:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Amelia Gray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/452507-just-because-you-made-it-warm-doesn-t-make-it-yours]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just because you made it warm doesn't make it yours" -- Amelia Gray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:02:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know you're in love when you can't fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:02:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many books, so little time." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:03:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9131-if-you-tell-the-truth-you-don-t-have-to-remember</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:03:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9131-if-you-tell-the-truth-you-don-t-have-to-remember]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you tell the truth, you don't have to remember anything." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:02:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:04:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that everything happens for a reason. People change so that you can learn to let go, things go wrong so that you appreciate them when they're right, you believe lies so you eventually learn to trust no one but yourself, and sometimes good things fall apart so better things can fall together." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:04:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:12:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:12:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360-good-friends-good-books-and-a-sleepy-conscience-this-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:13:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360-good-friends-good-books-and-a-sleepy-conscience-this-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good friends, good books, and a sleepy conscience: this is the ideal life." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:14:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opposite of love is not hate, it's indifference. The opposite of art is not ugliness, it's indifference. The opposite of faith is not heresy, it's indifference. And the opposite of life is not death, it's indifference." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/778-it-is-not-a-lack-of-love-but-a-lack</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:15:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/778-it-is-not-a-lack-of-love-but-a-lack]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not a lack of love, but a lack of friendship that makes unhappy marriages." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:15:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Kent M. Keith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Paradoxical Commandments

People are illogical, unreasonable, and self-centered.
Love them anyway.

If you do good, people will accuse you of selfish ulterior motives.
Do good anyway.

If you are successful, you will win false friends and true enemies.
Succeed anyway.

The good you do today will be forgotten tomorrow.
Do good anyway.

Honesty and frankness make you vulnerable.
Be honest and frank anyway.

The biggest men and women with the biggest ideas can be shot down by the smallest men and women with the smallest minds.
Think big anyway.

People favor underdogs but follow only top dogs.
Fight for a few underdogs anyway.

What you spend years building may be destroyed overnight.
Build anyway.

People really need help but may attack you if you do help them.
Help people anyway.

Give the world the best you have and you'll get kicked in the teeth.
Give the world the best you have anyway." -- Kent M. Keith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:15:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is our choices, Harry, that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3670-it-does-not-do-to-dwell-on-dreams-and-forget</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:15:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3670-it-does-not-do-to-dwell-on-dreams-and-forget]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It does not do to dwell on dreams and forget to live." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:17:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:17:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512-there-is-no-greater-agony-than-bearing-an-untold-story</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:19:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512-there-is-no-greater-agony-than-bearing-an-untold-story]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no greater agony than bearing an untold story inside you." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:20:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that's what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that is holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life.  

A true soul mate is probably the most important person you'll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake.  But to live with a soul mate forever?  Nah. Too painful.  Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then leave.  

A soul mates purpose is to shake you up, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light can get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you have to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:21:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love never dies a natural death. It dies because we don't know how to replenish its source. It dies of blindness and errors and betrayals. It dies of illness and wounds; it dies of weariness, of witherings, of tarnishings." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:22:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finish each day and be done with it. You have done what you could.  Some blunders and absurdities no doubt crept in; forget them as soon as you can. Tomorrow is a new day.  You shall begin it serenely and with too high a spirit to be encumbered with your old nonsense." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4123-go-to-heaven-for-the-climate-and-hell-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:22:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4123-go-to-heaven-for-the-climate-and-hell-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Go to heaven for the climate and hell for the company." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5169-what-really-knocks-me-out-is-a-book-that-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:24:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5169-what-really-knocks-me-out-is-a-book-that-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What really knocks me out is a book that, when you're all done reading it, you wish the author that wrote it was a terrific friend of yours and you could call him up on the phone whenever you felt like it. That doesn't happen much, though." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3102-knowing-yourself-is-the-beginning-of-all-wisdom</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:25:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by Aristotle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3102-knowing-yourself-is-the-beginning-of-all-wisdom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Knowing yourself is the beginning of all wisdom." -- Aristotle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27992-do-you-remember-me-telling-you-we-are-practicing-non-verbal</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:25:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[azadeh add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27992-do-you-remember-me-telling-you-we-are-practicing-non-verbal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you remember me telling you we are practicing non-verbal spells, Potter?&quot;
&quot;Yes,&quot; said Harry stiffly.
&quot;Yes, sir.&quot;
&quot;There's no need to call me &quot;sir&quot; Professor.&quot;
The words had escaped him before he knew what he was saying." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
