<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/215600-christopher-plambeck]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/215600-christopher-plambeck" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 06:02:08 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177118-i-think-being-a-liberal-in-the-true-sense-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 06:02:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Walter Cronkite]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177118-i-think-being-a-liberal-in-the-true-sense-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think being a liberal, in the true sense, is being nondoctrinaire, nondogmatic, non-committed to a cause - but examining each case on its merits. Being left of center is another thing; it's a political position. I think most newspapermen by definition have to be liberal; if they're not liberal, by my definition of it, then they can hardly be good newspapermen. If they're preordained dogmatists for a cause, then they can't be very good journalists; that is, if they carry it into their journalism.&quot;

[Interview with Ron Powers (&lt;i&gt;Chicago Sun Times&lt;/i&gt;) for &lt;i&gt;Playboy&lt;/i&gt;, 1973]" -- Walter Cronkite]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76744-all-too-will-bear-in-mind-this-sacred-principle-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 06:03:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76744-all-too-will-bear-in-mind-this-sacred-principle-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All, too, will bear in mind this sacred principle, that though the will of the majority is in all cases to prevail, that will to be rightful must be reasonable; that the minority possess their equal rights, which equal law must protect, and to violate would be oppression. " -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 06:04:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not the critic who counts; not the man who points out how the strong man stumbles, or where the doer of deeds could have done them better. The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the arena, whose face is marred by dust and sweat and blood; who strives valiantly; who errs, who comes short again and again, because there is no effort without error and shortcoming; but who does actually strive to do the deeds; who knows great enthusiasms, the great devotions; who spends himself in a worthy cause; who at the best knows in the end the triumph of high achievement, and who at the worst, if he fails, at least fails while daring greatly, so that his place shall never be with those cold and timid souls who neither know victory nor defeat." -- Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/692677-novels-aren-t-just-happy-escapes-they-are-slivers-of-people-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 00:26:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/692677-novels-aren-t-just-happy-escapes-they-are-slivers-of-people-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Novels aren’t just happy escapes; they are slivers of people’s souls, nailed to the pages, dripping ink from veins of wood pulp. Reading the right one at the right time can make all the difference." -- Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
