<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/216152-gina-mcgrew]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/216152-gina-mcgrew" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 13:19:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/264155-as-far-as-food-is-concerned-the-great-extravagance-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 13:19:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Peter Singer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/264155-as-far-as-food-is-concerned-the-great-extravagance-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As far as food is concerned, the great extravagance is not caviar or truffles, but beef, pork and poultry. Some 38 percent of the world's grain crop is now fed to animals, as well as large quantities of soybeans. There are three times as many domestic animals on this planet as there are human beings. The combined weight of the world's 1.28 billion cattle alone exceeds that of the human population. While we look darkly at the number of babies being born in poorer parts of the world, we ignore the over-population of farm animals, to which we ourselves contribute...[t]hat, however, is only part of the damage done by the animals we deliberately breed. The energy intensive factory farming methods of the industrialised nations are responsible for the consumption of huge amounts of fossil fuels. Chemical fertilizers, used to grow the feed crops for cattle in feedlots and pigs and chickens kept indoors in sheds, produce nitrous oxide, another greenhouse gas. Then there is the loss of forests. Everywhere, forest-dwellers, both human and non-human, can be pushed out. Since 1960, 25 percent of the forests of Central America have been cleared for cattle. Once cleared, the poor soils will support grazing for a few years; then the graziers must move on. Shrub takes over the abandoned pasture, but the forest does not return. When the forests are cleared so the cattle can graze, billions of tons of carbon dioxide are released into the atmosphere. Finally, the world's cattle are thought to produce about 20 percent of the methane released into the atmosphere, and methane traps twenty-five times as much heat from the sun as carbon dioxide. Factory farm manure also produces methane because, unlike manured dropped naturally in the fields, it dies not decompose in the presence of oxygen. All of this amounts to a compelling reason...for a plant based diet." -- Peter Singer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46429-all-the-arguments-to-prove-man-s-superiority-cannot-shatter-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 13:19:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Peter Singer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46429-all-the-arguments-to-prove-man-s-superiority-cannot-shatter-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All the arguments to prove man's superiority cannot shatter this hard fact: in suffering the animals are our equals." -- Peter Singer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363941-to-protest-about-bullfighting-in-spain-the-eating-of-dogs</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 13:22:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Peter Singer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363941-to-protest-about-bullfighting-in-spain-the-eating-of-dogs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To protest about bullfighting in Spain, the eating of dogs in South Korea, or the slaughter of baby seals in Canada while continuing to eat eggs from hens who have spent their lives crammed into cages, or veal from calves who have been deprived of their mothers, their proper diet, and the freedom to lie down with their legs extended, is like denouncing apartheid in South Africa while asking your neighbors not to sell their houses to blacks." -- Peter Singer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:35:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:35:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:36:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one can make you feel inferior without your consent." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:36:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many books, so little time." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:36:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198-i-am-so-clever-that-sometimes-i-don-t-understand-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:36:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198-i-am-so-clever-that-sometimes-i-don-t-understand-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am so clever that sometimes I don't understand a single word of what I am saying." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:36:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:36:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be yourself in a world that is constantly trying to make you something else is the greatest accomplishment." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6384-imperfection-is-beauty-madness-is-genius-and-it-s-better-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:37:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6384-imperfection-is-beauty-madness-is-genius-and-it-s-better-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imperfection is beauty, madness is genius and it's better to be absolutely ridiculous than absolutely boring." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:38:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't see things as they are, we see them as we are." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/619-it-is-never-too-late-to-be-what-you-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:38:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/619-it-is-never-too-late-to-be-what-you-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is never too late to be what you might have been." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:39:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by William Nicholson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We read to know we're not alone." -- William Nicholson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:39:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:39:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always imagined that Paradise will be a kind of library." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512-there-is-no-greater-agony-than-bearing-an-untold-story</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:40:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512-there-is-no-greater-agony-than-bearing-an-untold-story]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no greater agony than bearing an untold story inside you." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11864-i-m-not-upset-that-you-lied-to-me-i-m-upset</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:40:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11864-i-m-not-upset-that-you-lied-to-me-i-m-upset]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not upset that you lied to me, I'm upset that from now on I can't believe you." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2209-the-question-isn-t-who-is-going-to-let-me-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:40:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2209-the-question-isn-t-who-is-going-to-let-me-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The question isn't who is going to let me; it's who is going to stop me." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62235-i-am-good-but-not-an-angel-i-do-sin</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:41:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62235-i-am-good-but-not-an-angel-i-do-sin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am good, but not an angel. I do sin, but I am not the devil. I am just a small girl in a big world trying to find someone to love." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54339-i-solemnly-swear-that-i-am-up-to-no-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:41:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54339-i-solemnly-swear-that-i-am-up-to-no-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I solemnly swear that I am up to no good." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:41:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12867-if-you-can-make-a-woman-laugh-you-can-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:42:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12867-if-you-can-make-a-woman-laugh-you-can-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can make a woman laugh, you can make her do anything." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:42:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finish each day and be done with it. You have done what you could.  Some blunders and absurdities no doubt crept in; forget them as soon as you can. Tomorrow is a new day.  You shall begin it serenely and with too high a spirit to be encumbered with your old nonsense." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:42:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5521-everything-you-can-imagine-is-real</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:43:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Pablo Picasso]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5521-everything-you-can-imagine-is-real]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything you can imagine is real." -- Pablo Picasso]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13146-never-trust-anyone-who-has-not-brought-a-book-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:43:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13146-never-trust-anyone-who-has-not-brought-a-book-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never trust anyone who has not brought a book with them." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13519-reality-continues-to-ruin-my-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:43:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Bill Watterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13519-reality-continues-to-ruin-my-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reality continues to ruin my life." -- Bill Watterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171595-the-real-lover-is-the-man-who-can-thrill-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 17:43:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171595-the-real-lover-is-the-man-who-can-thrill-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The real lover is the man who can thrill you by kissing your forehead or smiling into your eyes or just staring into space." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
