<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/216337-evan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/216337-evan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 17:31:41 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4226-no-man-really-knows-about-other-human-beings-the-best</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 17:31:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4226-no-man-really-knows-about-other-human-beings-the-best]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No man really knows about other human beings. The best he can do is to suppose that they are like himself." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5732-all-that-you-touch-you-change-all-that-you-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 20:05:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Octavia E. Butler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5732-all-that-you-touch-you-change-all-that-you-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that you touch
You Change.

All that you Change
Changes you.

The only lasting truth
is Change.

God
is Change." -- Octavia E. Butler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8206-do-i-contradict-myself-very-well-then-i-contradict-myself</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 14:02:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8206-do-i-contradict-myself-very-well-then-i-contradict-myself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do I contradict myself? Very well, then, I contradict myself; I am large -- I contain multitudes." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4343-i-never-saw-a-wild-thing-sorry-for-itself-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 14:07:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4343-i-never-saw-a-wild-thing-sorry-for-itself-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I never saw a wild thing sorry for itself.  A small bird will drop frozen dead from a bough without ever having felt sorry for itself." -- D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111725-get-yourself-in-that-intense-state-of-being-next-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2009 19:47:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111725-get-yourself-in-that-intense-state-of-being-next-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Get yourself in that intense state of being next to madness. Keep yourself in, not necessarily a frenzied state, but in a state of great intensity. The kind of state you would be in before going to bed with your partner. That heightened state when you're in a carnal embrace: time stops and nothing else matters. You should always write with an erection. Even if you're a woman." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26620-we-waste-time-looking-for-the-perfect-lover-instead-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2009 19:47:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26620-we-waste-time-looking-for-the-perfect-lover-instead-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We waste time looking for the perfect lover, instead of creating the perfect love." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2009 19:47:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39433-your-visions-will-become-clear-only-when-you-can-look</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 20:06:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by C.G. Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39433-your-visions-will-become-clear-only-when-you-can-look]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your visions will become clear only when you can look into your own heart. Who looks outside, dreams; who looks inside, awakes." -- C.G. Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165836-toni-morrison-said-the-function-of-freedom-is-to-free</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 23:25:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165836-toni-morrison-said-the-function-of-freedom-is-to-free]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Toni Morrison said, &quot;The function of freedom is to free someone else,&quot; and if you are no longer wracked or in bondage to a person or a way of life, tell your story. Risk freeing someone else. Not everyone will be glad that you did. Members of your family and other critics may wish you had kept your secrets. Oh, well, what are you going to do?" -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18179-freeing-yourself-was-one-thing-claiming-ownership-of-that-freed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 23:48:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18179-freeing-yourself-was-one-thing-claiming-ownership-of-that-freed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Freeing yourself was one thing, claiming ownership of that freed self was another." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15829-as-you-enter-positions-of-trust-and-power-dream-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 23:48:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15829-as-you-enter-positions-of-trust-and-power-dream-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As you enter positions of trust and power, dream a little before you think." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25526-to-get-to-a-place-where-you-could-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 23:51:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25526-to-get-to-a-place-where-you-could-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To get to a place where you could love anything you chose--not to need permission for desire--well now _that_ was freedom." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75995-is-there-no-context-for-our-lives-no-song-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 23:54:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75995-is-there-no-context-for-our-lives-no-song-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is there no context for our lives? No song, no literature, no poem full of vitamins, no history connected to experience that you can pass along to help us start strong? You are an adult. The old one, the wise one. Stop thinking about saving your face. Think of our lives and tell us your particularized world. Make up a story. Narrative is radical, creating us at the very moment it is being created. We will not blame you if your reach exceeds your grasp; if love so ignites your words they go down in flames and nothing is left but their scald. Or if, with the reticence of a surgeon's hands, your words suture only the places where blood might flow. We know you can never do it properly - once and for all. Passion is never enough; neither is skill. But try. For our sake and yours forget your name in the street; tell us what the world has been to you in the dark places and in the light. Don't tell us what to believe, what to fear. Show us belief s wide skirt and the stitch that unravels fear's caul. You, old woman, blessed with blindness, can speak the language that tells us what only language can: how to see without pictures. Language alone protects us from the scariness of things with no names. Language alone is meditation." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157843-anger-it-s-a-paralyzing-emotion-you-can-t-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 23:54:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157843-anger-it-s-a-paralyzing-emotion-you-can-t-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anger ... it's a paralyzing emotion ... you can't get anything done. People sort of think it's an interesting, passionate, and igniting feeling — I don't think it's any of that — it's helpless ... it's absence of control — and I need all of my skills, all of the control, all of my powers ... and anger doesn't provide any of that — I have no use for it whatsoever.&quot;

[Interview with CBS radio host Don Swaim, September 15, 1987.]" -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153685-let-me-tell-you-about-love-that-silly-word-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 23:54:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153685-let-me-tell-you-about-love-that-silly-word-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me tell you about love, that silly word you believe is about whether you like somebody or whether somebody likes you or whether you can put up with somebody in order to get something or someplace you want or you believe it has to do with how your body responds to another body like robins or bison or maybe you believe love is how forces or nature or luck is benign to you in particular not maiming or killing you but if so doing it for your own good. Love is none of that. There is nothing in nature like it. Not in robins or bison or in the banging tails of your hunting dogs and not in blossoms or suckling foal. Love is divine only and difficult always. If you think it is easy you are a fool. If you think it is natural you are blind. It is a learned application without reason or motive except that it is God. You do not deserve love regardless of the suffering you have endured. You do not deserve love because somebody did you wrong. You do not deserve love just because you want it. You can only earn - by practice and careful contemplations - the right to express it and you have to learn how to accept it. Which is to say you have to earn God. You have to practice God. You have to think God-carefully. And if you are a good and diligent student you may secure the right to show love. Love is not a gift. It is a diploma. A diploma conferring certain privileges: the privilege of expressing love and the privilege of receiving it. How do you know you have graduated? You don't. What you do know is that you are human and therefore educable, and therefore capable of learning how to learn, and therefore interesting to God, who is interested only in Himself which is to say He is interested only in love. Do you understand me? God is not interested in you. He is interested in love and the bliss it brings to those who understand and share the interest. Couples that enter the sacrament of marriage and are not prepared to go the distance or are not willing to get right with the real love of God cannot thrive. They may cleave together like robins or gulls or anything else that mates for life. But if they eschew this mighty course, at the moment when all are judged for the disposition of their eternal lives, their cleaving won't mean a thing. God bless the pure and holy. Amen." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113926-not-knowing-it-was-hard-knowing-it-was-harder</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 23:55:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113926-not-knowing-it-was-hard-knowing-it-was-harder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not knowing it was hard; knowing it was harder" -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204449-in-a-way-her-strangeness-her-naivet-her-craving-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 23:58:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204449-in-a-way-her-strangeness-her-naivet-her-craving-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a way, her strangeness, her naiveté, her craving for the other half of her equation was the consequence of an idle imagination. Had she paints, or clay, or knew the discipline of the dance, or strings, had she anything to engage her tremendous curiosity and her gift for metaphor, she might have exchanged the restlessness and preoccupation with whim for an activity that provided her with all she yearned for. And like an artist with no art form, she became dangerous." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61168-i-m-not-entangled-in-shaping-my-work-according-to-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 23:59:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61168-i-m-not-entangled-in-shaping-my-work-according-to-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not entangled in shaping my work according to other people's views of how I should have done it." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170530-she-had-been-looking-all-along-for-a-friend-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 00:03:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170530-she-had-been-looking-all-along-for-a-friend-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had been looking all along for a friend, and it took her a while to discover that a lover was not a comrade and could never be - for a woman. And that no one would ever be that version of herself which she sought to reach out to and touch with an ungloved hand. There was only her own mood and whim, and if that was all there was, she decided to turn the naked hand toward it, discover it and let others become as intimate with their own selves as she was." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182715-writing-is-really-a-way-of-thinking--not-just-feeling-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 00:04:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182715-writing-is-really-a-way-of-thinking--not-just-feeling-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing is really a way of thinking--not just feeling but thinking about things that are disparate, unresolved, mysterious, problematic or just sweet." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127938-this-is-the-time-for-every-artist-in-every-genre</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 00:06:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127938-this-is-the-time-for-every-artist-in-every-genre]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is the time for every artist in every genre to do what he or she does loudly and consistently. It doesn't matter to me what your position is. You've got to keep asserting the complexity and the originality of life, and the multiplicity of it, and the facets of it. This is about being a complex human being in the world, not about finding a villain. This is no time for anything else than the best that you've got." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212024-i-really-think-the-range-of-emotions-and-perceptions-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 01:13:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212024-i-really-think-the-range-of-emotions-and-perceptions-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I really think the range of emotions and perceptions I have had access to as a black person and as a female person are greater than those of people who are neither.... So it seems to me that my world did not shrink because I was a black female writer. It just got bigger." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55830-when-we-find-ourselves-believing-that-killing-a-man-makes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2011 23:17:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Jay Smooth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55830-when-we-find-ourselves-believing-that-killing-a-man-makes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we find ourselves believing that killing a man makes us more of a man, but loving a man makes us less of a man, it’s probably time to reexamine our criteria for manhood.

" -- Jay Smooth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46021-give-me-for-my-life-all-lives-give-me-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 21:05:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46021-give-me-for-my-life-all-lives-give-me-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Give me, for my life,
all lives,
give me all the pain
of everyone, 
I'm going to turn it into hope.
Give me 
all the joys,
even the most secret,
because otherwise
how will these things be known?
I have to tell them,
give me
the labors
of everyday,
for that's what I sing." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156618-here-i-came-to-the-very-edge-where-nothing-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 21:09:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156618-here-i-came-to-the-very-edge-where-nothing-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here I came to the very edge 
where nothing at all needs saying, 
everything is absorbed through weather and the sea, 
and the moon swam back, 
its rays all silvered, 
and time and again the darkness would be broken 
by the crash of a wave, 
and every day on the balcony of the sea, 
wings open, fire is born, 
and everything is blue again like morning. " -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111035-i-want-to-see-thirst-in-the-syllables-tough-fire</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 21:09:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111035-i-want-to-see-thirst-in-the-syllables-tough-fire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to see thirst
In the syllables,
Tough fire
In the sound;
Feel through the dark
For the scream." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167759-monsters-are-real-and-ghosts-are-real-too-they-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 14:43:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167759-monsters-are-real-and-ghosts-are-real-too-they-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Monsters are real, and ghosts are real too. They live inside us, and sometimes, they win." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6779-a-short-story-is-a-different-thing-all-together--</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 14:43:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6779-a-short-story-is-a-different-thing-all-together--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A short story is a different thing all together - a short story is like a kiss in the dark from a stranger." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48822-writing-isn-t-about-making-money-getting-famous-getting-dates-getting</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 14:49:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48822-writing-isn-t-about-making-money-getting-famous-getting-dates-getting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing isn't about making money, getting famous, getting dates, getting laid, or making friends. In the end, it's about enriching the lives of those who will read your work, and enriching your own life, as well. It's about getting up, getting well, and getting over. Getting happy, okay? Getting happy." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14908-it-is-the-tale-not-he-who-tells-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 14:52:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14908-it-is-the-tale-not-he-who-tells-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is the tale, not he who tells it." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
