<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/21661-sara-dempsey]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/21661-sara-dempsey" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 07:41:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13208-you-fight-your-superficiality-your-shallowness-so-as-to-try</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 07:41:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sara add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13208-you-fight-your-superficiality-your-shallowness-so-as-to-try]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You fight your superficiality, your shallowness, so as to try to come at people without unreal expectations, without an overload of bias or hope or arrogance, as untanklike as you can be, sans cannon and machine guns and steel plating half a foot thick; you come at them unmenacingly on your own ten toes instead of tearing up the turf with your caterpillar treads, take them on with an open mind, as equals, man to man, as we used to say, and yet you never fail to get them wrong.  You might as well have the brain of a tank.  You get them wrong before you meet them, while you're anticipating meeting them; you get them wrong while you're with them; and then you go home to tell somebody else about the meeting and you get them all wrong again.  Since the same generally goes for them with you, the whole thing is really a dazzling illusion. ...  The fact remains that getting people right is not what living is all about anyway.  It's getting them wrong that is living, getting them wrong and wrong and wrong and then, on careful reconsideration, getting them wrong again.  That's how we know we're alive:  we're wrong.  Maybe the best thing would be to forget being right or wrong about people and just go along for the ride.  But if you can do that -- well, lucky you." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118577-how-strange-it-is-we-have-these-deep-terrible-lingering</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 07:43:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sara add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118577-how-strange-it-is-we-have-these-deep-terrible-lingering]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How strange it is. We have these deep terrible lingering fears about ourselves and the people we love. Yet we walk around, talk to people, eat and drink. We manage to function. The feelings are deep and real. Shouldn't they paralyze us? How is it we can survive them, at least for a little while? We drive a car, we teach a class. How is it no one sees how deeply afraid we were, last night, this morning? Is it something we all hide from each other, by mutual consent? Or do we share the same secret without knowing it? Wear the same disguise?" -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145236-longing-on-a-large-scale-makes-history</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 07:45:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sara add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145236-longing-on-a-large-scale-makes-history]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Longing on a large scale makes history." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236832-loving-music-had-pushed-all-of-us-off-the-track-</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 08:13:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sara add a quote by Ann Powers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236832-loving-music-had-pushed-all-of-us-off-the-track-]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Loving music had pushed all of us off the track- away from the normal pursuit of career, mate, and family, on an endless quest for that vibrating high, the plunge beyond time that comes only when you submerge yourself beneath the waterline of amplified sound. We were addicts, in a way, but also adept, enlightened by a noise most people considered no more than a pleasant distraction. What was left for us but to practice our art of listening?" -- Ann Powers]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
