<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/216795-natalia-ospina]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/216795-natalia-ospina" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 06:38:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 06:38:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381-to-die-would-be-an-awfully-big-adventure</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 06:40:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381-to-die-would-be-an-awfully-big-adventure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To die would be an awfully big adventure." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15618-for-attractive-lips-speak-words-of-kindness-emsp-for-lovely-eyes</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 06:41:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Sam Levenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15618-for-attractive-lips-speak-words-of-kindness-emsp-for-lovely-eyes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For Attractive lips, speak words of kindness.
&amp;emsp;For lovely eyes, seek out the good in people.
&amp;emsp;For a slim figure, share your food with the hungry.
&amp;emsp;For beautiful hair, let a child run their fingers through it once a day.
&amp;emsp;For poise, walk with the knowledge that you never walk alone. 
&amp;emsp;People, more than things, have to be restored, renewed, revived, reclaimed, and redeemed. Remember, if you ever need a helping hand, you will find one at the end of each of your arms.
&amp;emsp;As you grow older, you will discover that you have two hands, one for helping yourself and the other for helping others." -- Sam Levenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5082-love-is-a-fire-but-whether-it-is-going-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 06:44:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Joan Crawford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5082-love-is-a-fire-but-whether-it-is-going-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a fire. But whether it is going to warm your hearth or burn down your house, you can never tell." -- Joan Crawford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 06:49:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that no matter what happens, or how bad it seems today, life does go on, and it will be better tomorrow. I've learned that you can tell a lot about a person by the way he/she handles these three things: a rainy day, lost luggage, and tangled Christmas tree lights. I've learned that regardless of your relationship with your parents, you'll miss them when they're gone from your life. I've learned that making a &quot;living&quot; is not the same thing as making a &quot;life.&quot; I've learned that life sometimes gives you a second chance. I've learned that you shouldn't go through life with a catcher's mitt on both hands; you need to be able to throw something back. I've learned that whenever I decide something with an open heart, I usually make the right decision. I've learned that even when I have pains, I don't have to be one. I've learned that every day you should reach out and touch someone. People love a warm hug, or just a friendly pat on the back. I've learned that I still have a lot to learn. I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 06:52:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27292-i-love-sleep-my-life-has-the-tendency-to-fall</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 06:55:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27292-i-love-sleep-my-life-has-the-tendency-to-fall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love sleep. My life has the tendency to fall apart when I'm awake, you know?" -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116153-i-heard-what-you-said-i-m-not-the-silly-romantic</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 06:58:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Shana Abe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116153-i-heard-what-you-said-i-m-not-the-silly-romantic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I heard what you said. I’m not the silly romantic you think. I don’t want the heavens or the shooting stars. I don’t want gemstones or gold. I have those things already. I want…a steady hand. A kind soul. I want to fall asleep, and wake, knowing my heart is safe. I want to love, and be loved." -- Shana Abe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67443-what-i-want-is-to-be-needed-what-i-need</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 06:58:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67443-what-i-want-is-to-be-needed-what-i-need]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I want is to be needed. What I need is to be indispensable to somebody. Who I need is somebody that will eat up all my free time, my ego, my attention. Somebody addicted to me. A mutual addiction." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2102-love-does-not-consist-of-gazing-at-each-other-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:00:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2102-love-does-not-consist-of-gazing-at-each-other-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love does not consist of gazing at each other, but in looking outward together in the same direction." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2377-these-woods-are-lovely-dark-and-deep-but-i-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:01:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2377-these-woods-are-lovely-dark-and-deep-but-i-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These woods are lovely, dark and deep,
But I have promises to keep,
And miles to go before I sleep,
And miles to go before I sleep." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204561-we-re-all-a-little-weird-and-life-is-a-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:02:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204561-we-re-all-a-little-weird-and-life-is-a-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We’re all a little weird. And life is a little weird. And when we find someone whose weirdness is compatible with ours, we join up with them and fall into mutually satisfying weirdness—and call it love—true love." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64899-if-you-love-something-set-it-free-but-don-t-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:11:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64899-if-you-love-something-set-it-free-but-don-t-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you love something set it free, but don't be surprised if it comes back with herpes." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84843-sometimes-love-means-letting-go-when-you-want-to-hold</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:14:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Melissa Marr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84843-sometimes-love-means-letting-go-when-you-want-to-hold]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes love means letting go when you want to hold on tighter." -- Melissa Marr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16113-the-difference-between-sex-and-love-is-that-sex-relieves</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:16:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Woody Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16113-the-difference-between-sex-and-love-is-that-sex-relieves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The difference between sex and love is that sex relieves tension and love causes it." -- Woody Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44520-i-love-to-see-a-young-girl-go-out-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:19:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by maya angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44520-i-love-to-see-a-young-girl-go-out-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love to see a young girl go out and grab the world by the lapels. Life's a bitch. You've got to go out and kick ass." -- maya angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230886-you-may-not-be-her-first-her-last-or-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:20:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230886-you-may-not-be-her-first-her-last-or-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may not be her first, her last, or her only. She loved before she may love again. But if she loves you now, what else matters? She's not perfect—you aren't either, and the two of you may never be perfect together but if she can make you laugh, cause you to think twice, and admit to being human and making mistakes, hold onto her and give her the most you can. She may not be thinking about you every second of the day, but she will give you a part of her that she knows you can break—her heart. So don't hurt her, don't change her, don't analyze and don't expect more than she can give. Smile when she makes you happy, let her know when she makes you mad, and miss her when she's not there." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12018-love-is-the-ultimate-outlaw-it-just-won-t-adhere-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:24:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12018-love-is-the-ultimate-outlaw-it-just-won-t-adhere-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is the ultimate outlaw. It just won't adhere to any rules. The most any of us can do is to sign on as its accomplice. Instead of vowing to honor and obey, maybe we should swear to aid and abet. That would mean that security is out of the question. The words &quot;make&quot; and &quot;stay&quot; become inappropriate. My love for you has no strings attached. I love you for free." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93997-love-the-life-you-live-live-the-life-you-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:26:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93997-love-the-life-you-live-live-the-life-you-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["love the life you live.
live the life you love." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9120-if-we-listened-to-our-intellect-we-d-never-have-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:30:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9120-if-we-listened-to-our-intellect-we-d-never-have-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we listened to our intellect we'd never have a love affair. We'd never have a friendship. We'd never go in business because we'd be cynical: &quot;It's gonna go wrong.&quot; Or &quot;She's going to hurt me.&quot; Or,&quot;I've had a couple of bad love affairs, so therefore . . .&quot; Well, that's nonsense. You're going to miss life. You've got to jump off the cliff all the time and build your wings on the way down." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64329-we-re-all-going-to-die-all-of-us-what-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:31:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64329-we-re-all-going-to-die-all-of-us-what-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're all going to die, all of us, what a circus! That alone should make us love each other but it doesn't. We are terrorized and flattened by trivialities, we are eaten up by nothing." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3388-love-is-a-snowmobile-racing-across-the-tundra-and-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:35:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Matt Groening]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3388-love-is-a-snowmobile-racing-across-the-tundra-and-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a snowmobile racing across the tundra and then suddenly it flips over, pinning you underneath. At night, the ice weasels come." -- Matt Groening]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29750-i-will-love-you-as-the-iceberg-loves-the-ship</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:36:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29750-i-will-love-you-as-the-iceberg-loves-the-ship]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will love you as the iceberg loves the ship, and the passengers love the lifeboat and the lifeboat loves the teeth of the sperm whale, and the sperm whale loves the flavor of naval uniforms." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31469-happiness-is-only-real-when-shared</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:40:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31469-happiness-is-only-real-when-shared]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["HAPPINESS [is] ONLY REAL WHEN SHARED" -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239692-some-women-choose-to-follow-men-and-some-women-choose</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:43:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Lady Gaga]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239692-some-women-choose-to-follow-men-and-some-women-choose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some women choose to follow men, and some women choose to follow their dreams. If you're wondering which way to go, remember that your career will never wake up and tell you that it doesn't love you anymore." -- Lady Gaga]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131148-i-read-once-that-the-ancient-egyptians-had-fifty-words</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:49:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Brian Andreas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131148-i-read-once-that-the-ancient-egyptians-had-fifty-words]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read once that the ancient Egyptians had fifty words for sand &amp; the Eskimos had a hundred words for snow. I wish I had a thousand words for love, but all that comes to mind is the way you move against me while you sleep &amp; there are no words for that." -- Brian Andreas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350-i-with-a-deeper-instinct-choose-a-man-who-compels</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 03:23:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350-i-with-a-deeper-instinct-choose-a-man-who-compels]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I, with a deeper instinct, choose a man who compels my strength, who makes enormous demands on me, who does not doubt my courage or my toughness, who does not believe me naïve or innocent, who has the courage to treat me like a woman." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12825-the-trouble-with-some-women-is-that-they-get-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 03:28:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Cher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12825-the-trouble-with-some-women-is-that-they-get-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble with some women is that they get all excited about nothing - and then marry him." -- Cher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63419-in-politics-if-you-want-anything-said-ask-a-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 03:31:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Margaret Thatcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63419-in-politics-if-you-want-anything-said-ask-a-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In politics, If you want anything said, ask a man. If you want anything done, ask a woman." -- Margaret Thatcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111546-as-lovers-the-difference-between-men-and-women-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 03:37:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111546-as-lovers-the-difference-between-men-and-women-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As lovers, the difference between men and women is that women can love all day long, but men only at times." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
