<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/217079-amanda]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/217079-amanda" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 08:58:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1944-a-woman-is-like-a-tea-bag-you-never-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 08:58:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1944-a-woman-is-like-a-tea-bag-you-never-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A woman is like a tea bag; you never know how strong it is until it's in hot water." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1930-think-of-all-the-beauty-still-left-around-you-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 09:10:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1930-think-of-all-the-beauty-still-left-around-you-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Think of all the beauty still left around you and be happy." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/805-when-it-is-dark-enough-you-can-see-the-stars</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 10:37:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/805-when-it-is-dark-enough-you-can-see-the-stars]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When it is dark enough, you can see the stars." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7941-when-i-do-good-i-feel-good-when-i-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 10:39:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7941-when-i-do-good-i-feel-good-when-i-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I do good, I feel good. When I do bad, I feel bad. That's my religion." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4647-having-children-makes-you-no-more-a-parent-than-having</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 10:40:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Michael Levine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4647-having-children-makes-you-no-more-a-parent-than-having]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Having children makes you no more a parent than having a piano makes you a pianist." -- Michael Levine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13421-how-wrong-is-it-for-a-woman-to-expect-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 13:40:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13421-how-wrong-is-it-for-a-woman-to-expect-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How wrong is it for a woman to expect the man to build the world she wants, rather than to create it herself?" -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4586-beer-is-proof-that-god-loves-us-and-wants-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 13:41:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4586-beer-is-proof-that-god-loves-us-and-wants-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beer is proof that God loves us and wants us to be happy.

[misquote of a letter about wine, see quotes/831031]" -- Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 10:01:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May your coming year be filled with magic and dreams and good madness. I hope you read some fine books and kiss someone who thinks you're wonderful, and don't forget to make some art -- write or draw or build or sing or live as only you can. And I hope, somewhere in the next year, you surprise yourself." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230886-you-may-not-be-her-first-her-last-or-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 09:00:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230886-you-may-not-be-her-first-her-last-or-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may not be her first, her last, or her only. She loved before she may love again. But if she loves you now, what else matters? She's not perfect—you aren't either, and the two of you may never be perfect together but if she can make you laugh, cause you to think twice, and admit to being human and making mistakes, hold onto her and give her the most you can. She may not be thinking about you every second of the day, but she will give you a part of her that she knows you can break—her heart. So don't hurt her, don't change her, don't analyze and don't expect more than she can give. Smile when she makes you happy, let her know when she makes you mad, and miss her when she's not there." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16455-i-am-coming-to-terms-with-the-fact-that-loving</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 09:02:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16455-i-am-coming-to-terms-with-the-fact-that-loving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am coming to terms with the fact that loving someone requires a leap of faith, and that a soft landing is never guaranteed." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 09:04:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that no matter what happens, or how bad it seems today, life does go on, and it will be better tomorrow. I've learned that you can tell a lot about a person by the way he/she handles these three things: a rainy day, lost luggage, and tangled Christmas tree lights. I've learned that regardless of your relationship with your parents, you'll miss them when they're gone from your life. I've learned that making a &quot;living&quot; is not the same thing as making a &quot;life.&quot; I've learned that life sometimes gives you a second chance. I've learned that you shouldn't go through life with a catcher's mitt on both hands; you need to be able to throw something back. I've learned that whenever I decide something with an open heart, I usually make the right decision. I've learned that even when I have pains, I don't have to be one. I've learned that every day you should reach out and touch someone. People love a warm hug, or just a friendly pat on the back. I've learned that I still have a lot to learn. I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 09:06:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13155-it-is-a-curious-thing-the-death-of-a-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 09:08:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13155-it-is-a-curious-thing-the-death-of-a-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a curious thing, the death of a loved one. We all know that our time in this world is limited, and that eventually all of us will end up underneath some sheet, never to wake up. And yet it is always a surprise when it happens to someone we know. It is like walking up the stairs to your bedroom in the dark, and thinking there is one more stair than there is. Your foot falls down, through the air, and there is a sickly moment of dark surprise as you try and readjust the way you thought of things." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65817-i-think-if-i-ve-learned-anything-about-friendship-it-s-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 09:08:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Jon Katz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65817-i-think-if-i-ve-learned-anything-about-friendship-it-s-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think if I've learned anything about friendship, it's to hang in, stay connected, fight for them, and let them fight for you. Don't walk away, don't be distracted, don't be too busy or tired, don't take them for granted. Friends are part of the glue that holds life and faith together. Powerful stuff." -- Jon Katz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117810-it-began-in-mystery-and-it-will-end-in-mystery</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 10:38:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Diane Ackerman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117810-it-began-in-mystery-and-it-will-end-in-mystery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It began in mystery, and it will end in mystery, but what a savage and beautiful country lies in between." -- Diane Ackerman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353982-mister-dresden-he-said-and-miss-rodriguez-i-believe-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 12:46:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Jim Butcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353982-mister-dresden-he-said-and-miss-rodriguez-i-believe-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mister Dresden,&quot; he said. &quot;And Miss Rodriguez, I believe. I didn't realize you were an art collector.&quot; 
&quot;I am the foremost collector of velvet Elvii in the city of Chicago,&quot; I said at once. 
&quot;Elvii?&quot; Marcone inquired. 
&quot;The plural could be Elvises, I guess,&quot; I said. &quot;But if I say that too often, I start muttering to myself and calling things 'my precious,' so I usually go with the Latin plural." -- Jim Butcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/524303-crotch-biting-menace-i-have-my-mouth-in-close-proximity-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 10:03:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Nick Harkaway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/524303-crotch-biting-menace-i-have-my-mouth-in-close-proximity-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Crotch biting menace:I have my mouth in close proximity to your genitals.Oh thou man who talks to my mistress over coffee.Do not irk or trifle with me! I possess but one tooth, oh, yes, for the rest were buried long ago in the flesh of sinners.Behold my jaws, upper and lower in righteous, symmetrical poverty.Move not, man of clocks, and heed my mistress, for she cherishes me, even in my foul old age." -- Nick Harkaway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717966-mr-pritchard-what-are-you-doing-is-that-o-soto-gari-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 10:09:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Nick Harkaway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717966-mr-pritchard-what-are-you-doing-is-that-o-soto-gari-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mr. Pritchard!  What are you doing?  Is that O-soto-gari?  No!  It is not!  It is a yak mating with a tractor!  That is really very very not very good!  My grandfather is weeping in Heaven, or he would if there were such a place, which there is not because religion is a mystification contrived by monarchists!  Again!  Again, and this time do it properly!" -- Nick Harkaway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717967-just-got-to-fnafflebrump-caddwallame-all-right-edie-says-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 10:12:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Nick Harkaway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717967-just-got-to-fnafflebrump-caddwallame-all-right-edie-says-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just got to fnafflebrump caddwallame, all right?&quot;  Edie says, and no one pays attention.  She learned at Lady Gravely's that nonsense which can be misheard is a very good way to lie without getting caught.  People just insert whatever they think you must be doing, and - having lied to themselves on your behalf - are disinclined to check up on you." -- Nick Harkaway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717970-joshua-joseph-has-no-real-hatred-of-modern-technology--</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 10:25:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Nick Harkaway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717970-joshua-joseph-has-no-real-hatred-of-modern-technology--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Joshua Joseph has no real hatred of modern technology - he just mistrusts the effortless, textureless surfaces, and the ease with which it trains you to do things in the way most convenient to the machine.  Above all, he mistrusts duplication.  A rare thing becomes a commonplace thing.  A skill becomes a feature.  The end is more important than the means.  The child of the soul gives place to a product of the system....For anything really important, Joe prefers something with a history, an item which can name the hand which assembled it and will warm to the one that deploys it.  A thing of life, rather than one of the many consumer items which humans use to make more clutter; strange parasitic devices with their own little ecosystems." -- Nick Harkaway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136751-here-is-a-relationship-booster-that-is-guaranteed-to-work</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 10:50:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136751-here-is-a-relationship-booster-that-is-guaranteed-to-work]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here is a relationship booster
that is guaranteed to
work:

Every time your spouse or lover says something stupid
make your eyes light up as if you
just heard something
brilliant." -- Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408082-all-my-days-i-have-longed-equally-to-travel-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2014 08:16:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Sigrid Undset]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408082-all-my-days-i-have-longed-equally-to-travel-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All my days I have longed equally to travel the right road and to take my own errant path." -- Sigrid Undset]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411386-i-m-bored-is-a-useless-thing-to-say-i-mean</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 11:05:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Louis C.K.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411386-i-m-bored-is-a-useless-thing-to-say-i-mean]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’m bored’ is a useless thing to say. I mean, you live in a great, big, vast world that you’ve seen none percent of. Even the inside of your own mind is endless; it goes on forever, inwardly, do you understand? The fact that you’re alive is amazing, so you don’t get to say ‘I’m bored." -- Louis C.K.]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
