<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/217327-angie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/217327-angie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2009 16:11:58 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47930-let-me-say-right-here-if-i-haven-t-made-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2009 16:11:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by Christopher Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47930-let-me-say-right-here-if-i-haven-t-made-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me say right here, if I haven't made it clear, that I have seen as many pale, naked old-man parts in the last twenty-four hours to bruise my delicate psyche for a lifetime, so don't be surprised if you someday find me wandering the moors at midnight, a crazed look in my eye, babbling about albino Tater Tots nesting in Brillo pads and being pursued by sagging man ass, because that shit can happen when you've been traumatized." -- Christopher Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104714-because-to-influence-a-person-is-to-give-him-one-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 20:59:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104714-because-to-influence-a-person-is-to-give-him-one-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because to influence a person is to give him one's own soul. He does not think his natural thoughts, or burn with his natural passions. His virtues are not real to him. His sins, if there are such things as sins, are borrowed. He becomes an echo of some one else's music, an actor of a part that has not been written for him. The aim of life is self-development. To realize one's nature perfectly -- that is what each of us is here for. People are afraid of themselves, nowadays. They have forgotten the highest of all duties, the duty that one owes to oneself. Of course they are charitable. They feed the hungry, and clothe the beggar. But their own souls starve, and are naked. Courage has gone out of our race. Perhaps we never really had it. The terror of society, which is the basis of morals, the terror of God, which is the secret of religion -- these are the two things that govern us." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132343-sometimes-humans-hit-on-a-moment-of-profundity-more-complete</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2009 18:41:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by Kelley Armstrong]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132343-sometimes-humans-hit-on-a-moment-of-profundity-more-complete]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes humans hit on a moment of profundity more complete than their dim minds could comprehend, and they took that nugget of truth and dumped it in the refuse for the bards and the poets to find, and mangle into yodeling paeans of love." -- Kelley Armstrong]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138574-all-right-then-her-first-rule-for-the-rest-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2009 16:06:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by J.R. Ward]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138574-all-right-then-her-first-rule-for-the-rest-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All right, then, her first rule for the rest of her days: no more looking outside for definitions. She might not have any clue who she was, but better to be lost and searching than shoved into a social box by someone else." -- J.R. Ward]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318771-and-is-death-not-the-ultimate-orgasm-a-return-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2010 01:51:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by Lydia Lunch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318771-and-is-death-not-the-ultimate-orgasm-a-return-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And is death not the ultimate orgasm, a return to that otherworldly ether, whose very origins were indeed a Big Bang, the ultimate explosion, the supreme chaos, whose resonance is the vibration we constantly seek to reproduce in everything we do." -- Lydia Lunch]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
