<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/21753-kirstin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/21753-kirstin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:12:19 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1976-disbelief-in-magic-can-force-a-poor-soul-into-believing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:12:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1976-disbelief-in-magic-can-force-a-poor-soul-into-believing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Disbelief in magic can force a poor soul into believing in government and business." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440-who-knows-how-to-make-love-stay-1-tell-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:12:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440-who-knows-how-to-make-love-stay-1-tell-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who knows how to make love stay?

1. Tell love you are going to Junior's Deli on Flatbush Avenue in Brooklyn to pick up a cheesecake, and if loves stays, it can have half. It will stay.

2. Tell love you want a momento of it and obtain a lock of its hair. Burn the hair in a dime-store incense burner with yin/yang symbols on three sides. Face southwest. Talk fast over the burning hair in a convincingly exotic language. Remove the ashes of the burnt hair and use them to paint a moustache on your face. Find love. Tell it you are someone new. It will stay.

3. Wake love up in the middle of the night. Tell it the world is on fire. Dash to the bedroom window and pee out of it. Casually return to bed and assure love that everything is going to be all right. Fall asleep. Love will be there in the morning." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12878-just-because-you-re-naked-doesn-t-mean-you-re-sexy-just-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:12:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12878-just-because-you-re-naked-doesn-t-mean-you-re-sexy-just-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just because you're naked doesn't mean you're sexy. Just because you're cynical doesn't mean you're cool." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4139-there-are-many-things-worth-living-for-a-few-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:12:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4139-there-are-many-things-worth-living-for-a-few-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are many things worth living for, a few things worth dying for, and nothing worth killing for." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12018-love-is-the-ultimate-outlaw-it-just-won-t-adhere-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:13:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12018-love-is-the-ultimate-outlaw-it-just-won-t-adhere-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is the ultimate outlaw. It just won't adhere to any rules. The most any of us can do is to sign on as its accomplice. Instead of vowing to honor and obey, maybe we should swear to aid and abet. That would mean that security is out of the question. The words &quot;make&quot; and &quot;stay&quot; become inappropriate. My love for you has no strings attached. I love you for free." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14851-a-sense-of-humor-is-superior-to-any-religion-so-far</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:13:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14851-a-sense-of-humor-is-superior-to-any-religion-so-far]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A sense of humor...is superior to any religion so far devised." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16729-in-the-haunted-house-of-life-art-is-the-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:13:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16729-in-the-haunted-house-of-life-art-is-the-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the haunted house of life, art is the only stair that doesn't creak." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13861-people-tend-the-take-everything-too-seriously-especially-themselves-yep</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:14:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13861-people-tend-the-take-everything-too-seriously-especially-themselves-yep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People tend the take everything too seriously. Especially themselves. Yep. And that's probably what makes 'em scared and hurt so much of the time. Life is too serious to take that seriously." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6650-if-by-the-quarter-of-the-twentieth-century-godliness-wasn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:15:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6650-if-by-the-quarter-of-the-twentieth-century-godliness-wasn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If by the quarter of the twentieth century godliness wasn’t next to something more interesting than cleanliness, it might be time to reevaluate our notions of godliness." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19375-humanity-has-advanced-when-it-has-advanced-not-because-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:15:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by tom robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19375-humanity-has-advanced-when-it-has-advanced-not-because-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humanity has advanced, when it has advanced, not because it has been sober, responsible, and cautious, but because it has been playful, rebellious, and immature." -- tom robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32545-albert-camus-wrote-that-the-only-serious-question-is-whether</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:15:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32545-albert-camus-wrote-that-the-only-serious-question-is-whether]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Albert Camus wrote that the only serious question is whether to kill yourself or not.
Tom Robbins wrote that the only serious question is whether time has a beginning and an end.
Camus clearly got up on the wrong side of bed, and Robbins must have forgotten to set the alarm.
There is only one serious question. And that is: Who knows how to make love stay?
Answer me that and I will tell you whether or not to kill yourself." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27570-there-is-no-such-thing-as-a-weird-human-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:15:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27570-there-is-no-such-thing-as-a-weird-human-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no such thing as a weird human being, It's just that some people require more understanding than others." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3659-people-of-ze-wurl-relax</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:16:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3659-people-of-ze-wurl-relax]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People of ze wurl, relax!" -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37972-the-function-of-the-artist-is-to-provide-what-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:16:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37972-the-function-of-the-artist-is-to-provide-what-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The function of the artist is to provide what life does not." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1577-he-was-rowed-down-from-the-north-in-a-leather</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:21:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1577-he-was-rowed-down-from-the-north-in-a-leather]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was rowed down from the north in a leather skiff manned by a crew of trolls. His fur cape was caked with candle wax, his brow stained blue by wine - though the latter was seldom noticed due to the fox mask he wore at-all times. A quill in his teeth, a solitary teardrop a-squirm in his palm, he was the young poet prince of Montreal, handsome, immaculate, searching for sturdier doors to nail his poignant verses on. 
In Manhattan, grit drifted into his ink bottle. In Vienna, his spice box exploded. On the Greek island of Hydra, Orpheus came to him at dawn astride a transparent donkey and restrung his cheap guitar. From that moment on, he shamelessly and willingly exposed himself to the contagion of music. To the secretly religious curiosity of the traveler was added the openly foolhardy dignity of the troubadour. By the time he returned to America, songs were working in him like bees in an attic. Connoisseurs developed cravings for his nocturnal honey, despite the fact that hearts were occasionally stung. 

Now, thirty years later, as society staggers towards the millennium - nailing and screeching at the while, like an orangutan with a steak knife in its side - Leonard Cohen, his vision, his gift, his perseverance, are finally getting their due. It may be because he speaks to this wounded zeitgeist with particular eloquence and accuracy, it may be merely cultural time-lag, another example of the slow-to-catch-on many opening their ears belatedly to what the few have been hearing all along. In any case, the sparkle curtain has shredded, the boogie-woogie gate has rocked loose from its hinges, and here sits L. Cohen at an altar in the garden, solemnly enjoying new-found popularity and expanded respect. 

From the beginning, his musical peers have recognized Cohen´s ability to establish succinct analogies among life´s realities, his talent for creating intimate relationships between the interior world of longing and language and the exterior world of trains and violins. Even those performers who have neither &quot;covered&quot; his compositions nor been overtly influenced by them have professed to admire their artfulness: the darkly delicious melodies - aural bouquets of gardenia and thistle - that bring to mind an electrified, de-Germanized Kurt Weill; the playfully (and therefore dangerously) mournful lyrics that can peel the apple of love and the peach of lust with a knife that cuts all the way to the mystery, a layer Cole Porter just could`t expose. It is their desire to honor L. Cohen, songwriter, that has prompted a delegation of our brightest artists to climb, one by one, joss sticks smoldering, the steep and salty staircase in the Tower of Song." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30315-suppose-neutral-angels-were-able-to-talk-yahweh-and-lucifer</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:27:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30315-suppose-neutral-angels-were-able-to-talk-yahweh-and-lucifer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suppose neutral angels were able to talk, Yahweh and Lucifer – God and Satan, to use their popular titles – into settling out of court. What would be the terms of the compromise? Specifically, how would they divide the assets of their early kingdom?

Would God be satisfied the loaves and fishes and itty-bitty thimbles of Communion wine, while Satan to have the red-eye gravy, eighteen-ounce New York Stakes, and buckets of chilled champagne? Would God really accept twice-a-month lovemaking for procreative purposes and give Satan the all night, no-holds-barred, nasty “can’t-get-enough-of-you” hot-as-hell-fucks?

Think about it. Would Satan get New Orleans, Bangkok, and the French Riviera and God get Salt Lake City? Satan get ice hockey, God get horseshoes? God get bingo, Satan get stud poker? Satan get LSD; God, Prozac? God get Neil Simon; Satan Oscar Wilde?" -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33495-zippers-are-primal-and-modern-at-the-very-same-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:29:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33495-zippers-are-primal-and-modern-at-the-very-same-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Zippers are primal and modern at the very same time. On the one hand, your zipper is primitive and reptilian, on the other mechanical and slick. A zipper is where the Industrial Revolution meets the Cobra Cult, don't you think? Ahh. Little alligators of ecstasy, that's what zippers are. Sexy, too. Now your button, a button is prim and persnickety. There's somethin' Victorian about a row o' buttons. But a zipper, why a zipper is the very snake at the gate of Eden, waitin' to escort a true believer into the Garden. Faith, I should be sewin' more zippers into me garments, for I have many erogenous zones that require speedy access. Mmm, old zipper creeper, hanging head down like the carcass of a lizard; the phantom viper that we shun in daytime and communicate with at night." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33488-she-closed-her-eyes-and-tried-to-imagine-sex-entering</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:30:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33488-she-closed-her-eyes-and-tried-to-imagine-sex-entering]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She closed her eyes and tried to imagine sex entering the picture. Would sex enter the picture in a silk robe, or would it be as nude as a platter of cold cuts? Would sex enter the picture from the left or the right? Would it ring first, or would it just slide in slyly, too quick and slippery to be denied; or, would sex barge in forcibly, red-faced and green-bereted, pushing all other things aside?" -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13332-here-s-my-theory-about-meetings-and-life-the-three-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:30:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13332-here-s-my-theory-about-meetings-and-life-the-three-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's my theory about meetings and life: the three things you can't fake are erections, competence and creativity." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19287-only-the-disenfranchised-can-party-with-abandon</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:31:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19287-only-the-disenfranchised-can-party-with-abandon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only the disenfranchised can party with abandon." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40842-i-am-aware-that-there-is-a-world-out-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:31:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40842-i-am-aware-that-there-is-a-world-out-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am aware that there is a world out there that functions without regard to me. There are wars and budgets and bombings and vast dimensions of wealth and greed and ambition and corruption. And yet I don't feel a part of that world, and I wouldn't know how to join if I tried." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41120-adventure-without-risk-is-disneyland</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:31:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41120-adventure-without-risk-is-disneyland]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Adventure without risk is Disneyland." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38827-figure-our-what-it-is-you-don-t-do-very-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:32:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38827-figure-our-what-it-is-you-don-t-do-very-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Figure our what it is you don't do very well, and then don't do it.  I'm not beating myself up about doing everything perfectly.  The litmus test I always use for myself is:  &quot;Okay, if you won 20 million tomorrow in the lottery would you still being doing the same thing you are doing now with your life, Dough?  The answer is &quot;yes&quot;.  I'm always very conscious of that." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:33:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:33:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the only people for me are the mad ones, the ones who are mad to live, mad to talk, mad to be saved, desirous of everything at the same time, the ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn like fabulous yellow roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5528-great-things-are-not-accomplished-by-those-who-yield-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:33:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5528-great-things-are-not-accomplished-by-those-who-yield-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Great things are not accomplished by those who yield to trends and fads and popular opinion." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4223-houses-are-full-of-things-that-gather-dust</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:34:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4223-houses-are-full-of-things-that-gather-dust]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Houses are full of things that gather dust" -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33561-something-good-will-come-of-all-things-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:35:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33561-something-good-will-come-of-all-things-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Something good will come of all things yet" -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22305-if-critics-say-your-work-stinks-it-s-because-they-want</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:35:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22305-if-critics-say-your-work-stinks-it-s-because-they-want]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If critics say your work stinks it's because they want it to stink and they can make it stink by scaring you into conformity with their comfortable little standards. Standards so low that they can no longer be considered &quot;dangerous&quot; but set in place in their compartmental understandings." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27557-life-must-be-rich-and-full-of-loving--it-s-no-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:35:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstin add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27557-life-must-be-rich-and-full-of-loving--it-s-no-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life must be rich and full of loving--it's no good otherwise, no good at all, for anyone." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
