<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/218269-laurie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/218269-laurie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 10:24:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83235-i-would-not-choose-to-live-in-any-age-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 10:24:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurie add a quote by Stephen Jay Gould (Dinosaur in a Haystack)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83235-i-would-not-choose-to-live-in-any-age-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would not choose to live in any age but my own; advances in medicine alone, and the consequent survival of children with access to these benefits, should preclude any temptation to trade for the past. But we cannot understand history if we saddle the past with pejorative categories based on our bad habits for dividing continua into compartments of increasing worth towards the present. These errors apply to the vast paleontological history of life, as much as to the temporally trivial chronicle of human beings. I cringe every time I read that this failed business, or that defeated team, has become a dinosaur is succumbing to progress. &lt;i&gt;Dinosaur&lt;/i&gt; should be a term of praise, not opprobrium. Dinosaurs reigned for more than 100 million years and died through no fault of their own; &lt;i&gt;Homo sapiens&lt;/i&gt; is nowhere near a million years old, and has limited prospects, entirely self-imposed, for extended geological longevity. " -- Stephen Jay Gould (Dinosaur in a Haystack)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95383-there-is-a-significant-moral-difference-between-a-person-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 07:15:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurie add a quote by Madeleine Albright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95383-there-is-a-significant-moral-difference-between-a-person-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a significant moral difference between a person who commits a violent crime and a person who tries to cross a border illegally in order to put food on the family table. Such migrants may violate our laws against illicit entry, but if that's all they do they are trespassers, not criminals. They deserve to have their dignity respected." -- Madeleine Albright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273789-part-of-the-blame-lies-with-intellectuals-who-are-unable</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 19:35:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurie add a quote by Michael Perry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273789-part-of-the-blame-lies-with-intellectuals-who-are-unable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Part of the blame lies with intellectuals who are unable or unwilling to convey their ideas in terms that will play down to the cafe. But anyone who sits in that cafe and dismisses complexity by reveling in their own simplicity is no less pretentious." -- Michael Perry]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
