<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/21925-isaac]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/21925-isaac" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 10:09:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164099-in-the-first-place-his-eyes-never-laughed-when-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 10:09:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Lermontov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164099-in-the-first-place-his-eyes-never-laughed-when-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the first place, [his eyes] never laughed when he laughed. Have you ever noticed this peculiarity some people have? It is either the sign of an evil nature or of a profound and lasting sorrow. " -- Lermontov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172554-i-ll-never-forget-you-your-husband-will-beat-you-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 22:43:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Denis Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172554-i-ll-never-forget-you-your-husband-will-beat-you-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'll never forget you. Your husband will beat you with an extension cord and the bus will pull away leaving you standing there in tears, but you were my mother." -- Denis Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18460-there-is-no-salvation-in-becoming-adapted-to-a-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 22:45:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18460-there-is-no-salvation-in-becoming-adapted-to-a-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no salvation in becoming adapted to a world which is crazy" -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2756-you-must-be-life-for-me-to-the-very-end</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 22:47:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2756-you-must-be-life-for-me-to-the-very-end]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must be life for me to the very end,&quot; so he writes. &quot;That is the only way in which to sustain my idea of you. Because you have gotten, as you see, tied up with something so vital to me, I do not think I shall ever shake you off. Nor do I wish to. I want you to live more vitally every day, as I am dead. That is why, when I speak of you to others, I am just a bit ashamed. It's hard to talk of one's self so intimately" -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114802-i-don-t-like-ass-kissers-flag-wavers-or-team-players</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 15:35:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114802-i-don-t-like-ass-kissers-flag-wavers-or-team-players]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't like ass kissers, flag wavers or team players. I like people who buck the system. Individualists. I often warn people: &quot;Somewhere along the way, someone is going to tell you, 'There is no &quot;I&quot; in team.' What you should tell them is, 'Maybe not. But there is an &quot;I&quot; in independence, individuality and integrity.'&quot; Avoid teams at all cost. Keep your circle small. Never join a group that has a name. If they say, &quot;We're the So-and-Sos,&quot; take a walk. And if, somehow, you must join, if it's unavoidable, such as a union or a trade association, go ahead and join. But don't participate; it will be your death. And if they tell you you're not a team player, congratulate them on being observant." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480870-why-did-the-old-persians-hold-the-sea-holy-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 22:25:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480870-why-did-the-old-persians-hold-the-sea-holy-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why did the old Persians hold the sea holy? Why did the Greeks give it a separate deity, and own brother Jove? Surely all this is not without meaning. And still deeper the meaning of that story of Narcissus, who because he could not grasp the tormenting mild image he saw in the fountain, plunged into it and was drowned. But that same image, we ourselves see in all rivers and oceans. It is the image of the ungraspable phantom of life; and this is the key to it all." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526-the-man-who-writes-about-himself-and-his-own-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2012 15:41:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526-the-man-who-writes-about-himself-and-his-own-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who writes about himself and his own time is the only man who writes about all people and all time." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18463-whoever-fights-monsters-should-see-to-it-that-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 21:45:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18463-whoever-fights-monsters-should-see-to-it-that-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whoever fights monsters should see to it that in the process he does not become a monster. And if you gaze long enough into an abyss, the abyss will gaze back into you." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102833-then-he-made-one-last-effort-to-search-in-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2012 18:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Gabriel Garcia Marquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102833-then-he-made-one-last-effort-to-search-in-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then he made one last effort to search in his heart for the place where his affection had rotted away, and he could not find it." -- Gabriel Garcia Marquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311790-i-don-t-believe-one-reads-to-escape-reality-a-person</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 10:01:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Lawrence Durrell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311790-i-don-t-believe-one-reads-to-escape-reality-a-person]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don’t believe one reads to escape reality. A person reads to confirm a reality he knows is there, but which he has not experienced." -- Lawrence Durrell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/304300-e-very-man-hath-liberty-to-write-but-few-ability-heretofore</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2012 08:12:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Robert Burton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/304300-e-very-man-hath-liberty-to-write-but-few-ability-heretofore]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[E]very man hath liberty to write, but few ability. Heretofore learning was graced by judicious scholars, but now noble sciences are vilified by base and illiterate scribblers, that either write for vain-glory, need, to get money, or as Parasites to flatter and collogue with some great men, they put out trifles, rubbish and trash. Among so many thousand Authors you shall scarce find one by reading of whom you shall be any whit better, but rather much worse; by which he is rather infected than any way perfected…

What a catalogue of new books this year, all his age (I say) have our Frankfurt Marts, our domestic Marts, brought out. Twice a year we stretch out wits out and set them to sale; after great toil we attain nothing…What a glut of books! Who can read them? As already, we shall have a vast Chaos and confusion of Books, we are oppressed with them, our eyes ache with reading, our fingers with turning. For my part I am one of the number—one of the many—I do not deny it..." -- Robert Burton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152427-the-traveling-salesmen-fed-me-pills-that-made-the-lining</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 14:34:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Denis Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152427-the-traveling-salesmen-fed-me-pills-that-made-the-lining]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The traveling salesmen fed me pills that made the lining of my veins feel scraped out, my jaw ached... I knew every raindrop by its name, I sensed everything before it happened.  Like I knew a certain oldsmobile would stop even before it slowed, and by the sweet voices of the family inside, I knew we'd have an accident in the rain.  I didn't care.  They said they'd take me all the way." -- Denis Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109397-all-these-weirdos-and-me-getting-a-little-better-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 14:34:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Denis Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109397-all-these-weirdos-and-me-getting-a-little-better-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All these weirdos, and me getting a little better every day right in the midst of them. I had never known, never even imagined for a heartbeat, that there might be a place for people like us." -- Denis Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169380-will-you-believe-me-when-i-tell-you-there-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 14:34:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Denis Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169380-will-you-believe-me-when-i-tell-you-there-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Will you believe me when I tell you there was kindness in his heart? His left hand didn't know what his right hand was doing. It was only that certain important connections had been burned through. If I opened up your head and ran a hot soldering iron around in your brain, I might turn you into someone like that." -- Denis Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303159-and-therefore-i-looked-down-into-the-great-pity-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 14:34:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Denis Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303159-and-therefore-i-looked-down-into-the-great-pity-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And therefore I looked down into the great pity of a person’s life on this earth. I don’t mean that we all end up dead, that’s not the great pity. I mean that he couldn’t tell me what he was dreaming, and I couldn’t tell him what was real." -- Denis Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3149-if-music-be-the-food-of-love-play-on-give</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 09:05:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3149-if-music-be-the-food-of-love-play-on-give]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If music be the food of love, play on,
Give me excess of it; that surfeiting,
The appetite may sicken, and so die." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427451-when-i-look-down-into-this-fucked-out-cunt-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 20:35:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427451-when-i-look-down-into-this-fucked-out-cunt-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I look down into this fucked-out cunt of a whore I feel the whole world beneath me, a world tottering and crumbling, a world used up and polished like a leper's skull. If there were a man who dared to say all that he thought of this world there would not be left him a square foot of ground to stand on. When a man appears the world bears down on him and breaks his back. There are always too many rotten pillars left standing, too much festering humanity for man to bloom. The superstructure is a lie and the foundation is a huge quaking fear. If at intervals of centuries there does appear a man with a desperate, hungry look in his eye, a man that would turn the world upside down in order to create a new race, the love that he brings to the world is turned to bile and he becomes a scourge. If now and then we encounter pages that explode, pages that wound and sear, that wring groans and tears and curses, know that they come from a man with his back up, a man whose only defenses left are his words and his words are always stronger than the lying, crushing weight of the world, stronger than all the racks and wheels which the cowardly invent to crush out the miracle of personality. If any man ever dared to translate all that is in his heart, to put down what is really his experience, what is truly his truth, I think then the world would go to smash, that it would be blown to smithereens and no god, no accident, no will could ever again assemble the pieces, the atoms, the indestructible elements that have gone to make up the world." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 18:53:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love never dies a natural death. It dies because we don't know how to replenish its source. It dies of blindness and errors and betrayals. It dies of illness and wounds; it dies of weariness, of witherings, of tarnishings." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74122-sublime-is-something-you-choke-on-after-a-shot-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2014 06:08:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74122-sublime-is-something-you-choke-on-after-a-shot-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sublime is something you choke on after a shot of tequila." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/400040-if-voting-made-any-difference-they-wouldn-t-let-us-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 20:45:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/400040-if-voting-made-any-difference-they-wouldn-t-let-us-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If voting made any difference they wouldn't let us do it." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
