<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/219241-erin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/219241-erin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 21:30:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/663213-his-name-was-paul-eluard-and-he-said-this-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 21:30:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Paul Murray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/663213-his-name-was-paul-eluard-and-he-said-this-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His name was Paul Eluard, and he said this thing once: There is another world, but it is in this one.

Ruprecht looked baffled.

It's about how -- she could feel herself going red, she squeezed her eyes shut, trying to remember what Mr Scott had told them -- like, how people are always going somewhere? Like everybody's always trying to be not where they are? Like they want to be in Stanford, or in Tuscany, or in Heaven, or in a bigger house on a fancier street? Or they want to be different, like thinner or smarter or richer or with cooler friends (or dead, she did not say). They're so busy trying to find their way somewhere else they don't see the world they're actually in. So this guy's saying, instead of searching for ways out of our lives, what we should be searching for are ways in. Because if you really look at the world, it's like ... it's like ...

It's like, you know, inside every stove there's a fire. Well, inside every  grass blade there's a grass blade, that's just like burning up with being a grass blade. And inside every tree, there's a tree, and inside every person there's a person, and inside this world that seems so boring and ordinary, if you look hard enough, there's a totally amazing magical beautiful world. And anything you would want to know, or anything you would want to happen, all the answers are right there where you are right now. In your life. She opened her eyes. Do you know what I mean?" -- Paul Murray]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
