<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/219696-anne-martens]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/219696-anne-martens" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 20:32:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94422-of-course-we-would-all-like-to-believe-in-something</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 20:32:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94422-of-course-we-would-all-like-to-believe-in-something]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of course we would all like to &quot;believe&quot; in something, like to assuage our private guilts in public causes, like to lose our tiresome selves; like, perhaps, to transform the white flag of defeat at home into the brave white banner of battle away from home. And of course it is all right to do that; that is how, immemorially, thing have gotten done. But I think it is all right only so long as we do not delude ourselves about what we are doing, and why. It is all right only so long as we remember that all the ad hoc committees, all the picket lines, all the brave signatures in The New York Times, all the tools of agitprop straight across the spectrum, do not confer upon anyone any ipso facto virtue. It is all right only so long as we recognize that the end may or may not be expedient, may or may not be a good idea, but in any case has nothing to do with &quot;morality.&quot; Because when we start deceiving ourselves into thinking not that we want something or need something, not that it is a pragmatic necessity for us to have it, but that it is a moral imperative that we have it, then is when we join the fashionable madmen, and then is when the thin whine of hysteria is heard in the land, and then is when we are in bad trouble. And I suspect we are already there." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78513-if-hatred-strikes-you-if-you-get-accused-thrown-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 19:09:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78513-if-hatred-strikes-you-if-you-get-accused-thrown-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If hatred strikes you, if you get accused, thrown to the lions, you can expect one of two reactions from people who know you: some of them will join in the kill, the others will discreetly pretend to know nothing, hear nothing, so you can go right on seeing them and talking to them.  That second category, discreet and tactful, those are your friends. 'Friends' in the modern sense of the term. Listen, Jean-Marc, I've known that forever." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/552239-darling-my-darling-don-t-think-that-i-don-t-love-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 19:07:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/552239-darling-my-darling-don-t-think-that-i-don-t-love-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Darling, my darling, don't think that I don't love you or that I didn't love you, but it's precisely because I love you that I couldn't have become what I am today if you were still here.  It's impossible to have a child and despise the world as it is, because that's the world we've put the child into.  The child makes us care about the world, think about it's future, willingly join in its racket and its turmoils, take its incurable stupidity seriously." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10839-music-has-always-been-a-matter-of-energy-to-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 20:37:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10839-music-has-always-been-a-matter-of-energy-to-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Music has always been a matter of Energy to me, a question of Fuel.  Sentimental people call it Inspiration, but what they really mean is Fuel.  I have always needed Fuel. I am a serious consumer.  On some nights I still believe that a car with the gas needle on empty can run about fifty more miles if you have the right music very loud on the radio." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47188-life-should-not-be-a-journey-to-the-grave-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 20:38:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47188-life-should-not-be-a-journey-to-the-grave-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life should not be a journey to the grave with the intention of arriving safely in a pretty and well preserved body, but rather to skid in broadside in a cloud of smoke, thoroughly used up, totally worn out, and loudly proclaiming &quot;Wow! What a Ride!" -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253047-come-sleep-with-me-we-won-t-make-love-love-will-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 20:42:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Julio Cortázar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253047-come-sleep-with-me-we-won-t-make-love-love-will-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Come sleep with me: We won't make Love,Love will make us." -- Julio Cortázar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84169-anxiety-is-love-s-greatest-killer-it-makes-others-feel-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 20:41:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84169-anxiety-is-love-s-greatest-killer-it-makes-others-feel-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anxiety is love's greatest killer. It makes others feel as you might when a drowning man holds on to you. You want to save him, but you know he will strangle you with his panic." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
