<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/220046-anne-holcomb]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/220046-anne-holcomb" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 06:04:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158499-without-turning-the-pharmacist-answered-that-he-liked-books-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 06:04:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Roberto Bolano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158499-without-turning-the-pharmacist-answered-that-he-liked-books-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without turning, the pharmacist answered that he liked books like The Metamorphosis, Bartleby, A Simple Heart, A Christmas Carol.  And then he said that he was reading Capote's Breakfast at Tiffany's. Leaving aside the fact that A Simple Heart and A Christmas Carol were stories, not books, there was something revelatory about the taste of this bookish young pharmacist, who ... clearly and inarguably preferred minor works to major ones.  He chose The Metamorphosis over The Trial, he chose Bartleby over Moby Dick, he chose A Simple Heart over Bouvard and Pecouchet, and A Christmas Carol over A Tale of Two Cities or The Pickwick Papers. What a sad paradox, thought Amalfitano.  Now even bookish pharmacists are afraid to take on the great, imperfect, torrential works, books that blaze a path into the unknown.  They choose the perfect exercises of the great masters.  Or what amounts to the same thing: they want to watch the great masters spar, but they have no interest in real combat, when the great masters struggle against that something, that something that terrifies us all, that something that cows us and spurs us on, amid blood and mortal wounds and stench." -- Roberto Bolano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121811-most-true-is-it-that-beauty-is-in-the-eye</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 09:10:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121811-most-true-is-it-that-beauty-is-in-the-eye]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most true is it that 'beauty is in the eye of the gazer.' My master’s colourless, olive face, square, massive brow, broad and jetty eyebrows, deep eyes, strong features, firm, grim mouth, — all energy, decision, will, — were not beautiful, according to rule; but they were more than beautiful to me; they were full of an interest, an influence that quite mastered me, — that took my feelings from my own power and fettered them in his. I had not intended to love him; the reader knows I had wrought hard to extirpate from my soul the germs of love there detected; and now, at the first renewed view of him, they spontaneously arrived, green and strong! He made me love him without looking at me." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21101-do-you-think-i-am-an-automaton-a-machine</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 09:10:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21101-do-you-think-i-am-an-automaton-a-machine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you think I am an automaton? — a machine without feelings? and can bear to have my morsel of bread snatched from my lips, and my drop of living water dashed from my cup? Do you think, because I am poor, obscure, plain, and little, I am soulless and heartless? You think wrong! — I have as much soul as you — and full as much heart! And if God had gifted me with some beauty and much wealth, I should have made it as hard for you to leave me, as it is now for me to leave you. I am not talking to you now through the medium of custom, conventionalities, nor even of mortal flesh: it is my spirit that addresses your spirit; just as if both had passed through the grave, and we stood at God's feet, equal — as we are!" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74559-we-still-think-of-a-powerful-man-as-a-born</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 09:11:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74559-we-still-think-of-a-powerful-man-as-a-born]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We still think of a powerful man as a born leader and a powerful woman as an anomaly." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173710-people-cry-at-weddings-for-the-same-reason-they-cry</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 09:14:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173710-people-cry-at-weddings-for-the-same-reason-they-cry]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People cry at weddings for the same reason they cry at happy endings: because they so desperately want to believe in something they know is not credible." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1895-you-can-never-be-overdressed-or-overeducated</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 09:18:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1895-you-can-never-be-overdressed-or-overeducated]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can never be overdressed or overeducated." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31784-the-public-have-an-insatiable-curiosity-to-know-everything-except</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 09:20:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31784-the-public-have-an-insatiable-curiosity-to-know-everything-except]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The public have an insatiable curiosity to know everything, except what is worth knowing." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10616-i-am-too-fond-of-reading-books-to-care-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 09:20:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10616-i-am-too-fond-of-reading-books-to-care-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am too fond of reading books to care to write them." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174741-love-is-as-strong-as-death-as-hard-as-hell</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 17:26:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Meister Eckhart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174741-love-is-as-strong-as-death-as-hard-as-hell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is as strong as death, as hard as Hell.  Death separates the soul from the body, but love separates all things from the soul." -- Meister Eckhart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467465-for-a-moment-everything-was-clear-and-when-that-happens</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 17:41:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467465-for-a-moment-everything-was-clear-and-when-that-happens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For a moment everything was clear, and when that happens you see that the world is barely there at all. Don't we all secretly know this? It's a perfectly balanced mechanism of shouts and echoes pretending to be wheels and cogs, a dreamclock chiming beneath a mystery-glass we call life. Behind it? Below it and around it? Chaos, storms. Men with hammers, men with knives, men with guns. Women who twist what they cannot dominate and belittle what they cannot understand. A universe of horror and loss surrounding a single lighted stage where mortals dance in defiance of the dark." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/288821-i-am-two-women-one-wants-to-have-all-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2012 13:32:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/288821-i-am-two-women-one-wants-to-have-all-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am two women: one wants to have all the joy, passion and adventure that life can give me. The other wants to be a slave to routine, to family life, to the things that can be planned and achieved. I'm a housewife and a prostitute, both of us living in the same body and doing battle with each other." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/906743-one-needs-no-strange-spiritual-faith-to-worship-the-earth</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 10:33:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by John Cowper Powys]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/906743-one-needs-no-strange-spiritual-faith-to-worship-the-earth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One needs no strange spiritual faith to worship the earth." -- John Cowper Powys]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
