<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/220336-anna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/220336-anna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 07:36:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739-when-i-despair-i-remember-that-all-through-history-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 07:36:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739-when-i-despair-i-remember-that-all-through-history-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I despair, I remember that all through history the way of truth and love have always won. There have been tyrants and murderers, and for a time, they can seem invincible, but in the end, they always fall. Think of it--always." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3420-even-now-all-possible-feelings-do-not-yet-exist-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 07:38:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3420-even-now-all-possible-feelings-do-not-yet-exist-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even now, all possible feelings do not yet exist, there are still those that lie beyond our capacity and our imagination.  From time to time, when a piece of music no one has ever written or a painting no one has ever painted, or something else impossible to predict, fathom or yet describe takes place, a new feeling enters the world.  And then, for the millionth time in the history of feeling, the heart surges and absorbs the impact." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39303-question-what-is-the-opposite-of-faith-not-disbelief-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 07:44:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39303-question-what-is-the-opposite-of-faith-not-disbelief-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Question: What is the opposite of faith? 

Not disbelief. Too final, certain, closed. Itself is a kind of belief. 

Doubt. 

The human condition, but what of the angelic? Halfway between Allahgod and homosap, did they ever doubt? They did: challenging God's will one day they hid muttering beneath the Throne, daring to ask forbidden things: antiquestions. Is it right that. Could it not be argued. Freedom, the old antiquest. He calmed them down, naturally, employing management skills a la god. Flattered them: you will be the instruments of my will on earth, the salvationdamnation of man, all the usual etcetera. And hey presto, the end of protest, on with the haloes, back to work. Angels are easily pacified; turn them into instruments and they'll play your harpy tune. Human beings are tougher nuts, can doubt anything, even the evidence of their own eyes. Of behing-their-own-eyes. Of what, as they sink heavy-lidded, transpires behind closed peepers ... angels, they don't have much in the way of a will. To will is to disagree; not to submit; to dissent." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
