<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/22041-jason-w-dean]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/22041-jason-w-dean" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 10:51:18 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476035-there-is-nothing-naud-wrote-that-renders-a-library-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 10:51:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Alberto Manguel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476035-there-is-nothing-naud-wrote-that-renders-a-library-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing,” Naudé wrote, “that renders a Library more recommendable, than when every man finds in it that which he is looking for and cannot find anywhere else; therefore the perfect motto is, that there exists no book, however bad or badly reviewed, that may not be sought after in some future time by a certain reader.” These remarks demand from us an impossibility, since every library is, by needs, an incomplete creation, a work-in-progress, and every empty shelf announces the books to come." -- Alberto Manguel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/910659-politics-is-a-story-about-the-relationship-between-the-past</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 18:35:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Jill Lepore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/910659-politics-is-a-story-about-the-relationship-between-the-past]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Politics is a story about the relationship between the past and the future; history is a story about the relationship between the past and the present. It’s what history and politics share - a vantage on the past - that makes writing the history of politics fraught. And it’s what they don’t share that makes the study of history vital. Politics is accountable to opinion; history is accountable to evidence." -- Jill Lepore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35578-historians-are-left-forever-chasing-shadows-painfully-aware-of-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 09:48:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Simon Schama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35578-historians-are-left-forever-chasing-shadows-painfully-aware-of-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Historians are left forever chasing shadows, painfully aware of their inability ever to reconstruct a dead world in its completeness however thorough or revealing their documentation. We are doomed to be forever hailing someone who has just gone around the corner and out of earshot." -- Simon Schama]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476036-it-is-likely-that-libraries-will-carry-on-and-survive</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 10:52:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Alberto Manguel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476036-it-is-likely-that-libraries-will-carry-on-and-survive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is likely that libraries will carry on and survive, as long as we persist in lending words to the world that surrounds us, and storing them for future readers." -- Alberto Manguel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476038-a-book-is-tremendously-important-nobody-ever-paid-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 10:54:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Louis I. Kahn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476038-a-book-is-tremendously-important-nobody-ever-paid-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book is tremendously important. Nobody ever paid for the price of a book, they only paid for the printing" -- Louis I. Kahn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770676-cataloguing-is-an-ancient-profession-there-are-examples-of-such</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 14:00:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Alberto Manguel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770676-cataloguing-is-an-ancient-profession-there-are-examples-of-such]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cataloguing is an ancient profession; there are examples of such “ordainers of the universe” (as they were called by the Sumerians) among the oldest vestiges of libraries." -- Alberto Manguel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/910662-history-is-the-art-of-making-an-argument-about-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 18:36:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Jill Lepore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/910662-history-is-the-art-of-making-an-argument-about-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["History is the art of making an argument about the past by telling a story accountable to evidence. In the writing of history, a story without an argument fades into antiquarianism; an argument without a story risks pedantry. Writing history requires empathy, inquiry, and debate. It requires forswearing condescension, cant, and nostalgia. The past isn’t quaint. Much of it, in fact, is bleak." -- Jill Lepore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476039-the-digital-communications-technology-that-was-once-imagined-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 10:55:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Simon Schama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476039-the-digital-communications-technology-that-was-once-imagined-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The digital communications technology that was once imagined as a universe of transparent and perpetual illumination, in which cancerous falsehoods would perish beneath a saturation bombardment of irradiating data, has instead generated a much murkier and verification-free habitat where a google-generated search will deliver an electronic page on which links to lies and lunacy appear in identical format as those to truths and sanity. But why should we ever have assumed that technology and reason would be mutually self-reinforcing?  The quickest visit to say, a site called Stormfront will persuade you that the demonic is in fact the best customer of the electronic." -- Simon Schama]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476037-in-the-ideal-public-library-we-are-all-readers-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 10:54:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Matthew Battles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476037-in-the-ideal-public-library-we-are-all-readers-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the ideal public library, we are all readers of the “middling sort.” Reading whatever we will, we fulfill a public function, preserving the sacrosanct space of inner thought that is our birthright. Assaults on that birthright in the forms of legislation, surveillance, and censorship ultimately are precisely as dangerous as our acquiescence in them." -- Matthew Battles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476040-over-the-years-my-experience-my-tastes-my-prejudices-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 10:59:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Alberto Manguel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476040-over-the-years-my-experience-my-tastes-my-prejudices-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Over the years, my experience, my tastes, my prejudices have changed: as the days go by, my memory keeps reshelving, cataloguing, discarding the volumes in my library, my words and my world - except for a few constant landmarks - are never one and the same. Heraclitus’s bon mot about time applies equally well to my reading: “You never dip into the same book twice." -- Alberto Manguel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67605-entering-a-library-i-am-always-stuck-by-the-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Alberto Manguel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67605-entering-a-library-i-am-always-stuck-by-the-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Entering a library, I am always stuck by the way in which a certain vision of the world is imposed upon the reader through its categories and its order." -- Alberto Manguel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/495151-museum-architectural-search-committees-have-invariably-included-the-kimbell-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 20:02:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Martin Filler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/495151-museum-architectural-search-committees-have-invariably-included-the-kimbell-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Museum architectural search committees have invariably included the Kimbell in their international scouting tours of exemplary art galleries (a practice pioneered by Velma Kimbell, the founder’s widow, in 1964). Those groups no doubt respond to the Kimbell with suitable reverence, but given the buildings they later commissioned, many post-Bilbao museum patrons obviously wanted something quite different. The disparity between Kahn’s museums and recent examples of that genre parallels the discrepancy he saw between postwar Modernism and ancient Classicism: “Our stuff looks tinny compared to it.” At a time when commercial values are systematically corrupting the museum - one of civilized society’s most elevating experiences - the example of Kahn, among the most courageous and successful architectural reformers of all time, seems more relevant and cautionary than ever." -- Martin Filler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/517530-we-all-behave-like-maxwell-s-demon-organisms-organize-in-everyday</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 10:05:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by James Gleick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/517530-we-all-behave-like-maxwell-s-demon-organisms-organize-in-everyday]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all behave like Maxwell’s demon. Organisms organize. In everyday experience lies the reason sober physicists across two centuries kept this cartoon fantasy alive. We sort the mail, build sand castles, solve jigsaw puzzles, separate wheat from chaff, rearrange chess pieces, collect stamps, alphabetize books, create symmetry, compose sonnets and sonatas, and put our rooms in order, and all this we do requires no great energy, as long as we can apply intelligence. We propagate structure (not just we humans but we who are alive). We disturb the tendency toward equilibrium. It would be absurd to attempt a thermodynamic accounting for such processes, but it is not absurd to say we are reducing entropy, piece by piece. Bit by bit. The original demon, discerning one molecules at a time, distinguishing fast from slow, and operating his little gateway, is sometimes described as “superintelligent,” but compared to a real organism it is an idiot savant. Not only do living things lessen the disorder in their environments; they are in themselves, their skeletons and their flesh, vesicles and membranes, shells and carapaces, leaves and blossoms, circulatory systems and metabolic pathways - miracles of pattern and structure. It sometimes seems as if curbing entropy is our quixotic purpose in the universe." -- James Gleick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67641-we-can-imagine-the-books-we-d-like-to-read-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 08:26:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Alberto Manguel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67641-we-can-imagine-the-books-we-d-like-to-read-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can imagine the books we'd like to read, even if they have not yet been written, and we can imagine libraries full of books we would like to possess, even if they are well beyond our reach, because we enjoy dreaming up a library that reflects every one of our interests and every one of our foibles--a library that, in its variety and complexity, fully reflects the reader we are." -- Alberto Manguel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274320-the-existence-of-any-library-even-mine-allows-readers-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 09:24:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Alberto Manguel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274320-the-existence-of-any-library-even-mine-allows-readers-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The existence of any library, even mine, allows readers a sense of what their craft is truly about, a craft that struggles against the stringencies of time by bringing fragments of the past into their present. It grants them a glimpse, however secret or distant, into the minds of other human beings, and allows them a certain knowledge of their own condition through the stories stored here for their perusal. Above all, it tells readers that their craft consist of the power to remember, actively, through the prompt of the page, selected moments of the human experience. This was the great practice established by the Library of Alexandria." -- Alberto Manguel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770678-the-categories-that-a-reader-brings-to-a-reading-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 14:01:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Alberto Manguel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770678-the-categories-that-a-reader-brings-to-a-reading-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The categories that a reader brings to a reading, and the categories in which that reading itself is placed - the learned social and political categories, and the physical categories into which a library is divided - constantly modify one another in ways that appear, over the years, more or less arbitrary or more or less imaginative. Every library is a library of preferences, and every chosen category implies an exclusion." -- Alberto Manguel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770681-the-bibliographer-in-the-digital-age-returns-to-the-revelatory</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 14:02:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Matthew Battles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770681-the-bibliographer-in-the-digital-age-returns-to-the-revelatory]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The bibliographer in the digital age returns to the revelatory practice of her medieval forebears. Librarians, like those scribes of the Middle Ages, do not merely keep and classify texts; they create them, in the form of online finding aids, CD-ROM concordances, and other electronic texts, not to mention paper study guides and published bibliographies." -- Matthew Battles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770683-what-we-face-is-not-a-loss-of-books-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 14:04:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Matthew Battles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770683-what-we-face-is-not-a-loss-of-books-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What we face is not a loss of books but the loss of a world. As in Alexandria after Aristotle’s time, or the universities and monasteries of the early Renaissance, or the cluttered-up research libraries of the nineteenth century, the Word shifts again in its modes, tending more and more to dwell in pixels and bits instead of paper and ink. It seems to disappear thereby, as it must have for the ancient Peripatetics, who considered writing a spectral shibboleth of living speech; or the princely collectors of manuscripts in the Renaissance, who saw the newly recovered world of antiquity endangered by the brute force of the press; or the lovers of handmade books in the early nineteenth century, to whom the penny dreadful represented the final dilution of the power of literature. And yet, the very fact that the library has endured these cycles seems to offer hope. In its custody of books and the words they contain, the library has confronted and tamed technology, the forces of change, and the power of princes time and again." -- Matthew Battles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770688-today-the-sight-that-discourages-book-people-most-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 14:07:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Larry McMurtry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770688-today-the-sight-that-discourages-book-people-most-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today the sight that discourages book people most is to walk into a public library and see computers where books used to be. In many cases not even the librarians want books to be there. What consumers want now is information, and information increasingly comes from computers. 
That is a preference I can’t grasp, much less share, though I’m well aware that computers have many valid uses. They save lives, and they make research in most cases a thing that’s almost instantaneous. 
They do many good things.
But they don’t really do what books do, and why should they usurp the chief function of a public library, which is to provide readers access to books? Books can accommodate the proximity of computers but it doesn’t seem to work the other way around. Computers now literally drive out books from the place that should, by definition, be books’ own home: the library." -- Larry McMurtry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/796753-heade-s-calm-is-unsteady-storm-stirred-we-respond-in-our-era</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 19:30:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by John Updike]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/796753-heade-s-calm-is-unsteady-storm-stirred-we-respond-in-our-era]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Heade’s calm is unsteady, storm-stirred; we respond in our era to its hint of the nervous and the fearful. His weather is interior weather, in a sense, and he perhaps was, if far from the first to portray a modern mood, an ambivalent mood tinged with dread and yet imbued with a certain lightness.The mood could even be said to be religious: not an aggressive preachment of God’s grandeur but a kind of Zen poise and acceptance, represented by the small sedentary or plodding foreground figures that appear uncannily at peace as the clouds blacken and the lightning flashes." -- John Updike]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/796754-the-river-tonally-does-not-recede-presenting-the-same-lifeless</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 19:31:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by John Updike]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/796754-the-river-tonally-does-not-recede-presenting-the-same-lifeless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The river, tonally, does not recede, presenting the same lifeless grey near and far, a depthless plane upon which Schmitt’s dragging oars inscribe parallel lines and Eakins’ oars, rising and falling, leave methodically spaced patches of disturbed water. The canvas is haunting - en evocation of the democracy’s idyllic, isolating spaciousness, present even in the midst of a great Eastern city." -- John Updike]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/796755-nevertheless-we-react-to-one-a-bit-differently-than-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 19:32:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by John Updike]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/796755-nevertheless-we-react-to-one-a-bit-differently-than-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nevertheless, we react to one a bit differently than we do to Rothko’s hovering panels or Barnett Newman’s stripes, though Whistler does approach their extremity of abstraction; part of our pleasure lies in recognizing bridges and buildings in the mist, and in sensing the damp riverine silence, the glimmering metropolitan presence. … The painting - a single blurred stripe of urban shore - is additionally daring in that the sky and sea are no shade of blue, but, instead, an improbable, pervasive cobalt green. Human vision is here taken to its limits, and modern painting, as a set of sensations realized in paint, is achieved." -- John Updike]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/910664-still-it-strikes-me-that-taken-together-they-do-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 18:36:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Jill Lepore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/910664-still-it-strikes-me-that-taken-together-they-do-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Still, it strikes me that, taken together, they do make an argument, and it is this: the rise of American democracy is bound up with the history of reading and writing, which is one of the reasons the study of American history is inseparable from the study of American literature. In the early United States, literacy rates rose and the price of books and magazines and newspapers fell during the same decades that suffrage was being extended. With everything from constitutions and ballots to almanacs and novels, American wrote and read their way into a political culture inked and stamped and pressed in print." -- Jill Lepore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1021866-consider-this-oddly-neglected-fact-the-west-was-acquired-conquested</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 12:53:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Elliott West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1021866-consider-this-oddly-neglected-fact-the-west-was-acquired-conquested]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Consider this oddly neglected fact: the West was acquired, conquested, and largely consolidated into the nation coincident with the greatest breakthrough in the history of human communication. The breakthrough was the telegraph. The great advances that followed it, the telephone, radio, television, and the Internet, were all elaborations on its essential contribution. The telegraph separated the person from the message. Before it, with a few exceptions such as a sephamore and carrier pigeons, information moved only as fast as people did. By the nineteenth century, people were certainly moving a lot faster, and indeed a second revolution, that of transportation, was equally critical in creating the West, but before the telegraph a message still had to move with a person, either as a document or in somebody’s head. The telegraph liberated information. Now it could travel virtually at the speed of light. The railroad carried people and things, including letters, ten to fifteen times faster than the next most rapid form of movement. The telegraph accelerated communication more than forty million times. A single dot of Morse code traveled from Kansas City to Denver faster than the click it produced moved from the receiver to the telegrapher’s eardrum." -- Elliott West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1032740-a-frustrated-friend-once-told-me-that-i-couldn-t-comment</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2014 11:40:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Elliott West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1032740-a-frustrated-friend-once-told-me-that-i-couldn-t-comment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A frustrated friend once told me that I couldn’t comment on a new traffic light at Maple and Arkansas without starting with the Magna Carta. Explanations do indeed seem to seep backward in all directions. The hard part is keeping them under control and giving them some focus." -- Elliott West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1053269-in-wright-morris-s-novel-plains-song-the-narrator-asks-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 19:27:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Elliott West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1053269-in-wright-morris-s-novel-plains-song-the-narrator-asks-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In Wright Morris's novel Plains Song, the narrator asks, &quot;Is the past a story we are persuaded to believe, in the teeth of the life we endure in the present?&quot; The question is always open. How we treat our world and each other grows from our vision of how we have come to where we are. Ultimately, of course, the issue is not survival but decency and common sense. Everything passes, the psalmist reminds us. No one escapes. The best we can hope is to learn a little from the speaking dead, to find in our deep past some help in acting wisely in the teeth of life." -- Elliott West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256725-history-is-hereditary-only-in-this-way-we-all-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 12:31:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason W. add a quote by Jill Lepore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256725-history-is-hereditary-only-in-this-way-we-all-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["History is hereditary only in this way: we, all of us, inherit everything, and then we choose what to cherish, what to disavow, and what do do next, which is why it's worth trying to know where things come from." -- Jill Lepore]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
