<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/220570-kelly]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/220570-kelly" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 13:46:40 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109062-think-outside-the-box-collapse-the-box-and-take-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 13:46:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Banksy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109062-think-outside-the-box-collapse-the-box-and-take-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Think outside the box, collapse the box, and take a fucking sharp knife to it." -- Banksy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217457-the-greatest-crimes-in-the-world-are-not-committed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 13:47:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Banksy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217457-the-greatest-crimes-in-the-world-are-not-committed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greatest crimes in the world are not committed by people breaking the rules but by people following the rules. It's people who follow orders that drop bombs and massacre villages." -- Banksy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51738-a-lot-of-mothers-will-do-anything-for-their-children</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 13:47:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Banksy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51738-a-lot-of-mothers-will-do-anything-for-their-children]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A lot of mothers will do anything for their children, except let them be themselves." -- Banksy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51722-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-king-who-ruled</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 13:48:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Banksy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51722-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-king-who-ruled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time, there was a king who ruled a great and glorious nation. Favourite amongst his subjects was the court painter of whom he was very proud. Everybody agreed this wizzened old man pianted the greatest pictures in the whole kingdom and the king would spend hours each day gazing at them in wonder. However, one day a dirty and dishevelled stranger presented himself at the court claiming that in fact he was the greatest painter in the land. The indignant king decreed a competition would be held between the two artists, confident it would teach the vagabond an embarrassing lesson. Within a month they were both to produce a masterpiece that would out do the other. After thirty days of working feverishly day and night, both artists were ready. They placed their paintings, each hidden by a cloth, on easels in the great hall of the castle. As a large crowd gathered, the king ordered the cloth be pulled first from the court artist’s easel. Everyone gasped as before them was revealed a wonderful oil painting of a table set with a feast. At its centre was an ornate bowl full of exotic fruits glistening moistly in the dawn light. As the crowd gazed admiringly, a sparrow perched high up on the rafters of the hall swooped down and hungrily tried to snatch one of the grapes from the painted bowl only to hit the canvas and fall down dead with shock at the feet of the king. ’Aha!’ exclaimed the king. ’My artist has produced a painting so wonderful it has fooled nature herself, surely you must agree that he is the greatest painter who ever lived!’ But the vagabond said nothing and stared solemnly at his feet. ’Now, pull the blanket from your painting and let us see what you have for us,’ cried the king. But the tramp remained motionless and said nothing. Growing impatient, the king stepped forward and reached out to grab the blanket only to freeze in horror at the last moment. ’You see,’ said the tramp quietly, ’there is no blanket covering the painting. This is actually just a painting of a cloth covering a painting. And whereas your famous artist is content to fool nature, I’ve made the king of the whole country look like a clueless little twat." -- Banksy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48819-people-who-get-up-early-in-the-morning-cause-war</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 13:49:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Banksy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48819-people-who-get-up-early-in-the-morning-cause-war]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People who get up early in the morning cause war, death and famine." -- Banksy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163503-the-people-who-run-our-cities-dont-understand-graffiti-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 13:50:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Banksy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163503-the-people-who-run-our-cities-dont-understand-graffiti-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the people who run our cities dont understand graffiti because they think nothing has the right to exist unless it makes a profit...
the people who truly deface our neighborhoods are the companies that scrawl giant slogans across buildings and buses trying to make us feel inadequate unless we buy their stuff....
any advertisement in public space that gives you no choice whether you see it or not is yours, it belongs to you ,, its yours to take, rearrange and re use.Asking for permission is like asking to keep a rock someone just threw at your head.." -- Banksy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48818-only-when-the-last-tree-has-been-cut-down-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 13:50:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Banksy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48818-only-when-the-last-tree-has-been-cut-down-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only when the last tree has been cut down and the last river has dried up will man realise that reciting red indian proverbs makes you sound like a fucking muppet." -- Banksy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
