<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/221089-robin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/221089-robin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 18:50:41 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21396-if-you-can-see-your-path-laid-out-in-front</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 18:50:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robin add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21396-if-you-can-see-your-path-laid-out-in-front]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can see your path laid out in front of you step by step, you know it's not your path.  Your own path you make with every step you take.  That's why it's your path." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163742-be-ruthless-about-protecting-writing-days-i-e-do-not-cave</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 09:25:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robin add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163742-be-ruthless-about-protecting-writing-days-i-e-do-not-cave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be ruthless about protecting writing days, i.e., do not cave in to endless requests to have &quot;essential&quot; and &quot;long overdue&quot; meetings on those days.  The funny thing is that, although writing has been my actual job for several years now, I still seem to have to fight for time in which to do it.  Some people do not seem to grasp that I still have to sit down in peace and write the books, apparently believing that they pop up like mushrooms without my connivance.  I must therefore guard the time allotted to writing as a Hungarian Horntail guards its firstborn egg." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163748-be-so-strong-that-nothing-can-disturb-your-peace-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 09:35:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robin add a quote by Norman Vincent Peale]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163748-be-so-strong-that-nothing-can-disturb-your-peace-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be so strong that nothing can disturb your peace of mind. Talk health, happiness, and prosperity to every person you meet. Make all your friends feel there is something special in them. Look at the sunny side of everything. Think only the best, be as enthusiastic about the success of others as you are about your own.

Forget the mistakes of the past and press on to the greater achievements of the future. Give everyone a smile. Spend so much time improving yourself that you have no time left to criticize others. Be too big for worry and too noble for anger." -- Norman Vincent Peale]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231052-beyond-work-and-love-i-would-add-two-other-ingredients</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 13:57:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robin add a quote by Michio Kaku]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231052-beyond-work-and-love-i-would-add-two-other-ingredients]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beyond work and love, I would add two other ingredients that give meaning to life.  First, to fulfill whatever talents we are born with.  However blessed we are by fate with different abilities and strengths, we should try to develop them to the fullest, rather than allow them to atrophy and decay.  We all know individuals who did not fulfill the promise they showed in childhood.  Many of them became haunted by the image of what they might have become.  Instead of blaming fate, I think we should accept ourselves as we are and try to fulfill whatever dreams are within our capability.

Second, we should try to leave the world a better place than when we entered it.  As individuals, we can make a difference, whether it is to probe the secrets of Nature, to clean up the environment and work for peace and social justice, or to nurture the inquisitive, vibrant spirit of the young by being a mentor and a guide." -- Michio Kaku]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1117176-i-ve-always-found-that-if-your-life-is-hurtling-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 12:55:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robin add a quote by Robin Brande]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1117176-i-ve-always-found-that-if-your-life-is-hurtling-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've always found that if your life is hurtling out of control, it's best to bake a batch of chocolate chip cookies." -- Robin Brande]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465139-i-m-the-kind-of-person-who-would-rather-get-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 12:35:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robin add a quote by Mindy Kaling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465139-i-m-the-kind-of-person-who-would-rather-get-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm the kind of person who would rather get my hopes up really high and watch them get dashed to pieces than wisely keep my expectations at bay and hope they are exceeded. This quality has made me a needy and theatrical friend, but has given me a spectacularly dramatic emotional life." -- Mindy Kaling]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
