<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/221173-amy-lynn-ferguson]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/221173-amy-lynn-ferguson" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 10:30:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/733213-don-t-give-up-on-the-power-of-books-to-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 10:30:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy Lynn add a quote by David   Marshall]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/733213-don-t-give-up-on-the-power-of-books-to-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't give up on the power of books to change lives and the world. As everything goes digital, book formats will morph, but their profound influence will endure." -- David   Marshall]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49274-if-what-s-always-distinguished-bad-writing--flat-characters-a-narrative-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 10:16:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy Lynn add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49274-if-what-s-always-distinguished-bad-writing--flat-characters-a-narrative-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If what's always distinguished bad writing--flat characters, a narrative world that's clichéd and not recognizably human, etc.--is also a description of today's world, then bad writing becomes an ingenious mimesis of a bad world. If readers simply believe the world is stupid and shallow and mean, then [Bret] Ellis can write a mean shallow stupid novel that becomes a mordant deadpan commentary on the badness of everything. Look man, we'd probably most of us agree that these are dark times, and stupid ones, but do we need fiction that does nothing but dramatize how dark and stupid everything is? In dark times, the definition of good art would seem to be art that locates and applies CPR to those elements of what's human and magical that still live and glow despite the times' darkness. Really good fiction could have as dark a worldview as it wished, but it'd find a way both to depict this world and to illuminate the possibilities for being alive and human in it.

Postmodern irony and cynicism's become an end in itself, a measure of hip sophistication and literary savvy. Few artists dare to try to talk about ways of working toward redeeming what's wrong, because they'll look sentimental and naive to all the weary ironists. Irony's gone from liberating to enslaving. There's some great essay somewhere that has a line about irony being the song of the prisoner who's come to love his cage… The postmodern founders' patricidal work was great, but patricide produces orphans, and no amount of revelry can make up for the fact that writers my age have been literary orphans throughout our formative years.

We enter a spiritual puberty where we snap to the fact that the great transcendent horror is loneliness, excluded encagement in the self. Once we’ve hit this age, we will now give or take anything, wear any mask, to fit, be part-of, not be Alone, we young. The U.S. arts are our guide to inclusion. A how-to. We are shown how to fashion masks of ennui and jaded irony at a young age where the face is fictile enough to assume the shape of whatever it wears. And then it’s stuck there, the weary cynicism that saves us from gooey sentiment and unsophisticated naïveté. Sentiment equals naïveté on this continent.

You burn with hunger for food that does not exist.

A U. S. of modern A. where the State is not a team or a code, but a sort of sloppy intersection of desires and fears, where the only public consensus a boy must surrender to is the acknowledged primacy of straight-line pursuing this flat and short-sighted idea of personal happiness." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/506464-everything-i-ve-ever-let-go-of-has-claw-marks-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 10:17:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy Lynn add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/506464-everything-i-ve-ever-let-go-of-has-claw-marks-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything I’ve ever let go of has claw marks on it." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261556-the-parts-of-me-that-used-to-think-i-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 10:17:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy Lynn add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261556-the-parts-of-me-that-used-to-think-i-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The parts of me that used to think I was different or smarter or whatever, almost made me die." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118882-in-real-life-i-always-seem-to-have-a-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 10:19:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy Lynn add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118882-in-real-life-i-always-seem-to-have-a-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...in real life I always seem to have a hard time winding up a conversation or asking somebody to leave, and sometimes the moment becomes so delicate and fraught with social complexity that I'll get overwhelmed trying to sort out all the different possible ways of saying it and all the different implications of each option and will just sort of blank out and do it totally straight -- 'I want to terminate the conversation and not have you be in my apartment anymore' -- which evidently makes me look either as if I'm very rude and abrupt or as if I'm semi-autistic and have no sense of how to wind up a conversation gracefully...I've actually lost friends this way." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
