<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/221778-hardiansyah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/221778-hardiansyah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 04:12:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 04:12:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I went to the woods because I wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and see if I could not learn what it had to teach, and not, when I came to die, discover that I had not lived. I did not wish to live what was not life, living is so dear; nor did I wish to practise resignation, unless it was quite necessary. I wanted to live deep and suck out all the marrow of life, to live so sturdily and Spartan-like as to put to rout all that was not life, to cut a broad swath and shave close, to drive life into a corner, and reduce it to its lowest terms." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7762-rather-than-love-than-money-than-fame-give-me-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 04:12:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7762-rather-than-love-than-money-than-fame-give-me-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Rather than love, than money, than fame, give me truth." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2010 07:56:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65707-through-my-love-for-you-i-want-to-express-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 01:27:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65707-through-my-love-for-you-i-want-to-express-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Through my love for you, I want to express my love for the whole cosmos, the whole of humanity, and all beings. By living with you, I want to learn to love everyone and all species. If I succeed in loving you, I will be able to love everyone and all species on Earth... This is the real message of love." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 23:54:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4310-when-another-person-makes-you-suffer-it-is-because-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 23:54:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4310-when-another-person-makes-you-suffer-it-is-because-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When another person makes you suffer, it is because he suffers deeply within himself, and his suffering is spilling over. He does not need punishment; he needs help. That's the message he is sending." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11097-freethinkers-are-those-who-are-willing-to-use-their-minds</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 23:54:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11097-freethinkers-are-those-who-are-willing-to-use-their-minds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Freethinkers are those who are willing to use their minds without prejudice and without fearing to understand things that clash with their own customs, privileges, or beliefs. This state of mind is not common, but it is essential for right thinking..." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74804-if-you-look-for-perfection-you-ll-never-be-content</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 23:53:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74804-if-you-look-for-perfection-you-ll-never-be-content]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you look for perfection, you'll never be content." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55320-every-book-every-volume-you-see-here-has-a-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 23:53:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Carlos Ruiz Zafón]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55320-every-book-every-volume-you-see-here-has-a-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every book, every volume you see here, has a soul. The soul of the person who wrote it and of those who read it and lived and dreamed with it. Every time a book changes hands, every time someone runs his eyes down its pages, its spirit grows and strengthens." -- Carlos Ruiz Zafón]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1342-goodbye-said-the-fox-and-now-here-is-my-secret</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 08:04:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1342-goodbye-said-the-fox-and-now-here-is-my-secret]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Goodbye,&quot; said the fox. &quot;And now here is my secret, a very simple secret: It is only with the heart that one can see rightly; what is essential is invisible to the eye." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265991-j-aime-bien-les-couchers-de-soleil-allons-voir-un-coucher</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 08:07:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265991-j-aime-bien-les-couchers-de-soleil-allons-voir-un-coucher]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["J'aime bien les couchers de soleil. Allons voir un coucher de soleil..." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92347-in-general-the-art-of-government-consists-in-taking-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 18:11:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Voltaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92347-in-general-the-art-of-government-consists-in-taking-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In general, the art of government consists in taking as much money as possible from one party of the citizens to give to the other." -- Voltaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152238-and-when-you-look-at-the-sky-you-know-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 18:23:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Mark Haddon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152238-and-when-you-look-at-the-sky-you-know-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And when you look at the sky you know you are looking at stars which are hundreds and thousands of light-years away from you. And some of the stars don’t even exist anymore because their light has taken so long to get to us that they are already dead, or they have exploded and collapsed into red dwarfs. And that makes you seem very small, and if you have difficult things in you life it is nice to think that they are what is called negligible, which means they are so small you don’t have to take them into account when you are calculating something." -- Mark Haddon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7692-if-there-is-no-love-in-the-world-we-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 03:58:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7692-if-there-is-no-love-in-the-world-we-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there is no love in the world, we will make a new world, and we will give it walls, and we will furnish it with soft, red interiors, from the inside out, and give it a knocker that resonates like a diamond falling to a jeweller's felt so that we should never hear it. Love me, because love doesn't exist, and I have tried everything that does." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251780-so-many-people-live-within-unhappy-circumstances-and-yet-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2010 16:23:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251780-so-many-people-live-within-unhappy-circumstances-and-yet-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many people live within unhappy circumstances and yet will not take the initiative to change their situation because they are conditioned to a life of security, conformity, and conservatism, all of which may appear to give one peace of mind, but in reality nothing is more dangerous to the adventurous spirit within a man than a secure future. The very basic core of a man’s living spirit is his passion for adventure. The joy of life comes from our encounters with new experiences, and hence there is no greater joy than to have an endlessly changing horizon, for each day to have a new and different sun." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150700-love-doesn-t-happen-in-an-instant-it-creeps-up-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2011 04:10:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Vikas Swarup]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150700-love-doesn-t-happen-in-an-instant-it-creeps-up-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love doesn't happen in an instant.  It creeps up on you and then it turns your life upside down.  It colors your waking moments, and fills your dreams.  You begin to walk on air and see life in brilliant new shades.  But it also brings with it a sweet agony, a delicious torture." -- Vikas Swarup]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/450503-dalam-perjalanannya-dengan-kuda-berlangsung-berhari-hari-setelah-rehat-beliau-membaca</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 17:34:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Syed Hussein Alatas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/450503-dalam-perjalanannya-dengan-kuda-berlangsung-berhari-hari-setelah-rehat-beliau-membaca]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dalam perjalanannya dengan kuda berlangsung berhari-hari, setelah rehat, beliau membaca buku-buku ilmiah yang dibawanya. Membaca, bergaul dengan ahli-ahli ilmu pengetahuan adalah matlamat penting dalam program hidup Sultan Salahuddin al-Ayubi." -- Syed Hussein Alatas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467840-throughout-history-many-nations-have-suffered-a-physical-defeat-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 23:43:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Ibn Khaldun]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467840-throughout-history-many-nations-have-suffered-a-physical-defeat-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Throughout history many nations have suffered a physical defeat, but that has never marked the end of a nation. But when a nation has become the victim of a psychological defeat, then that marks the end of a nation." -- Ibn Khaldun]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430175-the-satisfactions-of-manifesting-oneself-concretely-in-the-world-through</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2012 17:33:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Matthew B. Crawford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430175-the-satisfactions-of-manifesting-oneself-concretely-in-the-world-through]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The satisfactions of manifesting oneself concretely in the world through manual competence have been known to make a man quiet and easy. They seem to relieve him of the felt need to offer chattering interpretations of himself to vindicate his worth. He can simply point: the building stands, the car now runs, the lights are on. Boasting is what a boy does, because he has no real effect in the world. But the tradesman must reckon with the infallible judgment of reality, where one’s failures or shortcomings cannot be interpreted away. His well-founded pride is far from the gratuitous “self-esteem” that educators would impart to students, as though by magic." -- Matthew B. Crawford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 03:43:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes fate is like a small sandstorm that keeps changing directions. You change direction but the sandstorm chases you. You turn again, but the storm adjusts. Over and over you play this out, like some ominous dance with death just before dawn. Why? Because this storm isn't something that blew in from far away, something that has nothing to do with you. This storm is you. Something &lt;i&gt;inside&lt;/i&gt; of you. So all you can do is give in to it, step right inside the storm, closing your eyes and plugging up your ears so the sand doesn't get in, and walk through it, step by step. There's no sun there, no moon, no direction, no sense of time. Just fine white sand swirling up into the sky like pulverized bones. That's the kind of sandstorm you need to imagine.

An you really will have to make it through that violent, metaphysical, symbolic storm. No matter how metaphysical or symbolic it might be, make no mistake about it: it will cut through flesh like a thousand razor blades. People will bleed there, and &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; will bleed too. Hot, red blood. You'll catch that blood in your hands, your own blood and the blood of others.

And once the storm is over you won't remember how you made it through, how you managed to survive. You won't even be sure, in fact, whether the storm is really over. But one thing is certain. When you come out of the storm you won't be the same person who walked in. That's what this storm's all about." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178424-see-the-poor-dream-all-their-lives-of-getting-enough</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2012 00:37:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Aravind Adiga]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178424-see-the-poor-dream-all-their-lives-of-getting-enough]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["See, the poor dream all their lives of getting enough to eat and looking like the rich. And what do the rich dream of?? Losing weight and looking like the poor." -- Aravind Adiga]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72160-if-you-only-read-the-books-that-everyone-else-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2012 00:37:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72160-if-you-only-read-the-books-that-everyone-else-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you only read the books that everyone else is reading, you can only think what everyone else is thinking." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/575997-if-writers-only-wrote-about-things-everybody-knew-what-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 08:00:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/575997-if-writers-only-wrote-about-things-everybody-knew-what-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If writers only wrote about things everybody knew, what the hell would be the point of writing?" -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184516-everything-is-possible-the-impossible-just-takes-longer</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2014 00:34:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Dan Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184516-everything-is-possible-the-impossible-just-takes-longer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything is possible. The impossible just takes longer." -- Dan Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1152552-jangan-terpaku-pada-kekurangan-kita-tapi-ada-baiknya-mengasah-keunggulan</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 07:15:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Nana Sitompul]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1152552-jangan-terpaku-pada-kekurangan-kita-tapi-ada-baiknya-mengasah-keunggulan]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["jangan terpaku pada kekurangan kita, tapi ada baiknya mengasah keunggulan yang kita miliki" -- Nana Sitompul]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004828-tolstoy-meant-that-in-order-to-be-happy-a-marriage</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 05:17:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hardiansyah add a quote by Jared Diamond]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004828-tolstoy-meant-that-in-order-to-be-happy-a-marriage]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tolstoy meant that, in order to be happy, a marriage must succeed in many different respects: sexual attraction, agreement about money, child discipline, religion, in-laws, and other vital issues." -- Jared Diamond]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
