<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/22184-laura]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/22184-laura" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 19:05:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533036-when-the-leaves-rustle-they-sound-very-much-like-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 19:05:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Daphne du Maurier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533036-when-the-leaves-rustle-they-sound-very-much-like-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the leaves rustle, they sound very much like the stealthy movement of a woman in evening dress, and when they shiver suddenly, and fall, and scatter away along the ground, they might be the patter of a woman’s hurrying footsteps, and the mark in the gravel the imprint of a high-heeled shoe." -- Daphne du Maurier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12631-the-problem-with-putting-two-and-two-together-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 22:48:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Dashiell Hammett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12631-the-problem-with-putting-two-and-two-together-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem with putting two and two together is that sometimes you get four, and sometimes you get twenty-two." -- Dashiell Hammett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34107-you-expected-to-be-sad-in-the-fall-part-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 11:05:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34107-you-expected-to-be-sad-in-the-fall-part-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You expected to be sad in the fall. Part of you died each year when the leaves fell from the trees and their branches were bare against the wind and the cold, wintery light. But you knew there would always be the spring, as you knew the river would flow again after it was frozen. When the cold rains kept on and killed the spring, it was as though a young person died for no reason." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5850-human-speech-is-like-a-cracked-kettle-on-which-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 11:26:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5850-human-speech-is-like-a-cracked-kettle-on-which-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human speech is like a cracked kettle on which we tap crude rhythms for bears to dance to, while we long to make music that will melt the stars." -- Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416906-i-wondered-why-it-was-that-places-are-so-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 19:01:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Daphne du Maurier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416906-i-wondered-why-it-was-that-places-are-so-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wondered why it was that places are so much lovelier when one is alone. How commonplace and stupid it would be if I had a friend now, sitting beside me, someone I had known at school, who would say: “By-the-way, I saw old Hilda the other day. You remember her, the one who was so good at tennis. She’s married, with two children.” And the bluebells beside us unnoticed, and the pigeons overhead unheard. I did not want anyone with me. Not even Maxim. If Maxim had been there I should not be lying as I was now, chewing a piece of grass, my eyes shut. I should have been watching him, watching his eyes, his expression. Wondering if he liked it, if he was bored. Wondering what he was thinking. Now I could relax, none of these things mattered. Maxim was in London. How lovely it was to be alone again." -- Daphne du Maurier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315932-once-a-little-boy-sent-me-a-charming-card-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 14:47:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Maurice Sendak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315932-once-a-little-boy-sent-me-a-charming-card-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once a little boy sent me a charming card with a little drawing on it. I loved it. I answer all my children’s letters — sometimes very hastily — but this one I lingered over. I sent him a card and I drew a picture of a Wild Thing on it. I wrote, “Dear Jim: I loved your card.” Then I got a letter back from his mother and she said, “Jim loved your card so much he ate it.” That to me was one of the highest compliments I’ve ever received. He didn’t care that it was an original Maurice Sendak drawing or anything. He saw it, he loved it, he ate it." -- Maurice Sendak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164277-having-a-coke-with-you-is-even-more-fun-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 10:04:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Frank O'Hara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164277-having-a-coke-with-you-is-even-more-fun-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Having a Coke with You

is even more fun than going to San Sebastian, Irún, Hendaye, Biarritz, Bayonne
or being sick to my stomach on the Travesera de Gracia in Barcelona
partly because in your orange shirt you look like a better happier St. Sebastian
partly because of my love for you, partly because of your love for yoghurt
partly because of the fluorescent orange tulips around the birches
partly because of the secrecy our smiles take on before people and statuary
it is hard to believe when I’m with you that there can be anything as still
as solemn as unpleasantly definitive as statuary when right in front of it
in the warm New York 4 o’clock light we are drifting back and forth
between each other like a tree breathing through its spectacles

and the portrait show seems to have no faces in it at all, just paint
you suddenly wonder why in the world anyone ever did them

I look
at you and I would rather look at you than all the portraits in the world
except possibly for the Polish Rider occasionally and anyway it’s in the Frick
which thank heavens you haven’t gone to yet so we can go together the first time
and the fact that you move so beautifully more or less takes care of Futurism
just as at home I never think of the Nude Descending a Staircase or
at a rehearsal a single drawing of Leonardo or Michelangelo that used to wow me
and what good does all the research of the Impressionists do them
when they never got the right person to stand near the tree when the sun sank
or for that matter Marino Marini when he didn’t pick the rider as carefully
as the horse

it seems they were all cheated of some marvelous experience
which is not going to go wasted on me which is why I am telling you about it" -- Frank O'Hara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57214-saying-i-notice-you-re-a-nerd-is-like-saying-hey</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 18:48:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57214-saying-i-notice-you-re-a-nerd-is-like-saying-hey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Saying 'I notice you're a nerd' is like saying, 'Hey, I notice that you'd rather be intelligent than be stupid, that you'd rather be thoughtful than be vapid, that you believe that there are things that matter more than the arrest record of Lindsay Lohan. Why is that?' In fact, it seems to me that most contemporary insults are pretty lame. Even 'lame' is kind of lame. Saying 'You're lame' is like saying 'You walk with a limp.' Yeah, whatever, so does 50 Cent, and he's done all right for himself." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/732246-femininity-is-depicted-as-weakness-the-sapping-of-strength-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 06:56:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Gwen Sharp]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/732246-femininity-is-depicted-as-weakness-the-sapping-of-strength-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Femininity is depicted as weakness, the sapping of strength, yet masculinity is so fragile that apparently even the slightest brush with the feminine destroys it." -- Gwen Sharp]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189740-they-agreed-that-it-was-neither-possible-nor-necessary-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2014 00:51:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189740-they-agreed-that-it-was-neither-possible-nor-necessary-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[They] agreed that it was neither possible nor necessary to educate people who never questioned anything." -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
