<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/222509-rebecca]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/222509-rebecca" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 08:35:34 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/379013-i-pulled-myself-up-and-told-myself-to-stop-these</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 08:35:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rebecca add a quote by Barbara Pym]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/379013-i-pulled-myself-up-and-told-myself-to-stop-these]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I pulled myself up and told myself to stop these ridiculous thoughts, wondering why it is that we can never stop trying to analyse the motives of people who have no personal interest in us, in the vain hope of finding that perhaps they may have just a little after all." -- Barbara Pym]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/499997-self-esteem-is-for-sissies-accept-that-you-re-a-pimple-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 08:39:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rebecca add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/499997-self-esteem-is-for-sissies-accept-that-you-re-a-pimple-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Self-esteem is for sissies. Accept that you're a pimple and try to keep a lively sense of humor about it. That way lies grace - and maybe even glory." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/553036-are-you-one-of-those-people-who-says-on-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2012 12:46:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rebecca add a quote by Augusten Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/553036-are-you-one-of-those-people-who-says-on-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Are you one of those people who says on a first date, 'I'm really not in a hurry to meet somebody, I figure if it happens, it happens'? Because those are the most desperate people of all. I'm just saying this so that if you are this person, you aren't hiding it from anybody.

There is no shame in being hungry for another person. There is no shame in wanting very much to share your life with somebody." -- Augusten Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155562-and-when-at-last-you-find-someone-to-whom-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 22:21:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rebecca add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155562-and-when-at-last-you-find-someone-to-whom-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And when at last you find someone to whom you feel you can pour out your soul, you stop in shock at the words you utter— they are so rusty, so ugly, so meaningless and feeble from being kept in the small cramped dark inside you so long." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153404-we-tell-ourselves-stories-in-order-to-live-the-princess</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 08:23:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rebecca add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153404-we-tell-ourselves-stories-in-order-to-live-the-princess]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We tell ourselves stories in order to live. The princess is caged in the consulate. The man with the candy will lead the children into the sea. The naked woman on the ledge outside the window on the sixteenth floor is a victim of accidie, or the naked woman is an exhibitionist, and it would be 'interesting' to know which. We tell ourselves that it makes some difference whether the naked woman is about to commit a mortal sin or is about to register a political protest or is about to be, the Aristophanic view, snatched back to the human condition by the fireman in priest's clothing just visible in the window behind her, the one smiling at the telephoto lens. We look for the sermon in the suicide, for the social or moral lesson in the murder of five. We interpret what we see, select the most workable of the multiple choices. We live entirely... by the imposition of a narrative line upon disparate images, by the 'ideas' with which we have learned to freeze the shifting phantasmagoria — which is our actual experience." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153664-what-new-england-is-is-a-state-of-mind-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 08:49:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rebecca add a quote by Willem Lange]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153664-what-new-england-is-is-a-state-of-mind-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What New England is, is a state of mind, a place where dry humor and perpetual disappointment blend to produce an ironic pessimism that folks from away find most perplexing" -- Willem Lange]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106957-we-are-the-hero-of-our-own-story</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 11:51:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rebecca add a quote by Mary McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106957-we-are-the-hero-of-our-own-story]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are the hero of our own story." -- Mary McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/537670-what-s-the-use-of-falling-in-love-if-you-both</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 11:51:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rebecca add a quote by Mary McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/537670-what-s-the-use-of-falling-in-love-if-you-both]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What's the use of falling in love if you both remain inertly as you were?" -- Mary McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
