<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/224472-megan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/224472-megan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 16:33:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/618008-if-there-s-one-thing-i-ve-learned-it-s-this-we-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 16:33:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by David Levithan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/618008-if-there-s-one-thing-i-ve-learned-it-s-this-we-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there's one thing I've learned, it's this: We all want everything to be okay. We don't even wish so much for fantastic or marvelous or outstanding. We will happily settle for okay, because most of the time, okay is enough." -- David Levithan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/340928-trying-to-write-about-love-is-ultimately-like-trying-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 16:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by David Levithan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/340928-trying-to-write-about-love-is-ultimately-like-trying-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Trying to write about love is ultimately like trying to have a dictionary represent life. No matter how many words there are, there will never be enough." -- David Levithan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620991-i-have-been-to-many-religious-services-over-the-years</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 16:35:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by David Levithan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620991-i-have-been-to-many-religious-services-over-the-years]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have been to many religious services over the years. Each one I go to only reinforces my general impression that religions have much, much more in common than they like to admit. The beliefs are almost always the same; it's just that the histories are different. Everybody wants to believe in a higher power. Everybody wants to belong to something bigger than themselves, and everybody wants company in doing that. They want there to be a force of good on earth, and they want an incentive to be a part of that force. They want to be able to prove their belief and their belonging, through rituals and devotion. They want to touch the enormity.
It's only in the finer points that it gets complicated and contentious, the inability to realize that no matter what our religion or gender or race or geographic background, we all have about 98 percent in common with each other. yes, the differences between male and female are biological, but if you look at the biology as a matter of percentage, there aren't a whole lot of things that are different. Race is different purely as a social construction, not as an inherent difference. And religion--whether you believe in God or Yahweh or Allah or something else, odds are that at heart you want the same things. For whatever reason, we like to focus on the 2 percent that's different, and most of the conflict in the world comes from that." -- David Levithan]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
