<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/22493-val-jones]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/22493-val-jones" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 11:15:54 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28486-now-i-know-that-our-world-is-no-more-permanent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 11:15:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Arthur Golden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28486-now-i-know-that-our-world-is-no-more-permanent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now I know that our world is no more permanent than a wave rising on the ocean. Whatever our struggles and triumphs, however we may suffer them, all too soon they bleed into a wash, just like watery ink on paper." -- Arthur Golden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18125-adversity-is-like-a-strong-wind-i-don-t-mean-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 11:16:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Arthur Golden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18125-adversity-is-like-a-strong-wind-i-don-t-mean-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Adversity is like a strong wind.  I don't mean just that it holds us back from places we might otherwise go.  It also tears away from us all but the things that cannot be torn, so that afterward we see ourselves as we really are, and not merely as we might like to be." -- Arthur Golden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18128-from-this-experience-i-understood-the-danger-of-focusing-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 11:17:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Arthur Golden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18128-from-this-experience-i-understood-the-danger-of-focusing-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From this experience, I understood the danger of focusing only on what isn't there.  What if I came to the end of my life and realized that I'd spent every day watching for a man who would never come to me?  What an unbearable sorrow it would be, to realize I'd never really tasted the things I'd eaten, or seen the places I'd been, because I'd thought of nothing but the Chairman even while my life was drifting away from me.  And yet if I drew my thoughts back from him, what life would I have?  I would be like a dancer who had practiced since childhood for a performance she would never give." -- Arthur Golden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18129-if-you-shut-your-eyes-and-are-a-lucky-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 11:19:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18129-if-you-shut-your-eyes-and-are-a-lucky-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you shut your eyes and are a lucky one, you may see at times a shapeless pool of lovely pale colours suspended in the darkness; then if you squeeze your eyes tighter, the pool begins to take shape, and the colours become so vivid that with another squeeze they must go on fire." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18130-you-need-not-be-sorry-for-her-she-was-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 11:19:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18130-you-need-not-be-sorry-for-her-she-was-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You need not be sorry for her.  She was one of the kind that likes to grow up.  In the end she grew up of her own free will a day quicker than the other girls." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18132-occupied-in-observing-mr-bingley-s-attentions-to-her-sister-elizabeth</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 11:21:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18132-occupied-in-observing-mr-bingley-s-attentions-to-her-sister-elizabeth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Occupied in observing Mr. Bingley’s attentions to her sister, Elizabeth was far from suspecting that she was herself becoming an object of some interest in the eyes of his friend. Mr. Darcy had at first scarcely allowed her to be pretty: he had looked at her without admiration at the ball; and when they next met, he looked at her only to criticise. But no sooner had he made it clear to himself and his friends that she had hardly a good feature in her face, than he began to find it was rendered uncommonly intelligent by the beautiful expression of her dark eyes. To this discovery succeeded some others equally mortifying. Though he had detected with a critical eye more than one failure of perfect symmetry in her form, he was forced to acknowledge her figure to be light and pleasing; and in spite of his asserting that her manners were not those of the fashionable world, he was caught by their easy playfulness. Of this she was perfectly unaware: to her he was only the man who made himself agreeable nowhere, and who had not thought her handsome enough to dance with." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18133-reflection-must-be-reserved-for-solitary-hours-whenever-she-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 11:22:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18133-reflection-must-be-reserved-for-solitary-hours-whenever-she-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reflection must be reserved for solitary hours; whenever she was alone, she gave way to it as the greatest relief; and not a day went by without a solitary walk, in which she might indulge in all the delight of unpleasant recollections." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18139-true-life-lies-in-laughter-love-and-work</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 11:26:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18139-true-life-lies-in-laughter-love-and-work]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["True life lies in laughter, love and work." -- Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18140-dreams-are-real-while-they-last-can-we-say-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 11:27:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Havelock Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18140-dreams-are-real-while-they-last-can-we-say-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dreams are real while they last.  Can we say more of life? " -- Havelock Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
