<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/225007-melody]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/225007-melody" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 08:00:09 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30838-the-spirit-in-the-body-is-like-wine-in-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 08:00:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by Anne Michaels]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30838-the-spirit-in-the-body-is-like-wine-in-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The spirit in the body is like wine in a glass; when it spills, it seeps into air and earth and light….It’s a mistake to think it’s the small things we control and not the large, it’s the other way around! We can’t stop the small accident, the tiny detail that conspires into fate: the extra moment you run back for something forgotten, a moment that saves you from an accident – or causes one. But we can assert the largest order, the large human values daily, the only order large enough to see." -- Anne Michaels]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30840-cakes-have-gotten-a-bad-rap-people-equate-virtue-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 08:01:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melody add a quote by Jeanne Ray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30840-cakes-have-gotten-a-bad-rap-people-equate-virtue-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cakes have gotten a bad rap. People equate virtue with turning down dessert. There is always one person at the table who holds up her hand when I serve the cake. No, really, I couldn’t she says, and then gives her flat stomach a conspiratorial little pat. Everyone who is pressing a fork into that first tender layer looks at the person who declined the plate, and they all think, That person is better than I am. That person has discipline. But that isn’t a person with discipline; that is a person who has completely lost touch with joy. A slice of cake never made anybody fat. You don’t eat the whole cake. You don’t eat a cake every day of your life. You take the cake when it is offered because the cake is delicious. You have a slice of cake and what it reminds you of is someplace that’s safe, uncomplicated, without stress. A cake is a party, a birthday, a wedding. A cake is what’s served on the happiest days of your life. This is a story of how my life was saved by cake, so, of course, if sides are to be taken, I will always take the side of cake." -- Jeanne Ray]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
