<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/225656-erin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/225656-erin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 11:22:58 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 11:22:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1668-there-is-neither-happiness-nor-misery-in-the-world-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 11:23:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1668-there-is-neither-happiness-nor-misery-in-the-world-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is neither happiness nor misery in the world; there is only the comparison of one state with another, nothing more. He who has felt the deepest grief is best able to experience supreme happiness. We must have felt what it is to die, Morrel, that we may appreciate the enjoyments of life. 
&quot; Live, then, and be happy, beloved children of my heart, and never forget, that until the day God will deign to reveal the future to man, all human wisdom is contained in these two words, 'Wait and Hope." -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9747-i-love-being-married-it-s-so-great-to-find-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2008 08:02:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Rita Rudner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9747-i-love-being-married-it-s-so-great-to-find-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love being married. It's so great to find that one special person you want to annoy for the rest of your life." -- Rita Rudner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22842-you-have-brains-in-your-head-you-have-feet-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 19:47:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22842-you-have-brains-in-your-head-you-have-feet-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have brains in your head. You have feet in your shoes. You can steer yourself any direction you choose. You're on your own. And you know what you know. And YOU are the one who'll decide where to go..." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12405-tell-your-heart-that-the-fear-of-suffering-is-worse</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 12:27:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12405-tell-your-heart-that-the-fear-of-suffering-is-worse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tell your heart that the fear of suffering is worse than the suffering itself. And that no heart has ever suffered when it goes in search of its dreams, because every second of the search is a second's encounter with God and with eternity." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37947-it-was-the-pure-language-of-the-world-it-required</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 12:29:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37947-it-was-the-pure-language-of-the-world-it-required]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was the pure Language of the World. It required no explanation, just as the universe needs none as it travels through endless time. What the boy felt at that moment was that he was in the presence of the only woman in his life, and that, with no need for words, she recognized the same thing. He was more certain of it than of anything in the world. He had been told by his parents and grandparents that he must fall in love and really know a person before becoming committed. But maybe people who felt that way had never learned the universal language. Because, when you know that language, it's easy to understand that someone in the world awaits you, whether it's in the middle of the desert or in some great city. And when two such people encounter each other, and their eyes meet, the past and the future become unimportant. There is only that moment, and the incredible certainty that everything under the sun has been written by one hand only. It is the hand that evokes love, and creates a twin soul for every person in the world. Without such love, one's dreams would have no meaning." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
