<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/227556-natasha]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/227556-natasha" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:51:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141511-suffering-has-been-stronger-than-all-other-teaching-and-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:51:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141511-suffering-has-been-stronger-than-all-other-teaching-and-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suffering has been stronger than all other teaching, and has taught me to understand what your heart used to be. I have been bent and broken, but - I hope - into a better shape." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470-it-is-a-far-far-better-thing-that-i-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:51:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470-it-is-a-far-far-better-thing-that-i-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a far, far better thing that I do, than I have ever done; it is a far, far better rest that I go to than I have ever known." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5453-to-conceal-anything-from-those-to-whom-i-am-attached</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:52:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by charles dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5453-to-conceal-anything-from-those-to-whom-i-am-attached]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To conceal anything from those to whom I am attached, is not in my nature. I can never close my lips where I have opened my heart." -- charles dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90996-you-have-been-the-last-dream-of-my-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:52:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90996-you-have-been-the-last-dream-of-my-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have been the last dream of my soul." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94104-family-not-only-need-to-consist-of-merely-those-whom</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:52:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94104-family-not-only-need-to-consist-of-merely-those-whom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Family not only need to consist of merely those whom we share blood, but also for those whom we'd give blood." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180993-the-unqualified-truth-is-that-when-i-loved-estella-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:53:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180993-the-unqualified-truth-is-that-when-i-loved-estella-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The unqualified truth is, that when I loved Estella with the love of a man, I loved her simply because I found her irresistible. Once for all; I knew to my sorrow, often and often, if not always, that I loved her against reason, against promise, against peace, against hope, against happiness, against all discouragement that could be. Once for all; I love her none the less because I knew it, and it had no more influence in restraining me, than if I had devoutly believed her to be human perfection." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341391-it-was-the-best-of-times-it-was-the-worst</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:53:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341391-it-was-the-best-of-times-it-was-the-worst]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was the best of times, it was the worst of times, it was the age of wisdom, it was the age of foolishness, it was the epoch of belief, it was the epoch of incredulity, it was the season of light, it was the season of darkness, it was the spring of hope, it was the winter of despair." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31121-sadly-sadly-the-sun-rose-it-rose-upon-no-sadder</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:53:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31121-sadly-sadly-the-sun-rose-it-rose-upon-no-sadder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sadly, sadly, the sun rose; it rose upon no sadder sight than the man of good abilities and good emotions, incapable of their directed exercise, incapable of his own help and his own happiness, sensible of the blight on him, and resigning himself to let it eat him away." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182796-out-of-my-thoughts-you-are-part-of-my-existence</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:54:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182796-out-of-my-thoughts-you-are-part-of-my-existence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Out of my thoughts! You are part of my existence, part of myself. You have been in every line I have ever read, since I first came here, the rough common boy whose poor heart you wounded even then. You have been in every prospect I have ever seen since – on the river, on the sails of the ships, on the marshes, in the clouds, in the light, in the darkness, in the wind, in the woods, in the sea, in the streets. You have been the embodiment of every graceful fancy that my mind has ever become acquainted with. The stones of which the strongest London buildings are made, are not more real, or more impossible to displace with your hands, than your presence and influence have been to me, there and everywhere, and will be. Estella, to the last hour of my life, you cannot choose but remain part of my character, part of the little good in me, part of the evil. But, in this separation I associate you only with the good, and I will faithfully hold you to that always, for you must have done me far more good than harm, let me feel now what sharp distress I may. O God bless you, God forgive you!" -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69332-for-you-and-for-any-dear-to-you-i-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:54:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69332-for-you-and-for-any-dear-to-you-i-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For you, and for any dear to you, I would do anything. If my career were of that better kind that there was any opportunity or capacity of sacrifice in it, I would embrace any sacrifice for you and for those dear to you. Try to hold me in your mind, at some quiet times, as ardent and sincere in this one thing. The time will come, the time will not be long in coming, when new ties will be formed about you--ties that will bind you yet more tenderly and strongly to the home you so adorn--the dearest ties that will ever grace and gladden you. O Miss Manette, when the little picture of a happy father's face looks up in yours, when you see your own bright beauty springing up anew at your feet, think now and then that there is a man who would give his life, to keep a life you love beside you!" -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77145-a-dream-all-a-dream-that-ends-in-nothing-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:55:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77145-a-dream-all-a-dream-that-ends-in-nothing-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A dream, all a dream, that ends in nothing, and leaves the sleeper where he lay down, but I wish you to know that you inspired it." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17361-death-may-beget-life-but-oppression-can-beget-nothing-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:55:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17361-death-may-beget-life-but-oppression-can-beget-nothing-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death may beget life, but oppression can beget nothing other than itself." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245586-i-have-been-bent-and-broken-but---i-hope</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:56:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245586-i-have-been-bent-and-broken-but---i-hope]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have been bent and broken, but - I hope - into a better shape." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109862-that-was-a-memorable-day-to-me-for-it-made</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:56:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109862-that-was-a-memorable-day-to-me-for-it-made]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That was a memorable day to me, for it made great changes in me. But it is the same with any life. Imagine one selected day struck out of it, and think how different its course would have been. Pause you who read this, and think for a moment of the long chain of iron or gold, of thorns or flowers, that would never have bound you, but for the formation of the first link on one memorable day." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78924-before-i-go-he-said-and-paused----i-may</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:56:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78924-before-i-go-he-said-and-paused----i-may]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Before I go,&quot; he said, and paused -- &quot;I may kiss her?&quot;

It was remembered afterwards that when he bent down and touched her face with his lips, he murmured some words. The child, who was nearest to him, told them afterwards, and told her grandchildren when she was a handsome old lady, that she heard him say, &quot;A life you love." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49226-crush-humanity-out-of-shape-once-more-under-similar-hammers</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:56:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49226-crush-humanity-out-of-shape-once-more-under-similar-hammers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Crush humanity out of shape once more, under similar hammers, and it will twist itself into the same tortured forms.  Sow the same seeds of rapacious licence and oppression over again, and it will surely yield the same fruit according to its kind." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136712-then-tell-wind-and-fire-where-to-stop-returned-madame</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:57:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136712-then-tell-wind-and-fire-where-to-stop-returned-madame]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then tell Wind and Fire where to stop,&quot; returned madame; &quot;but don't tell me." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296088-and-yet-i-have-had-the-weakness-and-have-still</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:58:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296088-and-yet-i-have-had-the-weakness-and-have-still]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["‎And yet I have had the weakness, and have still the weakness, to wish you to know with what a sudden mastery you kindled me, heap of ashes that I am, into fire." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152631-i-see-a-beautiful-city-and-a-brilliant-people-rising</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:58:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152631-i-see-a-beautiful-city-and-a-brilliant-people-rising]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I see a beautiful city and a brilliant people rising from this abyss, and, in their struggles to be truly free, in their triumphs and defeats, through long years to come, I see the evil of this time and of the previous time of which this is the natural birth, gradually making expiation for itself and wearing out..." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238200-i-wish-you-to-know-that-you-have-been-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:59:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238200-i-wish-you-to-know-that-you-have-been-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish you to know that you have been the last dream of my soul." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/400854-i-loved-her-against-reason-against-promise-against-peace-against</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 14:59:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/400854-i-loved-her-against-reason-against-promise-against-peace-against]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I loved her against reason, against promise, against peace, against hope, against happiness, against all discouragement that could be." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195549-all-through-it-i-have-known-myself-to-be-quite</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 15:01:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195549-all-through-it-i-have-known-myself-to-be-quite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All through it, I have known myself to be quite undeserving. And yet I have had the weakness, and have still the weakness, to wish you to know with what a sudden mastery you kindled me, heap of ashes that I am, into fire- a fire, however, inseparable in its nature from myself, quickening nothing, lighting nothing, doing no service, idly burning away." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80233-when-they-took-a-young-man-into-tellson-s-london-house</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 15:02:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80233-when-they-took-a-young-man-into-tellson-s-london-house]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When they took a young man into Tellson's London house, they hid him somewhere till he was old.  They kept him in a dark place, like a cheese, until he had the full Tellson flavour and blue-mould upon him.  Then only was he permitted to be seen, spectacularly poring over large books, and casting his breeches and gaiters into the general weight of the establishment." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312944-a-wonderful-fact-to-reflect-upon-that-every-human-creature</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 15:04:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natasha add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312944-a-wonderful-fact-to-reflect-upon-that-every-human-creature]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A wonderful fact to reflect upon, that every human creature is constituted to be that profound secret and mystery to every other. A solemn consideration, when I enter a great city by night, that every one of those darkly clustered houses encloses its own secret; that every room in every one of them encloses its own secret; that every beating heart in the hundreds of thousands of breasts there, is, in some of its imaginings, a secret to the heart nearest it! Something of the awfulness, even of Death itself, is referable to this. No more can I turn the leaves of this dear book that I loved, and vainly hope in time to read it all. No more can I look into the depths of this unfathomable water, wherein, as momentary lights glanced into it, I have had glimpses of buried treasure and other things submerged. It was appointed that the book should shut with a a spring, for ever and for ever, when I had read but a page. It was appointed that the water should be locked in an eternal frost, when the light was playing on its surface, and I stood in ignorance on the shore. My friend is dead, my neighbour is dead, my love, the darling of my soul, is dead; it is the inexorable consolidation and perpetuation of the secret that was always in that individuality, and which I shall carry in mine to my life's end. In any of the burial-places of this city through which I pass, is there a sleeper more inscrutable than its busy inhabitants are, in their innermost personality, to me, or than I am to them?" -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
