<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/227755-jenniffer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/227755-jenniffer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:15:23 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3860-there-were-times-when-he-allowed-himself-to-see-clearly</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:15:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by A.S. Byatt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3860-there-were-times-when-he-allowed-himself-to-see-clearly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There were times when [he] allowed himself to see clearly that he would end his working life, that was to say, his conscious thinking life, in this task, that all his thoughts would have been another man's thoughts, all his work another man's work. And then he thought it did not perhaps matter so greatly... It was a pleasant subordination, if he was a subordinate." -- A.S. Byatt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1222-you-cannot-find-peace-by-avoiding-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:16:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1222-you-cannot-find-peace-by-avoiding-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You cannot find peace by avoiding life." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1858-for-most-of-history-anonymous-was-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:16:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1858-for-most-of-history-anonymous-was-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For most of history, Anonymous was a woman." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4819-when-you-consider-things-like-the-stars-our-affairs-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:17:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Virginia Woolf ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4819-when-you-consider-things-like-the-stars-our-affairs-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you consider things like the stars, our affairs don't seem to matter very much, do they?" -- Virginia Woolf ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1856-different-though-the-sexes-are-they-inter-mix-in-every-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:17:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1856-different-though-the-sexes-are-they-inter-mix-in-every-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Different though the sexes are, they inter-mix. In every human being a vacillation from one sex to the other takes place, and often it is only the clothes that keep the male or female likeness, while underneath the sex is the very opposite of what it is above. " -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1860-one-cannot-think-well-love-well-sleep-well-if-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:17:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1860-one-cannot-think-well-love-well-sleep-well-if-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One cannot think well, love well, sleep well, if one has not dined well." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4047-the-eyes-of-others-our-prisons-their-thoughts-our-cages</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:18:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4047-the-eyes-of-others-our-prisons-their-thoughts-our-cages]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The eyes of others our prisons; their thoughts our cages." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2807-as-a-woman-i-have-no-country-as-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:18:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by virginia woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2807-as-a-woman-i-have-no-country-as-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As a woman I have no country. As a woman I want no country. As a woman, my country is the whole world." -- virginia woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2147-she-could-have-wept-it-was-bad-it-was-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:18:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2147-she-could-have-wept-it-was-bad-it-was-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She could have wept. It was bad, it was bad, it was infinitely bad! She could have done it differently of course; the colour could have been thinned and faded; the shapes etherealised; that was how Paunceforte would have seen it. But then she did not see it like that. She saw the colour burning on a framework of steel; the light of a butterfly’s wing lying upon the arches of a cathedral. Of all that only a few random marks scrawled upon the canvas remained. And it would never be seen; never be hung even, and there was Mr Tansley whispering in her ear, “Women can’t paint, women can’t write ...”

She now remembered what she had been going to say about Mrs Ramsay. She did not know how she would have put it; but it would have been something critical. She had been annoyed the other night by some highhandedness. Looking along the level of Mr Bankes’s glance at her, she thought that no woman could worship another woman in the way he worshipped; they could only seek shelter under the shade which Mr Bankes extended over them both. Looking along his beam she added to it her different ray, thinking that she was unquestionably the loveliest of people (bowed over her book); the best perhaps; but also, different too from the perfect shape which one saw there. But why different, and how different? she asked herself, scraping her palette of all those mounds of blue and green which seemed to her like clods with no life in them now, yet she vowed, she would inspire them, force them to move, flow, do her bidding tomorrow. How did she differ? What was the spirit in her, the essential thing, by which, had you found a crumpled glove in the corner of a sofa, you would have known it, from its twisted finger, hers indisputably? She was like a bird for speed, an arrow for directness. She was willful; she was commanding (of course, Lily reminded herself, I am thinking of her relations with women, and I am much younger, an insignificant person, living off the Brompton Road). She opened bedroom windows. She shut doors. (So she tried to start the tune of Mrs Ramsay in her head.) Arriving late at night, with a light tap on one’s bedroom door, wrapped in an old fur coat (for the setting of her beauty was always that—hasty, but apt), she would enact again whatever it might be—Charles Tansley losing his umbrella; Mr Carmichael snuffling and sniffing; Mr Bankes saying, “The vegetable salts are lost.” All this she would adroitly shape; even maliciously twist; and, moving over to the window, in pretence that she must go,—it was dawn, she could see the sun rising,—half turn back, more intimately, but still always laughing, insist that she must, Minta must, they all must marry, since in the whole world whatever laurels might be tossed to her (but Mrs Ramsay cared not a fig for her painting), or triumphs won by her (probably Mrs Ramsay had had her share of those), and here she saddened, darkened, and came back to her chair, there could be no disputing this: an unmarried woman (she lightly took her hand for a moment), an unmarried woman has missed the best of life. The house seemed full of children sleeping and Mrs Ramsay listening; shaded lights and regular breathing." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1861-the-history-of-men-s-opposition-to-women-s-emancipation-is-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:19:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1861-the-history-of-men-s-opposition-to-women-s-emancipation-is-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The history of men's opposition to women's emancipation is more interesting perhaps than the story of that emancipation itself." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1718-the-very-least-you-can-do-in-your-life-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:34:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1718-the-very-least-you-can-do-in-your-life-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The very least you can do in your life is figure out what you hope for. And the most you can do is live inside that hope. Not admire it from a distance but live right in it, under its roof." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3897-listen-to-live-is-to-be-marked-to-live-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:34:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3897-listen-to-live-is-to-be-marked-to-live-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen. To live is to be marked. To live is to change, to acquire the words of a story, and that is the only celebration we mortals really know. In perfect stillness, frankly, I've only found sorrow." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3666-isn-t-that-how-it-is-when-you-must-decide-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:36:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Amy Tan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3666-isn-t-that-how-it-is-when-you-must-decide-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't that how it is when you must decide with your heart? You are not just choosing one thing over another. You are choosing what you want. And you are also choosing what somebody else does not want, and all the consequences that follow. You can tell yourself, That's not my problem, but those words do not wash the trouble away. Maybe it is no longer a problem in your life. But it is always a problem in your heart." -- Amy Tan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/933-i-think-it-would-be-well-and-proper-and-obedient</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:36:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/933-i-think-it-would-be-well-and-proper-and-obedient]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think it would be well, and proper, and obedient, and pure, to grasp your one necessity and not let it go, to dangle from it limp wherever it takes you." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1204-how-we-spend-our-days-is-of-course-how-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:36:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1204-how-we-spend-our-days-is-of-course-how-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How we spend our days is, of course, how we spend our lives." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1216-we-pass-through-this-world-but-once-few-tragedies-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:37:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1216-we-pass-through-this-world-but-once-few-tragedies-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We pass through this world but once. Few tragedies can be more extensive than the stunting of life, few injustices deeper than the denial of an opportunity to strive or even to hope, by a limit imposed from without, but falsely identified as lying within." -- Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3645-we-have-become-by-the-power-of-a-glorious-evolutionary</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:37:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3645-we-have-become-by-the-power-of-a-glorious-evolutionary]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have become, by the power of a glorious evolutionary accident called intelligence, the stewards of life's continuity on earth.  We did not ask for this role, but we cannot abjure it.  We may not be suited to it, but here we are." -- Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2019-they-sicken-of-the-calm-who-know-the-storm</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:39:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Dorothy Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2019-they-sicken-of-the-calm-who-know-the-storm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They sicken of the calm who know the storm." -- Dorothy Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/397-there-is-no-flag-large-enough-to-cover-the-shame</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:41:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/397-there-is-no-flag-large-enough-to-cover-the-shame]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no flag large enough to cover the shame of killing innocent people." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2229-to-be-hopeful-in-bad-times-is-not-just-foolishly</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:42:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2229-to-be-hopeful-in-bad-times-is-not-just-foolishly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["TO BE HOPEFUL in bad times is not just foolishly romantic. It is based on the fact that human history is a history not only of cruelty, but also of compassion, sacrifice, courage, kindness.
What we choose to emphasize in this complex history will determine our lives. If we see only the worst, it destroys our capacity to do something. If we remember those times and places—and there are so many—where people have behaved magnificently, this gives us the energy to act, and at least the possibility of sending this spinning top of a world in a different direction.
And if we do act, in however small a way, we don’t have to wait for some grand utopian future. The future is an infinite succession of presents, and to live now as we think human beings should live, in defiance of all that is bad around us, is itself a marvelous victory." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4994-we-are-the-music-makers-and-we-are-the-dreamers</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:43:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Arthur William Edgar O'Shaughnessy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4994-we-are-the-music-makers-and-we-are-the-dreamers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are the music makers, and we are the dreamers of dreams." -- Arthur William Edgar O'Shaughnessy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7032-and-above-all-watch-with-glittering-eyes-the-whole-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:43:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Roald Dahl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7032-and-above-all-watch-with-glittering-eyes-the-whole-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And above all, watch with glittering eyes the whole world around you because the greatest secrets are always hidden in the most unlikely places. Those who don't believe in magic will never find it." -- Roald Dahl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:44:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to write the book that wants to be written. And if the book will be too difficult for grown-ups, then you write it for children." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5193-a-book-too-can-be-a-star-a-living-fire</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:44:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5193-a-book-too-can-be-a-star-a-living-fire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book, too, can be a star, a living fire to lighten the darkness, leading out into the expanding universe." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460-they-are-very-young-and-on-their-earth-as-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:45:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460-they-are-very-young-and-on-their-earth-as-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They are very young. And on their earth, as they call it, they never communicate with other planets. They revolve about all alone in space.&quot;
&quot;Oh,&quot; the thin beast said. &quot;Aren't they lonely?" -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 08:47:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 08:47:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 08:48:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened." -- Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919-the-man-who-does-not-read-has-no-advantage-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 08:48:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919-the-man-who-does-not-read-has-no-advantage-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who does not read has no advantage over the man who cannot read." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 08:49:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenniffer add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
