<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/229054-ash]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/229054-ash" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 08:41:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/835234-if-you-wake-up-feeling-no-pain-you-know-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 08:41:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ash add a quote by Andrew Solomon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/835234-if-you-wake-up-feeling-no-pain-you-know-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you wake up feeling no pain, you know you're dead. (Russian expression)" -- Andrew Solomon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/835236-if-you-put-your-energy-into-how-much-a-fall</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 08:43:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ash add a quote by Tana French]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/835236-if-you-put-your-energy-into-how-much-a-fall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you put your energy into how much a fall would hurt, you're already half way down." -- Tana French]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/835240-there-are-fights-that-you-may-lose-without-losing-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 08:49:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ash add a quote by Robert M. Edsel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/835240-there-are-fights-that-you-may-lose-without-losing-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are fights that you may lose without losing your honor; what makes you lose your honor is not to fight.
-Jaques Jaujard" -- Robert M. Edsel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215518-i-am-not-good-at-noticing-when-i-m-happy-except</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 12:18:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ash add a quote by Tana French]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215518-i-am-not-good-at-noticing-when-i-m-happy-except]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am not good at noticing when I'm happy, except in retrospect." -- Tana French]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916804-my-childhood-is-streets-upon-streets-upon-streets-upon-streets</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 11:15:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ash add a quote by Morrissey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916804-my-childhood-is-streets-upon-streets-upon-streets-upon-streets]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My childhood is streets upon streets upon streets upon streets. Streets to define you and streets to confine you, with no sign of motorway, freeway or highway." -- Morrissey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/890291-you-want-to-know-what-i-really-learned-i-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 10:32:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ash add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/890291-you-want-to-know-what-i-really-learned-i-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You want to know what I really learned? I learned that people don’t consider time alone as part of their life. Being alone is just a stretch of isolation they want to escape from. I saw a lot of wine-drinking, a lot of compulsive drug use, a lot of sleeping with the television on. It was less festive than I anticipated. My view had always been that I was my most alive when I was totally alone, because that was the only time I could live without fear of how my actions were being scrutinized and interpreted. What I came to realize is that people need their actions to be scrutinized and interpreted in order to feel like what they’re doing matters. Singular, solitary moments are like television pilots that never get aired. They don’t count. This, I think, explains the fundamental urge to get married and have kids[…]. We’re self-conditioned to require an audience, even if we’re not doing anything valuable or interesting. I’m sure this started in the 1970s. I know it did. I think Americans started raising offspring with this implicit notion that they had to tell their children, “You’re amazing, you can do anything you want, you’re a special person.” [...] But—when you really think about it—that emotional support only applies to the experience of living in public. We don’t have ways to quantify ideas like “amazing” or “successful” or “lovable” without the feedback of an audience. Nobody sits by himself in an empty room and thinks, “I’m amazing.” It’s impossible to imagine how that would work. But being “amazing” is supposed to be what life is about. As a result, the windows of time people spend by themselves become these meaningless experiences that don’t really count. It’s filler." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/914114-better-to-be-at-the-bottom-of-a-ladder-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 07:06:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ash add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/914114-better-to-be-at-the-bottom-of-a-ladder-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Better to be at the bottom of a ladder you want to climb than in the middle of some ladder you don’t, right?" -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/936946-the-abyss-in-which-i-live-hasn-t-the-wit-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 08:16:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ash add a quote by Morrissey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/936946-the-abyss-in-which-i-live-hasn-t-the-wit-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The abyss in which I live hasn't the wit to save itself from savage ignorance, and I now feel assured that I am not in the company of my own species (at least, I &lt;i&gt;hope&lt;/i&gt; I am not, for it I am, then I am &lt;i&gt;they&lt;/i&gt;). Dear God, let time pass quickly, and let this end. Let me be older and let this mediocrity pass as a dream - one in which the utmost was done to bury me alive." -- Morrissey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361190-a-rowboat-without-oars-an-outboard-motor-as-you-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 09:34:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ash add a quote by Renata Adler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361190-a-rowboat-without-oars-an-outboard-motor-as-you-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A rowboat, without oars. An outboard motor. As you can sit there for years, forever, with that outboard motor, pulling again, and yet again, that rope, or cord, or wire, or whatever it is, and winding yet again, and each time, every single time, the motor, though it may give a cough or two, will fail to start, though if it starts, and when it starts, you are, at whatever speed you choose, within the engine's limits and the hazards of the course, well on your way, &lt;i&gt;until&lt;/i&gt; it starts you are no nearer where you were going on the fifteenth try than on the first; the enterprise may last forever, and never yet quite begin. The fact seems to be, however, that unless some apparently unrelated event should intervene -- a bullet, a heart attack, a cry from shore that dinner's ready, or company has come, or junior's run away -- the engine will eventually start. In the meantime, though, while you have been intensely busy, it is difficult to account for how the time is spent." -- Renata Adler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1067200-camilla-you-sir-should-unmask-stranger-indeed-cassilda-indeed-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 10:14:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ash add a quote by Robert W. Chambers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1067200-camilla-you-sir-should-unmask-stranger-indeed-cassilda-indeed-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Camilla: You, sir, should unmask. Stranger: Indeed? Cassilda: Indeed it’s time. We all have laid aside disguise but you. Stranger: I wear no mask. Camilla: (Terrified, aside to Cassilda.) No mask? No mask! The King in Yellow, Act I, Scene 2." -- Robert W. Chambers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1079066-let-the-red-dawn-surmise-what-we-shall-do-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 10:20:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ash add a quote by Bliss Carman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1079066-let-the-red-dawn-surmise-what-we-shall-do-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let the red dawn surmise
What we shall do,
When this blue starlight dies
And all is through.
If we have loved but well
Under the sun,
Let the last morrow tell
What we have done." -- Bliss Carman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1249547-isn-t-this-what-we-also-fear-and-crave-simultaneously-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 19:01:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ash add a quote by Chang-rae Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1249547-isn-t-this-what-we-also-fear-and-crave-simultaneously-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...isn't this what we also fear and crave simultaneously, that some internal force which defies understanding might remake us into the people we dream we are?" -- Chang-rae Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
