<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/231004-chrissy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/231004-chrissy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 19:12:58 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/349942-she-remembered-one-of-her-boyfriends-asking-offhandedly-how-many</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 19:12:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chrissy add a quote by Eleanor Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/349942-she-remembered-one-of-her-boyfriends-asking-offhandedly-how-many]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She remembered one of her boyfriends asking, offhandedly, how many books she read in a year. &quot;A few hundred,&quot; she said.
&quot;How do you have the time?&quot; he asked, gobsmacked.
She narrowed her eyes and considered the array of potential answers in front of her. Because I don't spend hours flipping through cable complaining there's nothing on? Because my entire Sunday is not eaten up with pre-game, in-game, and post-game talking heads? Because I do not spend every night drinking overpriced beer and engaging in dick-swinging contests with the other financirati? Because when I am waiting in line, at the gym, on the train, eating lunch, I am not complaining about the wait/staring into space/admiring myself in reflective surfaces? I am reading!
&quot;I don't know,&quot; she said, shrugging." -- Eleanor Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/347724-there-are-times-in-our-lives-when-we-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 19:13:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chrissy add a quote by Eleanor Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/347724-there-are-times-in-our-lives-when-we-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are times in our lives when we have to realize our past is precisely what it is, and we cannot change it. But we can change the story we tell ourselves about it, and by doing that, we can change the future." -- Eleanor Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/336140-this-conversation-you-will-not-be-surprised-to-know-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 19:13:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chrissy add a quote by Eleanor Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/336140-this-conversation-you-will-not-be-surprised-to-know-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This conversation, you will not be surprised to know, was the impetus for their breakup, given that it caused her to realize the emotion that she had thought was her not liking him very much was, in fact, her not liking him at all.  Because despite his money and his looks and all the good-on-paper attributes he possessed, he was not a reader, and, well, let's just say that is the sort of nonsense up with which we will not put." -- Eleanor Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
