<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/231176-kevin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/231176-kevin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 15:06:58 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/936-study-hard-what-interests-you-the-most-in-the-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 15:06:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by Richard Feynmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/936-study-hard-what-interests-you-the-most-in-the-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Study hard what interests you the most in the most undisciplined, irreverent and original manner possible." -- Richard Feynmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9421-and-thus-i-clothe-my-naked-villainy-with-odd-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 13:04:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9421-and-thus-i-clothe-my-naked-villainy-with-odd-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And thus I clothe my naked villainy
With odd old ends stol'n out of holy writ;
And seem a saint, when most I play the devil." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/452329-now-is-the-winter-of-our-discontent-made-glorious-summer</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 13:05:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/452329-now-is-the-winter-of-our-discontent-made-glorious-summer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now is the winter of our discontent
Made glorious summer by this sun of York;
And all the clouds that lour'd upon our house
In the deep bosom of the ocean buried." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/379174-why-i-can-smile-and-murder-whiles-i-smile-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 13:05:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/379174-why-i-can-smile-and-murder-whiles-i-smile-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why, I can smile and murder whiles I smile,
And cry 'content' to that which grieves my heart,
And wet my cheeks with artificial tears,
And frame my face for all occasions" -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325360-no-beast-so-fierce-but-knows-some-touch-of-pity</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 13:05:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325360-no-beast-so-fierce-but-knows-some-touch-of-pity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No beast so fierce but knows some touch of pity. But I know none, and therefore am no beast." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/570963-what-do-i-fear-myself-there-s-none-else-by-richard</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 13:06:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/570963-what-do-i-fear-myself-there-s-none-else-by-richard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What do I fear? Myself? There’s none else by.
Richard loves Richard; that is, I and I.
Is there a murderer here? No. Yes, I am.
Then fly! What, from myself? Great reason why:
Lest I revenge. What, myself upon myself?
Alack, I love myself. Wherefore? For any good
That I myself have done unto myself?
O, no! Alas, I rather hate myself
For hateful deeds committed by myself.
I am a villain. Yet I lie. I am not.
Fool, of thyself speak well. Fool, do not flatter:
My conscience hath a thousand several tongues,
And every tongue brings in a several tale,
And every tale condemns me for a villain.
Perjury, perjury, in the highest degree;
Murder, stern murder, in the direst degree;
All several sins, all used in each degree,
Throng to the bar, crying all, “Guilty! guilty!”
I shall despair. There is no creature loves me,
And if I die no soul will pity me.
And wherefore should they, since that I myself
Find in myself no pity to myself?" -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/539585-i-will-come-back-to-you-i-swear-i-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2013 21:41:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by Edna St. Vincent Millay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/539585-i-will-come-back-to-you-i-swear-i-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will come back to you, I swear I will;
And you will know me still.
I shall be only a little taller
Than when I went." -- Edna St. Vincent Millay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84169-anxiety-is-love-s-greatest-killer-it-makes-others-feel-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 22:21:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84169-anxiety-is-love-s-greatest-killer-it-makes-others-feel-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anxiety is love's greatest killer. It makes others feel as you might when a drowning man holds on to you. You want to save him, but you know he will strangle you with his panic." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189542-it-did-what-all-ads-are-supposed-to-do-create</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 22:21:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189542-it-did-what-all-ads-are-supposed-to-do-create]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It did what all ads are supposed to do: create an anxiety relievable by purchase." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230446-the-acceptance-of-oneself-is-the-essence-of-the-whole</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 22:21:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by C.G. Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230446-the-acceptance-of-oneself-is-the-essence-of-the-whole]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The acceptance of oneself is the essence of the whole moral problem and the epitome of a whole outlook on life.  That I feed the hungry, that I forgive an insult, that I love my enemy in the name of Christ -- all these are undoubtedly great virtues.  What I do unto the least of my brethren, that I do unto Christ.  But what if I should discover that the least among them all, the poorest of all the beggars, the most impudent of all the offenders, the very enemy himself -- that these are within me, and that I myself stand in need of the alms of my own kindness -- that I myself am the enemy who must be loved -- what then?  As a rule, the Christian's attitude is then reversed; there is no longer any question of love or long-suffering; we say to the brother within us &quot;Raca,&quot; and condemn and rage against ourselves.  We hide it from the world; we refuse to admit ever having met this least among the lowly in ourselves." -- C.G. Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138054-to-venture-causes-anxiety-but-not-to-venture-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 22:22:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138054-to-venture-causes-anxiety-but-not-to-venture-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To venture causes anxiety, but not to venture is to lose one's self.... And to venture in the highest is precisely to be conscious of one's self." -- Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113808-man-is-not-worried-by-real-problems-so-much-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 22:22:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by Epictetus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113808-man-is-not-worried-by-real-problems-so-much-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man is not worried by real problems so much as by his imagined anxieties about real problems" -- Epictetus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18485-anxiety-is-the-dizziness-of-freedom</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 22:22:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by Søren Kierkegaard ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18485-anxiety-is-the-dizziness-of-freedom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anxiety is the dizziness of freedom." -- Søren Kierkegaard ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217049-the-writer-umberto-eco-belongs-to-that-small-class-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 09:42:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by Nassim Nicholas Taleb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217049-the-writer-umberto-eco-belongs-to-that-small-class-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The writer Umberto Eco belongs to that small class of scholars who are encyclopedic, insightful, and nondull. He is the owner of a large personal library (containing thirty thousand books), and separates visitors into two categories: those who react with “Wow! Signore, professore dottore Eco, what a library you have ! How many of these books have you read?” and the others - a very small minority - who get the point that a private library is not an ego-boosting appendage but a research tool. Read books are far less valuable than unread ones. The library should contain as much of what you don’t know as your financial means, mortgage rates and the currently tight real-estate market allows you to put there. You will accumulate more knowledge and more books as you grow older, and the growing number of unread books on the shelves will look at you menancingly. Indeed, the more you know, the larger the rows of unread books. Let us call this collection of unread books an antilibrary." -- Nassim Nicholas Taleb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110518-if-at-first-the-idea-is-not-absurd-then-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 09:42:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110518-if-at-first-the-idea-is-not-absurd-then-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If at first the idea is not absurd, then there is no hope for it." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/906734-we-should-not-expect-individuals-to-produce-good-open-minded-truth-seeking</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 20:36:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by Jonathan Haidt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/906734-we-should-not-expect-individuals-to-produce-good-open-minded-truth-seeking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We should not expect individuals to produce good, open-minded, truth-seeking reasoning, particularly when self-interest or reputational concerns are in play. But if you put individuals together in the right way, such that some individuals can use their reasoning powers to disconfirm the claims of others, and all individuals feel some common bond or shared fate that allows them to interact civilly, you can create a group that ends up producing good reasoning as an emergent property of the social system. This is why it's so important to have intellectual and ideological diversity within any group or institution whose goal is to find truth (such as an intelligence agency or a community of scientists) or to produce good public policy (such as a legislature or advisory board)." -- Jonathan Haidt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878564-understanding-the-simple-fact-that-morality-differs-around-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 20:37:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by Jonathan Haidt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878564-understanding-the-simple-fact-that-morality-differs-around-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Understanding the simple fact that morality differs around the world, and even within societies, is the first step toward understanding your righteous mind." -- Jonathan Haidt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1144831-do-people-believe-in-human-rights-because-such-rights-actually</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 20:37:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by Jonathan Haidt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1144831-do-people-believe-in-human-rights-because-such-rights-actually]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do people believe in human rights because such rights actually exist, like mathematical truths, sitting on a cosmic shelf next to the Pythagorean theorem just waiting to be discovered by Platonic reasoners? Or do people feel revulsion and sympathy when they read accounts of torture, and then invent a story about universal rights to help justify their feelings?" -- Jonathan Haidt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1231560-schwitzgebel-even-scrounged-up-the-missing-book-lists-from-dozens-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 20:37:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by Jonathan Haidt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1231560-schwitzgebel-even-scrounged-up-the-missing-book-lists-from-dozens-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Schwitzgebel even scrounged up the missing-book lists from dozens of libraries and found that academic books on ethics, which are presumably borrowed mostly by ethicists, are more likely to be stolen or just never returned than books in other areas of philosophy.49 In other words, expertise in moral reasoning does not seem to improve moral behavior, and it might even make it worse (perhaps by making the rider more skilled at post hoc justification)." -- Jonathan Haidt]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
