<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/231809-vahid]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/231809-vahid" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2008 23:08:51 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30432-he-stumbled-almost-fell-and-decided-to-sit-down-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2008 23:08:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vahid add a quote by Jeff VanderMeer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30432-he-stumbled-almost-fell-and-decided-to-sit-down-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He stumbled, almost fell, and decided to sit down, with his back against the tunnel wall, his feet resting against the opposite wall.  Roaring out of the morass of pity, terror, happiness, joy, sadness, elation that he had inherited - shooting forth from this void, the single sharp thought: She does not love me.  It was almost more than he could take.  But he was not the kind of person to fold, to crack, to be broken, and so instead, in those moments after the realization, he bent - and bent, and kept on bending beneath the pressure of this new and terrible knowledge.  Soon he would bend into a totally new shape altogether.  He welcomed that.  He wanted that.  Maybe the new thing he would become would no longer hurt, would no longer fear, would no longer look back down into the void and wonder what was left of him.

She did not love him.  It made him laugh as he sat there -- great belly laughs that doubled him over in the dust, where he lay for a long moment, recovering.  It was funny beyond bearing.  He had fought through a dozen terrors all for love of her.  And she did not love him.  He felt like a character in a holovid - the jester, the clown, the fool." -- Jeff VanderMeer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102567-i-will-tell-you-the-deeper-significance-of-this-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 18:15:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vahid add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102567-i-will-tell-you-the-deeper-significance-of-this-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will tell you the deeper significance of this, which otherwise might seem a banal hydraulic joke. Caus knew that if one fills a vessel with water and seals it at the top, the water, even if one then opens a hole in the bottom, will not come out.  But if one opens a hole in the top, also, the water spurts out below.&quot;
  &quot;Isn't that obvious?&quot; I said. &quot;Air enters at the top and presses the water down.&quot;
  &quot;A typical scientific explanation, in which the cause is mistaken for the effect, or vice versa.  The question is not why the water comes out in the second place, but why it refuses to come out in the first case.&quot;
  &quot;And why does it refuse?&quot; Garamond asked eagerly.
  &quot;Because, if it came out, it would leave a vacuum in the vessel, and nature abhors a vacuum.  Nequaquam vacui was a Rosicrucian principle, which modern science has forgotten.&quot;
  &quot;Excuse me,&quot; Belbo said to Agliè, &quot;but your argument is simply post hoc ergo ante hoc.  What follows causes what came before.
You must not think linearly.  The water in these fountains doesn't. Nature doesn't; nature knows nothing of time.  Time is an invention of the West." -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/704802-over-the-years-i-ve-made-good-money-in-real-estate</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 06:25:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vahid add a quote by Wells Tower]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/704802-over-the-years-i-ve-made-good-money-in-real-estate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Over the years, I've made good money in real estate, and for some reason, this hurts Stephen's feelings.  He's not a churchman, but he's extremely big on piety and sacrifice and letting you know what fine values he's got.  As far as I can tell, these values consist of little more than eating ramen noodles by the case, getting laid once every fifteen years or so, and arching his back at the sight of people like me -- that is, people who have amounted to something and don't smell heavily of thrift stores." -- Wells Tower]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/704806-it-didn-t-make-much-sense-to-me-then-what-gnut</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 06:29:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vahid add a quote by Wells Tower]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/704806-it-didn-t-make-much-sense-to-me-then-what-gnut]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It didn't make much sense to me then, what Gnut was going through, but after Pila and me had our little twins, and we put a family together, I got an understanding of how terrible love can be.  You wish you hated those people, your wife and children, because you know the things the world will do to them, because you have done some of those things yourself.  It's crazy-making, yet you cling to them with everything and close your eyes against the rest of it.   But still you wake up late at night and lie there listening for the creak and splash of oars, the clank of steel, the sounds of men rowing toward your home." -- Wells Tower]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
