<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/231803-allison]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/231803-allison" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 21:35:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 21:35:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1958-whenever-i-feel-the-need-to-exercise-i-lie-down</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 21:58:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Paul   Terry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1958-whenever-i-feel-the-need-to-exercise-i-lie-down]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever I feel the need to exercise, I lie down until it goes away." -- Paul   Terry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 21:58:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The person, be it gentleman or lady, who has not pleasure in a good novel, must be intolerably stupid." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 22:10:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a soul, Doctor. You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; a soul. You &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a body, temporarily." -- Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 22:11:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100726-and-the-crazy-part-of-it-was-even-if-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 22:22:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Erica Jong]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100726-and-the-crazy-part-of-it-was-even-if-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the crazy part of it was even if you were clever, even if you spent your adolescence reading John Donne and Shaw, even if you studied history or zoology or physics and hoped to spend your life pursuing some difficult and challenging career, you still had a mind full of all the soupy longings that every high-school girl was awash in... underneath it, all you longed to be was annihilated by love, to be swept off your feet, to be filled up by a giant prick spouting sperm, soapsuds, silk and satins and, of course, money." -- Erica Jong]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6452-i-wanna-hold-your-hand-first-single-fucking-brilliant-perhaps</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 22:45:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Rachel Cohn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6452-i-wanna-hold-your-hand-first-single-fucking-brilliant-perhaps]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I Wanna Hold Your Hand.’ First single. Fucking brilliant. Perhaps the most fucking brilliant song ever written. Because they nailed it. That’s what everyone wants. Not 24-7 hot wet sex. Not a marriage that lasts a hundred years. Not a Porsche or a blow job or a million-dollar crib. No. They wanna hold your hand. They have a feeling that they can’t hide." -- Rachel Cohn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35446-what-about-little-microphones-what-if-everyone-swallowed-them-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2009 06:21:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35446-what-about-little-microphones-what-if-everyone-swallowed-them-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What about little microphones? What if everyone swallowed them, and they played the sounds of our hearts through little speakers, which could be in the pouches of our overalls? When you skateboarded down the street at night you could hear everyone's heartbeat, and they could hear yours, sort of like sonar. One weird thing is, I wonder if everyone's hearts would start to beat at the same time, like how women who live together have their menstrual periods at the same time, which I know about, but don't really want to know about. That would be so weird, except that the place in the hospital where babies are born would sound like a crystal chandelier in a houseboat, because the babies wouldn't have had time to match up their heartbeats yet. And at the finish line at the end of the New York City Marathon it would sound like war." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56677-do-you-think-i-m-wonderful-she-asked-him-one-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2010 09:11:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56677-do-you-think-i-m-wonderful-she-asked-him-one-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you think I'm wonderful?  she asked him one day as they leaned against the trunk of a petrified maple.  No, he said.  Why?  Because so many girls are wonderful.  I imagine hundreds of men have called their loves wonderful today, and it's only noon.  You couldn't be something that hundreds of others are." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
