<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/232642-amy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/232642-amy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 11:29:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152137-on-more-than-one-occasion-i-have-been-ready-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 11:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152137-on-more-than-one-occasion-i-have-been-ready-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On more than one occasion I have been ready to abandon my whole life for love. To alter everything that makes sense to me and to move into a different world where the only known will be the beloved. Such a sacrifice must be the result of love... or is it that the life itself was already worn out? I had finished with that life, perhaps, and could not admit it, being stubborn or afraid, or perhaps did not known it, habit being a great binder. I think it is often so that those most in need of change choose to fall in love and then throw up their hands and blame it all on fate. But it is not fate, at least, not if fate is something outside of us; it is a choice made in secret after nights of longing.
... I may be cynical when I say that very rarely is the beloved more than a shaping spirit for the lover's dreams... To be a muse may be enough. The pain is when the dreams change, as they do, as they must. Suddenly the enchanted city fades and you are left alone again in the windy desert. As for your beloved, she didn't understand you.
The truth is, you never understood yourself." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152135-a-curse-on-this-game-how-can-you-stick-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 11:27:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152135-a-curse-on-this-game-how-can-you-stick-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A curse on this game. How can you stick at a game when the rules keep on changing? I shall call myself Alice and play croquet with the flamingos. In Wonderland everyone cheats and love is Wonderland, isn't it? " -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70739-ours-is-essentially-a-tragic-age-so-we-refuse-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 11:30:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70739-ours-is-essentially-a-tragic-age-so-we-refuse-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ours is essentially a tragic age, so we refuse to take it tragically. The cataclysm has happened, we are among the ruins, we start to build up new little habitats, to have new little hopes. It is rather hard work: there is now no smooth road into the future: but we go round, or scramble over the obstacles. We’ve got to live, no matter how many skies have fallen." -- D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/489023-i-did-it-to-win-love-and-to-prove-myself</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 13:18:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/489023-i-did-it-to-win-love-and-to-prove-myself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I did it to win love, and to prove myself capable.  Not to move mountains.  In my opinions, mountains don't move.  They only look changed when you look down on them from great height." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/489029-it-s-one-thing-to-carry-your-life-wherever-you-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 13:25:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/489029-it-s-one-thing-to-carry-your-life-wherever-you-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's one thing to carry your life wherever you go.  Another thing to always go looking for it somewhere else." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497178-strange-how-it-is-that-men-never-act-crueler-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 12:36:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Marcel Theroux]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497178-strange-how-it-is-that-men-never-act-crueler-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Strange how it is that men never act crueler than when they're fighting for the sake of an idea.  We've been killing since Cain over who stands closer to god.  It seems to me that cruelty is just in the way of things.  You drive yourself mad if you take it all personal.  Those who hurt you don't have the power over you they would like.  That's why they do what they do." -- Marcel Theroux]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497755-money-should-not-be-spent-according-to-what-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2012 13:37:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by William Easterly]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497755-money-should-not-be-spent-according-to-what-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["... money should not be spent according to what the West considers the most dramatic kind of suffering." -- William Easterly]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374641-you-force-people-to-stop-asking-questions-and-before-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 06:18:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374641-you-force-people-to-stop-asking-questions-and-before-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You force people to stop asking questions, and before you know it they have auctioned off the question mark, or sold it for scrap. No boldness. No good ideas for fixing what's broken in the land. Because if you happen to mention it's broken, you are automatically disqualified." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169307-why-is-there-ever-this-perverse-cruelty-in-humankind-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 07:48:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Jacqueline Carey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169307-why-is-there-ever-this-perverse-cruelty-in-humankind-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why is there ever this perverse cruelty in humankind, that makes us hurt most those we love best?" -- Jacqueline Carey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321402-there-are-no-wrong-turnings-only-paths-we-had-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 07:50:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Guy Gavriel Kay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321402-there-are-no-wrong-turnings-only-paths-we-had-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are no wrong turnings. Only paths we had not known we were meant to walk." -- Guy Gavriel Kay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1151391-for-god-and-nothing-have-a-lot-in-common-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 07:13:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1151391-for-god-and-nothing-have-a-lot-in-common-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For God and Nothing have a lot in common. You look either one of Them straight in the eye for a second and the immediate effect on the human constitution is the same." -- Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1152085-but-i-m-not-a-lawyer-that-s-why-i-can-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 19:47:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1152085-but-i-m-not-a-lawyer-that-s-why-i-can-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I'm not a lawyer. That's why I can see what the law is like. It's like a single-bed blanket on a double bed  and three folks on a cold night. There ain't ever enough blanket to cover the case, no matter how much pulling and hauling, and somebody is always going to nigh catch pneumonia.  Hell, the law is like the pants you bought last year for a growing boy, but it is always this year and the seams are popped and the shankbone's in the breeze. The law is always too short and too tight for growing humankind. The best you can do is do something and then  make up some law to fit and by the time that law gets on the books you would  have done something different..." -- Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
