<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/232601-theresa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/232601-theresa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 20:15:06 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106872-that-s-what-i-love-about-reading-one-tiny-thing-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 20:15:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Mary Ann Shaffer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106872-that-s-what-i-love-about-reading-one-tiny-thing-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's what I love about reading: one tiny thing will interest you in a book, and that tiny thing will lead you to another book, and another bit there will lead you onto a third book. It's geometrically progressive - all with no end in sight, and for no other reason than sheer enjoyment." -- Mary Ann Shaffer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362-if-you-don-t-stand-for-something-you-will-fall-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 20:15:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Gordon A. Eadie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362-if-you-don-t-stand-for-something-you-will-fall-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you don't stand for something you will fall for anything." -- Gordon A. Eadie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2253-live-as-if-you-were-to-die-tomorrow-learn-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 20:15:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2253-live-as-if-you-were-to-die-tomorrow-learn-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 19:10:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353-for-every-minute-you-are-angry-you-lose-sixty-seconds</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 19:11:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353-for-every-minute-you-are-angry-you-lose-sixty-seconds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For every minute you are angry you lose sixty seconds of happiness." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2203-it-is-what-you-read-when-you-don-t-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 19:11:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2203-it-is-what-you-read-when-you-don-t-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is what you read when you don't have to that determines what you will be when you can't help it." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/356-i-learned-this-at-least-by-my-experiment-that-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 19:13:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/356-i-learned-this-at-least-by-my-experiment-that-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I learned this, at least, by my experiment: that if one advances confidently in the direction of his dreams, and endeavors to live the life which he has imagined, he will meet with a success unexpected in common hours." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 19:15:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/802-in-a-good-bookroom-you-feel-in-some-mysterious-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 19:17:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/802-in-a-good-bookroom-you-feel-in-some-mysterious-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a good bookroom you feel in some mysterious way that you are absorbing the wisdom contained in all the books through your skin, without even opening them." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5647-and-when-you-want-something-all-the-universe-conspires-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 19:25:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5647-and-when-you-want-something-all-the-universe-conspires-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And, when you want something, all the universe conspires in helping you to achieve it." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1420-i-wanted-a-perfect-ending-now-i-ve-learned-the-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 19:28:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Gilda Radner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1420-i-wanted-a-perfect-ending-now-i-ve-learned-the-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted a perfect ending. Now I've learned, the hard way, that some poems don't rhyme, and some stories don't have a clear beginning, middle, and end. Life is about not knowing, having to change, taking the moment and making the best of it, without knowing what's going to happen next.
Delicious Ambiguity." -- Gilda Radner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3823-you-gain-strength-courage-and-confidence-by-every-experience-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 19:30:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3823-you-gain-strength-courage-and-confidence-by-every-experience-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You gain strength, courage and confidence by every experience in which you really stop to look fear in the face. You are able to say to yourself, 'I have lived through this horror. I can take the next thing that comes along.' You must do the thing you think you cannot do." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 19:31:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3616-i-am-nothing-special-of-this-i-am-sure-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2008 05:57:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3616-i-am-nothing-special-of-this-i-am-sure-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am nothing special, of this I am sure. I am a common man with common thoughts and I've led a common life. There are no monuments dedicated to me and my name will soon be forgotten, but I've loved another with all my heart and soul, and to me, this has always been enough.." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9529-it-may-be-unfair-but-what-happens-in-a-few</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 21:47:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9529-it-may-be-unfair-but-what-happens-in-a-few]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It may be unfair, but what happens in a few days, sometimes even a single day, can change the course of a whole lifetime..." -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 19:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be the change that you wish to see in the world." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 19:00:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 19:11:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/769-books-are-the-quietest-and-most-constant-of-friends-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 19:14:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Charles W. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/769-books-are-the-quietest-and-most-constant-of-friends-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are the quietest and most constant of friends; they are the most accessible and wisest of counselors, and the most patient of teachers." -- Charles W. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 19:14:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that's what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that is holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life.  

A true soul mate is probably the most important person you'll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake.  But to live with a soul mate forever?  Nah. Too painful.  Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then leave.  

A soul mates purpose is to shake you up, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light can get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you have to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 19:16:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think your pain and your heartbreak are unprecedented in the history of the world, but then you read. It was books that taught me that the things that tormented me most were the very things that connected me with all the people who were alive, or who had ever been alive." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6702-i-declare-after-all-there-is-no-enjoyment-like-reading</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 19:18:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6702-i-declare-after-all-there-is-no-enjoyment-like-reading]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I declare after all there is no enjoyment like reading! How much sooner one tires of any thing than of a book! -- When I have a house of my own, I shall be miserable if I have not an excellent library." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10837-happiness-is-the-consequence-of-personal-effort-you-fight-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 19:25:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10837-happiness-is-the-consequence-of-personal-effort-you-fight-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is the consequence of personal effort.  You fight for it, strive for it, insist upon it, and sometimes even travel around the world looking for it.  You have to participate relentlessly in the manifestations of your own blessings.  And once you have achieved a state of happiness, you must never become lax about maintaining it.  You must make a mighty effort to keep swimming upward into that happiness forever, to stay afloat on top of it." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24765-it-is-better-to-live-your-own-destiny-imperfectly-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 19:25:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24765-it-is-better-to-live-your-own-destiny-imperfectly-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to live your own destiny imperfectly than to live an imitation of somebody else's life with perfection." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25512-never-forget-that-once-upon-a-time-in-an-unguarded</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 19:25:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25512-never-forget-that-once-upon-a-time-in-an-unguarded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never forget that once upon a time, in an unguarded moment, you recognized yourself as a friend." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38669-there-is-so-much-about-my-fate-that-i-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 19:26:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38669-there-is-so-much-about-my-fate-that-i-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is so much about my fate that I cannot control, but other things do fall under the jurisdiction. I can decide how I spend my time, whom I interact with, whom I share my body and life and money and energy with. I can select what I can read and eat and study. I can choose how  I'm going to regard unfortunate circumstances in my life-whether I will see them as curses or opportunities. I can choose my words and the tone of voice in which I speak to others. And most of all, I can choose my thoughts." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38668-faith-is-walking-face-first-and-full-speed-into-the-dark-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 19:27:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38668-faith-is-walking-face-first-and-full-speed-into-the-dark-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Faith is walking face-first and full-speed into the dark. If we truly knew all the answers in advance as to the meaning of life and the nature of God and the destiny of our souls, our belief would not be a leap of faith and it would not be a courageous act of humanity; it would just be... a prudent insurance policy." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6289-i-am-alone-i-am-all-alone-i-am-completely</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 19:27:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6289-i-am-alone-i-am-all-alone-i-am-completely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am alone, I am all alone, I am completely alone. Grasping this reality, I let go of my bag, drop to my knees and press my forehead against the floor. There, I offer up to the universe a fervent prayer of thanks. First in English. Then in Italian. And then - just to get the point across - in Sanskrit." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14438-that-s-the-thing-about-a-human-life-there-s-no-control-group</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 19:28:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14438-that-s-the-thing-about-a-human-life-there-s-no-control-group]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That’s the thing about a human life-there’s no control group, no way to ever know how any of us would have turned out if any variables had been changed." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28145-my-guru-says-that-people-universally-tend-to-think-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 19:30:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28145-my-guru-says-that-people-universally-tend-to-think-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[My guru] says that people universally tend to think that happiness is a stroke of luck, something that will maybe descend upon you like fine weather if you are fortunate enough. But that's not how happiness works. Happiness is the consequence of personal effort. You fight for it, strive for it, insist upon it, and sometimes even travel around the world looking for it. You have to participate relentlessly in the manifestations of your own blessings. And once you have achieved a state of happiness, you must never become lax about maintaining it..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
