<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/232609-faye]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/232609-faye" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 14:00:15 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44274-people-speak-sometimes-about-the-bestial-cruelty-of-man-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 14:00:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Faye add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky  ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44274-people-speak-sometimes-about-the-bestial-cruelty-of-man-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People speak sometimes about the &quot;bestial&quot; cruelty of man, but that is terribly unjust and offensive to beasts, no animal could ever be so cruel as a man, so artfully, so artistically cruel." -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky  ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/340-the-greatness-of-a-nation-and-its-moral-progress-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 14:00:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Faye add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/340-the-greatness-of-a-nation-and-its-moral-progress-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greatness of a nation and its moral progress can be judged by the way its animals are treated." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21525-i-ask-people-why-they-have-deer-heads-on-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 14:00:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Faye add a quote by Ellen DeGeneres]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21525-i-ask-people-why-they-have-deer-heads-on-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I ask people why they have deer heads on their walls. They always say because it's such a beautiful animal. There you go. I think my mother is attractive, but I have photographs of her." -- Ellen DeGeneres]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84355-answer-me-you-who-believe-that-animals-are-only-machines</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 14:03:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Faye add a quote by Voltaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84355-answer-me-you-who-believe-that-animals-are-only-machines]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Answer me, you who believe that animals are only machines.  Has nature arranged for this animal to have all the machinery of feelings only in order for it not to have any at all?" -- Voltaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109778-the-heavenly-light-you-admire-is-fossil-light-it-s-the-unfathomably</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 15:37:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Faye add a quote by Joyce Carol Oates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109778-the-heavenly-light-you-admire-is-fossil-light-it-s-the-unfathomably]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The heavenly light you admire is fossil-light, it's the unfathomably distant past you gaze into, stars long extinct" -- Joyce Carol Oates]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50497-the-strangeness-of-time-not-in-its-passing-which-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 15:37:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Faye add a quote by Joyce Carol Oates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50497-the-strangeness-of-time-not-in-its-passing-which-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The strangeness of Time.  Not in its passing, which can seem infinite, like a tunnel whose end you can't see, whose beginning you've forgotten, but in the sudden realization that something finite, has passed, and is irretrievable." -- Joyce Carol Oates]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244303-i-can-explain-myself-if-you-want-to-be-safe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2013 12:34:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Faye add a quote by Emilie Autumn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244303-i-can-explain-myself-if-you-want-to-be-safe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can explain myself: If you want to be safe, walk in the middle of the street. I’m not joking. You’ve been told to look both ways before crossing the street, and the sidewalk is your friend, right? Wrong. I’ve spent years walking sidewalks at night. I’ve looked around me when it was dark, when there were men following me, creeping out of alleyways, attempting to goad me into speaking to them and shouting obscenities at me when I wouldn’t, and I suddenly realised that the only place left to go was the middle of street. But why would I risk it? Because the odds are in my favour. In the States, someone is killed in a car accident on average every 12.5 minutes, while someone is raped on average every 2.5 minutes. Even when factoring in that, one, I am generously including ALL car-related accidents and not just those involving accidents, and two, that the vast majorities of rapes still go unreported […] And, thus, this is now the way I live my life: out in the open, in the middle of everything, because the middle of the street is actually the safest place to walk." -- Emilie Autumn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460599-what-to-the-american-slave-is-your-fourth-of-july</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2013 09:28:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Faye add a quote by Frederick Douglass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460599-what-to-the-american-slave-is-your-fourth-of-july]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What, to the American slave, is your Fourth of July?

I answer: a day that reveals to him, more than all other days in the year, the gross injustice and cruelty to which he is the constant victim. To him, your celebration is a sham; your boasted liberty, an unholy license; your national greatness, swelling vanity; your sounds of rejoicing are empty and heartless; your denunciation of tyrants, brass-fronted impudence; your shouts of liberty and equality, hollow mockery; your prayers and hymns, your sermons and thanksgivings, with all your religious parade and solemnity, mere bombast, fraud, deception, impiety, and hypocrisy-a thin veil to cover up crimes which would disgrace a nation of savages." -- Frederick Douglass]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
