<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/232723-jami]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/232723-jami" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 22:41:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57738-each-contact-with-a-human-being-is-so-rare-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 22:41:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jami add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57738-each-contact-with-a-human-being-is-so-rare-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each contact with a human being is so rare, so precious, one should preserve it." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2012 20:43:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jami add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love never dies a natural death. It dies because we don't know how to replenish its source. It dies of blindness and errors and betrayals. It dies of illness and wounds; it dies of weariness, of witherings, of tarnishings." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18875-it-is-not-the-strongest-of-the-species-that-survives</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 09:21:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jami add a quote by Leon C. Megginson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18875-it-is-not-the-strongest-of-the-species-that-survives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not the strongest of the species that survives, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change." -- Leon C. Megginson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/285665-you-cannot-save-people-you-can-only-love-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 00:15:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jami add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/285665-you-cannot-save-people-you-can-only-love-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You cannot save people. You can only love them." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 00:22:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jami add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411956-was-not-hypatia-the-greatest-philosopher-of-alexandria-and-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 14:30:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jami add a quote by Iain Pears]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411956-was-not-hypatia-the-greatest-philosopher-of-alexandria-and-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Was not Hypatia the greatest philosopher of Alexandria, and a true martyr to the old values of learning?  She was torn to pieces by a mob of incensed Christians not because she was a woman, but because her learning was so profound, her skills at dialectic so extensive that she reduced all who queried her to embarrassed silence.  They could not argue with her, so they murdered her." -- Iain Pears]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/359880-think-of-an-experience-from-your-childhood-something-you-remember</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 01:42:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jami add a quote by Richard Dawkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/359880-think-of-an-experience-from-your-childhood-something-you-remember]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Think of an experience from your childhood. Something you remember clearly, something you can see, feel, maybe even smell, as if you were really there. After all you really were there at the time, weren’t you?
How else could you remember it? But here is the bombshell: you weren’t there. Not a single atom that is in your body today was there when that event took place .... Matter flows from place to place and momentarily comes together to be you. Whatever you are, therefore, you are not the stuff of which you are made. If that does not make the hair stand up on the back of your neck, read it again until it does, because it is important." -- Richard Dawkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/668006-the-idea-that-the-creative-endeavor-and-mind-altering-substances-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 12:52:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jami add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/668006-the-idea-that-the-creative-endeavor-and-mind-altering-substances-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The idea that the creative endeavor and mind-altering substances are entwined is one of the great pop-intellectual myths of our time. ... Substance abusing writers are just substance abusers — common garden variety drunks and druggies, in other words. Any claims that the drugs and alcohol are necessary to dull a finer sensibility are just the usual self-serving bullshit. I've heard alcoholic snowplow drivers make the same claim, that they drink to still the demons." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118694-the-secret-of-joy-is-the-mastery-of-pain</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 16:37:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jami add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118694-the-secret-of-joy-is-the-mastery-of-pain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The secret of joy is the mastery of pain." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145140-a-book-is-made-from-a-tree-it-is-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 07:55:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jami add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145140-a-book-is-made-from-a-tree-it-is-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book is made from a tree. It is an assemblage of flat, flexible parts (still called &quot;leaves&quot;) imprinted with dark pigmented squiggles. One glance at it and you hear the voice of another person, perhaps someone dead for thousands of years. Across the millennia, the author is speaking, clearly and silently, inside your head, directly to you. Writing is perhaps the greatest of human inventions, binding together people, citizens of distant epochs, who never knew one another. Books break the shackles of time ― proof that humans can work magic." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2021-do-not-be-too-moral-you-may-cheat-yourself-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 00:03:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jami add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2021-do-not-be-too-moral-you-may-cheat-yourself-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not be too moral. You may cheat yourself out of much life so. Aim above morality. Be not simply good, be good for something." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50588-you-must-live-in-the-present-launch-yourself-on-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 00:03:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jami add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50588-you-must-live-in-the-present-launch-yourself-on-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must live in the present, launch yourself on every wave, find your eternity in each moment. Fools stand on their island of opportunities and look toward another land. There is no other land; there is no other life but this." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
