<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/234474-suzanne]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/234474-suzanne" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 06:15:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35482-and-i-asked-myself-about-the-present-how-wide-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 06:15:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35482-and-i-asked-myself-about-the-present-how-wide-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I asked myself about the present: how wide it was, how deep it was, how much was mine to keep." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5169-what-really-knocks-me-out-is-a-book-that-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 08:53:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5169-what-really-knocks-me-out-is-a-book-that-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What really knocks me out is a book that, when you're all done reading it, you wish the author that wrote it was a terrific friend of yours and you could call him up on the phone whenever you felt like it. That doesn't happen much, though." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 02:48:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes fate is like a small sandstorm that keeps changing directions. You change direction but the sandstorm chases you. You turn again, but the storm adjusts. Over and over you play this out, like some ominous dance with death just before dawn. Why? Because this storm isn't something that blew in from far away, something that has nothing to do with you. This storm is you. Something &lt;i&gt;inside&lt;/i&gt; of you. So all you can do is give in to it, step right inside the storm, closing your eyes and plugging up your ears so the sand doesn't get in, and walk through it, step by step. There's no sun there, no moon, no direction, no sense of time. Just fine white sand swirling up into the sky like pulverized bones. That's the kind of sandstorm you need to imagine.

An you really will have to make it through that violent, metaphysical, symbolic storm. No matter how metaphysical or symbolic it might be, make no mistake about it: it will cut through flesh like a thousand razor blades. People will bleed there, and &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; will bleed too. Hot, red blood. You'll catch that blood in your hands, your own blood and the blood of others.

And once the storm is over you won't remember how you made it through, how you managed to survive. You won't even be sure, in fact, whether the storm is really over. But one thing is certain. When you come out of the storm you won't be the same person who walked in. That's what this storm's all about." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232529-i-think-that-one-of-these-days-he-said-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 08:53:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232529-i-think-that-one-of-these-days-he-said-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think that one of these days,&quot; he said, &quot;you're going to have to find out where you want to go. And then you've got to start going there. But immediately. You can't afford to lose a minute. Not you." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2355-people-are-afraid-to-merge-on-freeways-in-los-angeles</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 08:54:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2355-people-are-afraid-to-merge-on-freeways-in-los-angeles]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People are afraid to merge on freeways in Los Angeles. This is the first thing I hear when I come back to the city. Blair picks me up from LAX and mutters this under her breath as she drives up the onramp. She says, &quot;People are afraid to merge on freeways in Los Angeles.&quot; Though that sentence shouldn't bother me, it stays in my mind for an uncomfortably long time. Nothing else seems to matter. Not the fact that I'm eighteen and it's December and the ride on the plane had been rough and the couple from Santa Barbara, who were sitting across from me in first class, had gotten pretty drunk. Not the mud that had splattered on the legs of my jeans, which felt kind of cold and loose, earlier that day at an airport in  New Hampshire. Not the stain on the arm of the wrinkled, damp shirt I wear, a shirt which looked fresh and clean this morning. Not the tear on the neck of my gray argyle vest, which seems vaguely more eastern than before, especially next to Blair's clean tight jeans and her pale-blue shirt. All of this seems irrelevant next to that one sentence. It seems easier to hear that people are afraid to merge than &quot;I'm pretty sure Muriel is anorexic&quot; or the singer on the radio crying out about magnetic waves. Nothing else seems to matter to me but those ten words. Not the warm winds, which seem to propel the car down the empty asphalt freeway, or the faded smell of marijuana which still faintly permeates Blaire's car. All it comes down to is the fact that I'm a boy coming home for a month and meeting someone whom I haven't seen for four months and people are afraid to merge." -- Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2058-there-is-no-friend-as-loyal-as-a-book</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 08:54:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2058-there-is-no-friend-as-loyal-as-a-book]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no friend as loyal as a book." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13299-i-was-born-lost-and-take-no-pleasure-in-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 08:54:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13299-i-was-born-lost-and-take-no-pleasure-in-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was born lost and take no pleasure in being found." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12483-all-good-books-are-alike-in-that-they-are-truer</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 08:54:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Ernest Hemingway ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12483-all-good-books-are-alike-in-that-they-are-truer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All good books are alike in that they are truer than if they had really happened and after you are finished reading one you will feel that all that happened to you and afterwards it all belongs to you: the good and the bad, the ecstasy, the remorse and sorrow, the people and the places and how the weather was. If you can get so that you can give that to people, then you are a writer." -- Ernest Hemingway ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66336-pain-and-suffering-are-always-inevitable-for-a-large-intelligence</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 08:54:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66336-pain-and-suffering-are-always-inevitable-for-a-large-intelligence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pain and suffering are always inevitable for a large intelligence and a deep heart. The really great men must, I think, have great sadness on earth." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222128-disappear-here</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 08:54:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222128-disappear-here]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Disappear here" -- Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22092-i-have-always-lived-violently-drunk-hugely-eaten-too-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 02:15:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22092-i-have-always-lived-violently-drunk-hugely-eaten-too-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always lived violently, drunk hugely, eaten too much or not at all, slept around the clock or missed two nights of sleeping, worked too hard and too long in glory, or slobbed for a time in utter laziness. I've lifted, pulled, chopped, climbed, made love with joy and taken my hangovers as a consequence, not as a punishment." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/397-there-is-no-flag-large-enough-to-cover-the-shame</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 02:15:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/397-there-is-no-flag-large-enough-to-cover-the-shame]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no flag large enough to cover the shame of killing innocent people." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251780-so-many-people-live-within-unhappy-circumstances-and-yet-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 02:15:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251780-so-many-people-live-within-unhappy-circumstances-and-yet-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many people live within unhappy circumstances and yet will not take the initiative to change their situation because they are conditioned to a life of security, conformity, and conservatism, all of which may appear to give one peace of mind, but in reality nothing is more dangerous to the adventurous spirit within a man than a secure future. The very basic core of a man’s living spirit is his passion for adventure. The joy of life comes from our encounters with new experiences, and hence there is no greater joy than to have an endlessly changing horizon, for each day to have a new and different sun." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18782-most-men-are-a-little-better-than-their-circumstances-give</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 02:15:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18782-most-men-are-a-little-better-than-their-circumstances-give]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most men are a little better than their circumstances give them a chance to be." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180558-trippers-and-askers-surround-me-people-i-meet-the-effect</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 02:15:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180558-trippers-and-askers-surround-me-people-i-meet-the-effect]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Trippers and askers  surround me,
People I meet.... the effect upon me of my early life.....
        of the ward and city I live in....of the nation,
The latest news....discoveries, inventions, societies....
        authors old and new,
My dinner, dress, associates, looks, business, compliments,
        dues,
The real or fancified indifference of some man or woman
         I love,
The sickness of one of my folks- or of myself....or
         ill-doing....or loss or lack of money....or
         depressions or exaltations,
They come to me days and nights and go from me again,
But they are not the Me myself." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209234-i-celebrate-myself-and-sing-myself-and-what-i-assume</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 02:15:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209234-i-celebrate-myself-and-sing-myself-and-what-i-assume]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I celebrate myself, and sing myself, 
And what I assume you shall assume,
For every atom belonging to me as good belongs to you." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6145-he-who-controls-the-past-controls-the-future-he-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 06:15:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6145-he-who-controls-the-past-controls-the-future-he-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He who controls the past controls the future. He who controls the present controls the past." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37505-it-s-everybody-i-mean-everything-everybody-does-is-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 06:15:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37505-it-s-everybody-i-mean-everything-everybody-does-is-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's everybody, I mean. Everything everybody does is so — I don't know — not wrong, or even mean, or even stupid necessarily. But just so tiny and meaningless and — sad-making. And the worst part is, if you go bohemian or something crazy like that, you're conforming just as much only in a different way." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22842-you-have-brains-in-your-head-you-have-feet-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2014 03:25:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22842-you-have-brains-in-your-head-you-have-feet-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have brains in your head. You have feet in your shoes. You can steer yourself any direction you choose. You're on your own. And you know what you know. And YOU are the one who'll decide where to go..." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175214-i-m-afraid-that-sometimes-you-ll-play-lonely-games-too-games</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2014 03:27:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175214-i-m-afraid-that-sometimes-you-ll-play-lonely-games-too-games]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm afraid that sometimes you'll play lonely games too. Games you can't win 'cause you'll play against you." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980494-if-you-re-offered-a-seat-on-a-rocket-ship-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 09:13:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Sheryl Sandberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980494-if-you-re-offered-a-seat-on-a-rocket-ship-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you’re offered a seat on a rocket ship, you don’t ask what seat. You just get on." -- Sheryl Sandberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309296-first-individual-rights-cannot-be-sacrificed-for-the-sake-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2014 03:26:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Michael J. Sandel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309296-first-individual-rights-cannot-be-sacrificed-for-the-sake-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First, individual rights cannot be sacrificed for the sake of the general good, and second, the principles of justice that specify these rights cannot be premised on any particular vision of the good life.  What justifies the rights is not that they maximize the general welfare or otherwise promote the good, but rather that they comprise a fair framework within which individuals and groups can choose their own values and ends, consistent with a similar liberty for others." -- Michael J. Sandel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 08:01:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Darkness cannot drive out darkness: only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate: only love can do that." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23127-what-is-fiction-in-particular-is-truth-in-general</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 02:36:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Multatuli (Eduard Douwes Dekker)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23127-what-is-fiction-in-particular-is-truth-in-general]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["what is fiction in particular is truth in general." -- Multatuli (Eduard Douwes Dekker)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2177-i-am-enough-of-an-artist-to-draw-freely-upon</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 02:48:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2177-i-am-enough-of-an-artist-to-draw-freely-upon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am enough of an artist to draw freely upon my imagination. Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/875444-we-realize-the-importance-of-our-voices-only-when-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 13:02:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Malala Yousafzai]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/875444-we-realize-the-importance-of-our-voices-only-when-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We realize the importance of our voices only when we are silenced" -- Malala Yousafzai]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7086-in-a-time-of-deceit-telling-the-truth-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 13:05:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7086-in-a-time-of-deceit-telling-the-truth-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a time of deceit telling the truth is a revolutionary act." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173993-listen-to-the-mustn-ts-child-listen-to-the-don-ts-listen</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 06:32:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Shel Silverstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173993-listen-to-the-mustn-ts-child-listen-to-the-don-ts-listen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["​Listen to the MUSTN'TS, child,
Listen to the DON'TS
Listen to the SHOULDN'TS
The IMPOSSIBLES, the WON'TS
Listen to the NEVER HAVES
Then listen close to me—
Anything can happen, child,
ANYTHING can be." -- Shel Silverstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/638614-niets-bestaat-dat-niet-iets-anders-aanraakt</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 00:48:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzanne add a quote by Jeroen Brouwers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/638614-niets-bestaat-dat-niet-iets-anders-aanraakt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Niets bestaat dat niet iets anders aanraakt." -- Jeroen Brouwers]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
