<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/234432-sori]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/234432-sori" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 20:20:02 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 20:20:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14013-the-fact-that-we-live-at-the-bottom-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2009 21:05:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14013-the-fact-that-we-live-at-the-bottom-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fact that we live at the bottom of a deep gravity well, on the surface of a gas covered planet going around a nuclear fireball 90 million miles away and think this to be normal is obviously some indication of how skewed our perspective tends to be." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7603-if-i-were-not-a-physicist-i-would-probably-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 22:18:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7603-if-i-were-not-a-physicist-i-would-probably-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I were not a physicist, I would probably be a musician. I often think in music. I live my daydreams in music. I see my life in terms of music." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2009 21:22:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37037-we-must-question-the-story-logic-of-having-an-all-knowing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2009 19:56:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Gene Roddenberry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37037-we-must-question-the-story-logic-of-having-an-all-knowing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must question the story logic of having an all-knowing all-powerful God, who creates faulty Humans, and then blames them for his own mistakes." -- Gene Roddenberry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5299-the-books-that-the-world-calls-immoral-are-books-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2009 20:10:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5299-the-books-that-the-world-calls-immoral-are-books-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The books that the world calls immoral are books that show the world its own shame." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54339-i-solemnly-swear-that-i-am-up-to-no-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2009 21:21:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54339-i-solemnly-swear-that-i-am-up-to-no-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I solemnly swear that I am up to no good." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8499-seize-the-moment-remember-all-those-women-on-the-titanic</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2009 22:20:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Erma Bombeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8499-seize-the-moment-remember-all-those-women-on-the-titanic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Seize the moment. Remember all those women on the 'Titanic' who waved off the dessert cart." -- Erma Bombeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98079-if-man-is-to-survive-he-will-have-learned-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 22:20:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Gene Roddenberry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98079-if-man-is-to-survive-he-will-have-learned-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If man is to survive, he will have learned to take a delight in the essential differences between men and between cultures. He will learn that differences in ideas and attitudes are a delight, part of life's exciting variety, not something to fear." -- Gene Roddenberry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9840-we-shall-not-cease-from-exploration-and-the-end-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2010 21:22:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by T. S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9840-we-shall-not-cease-from-exploration-and-the-end-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We shall not cease from exploration
And the end of all our exploring
Will be to arrive where we started
And know the place for the first time." -- T. S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131316-of-all-the-things-i-am-not-very-good-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 22:49:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131316-of-all-the-things-i-am-not-very-good-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of all the things I am not very good at, living in the real world is perhaps the most outstanding." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1981-my-experience-of-life-is-that-it-is-not-divided</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 12:04:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1981-my-experience-of-life-is-that-it-is-not-divided]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My experience of life is that it is not divided up into genres; it’s a horrifying, romantic, tragic, comical, science-fiction cowboy detective novel. You know, with a bit of pornography if you're lucky." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34703-paranoid-probably-but-just-because-you-re-paranoid-doesn-t-mean-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 22:31:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Jim Butcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34703-paranoid-probably-but-just-because-you-re-paranoid-doesn-t-mean-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Paranoid? Probably. But just because you're paranoid doesn't mean there isn't an invisible demon about to eat your face." -- Jim Butcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2310-america-will-never-be-destroyed-from-the-outside-if-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 22:32:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2310-america-will-never-be-destroyed-from-the-outside-if-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["America will never be destroyed from the outside.  If we falter and lose our freedoms, it will be because we destroyed ourselves." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2177-i-am-enough-of-an-artist-to-draw-freely-upon</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 23:21:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2177-i-am-enough-of-an-artist-to-draw-freely-upon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am enough of an artist to draw freely upon my imagination. Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103606-ladies-and-gentlemen-of-the-class-of-97-wear-sunscreen</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 23:23:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Mary Schmich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103606-ladies-and-gentlemen-of-the-class-of-97-wear-sunscreen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ladies and gentlemen of the class of '97:

Wear sunscreen.

If I could offer you only one tip for the future, sunscreen would be it. The long-term benefits of sunscreen have been proved by scientists, whereas the rest of my advice has no basis more reliable than my own meandering experience. I will dispense this advice now.

Enjoy the power and beauty of your youth. Oh, never mind. You will not understand the power and beauty of your youth until they've faded. But trust me, in 20 years, you'll look back at photos of yourself and recall in a way you can't grasp now how much possibility lay before you and how fabulous you really looked. You are not as fat as you imagine.

Don't worry about the future. Or worry, but know that worrying is as effective as trying to solve an algebra equation by chewing bubble gum. The real troubles in your life are apt to be things that never crossed your worried mind, the kind that blindside you at 4 p.m. on some idle Tuesday." -- Mary Schmich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53166-the-best-fantasy-is-written-in-the-language-of-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 22:29:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53166-the-best-fantasy-is-written-in-the-language-of-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best fantasy is written in the language of dreams. It is alive as dreams are alive, more real than real ... for a moment at least ... that long magic moment before we wake.

     Fantasy is silver and scarlet, indigo and azure, obsidian veined with gold and lapis lazuli. Reality is plywood and plastic, done up in mud brown and olive drab. Fantasy tastes of habaneros and honey, cinnamon and cloves, rare red meat and wines as sweet as summer. Reality is beans and tofu, and ashes at the end. Reality is the strip malls of Burbank, the smokestacks of Cleveland, a parking garage in Newark. Fantasy is the towers of Minas Tirith, the ancient stones of Gormenghast, the halls of Camelot. Fantasy flies on the wings of Icarus, reality on Southwest Airlines. Why do our dreams become so much smaller when they finally come true?

     We read fantasy to find the colors again, I think. To taste strong spices and hear the songs the sirens sang. There is something old and true in fantasy that speaks to something deep within us, to the child who dreamt that one day he would hunt the forests of the night, and feast beneath the hollow hills, and find a love to last forever somewhere south of Oz and north of Shangri-La.

     They can keep their heaven. When I die, I'd sooner go to middle Earth." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61763-have-been-unavoidably-detained-by-the-world-expect-us-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 23:35:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61763-have-been-unavoidably-detained-by-the-world-expect-us-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have been unavoidably detained by the world.  Expect us when you see us." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1815-do-not-believe-in-anything-simply-because-you-have-heard</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 18:57:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Buddha Siddhartha Guatama Shakyamuni]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1815-do-not-believe-in-anything-simply-because-you-have-heard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not believe in anything simply because you have heard it. Do not believe in anything simply because it is spoken and rumored by many. Do not believe in anything simply because it is found written in your religious books. Do not believe in anything merely on the authority of your teachers and elders. Do not believe in traditions because they have been handed down for many generations. But after observation and analysis, when you find that anything agrees with reason and is conducive to the good and benefit of one and all, then accept it and live up to it." -- Buddha Siddhartha Guatama Shakyamuni]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 11:54:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things need not have happened to be true. Tales and dreams are the shadow-truths that will endure when mere facts are dust and ashes, and forgot." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67857-why-do-you-go-away-so-that-you-can-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 11:55:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67857-why-do-you-go-away-so-that-you-can-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why do you go away?  So that you can come back.  So that you can see the place you came from with new eyes and extra colors.  And the people there see you differently, too.  Coming back to where you started is not the same as never leaving." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15214-do-you-know-what-we-call-opinion-in-the-absence</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 22:47:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Michael Crichton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15214-do-you-know-what-we-call-opinion-in-the-absence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you know what we call opinion in the absence of evidence?  We call it prejudice." -- Michael Crichton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190351-ah-coffee-the-sweet-balm-by-which-we-shall-accomplish</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 18:23:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Holly Black]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190351-ah-coffee-the-sweet-balm-by-which-we-shall-accomplish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ah coffee. The sweet balm by which we shall accomplish today's tasks." -- Holly Black]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6373-we-took-the-liberty-to-make-some-enquiries-concerning-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2012 21:17:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6373-we-took-the-liberty-to-make-some-enquiries-concerning-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We took the liberty to make some enquiries concerning the ground of their pretensions to make war upon nations who had done them no injury, and observed that we considered all mankind as our friends who had done us no wrong, nor had given us any provocation.

The Ambassador [of Tripoli] answered us that it was founded on the Laws of their Prophet, that it was written in their Koran, that all nations who should not have acknowledged their authority were sinners, that it was their right and duty to make war upon them wherever they could be found, and to make slaves of all they could take as Prisoners, and that every Musselman who should be slain in battle was sure to go to Paradise.

{&lt;i&gt;Letter from the commissioners, [author:John Adams|1480] &amp; Thomas Jefferson, to [author:John Jay|63860], 28 March 1786&lt;/i&gt;}" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44520-i-love-to-see-a-young-girl-go-out-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 20:42:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by maya angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44520-i-love-to-see-a-young-girl-go-out-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love to see a young girl go out and grab the world by the lapels. Life's a bitch. You've got to go out and kick ass." -- maya angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511366-the-problem-often-not-discovered-until-late-in-life-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 20:01:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Neil deGrasse Tyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511366-the-problem-often-not-discovered-until-late-in-life-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem, often not discovered until late in life, is that when you look for things in life like love, meaning, motivation, it implies they are sitting behind a tree or under a rock. The most successful people in life recognize, that in life they create their own love, they manufacture their own meaning, they generate their own motivation. For me, I am driven by two main philosophies, know more today about the world than I knew yesterday. And lessen the suffering of others. You'd be surprised how far that gets you. 

- Neil deGrasse Tyson's response on Reddit when asked &quot;What can you tell a young man looking for motivation in life itself?&quot;

http://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/qccer/i_am_neil_degrasse_tyson_ask_me_anything/" -- Neil deGrasse Tyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40891-the-more-i-learn-about-the-universe-the-less-convinced</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 20:01:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Neil deGrasse Tyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40891-the-more-i-learn-about-the-universe-the-less-convinced]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The more I learn about the universe, the less convinced I am that there's any sort of benevolent force that has anything to do with it, at all." -- Neil deGrasse Tyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460763-my-view-is-that-if-your-philosophy-is-not-unsettled</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 20:03:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sori add a quote by Neil deGrasse Tyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460763-my-view-is-that-if-your-philosophy-is-not-unsettled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My view is that if your philosophy is not unsettled daily then you are blind to all the universe has to offer." -- Neil deGrasse Tyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
