<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/234778-jabari]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/234778-jabari" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 11:11:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11000-i-thought-beatrice-keedsler-had-joined-hands-with-other-old-fashioned</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 11:11:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jabari add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11000-i-thought-beatrice-keedsler-had-joined-hands-with-other-old-fashioned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I thought Beatrice Keedsler had joined hands with other old-fashioned storytellers to make people believe that life had leading characters, minor characters, significant details, insignificant details, that it had lessons to be learned, tests to be passed, and a beginning, a middle, and an end.

As I approached my fiftieth birthday, I had become more and more enraged and mystified by the idiot decisions made by my countrymen. And then I had come suddenly to pity them, for I understood how innocent and natural it was for them to behave so abominably, and with such abominable results: They were doing their best to live like people invented in story books. This was the reason Americans shot each other so often: It was a convenient literary device for ending short stories and books.

Why were so many Americans treated by their government as though their lives were as disposable as paper facial tissues? Because that was the way authors customarily treated bit-part players in their madeup tales.

And so on.

Once I understood what was making America such a dangerous, unhappy nation of people who had nothing to do with real life, I resolved to shun storytelling. I would write about life. Every person would be exactly as important as any other. All facts would also be given equal weightiness. Nothing would be left out. Let others bring order to chaos. I would bring chaos to order, instead, which I think I have done.

If all writers would do that, then perhaps citizens not in the literary trades will understand that there is no order in the world around us, that we must adapt ourselves to the requirements of chaos instead.

It is hard to adapt to chaos, but it can be done. I am living proof of that: It can be done." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 11:13:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jabari add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24923-colorful-demonstrations-and-weekend-marches-are-vital-but-alone-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 11:14:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jabari add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24923-colorful-demonstrations-and-weekend-marches-are-vital-but-alone-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Colorful demonstrations and weekend marches are vital but alone are not powerful enough to stop wars. Wars will be stopped only when soldiers refuse to fight, when workers refuse to load weapons onto ships and aircraft, when people boycott the economic outposts of Empire that are strung across the globe. " -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11485-people-who-talk-about-revolution-and-class-struggle-without-referring</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 11:16:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jabari add a quote by -Raoul Vaneigem, “The Revolution Of Everyday Life”]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11485-people-who-talk-about-revolution-and-class-struggle-without-referring]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People who talk about revolution and class struggle
without referring explicitly to everyday life,
without understanding what is subversive about love
and what is positive in the refusal of constraints,
such people have a corpse in their mouth." -- -Raoul Vaneigem, “The Revolution Of Everyday Life”]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38906-who-wants-a-world-in-which-the-guarantee-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 11:16:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jabari add a quote by Raoul Vaneigem]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38906-who-wants-a-world-in-which-the-guarantee-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who wants a world in which the guarantee that we shall not die of starvation entails the risk of dying of boredom?" -- Raoul Vaneigem]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37342-to-be-rich-nowadays-merely-means-to-possess-a-large</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 11:16:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jabari add a quote by Raoul Vaneigem]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37342-to-be-rich-nowadays-merely-means-to-possess-a-large]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be rich nowadays merely means to possess a large number of poor objects." -- Raoul Vaneigem]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52631-the-nihilist-makes-one-mistake-he-does-not-realise-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 11:24:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jabari add a quote by Raoul Vaneigem]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52631-the-nihilist-makes-one-mistake-he-does-not-realise-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The nihilist makes one mistake: he does not realise that other people are also nihilists, and that the nihilism of other people is now an active historical factor.  He has no consciousness of the possibility of transcendence.  The fact is, however, that the present reign of survival, in which all the talk about progress expresses nothing so much as the fear that progress may be impossible, is itself a product of history, is itself the outcome of all the renunciations of humanity that have been made over the centuries.  Indeed, the history of survival is the historical movement which will eventually undo history itself.  For clear awareness of just how nightmarish life has become is on the point of fusing with a consciousness of the successive renunciations of the past, and thus too with the real desire to pick up the movement of transcendence everywhere in space and time where it has been prematurely interrupted." -- Raoul Vaneigem]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 11:26:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jabari add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
