<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/236606-tessa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/236606-tessa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 07:32:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82083-now-i-know-i-am-an-intellectual-i-saw-malcolm</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 07:32:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tessa add a quote by Sue Townsend]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82083-now-i-know-i-am-an-intellectual-i-saw-malcolm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now I know I am an intellectual.  I saw Malcolm Muggeridge on the television last night, and I understood nearly every word.  It all adds up.  A bad home, poor diet, not liking punk.  I think I will join the library and see what happens." -- Sue Townsend]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142689-when-he-went-out-it-was-freezing-and-a-pale</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 17:11:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tessa add a quote by Georges Simenon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142689-when-he-went-out-it-was-freezing-and-a-pale]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When he went out it was freezing, and a pale winter sun was rising over Paris.

No thought of escape had as yet crossed Monsieur Monde's mind.

'Morning, Joseph.'

'Morning, monsieur.'

As a matter of fact, it started like an attack of flu.  In the car he felt a shiver.  He was very susceptible to head colds.  Some winters they would hang on for weeks, and his pockets would be stuffed with wet handkerchiefs, which mortified him.  Moreover, that morning he ached all over, perhaps form having slept in an awkward position, or was it a touch of indigestion due to last night's supper?

'I'm getting flu,' he thought.

Then, just as they were crossing the Grands Boulevards, instead of automatically checking the time on the electric clock as he usually did, he raised his eyes and noticed the pink chimney pots outlined against a pale blue sky where a tiny white cloud was floating. 

It reminded him of the sea.  The harmony of blue and pink suddenly brought a breath of Mediterranean air to his mind, and he envied people who, at that time of year, lived in the South and wore white flannels." -- Georges Simenon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143599-forgive-me-also-that-i-didn-t-fight-like-lord-byron</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 13:40:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tessa add a quote by Zbigniew Herbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143599-forgive-me-also-that-i-didn-t-fight-like-lord-byron]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["forgive me also that I didn't fight like Lord Byron for the happiness of captive peoples that I watched only risings of the moon and museums" -- Zbigniew Herbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170296-as-i-followed-margo-s-directions-through-the-maze-of-one-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 07:52:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tessa add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170296-as-i-followed-margo-s-directions-through-the-maze-of-one-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As I followed Margo's directions through the maze of one-way streets, we saw a few people sleeping on the sidewalk or sitting on benches, but nobody was moving.  Margo rolled down the window, and I felt the thick air blow across my face, warmer than night ought to be.  I glanced over and saw strands of her hair blowing all around her face.  Even though I could see her there, I felt entirely alone among these big and empty buildings, like I'd survived the apocalypse and the world had been given to me, this whole and amazing and endless world, mine for the exploring." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184860-mario-d-fallen-in-love-with-the-first-madam-psychosis-programs</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 17:19:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tessa add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184860-mario-d-fallen-in-love-with-the-first-madam-psychosis-programs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mario'd fallen in love with the first Madam Psychosis programs because he felt like he was listening to someone sad read out loud from yellow letters she'd taken out of a shoebox on a rainy P.M, stuff about heartbreak and people you loved dying and U.S. woe, stuff that was real.  It is increasingly hard to find valid art that is about stuff that is real in this way.  The older Mario gets, the more confused he gets about the fact that everyone at E.T.A. over the age of about Kent Blott finds stuff that's really real uncomfortable and they get embarrassed.  It's like there's some rule that real stuff can only get mentioned if everybody rolls their eyes or laughs in a way that isn't happy." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204496-when-carleton-was-three-months-old-henry-had-realized-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2009 15:41:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tessa add a quote by Kelly Link]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204496-when-carleton-was-three-months-old-henry-had-realized-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When Carleton was three
months old, Henry had realized that they’d misunderstood something.
Babies weren’t babies—they were land mines; bear traps; wasp nests. They
were a noise, which was sometimes even not a noise, but merely a listening
for a noise; they were a damp, chalky smell; they were the heaving, jerky,
sticky manifestation of not-sleep. Once Henry had stood and watched
Carleton in his crib, sleeping peacefully. He had not done what he wanted
to do. He had not bent over and yelled in Carleton’s ear. Henry still hadn’t
forgiven Carleton, not yet, not entirely, not for making him feel that way." -- Kelly Link]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/210939-we-re-at-a-dinner-party-in-an-apartment-on-rue</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2009 15:02:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tessa add a quote by Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/210939-we-re-at-a-dinner-party-in-an-apartment-on-rue]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're at a dinner party in an apartment on Rue Paul Valéry between Avenue Foch and Avenue Victor Hugo and it's all rather subdued since a small percentage of the invited guests were blown up in the Ritz yesterday.  For comfort people went shopping, which is understandable even if they bought things a little too enthusiastically.  Tonight it's just wildflowers and white lilies, just W's Paris bureau chief, Donna Karan, Aerin Lauder, Ines de la Fressange and Christian Louboutin, who thinks I snubbed him and maybe I did but maybe I'm past the point of caring.  Just Annette Bening and Michael Stipe in a tomato-red wig.  Just Tammy on heroin, serene and glassy-eyed, her lips swollen from collagen injections, beeswax balm spread over her mouth, gliding through the party, stopping to listen to Kate Winslet, to Jean Reno, to Polly Walker, to Jacques Grange.  Just the smell of shit, floating, its fumes spreading everywhere.  Just another conversation with a chic sadist obsessed with origami.  Just another armless man waving a stump and whispering excitedly, &quot;Natasha's coming!&quot;  Just people tan and back from the Ariel Sands Beach Club in Bermuda, some of them looking reskinned.  Just me, making connections based on fear, experiencing vertigo, drinking a Woo-Woo." -- Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57409-one-of-the-strange-things-about-living-in-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 10:05:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tessa add a quote by Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57409-one-of-the-strange-things-about-living-in-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the strange things about living in the world is that it is only now and then one is quite sure one is going to live forever and ever and ever. One knows it sometimes when one gets up at the tender solemn dawn-time and goes out and stands out and throws one's head far back and looks up and up and watches the pale sky slowly changing and flushing and marvelous unknown things happening until the East almost makes one cry out and one's heart stands still at the strange unchanging majesty of the rising of the sun--which has been happening every morning for thousands and thousands and thousands of years. One knows it then for a moment or so. And one knows it sometimes when one stands by oneself in a wood at sunset and the mysterious deep gold stillness slanting through and under the branches seems to be saying slowly again and again something one cannot quite hear, however much one tries. Then sometimes the immense quiet of the dark blue at night with the millions of stars waiting and watching makes one sure; and sometimes a sound of far-off music makes it true; and sometimes a look in someone's eyes." -- Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434853-i-have-seen-it-over-and-over-the-same-sea</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2011 14:16:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tessa add a quote by Elizabeth Bishop]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434853-i-have-seen-it-over-and-over-the-same-sea]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have seen it over and over, the same sea, the same,
slightly, indifferently swinging above the stones,
icily free above the stones,
above the stones and then the world.
If you should dip your hand in,
your wrist would ache immediately,
your bones would begin to ache and your hand would burn
as if the water were a transmutation of fire
that feeds on stones and burns with a dark gray flame.
If you tasted it, it would first taste bitter,
then briny, then surely burn your tongue.
It is like what we imagine knowledge to be:
dark, salt, clear, moving, utterly free,
drawn form the cold hard mouth
of the world, derived from the rocky breasts
forever, flowing and drawn, and since
our knowledge is historical, flowing, and flown." -- Elizabeth Bishop]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/635548-lovely-and-unremarkable-the-clutter-of-mugs-and-books-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 14:08:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tessa add a quote by Marilyn Hacker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/635548-lovely-and-unremarkable-the-clutter-of-mugs-and-books-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lovely and unremarkable, the clutter
of mugs and books, the almost-empty Fig
Newtons box, thick dishes in a big
tin tray, the knife still standing in the butter,
change like the color of river water
in the delicate shift to day. Thin fog
veils the hedges, where a neighbor dog
makes rounds. 'Go to bed. It doesn't matter
about the washing-up. Take this book along.'
Whatever it was we said that night is gone,
framed like a photograph nobody took.
Stretched out on a camp cot with the book,
I think that we will talk all night again,
there, or another where, but I am wrong." -- Marilyn Hacker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/719882-then-they-went-on-to-discuss-other-things-because-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 20:09:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tessa add a quote by Sarah Schulman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/719882-then-they-went-on-to-discuss-other-things-because-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then they went on to discuss other things because there is always something more to a person than what somebody else does to them." -- Sarah Schulman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/720686-and-in-the-village-the-wind-sets-the-lids-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 19:01:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tessa add a quote by Paul Murray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/720686-and-in-the-village-the-wind-sets-the-lids-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And in the village the wind sets the lids of the wheelie bins chomping at nothing, and in the cinema Hulk bounces and swings his fists, and in the video-game shop the Christmas games are in, and in Ed’s there’s a special offer, two boxes of doughnuts for the price of one, someone says it’s because of what happened but someone else says no, actually they’re doing it in all the branches. It doesn’t matter where you go through, nowhere feels big enough to contain you, even if you’re right in the middle of the mall it still somehow seems too shallow, like when you were younger and you tried to make your Transformers visit your Lego town, and they were just out of scale, it didn’t work -- it’s like that, or maybe it isn’t, because you also feel really tinily small, you feel like a lump in somebody’s throat, or actually who cares what you feel, and everywhere you go you encounter other grey-clad boys from your year, looming up like hateful reflections -- Gary Toolan, John Keating, Maurice Wall, Vincent Bailey and all of the others that are the pinnacle of the evolution that began so many years ago with that one depressed fish that if you met him now you’d tell him to stay in the sea -- there they are, pale-faced but smirking, sleeves rolled up, and though it’s sad, it’s sadder than a three-legged dog, it’s also flat, it make you angry, so when someone says Skippy was a homo you’re almost glad because you can fight them, and they’re glad too, so you fight, until someone gets his jumper ripped or the security guard chases you out of the mall, and you’ve already been kicked out of the other mall, and it’s too cold to go to the park, and you think it must be almost time to go to bed but it’s not, it’s only just time for dinner, which is car-tyre with phlegm sauce and which you leave mostly uneaten, and privately you’re thinking Skippy is a homo too, you’re thinking, Fuck you Skippy, though you’re also thinking, Hey, where’s Skippy? or Skippy, did you borrow my -- and then you think, Oh fuck, and everything shakes around the edges again and you have to hold on tight to your lucky condom or your Tupac keyring or your actual live shotgun bullet, or if you don’t have one of those things, wedge your hands deeper in your pockets or throw a stone at a seagull or shout after a knacker in the village how his mother was in excellent form last night and run for it, and dream of being Hulk, or a Transformer in a Lego town going smash! bash! crash!  stomping the whole city to the ground, incinerating the little yellow-headed Lego people with your laser eyes till the smiles melt right off their faces.

And in the schoolyard the lisp of a last fallen leaf skating around the tarmac is the only sound, everywhere else is totally silent, even when people are talking, it’s like someone’s thrown a switch and reversed the polarity of everything so that being alive now is like being dead, like zombies, grey bodies shuffling loose-limbed through he perpetual gloaming, or like universes, same difference, matter or energy adrift in nothingness, descending, like veils, through the darkness." -- Paul Murray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/881620-by-solitude-the-soul-escapes-from-doing-or-suffering-magic</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 10:59:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tessa add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/881620-by-solitude-the-soul-escapes-from-doing-or-suffering-magic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By solitude the soul escapes from doing or suffering magic; it escapes from dullness, from boredom, by being aware. Nothing is boring if you are aware of it. It may be irritating, but it is not boring. If it is pleasant the pleasure will not fail so long as you are aware of it. Being aware is the hardest work the soul can do, I think." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739269-oh-god-midnight-s-not-bad-you-wake-and-go-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 12:55:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tessa add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739269-oh-god-midnight-s-not-bad-you-wake-and-go-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh God, midnight’s not bad, you wake and go back to sleep, one or two’s not bad, you toss but sleep again. Five or six in the morning, there’s hope, for dawn’s just under the horizon. But three, now, Christ, three A.M.! Doctors say the body’s at low tide then. The soul is out. The blood moves slow. You’re the nearest to dead you’ll ever be save dying. Sleep is a patch of death, but three in the morn, full wide-eyed staring, is living death! You dream with your eyes open. God, if you had strength to rouse up, you’d slaughter your half-dreams with buckshot! But no, you lie pinned to a deep well-bottom that’s burned dry. The moon rolls by to look at you down there, with its idiot face. It’s a long way back to sunset, a far way on to dawn, so you summon all the fool things of your life, the stupid lovely things done with people known so very well who are now so very dead – And wasn’t it true, had he read somewhere, more people in hospitals die at 3 A.M. than at any other time..." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119514-standing-on-a-street-corner-waiting-for-no-one-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 08:36:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tessa add a quote by Gregory Corso]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119514-standing-on-a-street-corner-waiting-for-no-one-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Standing on a street corner waiting for no one is power." -- Gregory Corso]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
