<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/237193-sara]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/237193-sara" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 14:46:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51816-the-lives-of-individuals-of-the-human-race-form-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 14:46:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51816-the-lives-of-individuals-of-the-human-race-form-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The lives of individuals of the human race form a constant plot, in which every attempt to isolate one piece of living that has a meaning separate from the rest-for example, the meeting of two people, which will become decisive for both-must bear in mind that each of the two brings with himself a texture of events, environments, other people, and that from the meeting, in turn, other stories will be derived which will break off from their common story." -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141956-in-her-enthusiasms-she-had-always-looked-for-something-tangible</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 09:41:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141956-in-her-enthusiasms-she-had-always-looked-for-something-tangible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In her enthusiasms she had always looked for something tangible: she had always loved church for its flowers, music for its romantic words, literature for its power to stir the passions and she rebelled before the mysteries of faith just as she grew ever more restive under discipline, which was antipathetic to her nature." -- Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156388-thanks-pal-but-i-tend-to-avoid-any-substance-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2009 16:17:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156388-thanks-pal-but-i-tend-to-avoid-any-substance-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thanks pal, but I tend to avoid any substance that makes me feel smarter, stronger, or better looking than I know I actually am.&quot;  There were, in his opinion, drugs that diminished ego and drugs that engorged ego, which is to say, revelatory drugs and delusory drugs, and on a psychic level, at least, he favored awe over swagger.  Should he ever aspire to become voluntarily delusional, then good old-fashioned alcohol would do the job effectively and inexpensively, thank you, and without the dubious bonus of jaw-clenching jitters." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176736-ennui-tea-leaves-thwart-those-who-court-catastrophe-designing-futures</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2009 19:39:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176736-ennui-tea-leaves-thwart-those-who-court-catastrophe-designing-futures]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ennui

Tea leaves thwart those who court catastrophe,
designing futures where nothing will occur:
cross the gypsy’s palm and yawning she
will still predict no perils left to conquer.
Jeopardy is jejune now: naïve knight
finds ogres out-of-date and dragons unheard
of, while blasé princesses indict
tilts at terror as downright absurd.

The beast in Jamesian grove will never jump,
compelling hero’s dull career to crisis;
and when insouciant angels play God’s trump,
while bored arena crowds for once look eager,
hoping toward havoc, neither pleas nor prizes
shall coax from doom’s blank door lady or tiger." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
