<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/237249-keleigh]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/237249-keleigh" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:49:51 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37-anyone-whose-goal-is-something-higher-must-expect-someday-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:49:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37-anyone-whose-goal-is-something-higher-must-expect-someday-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone whose goal is 'something higher' must expect someday to suffer vertigo. What is vertigo? Fear of falling? No, Vertigo is something other than fear of falling. It is the voice of the emptiness below us which tempts and lures us, it is the desire to fall, against which, terrified, we defend ourselves." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18729-in-the-sunset-of-dissolution-everything-is-illuminated-by-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:51:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18729-in-the-sunset-of-dissolution-everything-is-illuminated-by-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the sunset of dissolution, everything is illuminated by the aura of nostalgia, even the guillotine." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81050-making-love-with-a-woman-and-sleeping-with-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:51:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81050-making-love-with-a-woman-and-sleeping-with-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Making love with a woman and sleeping with a woman are two separate passions, not merely different but opposite. Love does not make itself felt in the desire for copulation (a desire that extends to an infinite number of women) but in the desire for shared sleep (a desire limited to one woman)." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65833-we-all-need-someone-to-look-at-us-we-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:53:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65833-we-all-need-someone-to-look-at-us-we-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all need someone to look at us. we can be divided into four categories according to the kind of look we wish to live under. the first category longs for the look of an infinite number of anonymous eyes, in other words, for the look of the public. the second category is made up of people who have a vital need to be looked at by many known eyes. they are the tireless hosts of cocktail parties and dinners. they are happier than the people in the first category, who, when they lose their public, have the feeling that the lights have gone out in the room of their lives. this happens to nearly all of them sooner or later. people in the second category, on the other hand, can always come up with the eyes they need. then there is the third category, the category of people who need to be constantly before the eyes of the person they love. their situation is as dangerous as the situation of people in the first category. one day the eyes of their beloved will close, and the room will go dark. and finally there is the fourth category, the rarest, the category of people who live in the imaginary eyes of those who are not present. they are the dreamers." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66096-the-brain-appears-to-possess-a-special-area-which-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:53:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66096-the-brain-appears-to-possess-a-special-area-which-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The brain appears to possess a special area which we might call poetic memory and which records everything that charms or touches us, that makes our lives beautiful ... Love begins with a metaphor. Which is to say, love begins at the point when a woman enters her first word into our poetic memory." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106111-but-when-the-strong-were-too-weak-to-hurt-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:53:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106111-but-when-the-strong-were-too-weak-to-hurt-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But when the strong were too weak to hurt the weak, the weak had to be strong enough to leave." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17940-living-is-being-happy-seeing-hearing-touching-drinking-eating-urinating</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:53:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17940-living-is-being-happy-seeing-hearing-touching-drinking-eating-urinating]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Living is being happy: seeing, hearing, touching, drinking, eating, urinating, defecating, diving into the water and gazing at the sky, laughing and crying." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106117-perhaps-the-reason-we-are-unable-to-love-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:53:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106117-perhaps-the-reason-we-are-unable-to-love-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps the reason we are unable to love is that we yearn to be loved, that is, we demand something (love) from our partner instead of delivering ourselves up to him demand-free and asking for nothing but his company." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48435-loves-are-like-empires-when-the-idea-they-are-founded</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:53:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48435-loves-are-like-empires-when-the-idea-they-are-founded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["loves are like empires: when the idea they are founded on crumbles, they, too, fade away." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80759-there-is-a-certain-part-of-all-of-us-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:53:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80759-there-is-a-certain-part-of-all-of-us-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a certain part of all of us that lives outside of time. Perhaps we become aware of our age only at exceptional moments and most of the time we are ageless." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39432-she-had-an-overwhelming-desire-to-tell-him-like-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:54:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39432-she-had-an-overwhelming-desire-to-tell-him-like-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had an overwhelming desire to tell him, like the most banal of women.  Don't let me go, hold me tight, make me your plaything, your slave, be strong!  But they were words she could not say.

The only thing she said when he released her from his embrace was, &quot;You don't know how happy I am to be with you.&quot;  That was the most her reserved nature allowed her to express." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1228-humanity-s-true-moral-test-its-fundamental-test-consists-of-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:55:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1228-humanity-s-true-moral-test-its-fundamental-test-consists-of-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humanity's true moral test, its fundamental test, consists of its attitude towards those who are at its mercy: animals.  And in this respect humankind has suffered a fundamental debacle, a debacle so fundamental that all others stem from it." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113539-kitsch-is-the-inability-to-admit-that-shit-exists</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:55:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113539-kitsch-is-the-inability-to-admit-that-shit-exists]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kitsch is the inability to admit that shit exists" -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81498-the-goals-we-pursue-are-always-veiled-a-girl-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:55:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81498-the-goals-we-pursue-are-always-veiled-a-girl-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The goals we pursue are always veiled. A girl who longs for marriage longs for something she knows nothing about. The boy who hankers after fame has no idea what fame is. The thing that gives our every move its meaning is always totally unknown to us." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95585-and-therein-lies-the-whole-of-man-s-plight-human-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:55:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95585-and-therein-lies-the-whole-of-man-s-plight-human-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And therein lies the whole of man's plight.  Human time does not turn in a circle; it runs ahead in a straight line.  That is why man cannot be happy: happiness is the longing for repetition." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23287-a-mismatched-outfit-a-slightly-defective-denture-an-exquisite-mediocrity</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:56:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23287-a-mismatched-outfit-a-slightly-defective-denture-an-exquisite-mediocrity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A mismatched outfit, a slightly defective denture, an exquisite mediocrity of the soul-those are the details that make a woman real, alive. The women you see on posters or in fashion magazines-the ones all the women try to imitate nowadays-how can they be attractive? They have no reality of their own; they're just the sum of a set of abstract rules. They aren't born of human bodies; they hatch ready-made from the computers.&quot; ~The Book of Laughter and Forgetting" -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125404-the-greek-word-for-return-is-nostos-algos-means-suffering</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:56:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125404-the-greek-word-for-return-is-nostos-algos-means-suffering]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Greek word for &quot;return&quot; is nostos. Algos means &quot;suffering.&quot; So nostalgia is the suffering caused by an unappeased yearning to return." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49277-the-worst-thing-is-not-that-the-world-is-unfree</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:58:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49277-the-worst-thing-is-not-that-the-world-is-unfree]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worst thing is not that the world is unfree, but that people have unlearned their liberty.

The more indifferent people are to politics, to the interests of others, the more obsessed they become with their own faces. The individualism of our time.

Not being able to fall asleep and not allowing oneself to move: the marital bed.

If high culture is coming to an end, it is also the end of you and your paradoxical ideas, because paradox as such belongs to high culture and not to childish prattle. You remind me of the young men who supported the Nazis or communists not out of cowardice or out of opportunism but out of an excess of intelligence. For nothing requires a greater effort of thought than arguments to justify the rule of nonthought… You are the brilliant ally of your own gravediggers.

In the world of highways, a beautiful landscape means: an island of beauty connected by a long line with other islands of beauty.

How to live in a world with which you disagree? How to live with people when you neither share their suffering nor their joys? When you know that you don’t belong among them?... our century refuses to acknowledge anyone’s right to disagree with the world…All that remains of such a place is the memory, the ideal of a cloister, the dream of a cloister… 

Humor can only exist when people are still capable of recognizing some border between the important and the unimportant. And nowadays this border has become unrecognizable.

The majority of people lead their existence within a small idyllic circle bounded by their family, their home, and their work... They live in a secure realm somewhere between good and evil. They are sincerely horrified by the sight of a killer. And yet all you have to do is remove them from this peaceful circle and they, too, turn into murderers, without quite knowing how it happened.

The longing for order is at the same time a longing for death, because life is an incessant disruption of order. Or to put it the other way around: the desire for order is a virtuous pretext, an excuse for virulent misanthropy.

A long time a go a certain Cynic philosopher proudly paraded around Athens in a moth-eaten coat, hoping that everyone would admire his contempt for convention. When Socrates met him, he said: Through the hole in your coat I see your vanity. Your dirt, too, dear sir, is self-indulgent and your self-indulgence is dirty.

You are always living below the level of true existence, you bitter weed, you anthropomorphized vat of vinegar! You’re full of acid, which bubbles inside you like an alchemist’s brew. Your highest wish is to be able to see all around you the same ugliness as you carry inside yourself. That’s the only way you can feel for a few moments some kind of peace between yourself and the world. That’s because the world, which is beautiful, seems horrible to you, torments you and excludes you.

If the novel is successful, it must necessarily be wiser than its author. This is why many excellent French intellectuals write mediocre novels. They are always more intelligent than their books.

By a certain age, coincidences lose their magic, no longer surprise, become run-of-the-mill.

Any new possibility that existence acquires, even the least likely, transforms everything about existence." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23288-he-was-well-aware-that-of-the-two-of-three</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:59:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23288-he-was-well-aware-that-of-the-two-of-three]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was well aware that of the two of three thousand times he had made love (how many times had he made love in his life?) only two or three were really essential and unforgettable.  The rest were mere echoes, imitations, repetitions, or reminiscences." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105522-physical-love-is-unthinkable-without-violence</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 12:59:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105522-physical-love-is-unthinkable-without-violence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Physical love is unthinkable without violence." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64506-the-heaviest-of-burdens-crushes-us-we-sink-beneath-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 09:12:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64506-the-heaviest-of-burdens-crushes-us-we-sink-beneath-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The heaviest of burdens crushes us, we sink beneath it, it pins us to the ground. But in love poetry of every age, the woman longs to be weighed down by the man's body.The heaviest of burdens is therefore simultaneously an image of life's most intense fulfillment. The heavier the burden, the closer our lives come to the earth, the more real and truthful they become. Conversely, the absolute absence of burden causes man to be lighter than air, to soar into heights, take leave of the earth and his earthly being, and become only half real, his movements as free as they are insignificant. What then shall we choose? Weight or lightness?" -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259381-as-human-beings-not-only-do-we-seek-resolution-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 20:47:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259381-as-human-beings-not-only-do-we-seek-resolution-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As human beings, not only do we seek resolution, but we also feel that we deserve resolution. However, not only do we not deserve resolution, we suffer from resolution. We don't deserve resolution; we deserve something better than that. We deserve our birthright, which is the middle way, an open state of mind that can relax with paradox and ambiguity." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23089-the-meeting-of-two-personalities-is-like-the-contact-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 08:48:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23089-the-meeting-of-two-personalities-is-like-the-contact-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The meeting of two personalities is like the contact of two chemical substances: if there is any reaction, both are transformed." -- Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143513-the-best-political-social-and-spiritual-work-we-can-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 08:51:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143513-the-best-political-social-and-spiritual-work-we-can-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best political, social, and spiritual work we can do is to withdraw the projection of our shadow onto others." -- Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2887-if-you-judge-people-you-have-no-time-to-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 10:38:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2887-if-you-judge-people-you-have-no-time-to-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you judge people, you have no time to love them." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/633-i-have-found-the-paradox-that-if-you-love-until</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 10:38:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Daphne Rae]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/633-i-have-found-the-paradox-that-if-you-love-until]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have found the paradox, that if you love until it hurts, there can be no more hurt, only more love." -- Daphne Rae]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7992-don-t-say-you-don-t-have-enough-time-you-have-exactly</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 10:38:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7992-don-t-say-you-don-t-have-enough-time-you-have-exactly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't say you don't have enough time. You have exactly the same number of hours per day that were given to Helen Keller, Pasteur, Michaelangelo, Mother Teresa, Leonardo da Vinci, Thomas Jefferson, and Albert Einstein." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9401-do-not-think-that-love-in-order-to-be-genuine</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 10:38:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9401-do-not-think-that-love-in-order-to-be-genuine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not think that love in order to be genuine has to be extraordinary. What we need is to love without getting tired. Be faithful in small things because it is in them that your strength lies." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4391-live-simply-so-others-may-simply-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 10:39:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4391-live-simply-so-others-may-simply-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Live simply so others may simply live." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23380-if-we-have-no-peace-it-is-because-we-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 10:39:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keleigh add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23380-if-we-have-no-peace-it-is-because-we-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we have no peace, it is because we have forgotten that we belong to each other." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
