<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/238070-lafcadio]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/238070-lafcadio" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 16:46:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41910-books-purchasable-at-low-cost-permit-us-to-interrogate-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 16:46:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41910-books-purchasable-at-low-cost-permit-us-to-interrogate-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books, purchasable at low cost, permit us to interrogate the past with high accuracy; to tap the wisdom of our species; to understand the point of view of others, and not just those in power; to contemplate--with the best teachers--the insights, painfully extracted from Nature, of the greatest minds that ever were, drawn from the entire planet and from all of our history. They allow people long dead to talk inside our heads. Books can accompany us everywhere. Books are patient where we are slow to understand, allow us to go over the hard parts as many times as we wish, and are never critical of our lapses. Books are key to understanding the world and participating in a democratic society." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3264-i-am-free-no-matter-what-rules-surround-me-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 12:08:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3264-i-am-free-no-matter-what-rules-surround-me-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am free, no matter what rules surround me. If I find them tolerable, I tolerate them; if I find them too obnoxious, I break them. I am free because I know that I alone am morally responsible for everything I do." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/436227-that-mess-about-judging-people-by-the-content-of-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 12:08:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by Emily Raboteau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/436227-that-mess-about-judging-people-by-the-content-of-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That mess about judging people by the content of their character and not the color of their skin—that's some bullshit. Nobody has the right to judge anybody else. Period. If you ain't been in my skin, you ain't never gonna understand my character." -- Emily Raboteau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 12:09:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907-when-i-was-a-child-adults-would-tell-me-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 12:08:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907-when-i-was-a-child-adults-would-tell-me-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was a child, adults would tell me not to make things up, warning me of what would happen if I did. As far as I can tell so far, it seems to involve lots of foreign travel and not having to get up too early in the morning." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71843-some-have-argued-that-because-the-universe-is-like-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 12:09:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by Thomas Cathcart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71843-some-have-argued-that-because-the-universe-is-like-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some have argued that because the universe is like a clock, there must be a Clockmaker. As the eighteenth-century British empiricist David Hume pointed out, this is a slippery argument, because there is nothing that is really perfectly analogous to the universe as a whole, unless it's another universe, so we shouldn't try to pass off anything that is just a part of this universe. Why a clock anyhow? Hume asks. Why not say the universe is analogous to a kangaroo? After all, both are organically interconnected systems. But the kangaroo analogy would lead to a very different conclusion about the origin of the universe: namely, that it was born of another universe after that universe had sex with a third universe. " -- Thomas Cathcart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 12:09:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finish each day and be done with it. You have done what you could.  Some blunders and absurdities no doubt crept in; forget them as soon as you can. Tomorrow is a new day.  You shall begin it serenely and with too high a spirit to be encumbered with your old nonsense." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 12:08:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fairy tales are more than true: not because they tell us that dragons exist, but because they tell us that dragons can be beaten." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22201-the-total-amount-of-suffering-per-year-in-the-natural</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 12:08:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by Richard Dawkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22201-the-total-amount-of-suffering-per-year-in-the-natural]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The total amount of suffering per year in the natural world is beyond all decent contemplation. During the minute that it takes me to compose this sentence, thousands of animals are being eaten alive, many others are running for their lives, whimpering with fear, others are slowly being devoured from within by rasping parasites, thousands of all kinds are dying of starvation, thirst, and disease. It must be so. If there ever is a time of plenty, this very fact will automatically lead to an increase in the population until the natural state of starvation and misery is restored. In a universe of electrons and selfish genes, blind physical forces and genetic replication, some people are going to get hurt, other people are going to get lucky, and you won't find any rhyme or reason in it, nor any justice. The universe that we observe has precisely the properties we should expect if there is, at bottom, no design, no purpose, no evil, no good, nothing but pitiless indifference." -- Richard Dawkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40777-a-process-cannot-be-understood-by-stopping-it-understanding-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2009 11:53:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by Frank Herbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40777-a-process-cannot-be-understood-by-stopping-it-understanding-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A process cannot be understood by stopping it.  Understanding must move with the flow of the process, must join it and flow with it." -- Frank Herbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72121-hope-looks-beyond-the-bounds-of-time-when-what-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 23:26:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by Edwin Francis Hatfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72121-hope-looks-beyond-the-bounds-of-time-when-what-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hope looks beyond the bounds of time, when what we now deplore shall rise, in full immortal prime, and bloom to fade no more." -- Edwin Francis Hatfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178439-the-cosmos-is-all-that-is-or-was-or-ever</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 12:07:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178439-the-cosmos-is-all-that-is-or-was-or-ever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Cosmos is all that is or was or ever will be. Our feeblest contemplations of the Cosmos stir us -- there is a tingling in the spine, a catch in the voice, a faint sensation, as if a distant memory, of falling from a height. We know we are approaching the greatest of mysteries." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4964-love-is-that-condition-in-which-the-happiness-of-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 12:09:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4964-love-is-that-condition-in-which-the-happiness-of-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is that condition in which the happiness of another person is essential to your own." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220528-whatever-the-cost-of-our-libraries-the-price-is-cheap</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 10:35:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by Walter Cronkite]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220528-whatever-the-cost-of-our-libraries-the-price-is-cheap]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever the cost of our libraries, the price is cheap compared to that of an ignorant nation." -- Walter Cronkite]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177489-i-do-things-like-get-in-a-taxi-and-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 23:44:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177489-i-do-things-like-get-in-a-taxi-and-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do things like get in a taxi and say, &quot;The library, and step on it." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6305-begin-at-the-beginning-the-king-said-very-gravely-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 21:27:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6305-begin-at-the-beginning-the-king-said-very-gravely-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Begin at the beginning,&quot; the King said, very gravely, &quot;and go on till you come to the end: then stop." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465202-the-moon-is-a-loyal-companion-it-never-leaves-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 20:49:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lafcadio add a quote by Tahereh Mafi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465202-the-moon-is-a-loyal-companion-it-never-leaves-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The moon is a loyal companion.
It never leaves. It’s always there, watching, steadfast, knowing us in our light and dark moments, changing forever just as we do. Every day it’s a different version of itself. Sometimes weak and wan, sometimes strong and full of light. The moon understands what it means to be human.
Uncertain. Alone. Cratered by imperfections." -- Tahereh Mafi]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
