<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/238313-perrie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/238313-perrie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 03:14:52 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/496772-begone-foul-dwimmerlaik-lord-of-carrion-leave-the-dead-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 03:14:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Perrie add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/496772-begone-foul-dwimmerlaik-lord-of-carrion-leave-the-dead-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Begone, foul dwimmerlaik, lord of carrion! Leave the dead in peace!&quot;

A cold voice answered: 'Come not between the Nazgûl and his prey! Or he will not slay thee in thy turn. He will bear thee away to the houses of lamentation, beyond all darkness, where thy flesh shall be devoured, and thy shrivelled mind be left naked to the Lidless Eye.&quot;

A sword rang as it was drawn. &quot;Do what you will; but I will hinder it, if I may.&quot;

&quot;Hinder me? Thou fool. No living man may hinder me!&quot;

Then Merry heard of all sounds in that hour the strangest. It seemed that Dernhelm laughed, and the clear voice was like the ring of steel. &quot;But no living man am I!" -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501308-i-don-t-like-anything-here-at-all-said-frodo-step</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 03:14:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Perrie add a quote by Tolkien John Ronald Reuel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501308-i-don-t-like-anything-here-at-all-said-frodo-step]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don’t like anything here at all.” said Frodo, “step or stone, breath or bone. Earth, air and water all seem accursed. But so our path is laid.”

“Yes, that’s so,” said Sam, “And we shouldn’t be here at all, if we’d known more about it before we started. But I suppose it’s often that way. The brave things in the old tales and songs, Mr. Frodo, adventures, as I used to call them. I used to think that they were things the wonderful folk of the stories went out and
looked for, because they wanted them, because they were exciting and life was a bit dull, a kind of a sport, as you might say. But that’s not the way of it with the tales that really mattered, or the ones that stay in the mind. Folk seem to have been just landed in them, usually their paths were laid that way, as you put it. But I expect they had lots of chances, like us, of turning back, only they didn’t. And if they had, we shouldn’t know, because they’d have been forgotten. We hear about those as just went on, and not all to a good end, mind you; at least not to what folk inside a story and not outside it call a good end. You know, coming home, and finding things all right, though not quite the same; like old Mr Bilbo. But those aren’t always the best tales to hear, though they may be the best tales to get landed in! I wonder what sort of a tale we’ve fallen into?”

“I wonder,” said Frodo, “But I don’t know. And that’s the way of a real tale. Take any one that you’re fond of. You may know, or guess, what kind of a tale it is, happy-ending or sad-ending, but the people in it don’t know. And you don’t want them to." -- Tolkien John Ronald Reuel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/710734-i-told-you-i-set-no-limits-on-my-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 02:28:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Perrie add a quote by Robin Hobb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/710734-i-told-you-i-set-no-limits-on-my-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I told you I set no limits on my love for you.  I don't.  Yet I have never expected you to offer me your body.  It was the whole of your heart, all for myself, that I sought.  Even though I've never had a right to it.  For you gave it away ere ever you saw me." -- Robin Hobb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334881-stop-longing-you-poison-today-s-ease-reaching-always-for-tomorrow</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 02:30:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Perrie add a quote by Robin Hobb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334881-stop-longing-you-poison-today-s-ease-reaching-always-for-tomorrow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stop longing.You poison today’s ease, reaching always for tomorrow." -- Robin Hobb]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
