<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/239610-joe-briggs]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/239610-joe-briggs" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 06:03:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303807-god-save-the-queen-and-a-fascist-regime-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 06:03:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303807-god-save-the-queen-and-a-fascist-regime-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God save the Queen and a fascist regime … a flabby toothless fascism, to be sure. Never go too far in any direction, is the basic law on which Limey-Land is built. The Queen stabilizes the whole sinking shithouse and keeps a small elite of wealth and privilege on top. The English have gone soft in the outhouse. England is like some stricken beast too stupid to know it is dead. Ingloriously foundering in its own waste products, the backlash and bad karma of empire" -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303808-he-remembers-his-fathers-last-words-stay-out-of-churches</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 06:03:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303808-he-remembers-his-fathers-last-words-stay-out-of-churches]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He remembers his fathers last words: “Stay out of churches, son. All they got a key to is the shit house. And swear to me you’ll never wear a lawman’s badge." -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303809-this-book-is-dedicated-to-the-ancient-ones-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 06:04:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303809-this-book-is-dedicated-to-the-ancient-ones-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This book is dedicated to the Ancient Ones, to the Lord of Abominations, Humwawa, whose face is a mass of entrails, whose breath is the stench of dung and the perfume of death, Dark Angel of all that is excreted and sours, Lord of Decay, Lord of the Future, who rides on a whispering south wind, to Pazuzu, Lord of Fevers and Plagues, Dark Angel of the Four Winds with rotting genitals from which he howls through sharpened teeth over stricken cities, to Kutulu, the Sleeping Serpent who cannot be summoned, to the Akhkharu, who such the blood of men since they desire to become men, to the Lalussu, who haunt the places of men, to Gelal and Lilit, who invade the beds of men and whose children are born in secret places, to Addu, raiser of storms who can fill the night sky with brightness, to Malah, Lord of Courage and Bravery, to Zahgurim, whose number is twenty-three and who kills in an unnatural fashion, to Zahrim, a warrior among warriors, to Itzamna, Spirit of Early Mists and Showers, to Ix Chel, the Spider-Web-that-Catches-the-Dew-of-Morning, to Zuhuy Kak, Virgin Fire, to Ah Dziz, the Master of Cold, to Kak U Pacat, who works in fire, to Ix Tab, Goddess of Ropes and Snares, patroness of those who hang themselves, to Schmuun, the Silent One, twin brother of Ix Tab, to Xolotl the Unformed, Lord of Rebirth, to Aguchi, Master of Ejaculations, to Osiris and Amen in phallic form, to Hex Chun Chan, the Dangerous One, to Ah Pook, the Destroyer, to the Great Old One and the Star Beast, to Pan, God of Panic, to the nameless gods of dispersal and emptiness, to Hassan i Sabbah, Master of Assassins. 

To all the scribes and artists and practitioners of magic through whom these spirits have been manifested….
NOTHING IS TRUE. EVERYTHING IS PERMITTED." -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303810-we-re-not-fighting-for-a-scrap-of-sharecropper-immortality-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 06:05:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303810-we-re-not-fighting-for-a-scrap-of-sharecropper-immortality-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We’re not fighting for a scrap of sharecropper immortality with the strings hanging off it like Mafioso spaghetti. We want the whole tamale. The Johnsons are taking over the Western Lands. We built it with our brains and our hands. We paid for it with our blood and our lives. It’s ours and we’re going to take it. And we are not applying in triplicate to the Immortality Control Board. Anybody gets in our way we will get our communal back against a rock or a tree and fight the way a raccoon will fight a fucking dog." -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205281-dance-like-you-re-stamping-on-a-human-face-forever-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 09:13:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Warren Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205281-dance-like-you-re-stamping-on-a-human-face-forever-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dance like you're stamping on a human face forever, love like you've been in a serious car crash that minced the front of your brain, stab like no one can arrest you, and live like there's no such thing as God." -- Warren Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321305-scrape-the-surface-of-language-and-you-will-behold-interstellar</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 09:15:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Velimir Khlebnikov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321305-scrape-the-surface-of-language-and-you-will-behold-interstellar]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Scrape the surface of language, and you will behold interstellar space and the skin that encloses it." -- Velimir Khlebnikov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321307-but-every-line-we-write-breathes-victory-and-challenge-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 09:17:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Velimir Khlebnikov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321307-but-every-line-we-write-breathes-victory-and-challenge-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But every line we write breathes victory and challenge, the bad temper of a conqueror, underground explosions, howls. We are a volcano. We vomit forth black smoke. 
The heavens open and out comes an imposing
Pile of garbage; it looks a lot like Leo Tolstoy" -- Velimir Khlebnikov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321412-sometimes-i-think-nothing-is-simple-but-the-feeling-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 16:09:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Lester Bangs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321412-sometimes-i-think-nothing-is-simple-but-the-feeling-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I think nothing is simple but the feeling of pain." -- Lester Bangs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321414-i-suspect-almost-every-day-that-i-m-living-for-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 16:09:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Lester Bangs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321414-i-suspect-almost-every-day-that-i-m-living-for-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I suspect almost every day that I’m living for nothing, I get depressed and I feel self-destructive and a lot of the time I don’t like myself. What’s more, the proximity of other humans often fills me with overwhelming anxiety, but I also feel that this precarious sentience is all we’ve got and, simplistic as it may seem, it’s a person’s duty to the potentials of his own soul to make the best of it. We’re all stuck on this often miserable earth where life is essentially tragic, but there are glints of beauty and bedrock joy that come shining through from time to precious time to remind anybody who cares to see that there is something higher and larger than ourselves. And I am not talking about your putrefying gods, I am talking about a sense of wonder about life itself and the feeling that there is some redemptive factor you must at least search for until you drop dead of natural causes." -- Lester Bangs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321415-the-trend-toward-narcissistic-flair-has-been-responsible-in-large</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 16:10:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Lester Bangs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321415-the-trend-toward-narcissistic-flair-has-been-responsible-in-large]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trend toward narcissistic flair has been responsible in large part for smiting rock with the superstar virus, which revolves around the substituting of attitudes and flamboyant trappings, into which the audience can project their fantasies, for the simple desire to make music, get loose, knock the folks out or get ‘em up dancin.’ It’s not enough just to do those things anymore; what you must do instead if you want success on any large scale is figure a way of getting yourself associated in the audience’s mind with their pieties and their sense of “community,” i.e., ram it home that you’re one of THEM; or, alternately, deck and bake yourself into an image configuration so blatant or outrageous that you become a culture myth." -- Lester Bangs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321416-look-at-it-this-way-there-are-many-here-among</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 16:11:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Lester Bangs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321416-look-at-it-this-way-there-are-many-here-among]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look at it this way: there are many here among us for whom the life force is best represented by the livid twitching of one tortured nerve, or even a full-scale anxiety attack. I do not subscribe to this point of view 100%, but I understand it, have lived it. Thus the shriek, the caterwaul, the chainsaw gnarlgnashing, the yowl and the whizz that decapitates may be reheard by the adventurous or emotionally damaged as mellifluous bursts of unarguable affirmation." -- Lester Bangs]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
