<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/240825-lindsay]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/240825-lindsay" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2010 08:44:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230609-thinking-as-he-had-thought-before-and-would-think-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2010 08:44:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230609-thinking-as-he-had-thought-before-and-would-think-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...thinking as he had thought before and would think again and as every other man has thought: how false the most profound book turns out to be when applied to life." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309485-nobody-tells-this-to-people-who-are-beginners-i-wish</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 15:27:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Ira Glass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309485-nobody-tells-this-to-people-who-are-beginners-i-wish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody tells this to people who are beginners, I wish someone told me. All of us who do creative work, we get into it because we have good taste. But there is this gap. For the first couple years you make stuff, it’s just not that good. It’s trying to be good, it has potential, but it’s not. But your taste, the thing that got you into the game, is still killer. And your taste is why your work disappoints you. A lot of people never get past this phase, they quit. Most people I know who do interesting, creative work went through years of this. We know our work doesn’t have this special thing that we want it to have. We all go through this. And if you are just starting out or you are still in this phase, you gotta know its normal and the most important thing you can do is do a lot of work. Put yourself on a deadline so that every week you will finish one story. It is only by going through a volume of work that you will close that gap, and your work will be as good as your ambitions. And I took longer to figure out how to do this than anyone I’ve ever met. It’s gonna take awhile. It’s normal to take awhile. You’ve just gotta fight your way through." -- Ira Glass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43220-people-have-their-own-reasons-for-dying-it-might-look</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 08:45:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43220-people-have-their-own-reasons-for-dying-it-might-look]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People have their own reasons for dying. It might look simple, but it never is. It's just like a rock. What's above ground is only a small part of it. But if you start pulling, it keeps coming and coming. The human mind dwells deep in darkness. Only the person himself knows the real reason, and maybe not even then." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398357-readers-will-always-insist-on-adventures-and-though-you-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 14:30:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398357-readers-will-always-insist-on-adventures-and-though-you-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Readers will always insist on adventures, and though you can have grief without adventures, you cannot have adventures without grief." -- Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
