<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/243214-anggita]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/243214-anggita" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 20:03:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24172-we-danced-too-wild-and-we-sang-too-long-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 20:03:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anggita add a quote by Pearl Cleage]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24172-we-danced-too-wild-and-we-sang-too-long-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We danced too wild, and we sang too long, and we hugged too hard, and we kissed too sweet, and howled just as loud as we wanted to howl, because by now we were all old enough to know that what looks like crazy on an ordinary day looks a lot like love if you catch it in the moonlight." -- Pearl Cleage]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464973-what-we-call-the-present-is-given-shape-by-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 20:07:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anggita add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464973-what-we-call-the-present-is-given-shape-by-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What we call the present is given shape by an accumulation of the past." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/534783-mathematicians-call-them-twin-primes-pairs-of-prime-numbers-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 20:09:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anggita add a quote by Paolo Giordano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/534783-mathematicians-call-them-twin-primes-pairs-of-prime-numbers-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mathematicians call them twin primes: pairs of prime numbers that are close to each other, almost neighbors, but between them there is always an even number that prevents them from truly touching. Numbers like 11 and 13, like 17 and 19, 41 and 43. If you have the patience to go on counting, you discover that these pairs gradually become rarer. You encounter increasingly isolated primes, lost in that silent, measured space made only of ciphers, and you develop a distressing presentiment that the pairs encountered up until that point were accidental, that solitude is the true destiny. Then, just when you’re about to surrender, when you no longer have the desire to go on counting, you come across another pair of twins, clutching each other tightly. There is a common conviction among mathematicians that however far you go, there will always be another two, even if no one can say where exactly, until they are discovered.

Mattia thought that he and Alice were like that, twin primes, alone and lost, close but not close enough to really touch each other. He had never told her that. When he imagined confessing these things to her, the thin layer of sweat on his hands evaporated completely and for a good ten minutes he was no longer capable of touching anything." -- Paolo Giordano]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
