<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/243744-janet]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/243744-janet" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 10:02:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/326007-excerpt-the-usual-i-say-essence-spirit-medicine-a-taste</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 10:02:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Nick Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/326007-excerpt-the-usual-i-say-essence-spirit-medicine-a-taste]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[excerpt] The usual I say. Essence. Spirit. Medicine. A taste. I say top shelf. Straight up. A shot. A sip. A nip. I say another round. I say brace yourself. Lift a few. Hoist a few. Work the elbow. Bottoms up. Belly up. Set ‘em up. What’ll it be. Name your poison. I say same again. I say all around. I say my good man. I say my drinking buddy. I say git that in ya. Then a quick one. Then a nightcap. Then throw one back. Then knock one down. Fast &amp; furious I say. Could savage a drink I say. Chug. Chug-a-lug. Gulp. Sauce. Mother’s milk. Everclear. Moonshine. White lightning. Firewater. Hootch. Relief. Now you’re talking I say. Live a little I say. Drain it I say. Kill it I say. Feeling it I say. Wobbly. Breakfast of champions I say. I say candy is dandy but liquor is quicker. I say Houston, we have a drinking problem. I say the cause of, and solution to, all of life’s problems. I say god only knows what I’d be without you. I say thirsty. I say parched. I say wet my whistle. Dying of thirst. Lap it up. Hook me up. Watering hole. Knock a few back. Pound a few down. My office. Out with the boys I say. Unwind I say. Nurse one I say. Apply myself I say. Toasted. Glow. A cold one a tall one a frosty I say. One for the road I say. Two-fisted I say. Never trust a man who doesn’t drink I say. Drink any man under the table I say. Then a binge then a spree then a jag then a bout. Coming home on all fours. Could use a drink I say. A shot of confidence I say. Steady my nerves I say. Drown my sorrows. I say kill for a drink. I say keep ‘em comin’. I say a stiff one. Drink deep drink hard hit the bottle. Two sheets to the wind then. Knackered then. Under the influence then. Half in the bag then. Out of my skull I say. Liquored up. Rip-roaring. Slammed. Fucking jacked. The booze talking. The room spinning. Feeling no pain. Buzzed. Giddy. Silly. Impaired. Intoxicated. Stewed. Juiced. Plotzed. Inebriated. Laminated. Swimming. Elated. Exalted. Debauched. Rock on. Drunk on. Bring it on. Pissed. Then bleary. Then bloodshot. Glassy-eyed. Red-nosed. Dizzy then. Groggy. On a bender I say. On a spree. I say off the wagon. I say on a slip. I say the drink. I say the bottle. I say drinkie-poo. A drink a drunk a drunkard. Swill. Swig. Shitfaced. Fucked up. Stupefied. Incapacitated. Raging. Seeing double. Shitty. Take the edge off I say. That’s better I say. Loaded I say. Wasted. Off my ass. Befuddled. Reeling. Tanked. Punch-drunk. Mean drunk. Maintenance drunk. Sloppy drunk happy drunk weepy drunk blind drunk dead drunk. Serious drinker. Hard drinker. Lush. Drink like a fish. Boozer. Booze hound. Alkie. Sponge. Then muddled. Then woozy. Then clouded. What day is it? Do you know me? Have you seen me? When did I start? Did I ever stop? Slurring. Reeling. Staggering. Overserved they say. Drunk as a skunk they say. Falling down drunk. Crawling down drunk. Drunk &amp; disorderly. I say high tolerance. I say high capacity. They say protective custody. Blitzed. Shattered. Zonked. Annihilated. Blotto. Smashed. Soaked. Screwed. Pickled. Bombed. Stiff. Frazzled. Blasted. Plastered. Hammered. Tore up. Ripped up. Destroyed. Whittled. Plowed. Overcome. Overtaken. Comatose. Dead to the world. The old K.O. The horrors I say. The heebie-jeebies I say. The beast I say. The dt’s. B’jesus &amp; pink elephants. A mindbender. Hittin’ it kinda hard they say. Go easy they say. Last call they say. Quitting time they say. They say shut off. They say dry out. Pass out. Lights out. Blackout. The bottom. The walking wounded. Cross-eyed &amp; painless. Gone to the world. Gone. Gonzo. Wrecked. Sleep it off. Wake up on the floor. End up in the gutter. Off the stuff. Dry. Dry heaves. Gag. White knuckle. Lightweight I say. Hair of the dog I say. Eye-opener I say. A drop I say. A slug. A taste. A swallow. Down the hatch I say. I wouldn’t say no I say. I say whatever he’s having. I say next one’s on me. I say bottoms up. Put it on my tab. I say one more. I say same again" -- Nick Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3273-if-people-bring-so-much-courage-to-this-world-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 16:26:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3273-if-people-bring-so-much-courage-to-this-world-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If people bring so much courage to this world the world has to kill them to break them, so of course it kills them. The world breaks every one and afterward many are strong at the broken places. But those that will not break it kills. It kills the very good and the very gentle and the very brave impartially. If you are none of these you can be sure it will kill you too but there will be no special hurry." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48859-alcohol-is-the-river-we-sit-on-the-banks-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 16:31:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Nick Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48859-alcohol-is-the-river-we-sit-on-the-banks-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alcohol is the river we sit on the banks of, contemplating.  Sometimes we watch ourselves float past, sometimes we watch ourselves sink." -- Nick Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220678-sometimes-i-d-see-my-father-walking-past-my-building-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 16:32:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Nick Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220678-sometimes-i-d-see-my-father-walking-past-my-building-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I'd see my father, walking past my building on his way to another nowhere. I could have given him a key, offered a piece of my floor. A futon. A bed. But I never did. If I let him inside I would become him, the line between us would blur, my own slow-motion car wreck would speed up. The slogan on the side of a moving company truck read TOGETHER WE ARE GOING PLACES--modified by a vandal or a disgruntled employee to read TOGETHER WE ARE GOING DOWN. If I went to the drowning man the drowning man would pull me under. I couldn't be his life raft." -- Nick Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102579-how-did-you-go-bankrupt-two-ways-gradually-then-suddenly</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 16:34:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102579-how-did-you-go-bankrupt-two-ways-gradually-then-suddenly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How did you go bankrupt?&quot; 
Two ways. Gradually, then suddenly." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/605867-this-wine-is-too-good-for-toast-drinking-my-dear-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 16:36:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/605867-this-wine-is-too-good-for-toast-drinking-my-dear-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This wine is too good for toast-drinking, my dear. You don't want to mix emotions up with a wine like that. You lose the taste." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/951979-every-few-months-or-so-at-home-pops-had-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 11:02:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Eddie Huang]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/951979-every-few-months-or-so-at-home-pops-had-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every few months or so at home, Pops had to have Taiwanese ’Mian. Not the Dan-Dan Mian you get at Szechuan restaurants or in Fuchsia Dunlop’s book, but Taiwanese Dan-Dan. The trademark of ours is the use of clear pork bone stock, sesame paste, and crushed peanuts on top. You can add chili oil if you want, but I take it clean because when done right, you taste the essence of pork and the bitterness of sesame paste; the texture is somewhere between soup and ragout. Creamy, smooth, and still soupy. A little za cai (pickled radish) on top, chopped scallions, and you’re done. I realized that day, it’s the simple things in life. It’s not about a twelve-course tasting of unfamiliar ingredients or mass-produced water-added rib-chicken genetically modified monstrosity of meat that makes me feel alive. It’s getting a bowl of food that doesn’t have an agenda. The ingredients are the ingredients because they work and nothing more. These noodles were transcendent not because he used the best produce or protein or because it was locally sourced, but because he worked his dish. You can’t buy a championship.
Did this old man invent Dan-Dan Mian? No. But did he perfect it with techniques and standards never before seen? Absolutely. He took a dish people were making in homes, made it better than anyone else, put it on front street, and established a standard. That’s professional cooking. To take something that already speaks to us, do it at the highest level, and force everyone else to step up, too. Food at its best uplifts the whole community, makes everyone rise to its standard. That’s what that Dan-Dan Mian did. If I had the honor of cooking my father’s last meal, I wouldn’t think twice. Dan-Dan Mian with a bullet, no question." -- Eddie Huang]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2032-there-is-nothing-to-writing-all-you-do-is-sit</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 11:08:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2032-there-is-nothing-to-writing-all-you-do-is-sit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing to writing. All you do is sit down at a typewriter and bleed." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27292-i-love-sleep-my-life-has-the-tendency-to-fall</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 11:08:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27292-i-love-sleep-my-life-has-the-tendency-to-fall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love sleep. My life has the tendency to fall apart when I'm awake, you know?" -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13299-i-was-born-lost-and-take-no-pleasure-in-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 11:09:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13299-i-was-born-lost-and-take-no-pleasure-in-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was born lost and take no pleasure in being found." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22092-i-have-always-lived-violently-drunk-hugely-eaten-too-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 11:09:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22092-i-have-always-lived-violently-drunk-hugely-eaten-too-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always lived violently, drunk hugely, eaten too much or not at all, slept around the clock or missed two nights of sleeping, worked too hard and too long in glory, or slobbed for a time in utter laziness. I've lifted, pulled, chopped, climbed, made love with joy and taken my hangovers as a consequence, not as a punishment." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328134-socialism-never-took-root-in-america-because-the-poor-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 11:09:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328134-socialism-never-took-root-in-america-because-the-poor-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Socialism never took root in America because the poor see themselves not as an exploited proletariat but as temporarily embarrassed millionaires." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90495-remember-that-the-most-beautiful-things-in-the-world-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 11:14:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90495-remember-that-the-most-beautiful-things-in-the-world-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember that the most beautiful things in the world are the most useless; peacocks and lilies for instance." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27294-i-like-people-and-i-like-them-to-like-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 10:48:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27294-i-like-people-and-i-like-them-to-like-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like people and I like them to like me, but I wear my heart where God put it, on the inside. " -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27324-here-s-to-alcohol-the-rose-colored-glasses-of-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 10:48:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27324-here-s-to-alcohol-the-rose-colored-glasses-of-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to alcohol, the rose colored glasses of life." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4738-first-you-take-a-drink-then-the-drink-takes-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 10:54:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4738-first-you-take-a-drink-then-the-drink-takes-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First you take a drink, then the drink takes a drink, then the drink takes you." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96713-never-confuse-a-single-defeat-with-a-final-defeat</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 10:55:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96713-never-confuse-a-single-defeat-with-a-final-defeat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never confuse a single defeat with a final defeat." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331949-i-m-a-slave-to-my-emotions-to-my-likes-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 11:31:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331949-i-m-a-slave-to-my-emotions-to-my-likes-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm a slave to my emotions, to my likes, to my hatred of boredom, to most of my desires." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40724-sometimes-it-is-harder-to-deprive-oneself-of-a-pain</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 11:32:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40724-sometimes-it-is-harder-to-deprive-oneself-of-a-pain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes it is harder to deprive oneself of a pain than of a pleasure." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57886-all-great-literature-is-one-of-two-stories-a-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 11:37:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Leo Tolstoy ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57886-all-great-literature-is-one-of-two-stories-a-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All great literature is one of two stories; a man goes on a journey or a stranger comes to town." -- Leo Tolstoy ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919-the-man-who-does-not-read-has-no-advantage-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 11:38:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919-the-man-who-does-not-read-has-no-advantage-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who does not read has no advantage over the man who cannot read." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85749-god-created-war-so-that-americans-would-learn-geography</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 11:39:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85749-god-created-war-so-that-americans-would-learn-geography]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God created war so that Americans would learn geography." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/600-wrinkles-should-merely-indicate-where-the-smiles-have-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 11:39:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/600-wrinkles-should-merely-indicate-where-the-smiles-have-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wrinkles should merely indicate where the smiles have been." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174533-never-allow-someone-to-be-your-priority-while-allowing-yourself</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 11:40:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174533-never-allow-someone-to-be-your-priority-while-allowing-yourself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never allow someone to be your priority while allowing yourself to be their option." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71748-boredom-the-desire-for-desires</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 11:41:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71748-boredom-the-desire-for-desires]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Boredom: the desire for desires." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37529-sometimes-i-wonder-whether-the-world-is-being-run-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 11:43:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37529-sometimes-i-wonder-whether-the-world-is-being-run-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I wonder whether the world is being run by smart people who are putting us on or by imbeciles who really mean it." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7076-the-most-effective-way-to-destroy-people-is-to-deny</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 13:48:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7076-the-most-effective-way-to-destroy-people-is-to-deny]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most effective way to destroy people is to deny and obliterate their own understanding of their history." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321226-if-people-cannot-write-well-they-cannot-think-well-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 15:15:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321226-if-people-cannot-write-well-they-cannot-think-well-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If people cannot write well, they cannot think well, and if they cannot think well, others will do their thinking for them." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2621-love-all-trust-a-few-do-wrong-to-none</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 17:42:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2621-love-all-trust-a-few-do-wrong-to-none]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love all, trust a few, do wrong to none." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1461-one-should-never-trust-a-woman-who-tells-one-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 17:47:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janet add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1461-one-should-never-trust-a-woman-who-tells-one-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One should never trust a woman who tells one her real age. A woman who would tell one that would tell one anything." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
