<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/244816-nicole]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/244816-nicole" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 13:55:18 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74329-i-talk-about-going-to-george-w-bush-s-inauguration-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 13:55:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Sarah Vowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74329-i-talk-about-going-to-george-w-bush-s-inauguration-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I talk about going to [George W. Bush's] Inauguration and crying
when he took the oath, 'cause I was so afraid he was going to
wreck the economy and muck up the drinking water'... the failure of
my pessimistic imagination at that moment boggles my mind now." -- Sarah Vowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 13:56:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The person, be it gentleman or lady, who has not pleasure in a good novel, must be intolerably stupid." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2627-the-trouble-with-having-an-open-mind-of-course-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 13:57:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2627-the-trouble-with-having-an-open-mind-of-course-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble with having an open mind, of course, is that people will insist on coming along and trying to put things in it." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25184-you-never-really-understand-a-person-until-you-consider-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 14:01:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25184-you-never-really-understand-a-person-until-you-consider-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You never really understand a person until you consider things from his point of view... Until you climb inside of his skin and walk around in it." -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61392-death-s-got-an-invisibility-cloak-harry-interrupted-again-so-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 14:02:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61392-death-s-got-an-invisibility-cloak-harry-interrupted-again-so-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death's got an Invisibility Cloak?&quot; Harry interrupted again.
&quot;So he can sneak up on people,&quot; said Ron. &quot;Sometimes he gets bored of running at them, flapping his arms and shrieking..." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57741-dumbledore-watched-her-fly-away-and-as-her-silvery-glow</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 14:03:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57741-dumbledore-watched-her-fly-away-and-as-her-silvery-glow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dumbledore watched her fly away, and as her silvery glow faded he turned back to Snape, and his eyes were full of tears.
&quot;After all this time?&quot;
&quot;Always,&quot; said Snape." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4566-in-vain-have-i-struggled-it-will-not-do-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 14:03:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4566-in-vain-have-i-struggled-it-will-not-do-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In vain have I struggled. It will not do. My feelings will not be repressed. You must allow me to tell you how ardently I admire and love you." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 14:24:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I say is, a town isn't a town without a bookstore. It may call itself a town, but unless it's got a bookstore it knows it's not fooling a soul." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3867-for-what-do-we-live-but-to-make-sport-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 14:43:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3867-for-what-do-we-live-but-to-make-sport-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For what do we live, but to make sport for our neighbors, and laugh at them in our turn?" -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584441-men-always-say-that-as-the-defining-compliment-don-t-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 09:40:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584441-men-always-say-that-as-the-defining-compliment-don-t-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men always say that as the defining compliment, don’t they? She’s a cool girl. Being the Cool Girl means I am a hot, brilliant, funny woman who adores football, poker, dirty jokes, and burping, who plays video games, drinks cheap beer, loves threesomes and anal sex, and jams hot dogs and hamburgers into her mouth like she’s hosting the world’s biggest culinary gang bang while somehow maintaining a size 2, because Cool Girls are above all hot. Hot and understanding. Cool Girls never get angry; they only smile in a chagrined, loving manner and let their men do whatever they want. Go ahead, shit on me, I don’t mind, I’m the Cool Girl.

Men actually think this girl exists. Maybe they’re fooled because so many women are willing to pretend to be this girl. For a long time Cool Girl offended me. I used to see men – friends, coworkers, strangers – giddy over these awful pretender women, and I’d want to sit these men down and calmly say: You are not dating a woman, you are dating a woman who has watched too many movies written by socially awkward men who’d like to believe that this kind of woman exists and might kiss them. I’d want to grab the poor guy by his lapels or messenger bag and say: The bitch doesn’t really love chili dogs that much – no one loves chili dogs that much! And the Cool Girls are even more pathetic: They’re not even pretending to be the woman they want to be, they’re pretending to be the woman a man wants them to be. Oh, and if you’re not a Cool Girl, I beg you not to believe that your man doesn’t want the Cool Girl. It may be a slightly different version – maybe he’s a vegetarian, so Cool Girl loves seitan and is great with dogs; or maybe he’s a hipster artist, so Cool Girl is a tattooed, bespectacled nerd who loves comics. There are variations to the window dressing, but believe me, he wants Cool Girl, who is basically the girl who likes every fucking thing he likes and doesn’t ever complain. (How do you know you’re not Cool Girl? Because he says things like: “I like strong women.” If he says that to you, he will at some point fuck someone else. Because “I like strong women” is code for “I hate strong women.”)" -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
