<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/245387-rachel-piper]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/245387-rachel-piper" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 22:54:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242608-how-could-i-have-been-so-ignorant-she-thinks-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 22:54:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242608-how-could-i-have-been-so-ignorant-she-thinks-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How could I have been so ignorant? she thinks. So stupid, so unseeing, so given over to carelessness. But without such ignorance, such carelessness, how could we live? If you knew what was going to happen, if you knew everything that was going to happen next—if you knew in advance the consequences of your own actions—you'd be doomed. You'd be as ruined as God. You'd be a stone. You'd never eat or drink or laugh or get out of bed in the morning. You'd never love anyone, ever again. You'd never dare to." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15873-was-everyone-else-really-as-alive-as-she-was-if-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 22:54:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15873-was-everyone-else-really-as-alive-as-she-was-if-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Was everyone else really as alive as she was?...If the answer was yes, then the world, the social world, was unbearably complicated, with two billion voices, and everyone's thoughts striving in equal importance and everyone's claim on life as intense, and everyone thinking they were unique, when no one was." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157019-i-kept-the-fingers-of-my-left-hand-crossed-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 21:01:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Mary Karr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157019-i-kept-the-fingers-of-my-left-hand-crossed-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I kept the fingers of my left hand crossed all the time, while on my right-hand fingers I counted anything at all—steps to the refrigerator, seconds on the clock, words in a sentence—to keep my head occupied. The counting felt like something to hang on to, as if finding the right numbers might somehow crack the code on whatever system ran the slippery universe we were moving through." -- Mary Karr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20787-sure-the-world-breeds-monsters-but-kindness-grows-just-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 21:03:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Mary Karr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20787-sure-the-world-breeds-monsters-but-kindness-grows-just-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sure the world breeds monsters, but kindness grows just as wild..." -- Mary Karr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53452-the-only-thing-you-can-do-easily-is-be-wrong</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 22:54:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Norton Juster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53452-the-only-thing-you-can-do-easily-is-be-wrong]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only thing you can do easily is be wrong, and that's hardly worth the effort." -- Norton Juster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100878-and-you-snap-out-of-it-or-are-snapped-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 22:54:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Mary Karr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100878-and-you-snap-out-of-it-or-are-snapped-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And you snap out of it. Or are snapped out of it. Never again will you lay a hand against yourself, not as long as there are plums to eat and somebody--anybody--who gives enough of a damn to haul them to you. So long as you bear the least nibblet of love for any other creature in this dark world, though in love portions are never stingy. There are no smidgens on pinches, only rolling abundance. That's how you acquire the resolution for survival that the upcoming years are about to demand. You don't give it. You earn it." -- Mary Karr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82221-you-know-when-it-works-love-is-pretty-amazing-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 21:06:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82221-you-know-when-it-works-love-is-pretty-amazing-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know, when it works, love is pretty amazing. It's not overrated. There's a reason for all those songs." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51288-revenge-may-be-wicked-but-it-s-natural</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 21:11:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by William Makepeace Thackeray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51288-revenge-may-be-wicked-but-it-s-natural]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Revenge may be wicked, but it’s natural." -- William Makepeace Thackeray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42147-right-now-i-d-like-all-my-troubles-to-stand-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 21:16:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Shannon Hale]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42147-right-now-i-d-like-all-my-troubles-to-stand-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Right now I'd like all my troubles to stand in front of me in a straight line, and one by one I'd give each a black eye. " -- Shannon Hale]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68226-and-this-i-believe-that-the-free-exploring-mind-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 21:23:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68226-and-this-i-believe-that-the-free-exploring-mind-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And this I believe: that the free, exploring mind of the individual human is the most valuable thing in the world. And this I would fight for: the freedom of the mind to take any direction it wishes, undirected. And this I must fight against: any idea, religion, or government which limits or destroys the individual. This is what I am and what I am about." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/379469-sometimes-we-become-what-we-see-sometimes-we-take-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2011 22:07:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Sharon Shinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/379469-sometimes-we-become-what-we-see-sometimes-we-take-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes we become what we see. Sometimes we take what we see and make it the model for what we refuse to become." -- Sharon Shinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1894-this-is-not-a-novel-to-be-tossed-aside-lightly</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2011 22:14:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Dorothy Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1894-this-is-not-a-novel-to-be-tossed-aside-lightly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is not a novel to be tossed aside lightly. It should be thrown with great force." -- Dorothy Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280130-it-happens-the-world-over---we-love-ourselves-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2011 22:22:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Irene Hunt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280130-it-happens-the-world-over---we-love-ourselves-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It happens the world over - we love ourselves more than we do the one we say we love.  We all want to be Number One, we've got to be Number One or nothing! We can't see that we could make ourselves loved and needed in the Number Two, or Three, or Four spot.  No sir, we've got to be Number One, and if we can't make it, we'll rip and tear at the loved one till we've ruined every smidgin of love that was ever there." -- Irene Hunt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23053-the-only-way-you-can-write-the-truth-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 13:20:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23053-the-only-way-you-can-write-the-truth-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only way you can write the truth is to assume that what you set down will never be read. Not by any other person, and not even by yourself at some later date. Otherwise you begin excusing yourself. You must see the writing as emerging like a long scroll of ink from the index finger of your right hand; you must see your left hand erasing it." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/469974-but-hidden-drawers-lockable-diaries-and-cryptographic-systems-could-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 22:09:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/469974-but-hidden-drawers-lockable-diaries-and-cryptographic-systems-could-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But hidden drawers, lockable diaries and cryptographic systems could not conceal from Briony the simple truth: she had no secrets. Her wish for a harmonious, organised world denied her the reckless possibilities of wrongdoing. Mayhem and destruction were too chaotic for her tastes, and she did not have it in her to be cruel. Her effective status as an only child, as well as the relative isolation of the Tallis house, kept her, at least during the long summer holidays, from girlish intrigues with friends. Nothing in her life was sufficiently interesting or shameful to merit hiding; no one knew about the squirrel's skull beneath her bed, but no one wanted to know." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341092-her-efforts-received-encouragement-in-fact-they-were-welcomed-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 22:18:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341092-her-efforts-received-encouragement-in-fact-they-were-welcomed-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her efforts received encouragement. In fact, they were welcomed as the Tallises began to understand that the baby of the family possessed a strange mind and a facility with words. The long afternoons she spent browsing through the dictionary and thesaurus made for constructions that were inept, but hauntingly so: the coins a villain concealed in his pocket were 'esoteric,' a hoodlum caught stealing a car wept in 'shameless auto-exculpation,' the heroine on her thoroughbred stallion made a 'cursory' journey through the night, the king's furrowed brow was the 'hieroglyph' of his displeasure." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/450547-briony-began-to-understand-the-chasm-that-lay-between-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 22:19:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/450547-briony-began-to-understand-the-chasm-that-lay-between-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Briony began to understand the chasm that lay between an idea and its execution" -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487934-and-the-truth-is-that-i-m-not-ed-is-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 11:11:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Daniel Handler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487934-and-the-truth-is-that-i-m-not-ed-is-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the truth is that I'm &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt;, Ed, is what I wanted to tell you. I'm not arty like everyone says who doesn't know me, I don't paint, I can't draw, I play no instrument, I can't sing. I'm not in plays, I wanted to say, I don't write poems. I can't dance except tipsy at dances. I'm not athletic, I'm not a goth or a cheerleader, I'm not treasurer or co-captain. I'm not gay and out and proud, I'm not that kid from Sri Lanka, not a triplet, a prep, a drunk, a genius, a hippie, a Christian, a slut, not even one of those super-Jewish girls with a yarmulke gang wishing everyone a happy Sukkoth. I'm not anything, this is what I realized ... I like movies, everyone knows I do -- I love them -- but I will never be in charge of one because my ideas are stupid and wrong in my head. There's nothing different about that, nothing fascinating, interesting, worth looking at." -- Daniel Handler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501040-leave-three-englishmen-in-a-room-and-they-will-invent</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 21:49:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Julian Fellowes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501040-leave-three-englishmen-in-a-room-and-they-will-invent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Leave three Englishmen in a room and they will invent a rule that prevents a fourth joining them." -- Julian Fellowes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/637613-he-might-have-been-encased-in-a-thick-glass-bubble</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2012 15:33:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/637613-he-might-have-been-encased-in-a-thick-glass-bubble]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He might have been encased in a thick glass bubble, so separate did he feel from his three dining companions. It was a sensation with which he was only too familiar, that of walking in a giant sphere of worry, enclosed by it, watching his own terrors roll by, obscuring the outside world." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1201295-we-can-still-talk-to-each-other-i-say-nothing-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 00:52:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Jenny Han]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1201295-we-can-still-talk-to-each-other-i-say-nothing-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can still talk to each other,” I say. “Nothing’s changed.” That’s the biggest lie I’ve ever told him, even bigger than the lie about my so-called dead twin Marcella. Until a couple of years ago Josh thought I had a twin sister named Marcella who died of leukemia." -- Jenny Han]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
