<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/245938-amber]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/245938-amber" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 18:18:23 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282001-friday-22-june-1821-halifax-i-owe-a-good-deal</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 18:18:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Anne Lister]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282001-friday-22-june-1821-halifax-i-owe-a-good-deal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friday 22 June 1821 [Halifax]

I owe a good deal to this journal.  By unburdening my mind on paper I feel, as it were, in some degree to get rid of it; it seems made over to a friend that hears it patiently, keeps it faithfully, and by never forgetting anything, is always ready to compare the past &amp; present and thus to cheer &amp; edify the future." -- Anne Lister]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23747-i-will-love-you-always-when-this-red-hair-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 18:19:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Laurell K. Hamilton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23747-i-will-love-you-always-when-this-red-hair-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will love you always. When this red hair is white, I will still love you. When the smooth softness of youth is replaced by the delicate softness of age, I will still want to touch your skin. When your face is full of the lines of every smile you have ever smiled, of every surprise I have seen flash through your eyes, when every tear you have ever cried has left its mark upon your face,I will treasure you all the more, because I was there to see it all. I will share your life with you, Meredith, and I will love you until the last breath leaves your body or mine." -- Laurell K. Hamilton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10488-life-is-a-series-of-surprises-and-would-not-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 18:20:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10488-life-is-a-series-of-surprises-and-would-not-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is a series of surprises and would not be worth taking or keeping if it were not." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159300-the-most-significant-gifts-are-the-ones-most-easily-overlooked</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 18:33:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159300-the-most-significant-gifts-are-the-ones-most-easily-overlooked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most significant gifts are the ones most easily overlooked.  Small, everyday blessings:  woods, health, music, laughter, memories, books, family, friends, second chances, warm fireplaces, and all the footprints scattered throughout our days." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156662-everything-is-more-complicated-than-you-think-you-only-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 18:33:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Charlie Kaufman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156662-everything-is-more-complicated-than-you-think-you-only-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything is more complicated than you think. You only see a tenth of what is true. There are a million little strings attached to every choice you make; you can destroy your life every time you choose. But maybe you won't know for twenty years. And you'll never ever trace it to its source. And you only get one chance to play it out. Just try and figure out your own divorce. And they say there is no fate, but there is: it's what you create. Even though the world goes on for eons and eons, you are here for a fraction of a fraction of a second. Most of your time is spent being dead or not yet born. But while alive, you wait in vain, wasting years, for a phone call or a letter or a look from someone or something to make it all right. And it never comes or it seems to but doesn't really. And so you spend your time in vague regret or vaguer hope for something good to come along. Something to make you feel connected, to make you feel whole, to make you feel loved." -- Charlie Kaufman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79464-nothing-like-being-with-people-you-ve-known-almost-your-entire</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 18:34:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Jane Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79464-nothing-like-being-with-people-you-ve-known-almost-your-entire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing like being with people you’ve known almost your entire life. Having a shared history is something you just can’t create with the new ones. No matter how much you like that, it just isn’t the same. " -- Jane Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/91432-second-chances-do-come-your-way-like-trains-they-arrive</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 18:34:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Jill A. Davis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/91432-second-chances-do-come-your-way-like-trains-they-arrive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Second chances do come your way. Like trains, they arrive and depart regularly. Recognizing the ones that matter is the trick." -- Jill A. Davis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240649-it-seemed-cruelly-unfair-to-me-even-then-how-fast</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 18:36:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240649-it-seemed-cruelly-unfair-to-me-even-then-how-fast]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seemed cruelly unfair to me, even then, how fast your life can change before you have an opportunity to rethink your choices. We should get second chances on the big stuff. We should come equipped with erasers attached to the tops of our heads. Like pencils. We should be able to flip over and scribble away mistakes, at least once or twice during the duration of our existence, especially in matters of life and death." -- Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50118-even-the-most-worthless-thing-in-the-world-can-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 18:39:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Robert R Mccammon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50118-even-the-most-worthless-thing-in-the-world-can-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even the most worthless thing in the world can be beautiful, it just takes the right touch" -- Robert R Mccammon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71891-all-my-life-i-ve-thought-i-needed-someone-to-complete</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 18:40:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71891-all-my-life-i-ve-thought-i-needed-someone-to-complete]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All my life I've thought I needed someone to complete me, now I know I need to belong to myself." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109715-stories-have-to-be-told-or-they-die-and-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 18:40:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109715-stories-have-to-be-told-or-they-die-and-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories have to be told or they die, and when they die, we can't remember who we are or why we're here." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202478-my-children-have-always-existed-at-the-deepest-center-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 18:44:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202478-my-children-have-always-existed-at-the-deepest-center-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My children have always existed at the deepest center of me, right there in the heart/hearth, but I struggled with the powerful demands of motherhood, chafing sometimes at the way they pulled me away from my separate life, not knowing how to balance them with my unwieldy need for solitude and creative expression." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161323-my-parents-danced-together-her-head-on-his-chest-both</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 19:48:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161323-my-parents-danced-together-her-head-on-his-chest-both]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My parents danced together, her head on his chest. Both had their eyes closed. They seemed so perfectly content. If you can find someone like that, someone who you can hold and close your eyes to the world with, then you're lucky. Even if it only lasts for a minute or a day. The image of them gently swaying to the music is how I picture love in my mind even after all these years." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146228-i-would-have-given-anything-to-keep-her-little-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 19:49:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146228-i-would-have-given-anything-to-keep-her-little-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would have given anything to keep her little.  They outgrow us so much faster than we outgrow them.
Brian Fitzgerald, talking about his children." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154024-i-suddenly-remember-being-very-little-and-being-embraced-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 19:50:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154024-i-suddenly-remember-being-very-little-and-being-embraced-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I suddenly remember being very little and being embraced by my father. I would try to put my arms around my father's waist, hug him back. I could never reach the whole way around the equator of his body; he was that much larger than life. Then one day, I could do it. I held him, instead of him holding me, and all I wanted at that moment was to have it back  the other way." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25651-the-only-time-you-truly-become-an-adult-is-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 19:53:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Douglas Kennedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25651-the-only-time-you-truly-become-an-adult-is-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only time you truly become an adult is when you finally forgive your parents for being just as flawed as everyone else." -- Douglas Kennedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78251-hug-and-kiss-whoever-helped-get-you---financially-mentally</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 19:54:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78251-hug-and-kiss-whoever-helped-get-you---financially-mentally]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hug and kiss whoever helped get you - financially, mentally, morally, emotionally - to this day. Parents, mentors, friends, teachers. If you're too uptight to do that, at least do the old handshake thing, but I recommend a hug and a kiss. Don't let the sun go down without saying thank you to someone, and without admitting to yourself that absolutely no one gets this far alone." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175011-stop-and-take-your-time-to-notice-things-and-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 20:39:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Cecelia Ahern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175011-stop-and-take-your-time-to-notice-things-and-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stop and take your time to notice things and make those things you notice matter." -- Cecelia Ahern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250408-you-know-the-reason-the-beatles-made-it-so-big-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 20:44:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by David Levithan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250408-you-know-the-reason-the-beatles-made-it-so-big-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know the reason The Beatles made it so big?...'I Wanna Hold Your Hand.' First single. Fucking brilliant. Perhaps the most fucking brilliant song ever written. Because they nailed it. That's what everyone wants. Not 24/7 hot wet sex. Not a marriage that lasts a hundred years. Not a Porsche...or a million-dollar crib. No. They wanna hold your hand. They have such a feeling that they can't hide. Every single successful song of the past fifty years can be traced back to 'I Wanna Hold Your Hand.' And every single successful love story has those unbearable and unbearably exciting moments of hand-holding." -- David Levithan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 18:11:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't see things as they are, we see them as we are." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4422-trust-yourself-you-know-more-than-you-think-you-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 18:11:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Benjamin Spock]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4422-trust-yourself-you-know-more-than-you-think-you-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Trust yourself. You know more than you think you do." -- Benjamin Spock]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28583-flatter-me-and-i-may-not-believe-you-criticize-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 18:45:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by William Arthur Ward]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28583-flatter-me-and-i-may-not-believe-you-criticize-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Flatter me, and I may not believe you. Criticize me, and I may not like you. Ignore me, and I may not forgive you. Encourage me, and I will not forget you. Love me and I may be forced to love you." -- William Arthur Ward]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186742-nothing-on-this-planet-can-compare-with-a-woman-s-love-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 18:45:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Steve Harvey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186742-nothing-on-this-planet-can-compare-with-a-woman-s-love-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing on this planet can compare with a woman’s love—it is kind and compassionate, patient and nurturing, generous and sweet and unconditional. Pure. If you are her man, she will walk on water and through a mountain for you, too, no matter how you’ve acted out, no matter what crazy thing you’ve done, no matter the time or demand. If you are her man, she will talk to you until there just aren’t any more words left to say, encourage you when you’re at rock bottom and think there just isn’t any way out, hold you in her arms when you’re sick, and laugh with you when you’re up. And if you’re her man and that woman loves you—I mean really loves you?—she will shine you up when you’re dusty, encourage you when you’re down, defend you even when she’s not so sure you were right, and hang on your every word, even when you’re not saying anything worth listening to. And no matter what you do, no matter how many times her friends say you’re no good, no matter how many times you slam the door on the relationship, she will give you her very best and then some, and keep right on trying to win over your heart, even when you act like everything she’s done to convince you she’s The One just isn’t good enough.
That’s a woman’s love—it stands the test of time, logic, and all circumstance. " -- Steve Harvey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98888-if-you-re-gonna-live-then-live-it-up-if-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 18:55:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Ben Harper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98888-if-you-re-gonna-live-then-live-it-up-if-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're gonna live, then live it up. If you're gonna give, then give it up. If you're gonna walk the Earth, then walk it proud. If you're gonna say the word, you got to say it loud." -- Ben Harper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6562-for-in-every-adult-there-dwells-the-child-that-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 19:22:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by John Connolly]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6562-for-in-every-adult-there-dwells-the-child-that-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For in every adult there dwells the child that was, and in every child there lies the adult that will be." -- John Connolly]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254542-that-s-what-makes-it-so-right-your-eyes-your-soul-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 19:25:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Bree Despain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254542-that-s-what-makes-it-so-right-your-eyes-your-soul-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's what makes it so right. Your eyes—your soul is there, but the rest of you is still so undefined. That's the beauty of childhood. The eyes show everything you've seen so far, but the rest of you is still so open to possibility, to whatever you might become." -- Bree Despain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216414-here-s-a-secret-everyone-if-they-live-long-enough-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 19:28:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Nick Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216414-here-s-a-secret-everyone-if-they-live-long-enough-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's a secret: Everyone, if they live long enough, will lose their way at some point. You will lose your way, you will wake up one morning and find yourself lost. This is a hard, simple truth. If it hasn't happened to you yet, consider yourself lucky. When it does, when one day you look around and nothing is recognizable, when you find yourself alone in a dark wood having lost the way, you may find it easier to blame it on someone else -- an errant lover, a missing father, a bad childhood -- or it may be easier to blame the map you were given -- folded too many times, out-of-date, tiny print -- but mostly, if you are honest, you will only be able to blame yourself.

One day I'll tell my daughter a story about a dark time, the dark days before she was born, and how her coming was a ray of light. We got lost for a while, the story will begin, but then we found our way." -- Nick Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6563-did-you-think-the-lion-was-sleeping-because-he-didn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 19:28:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Friedrich Schiller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6563-did-you-think-the-lion-was-sleeping-because-he-didn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did you think the lion was sleeping because he didn't roar?" -- Friedrich Schiller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58261-if-you-re-going-to-have-childhood-dreams-you-should-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 19:29:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Randy Pausch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58261-if-you-re-going-to-have-childhood-dreams-you-should-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you’re going to have childhood dreams you should have great parents who let you pursue them and express your creativity" -- Randy Pausch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136261-i-start-to-see-that-i-surround-myself-with-broken</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 19:30:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Julie Gregory]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136261-i-start-to-see-that-i-surround-myself-with-broken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I start to see that I surround myself with broken people; more broken than me. Ah, yes, let me count your cracks. Let's see, one hundred, two... yes, you'll do nicely. A cracked companion makes me look more whole, gives me something outside myself to care for. When I'm with whole, healed people I feel my own cracks, the shatters, the insanities of dislocation in myself." -- Julie Gregory]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
