<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/246035-juniar]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/246035-juniar" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2008 13:57:46 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65901-he-didn-t-mind-how-he-looked-to-other-people-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2008 13:57:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65901-he-didn-t-mind-how-he-looked-to-other-people-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He didn't mind how he looked to other people, because the nursery magic had made him Real, and when you are Real shabbiness doesn't matter." -- Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65921-you-have-swept-up-tea-leaves-from-the-tatami-mats</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2008 15:17:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Asari Yoshitoo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65921-you-have-swept-up-tea-leaves-from-the-tatami-mats]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have swept up tea leaves from the tatami mats;
hand peeled sun dried Japanese squash seeds;
cleaned the floors with the water that was used to clean the rice;
and finally you used your frequent super saver point card to save a few bucks,
to buy some nikuman to eat!!

Lucu Lucu book 3 ch.19 p.12" -- Asari Yoshitoo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65923-if-you-run-from-enemy-fire-i-ll-make-you-wash</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2008 15:31:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Naoki Urasawa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65923-if-you-run-from-enemy-fire-i-ll-make-you-wash]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you run from enemy fire, I'll make you wash dishes for the rest of your life!" -- Naoki Urasawa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66160-bagi-sebagian-orang-kebenaran-itu-penting-sebab-mereka-dapat-menerimanya</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 11:44:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Agatha Christie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66160-bagi-sebagian-orang-kebenaran-itu-penting-sebab-mereka-dapat-menerimanya]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bagi sebagian orang kebenaran itu penting, sebab mereka dapat menerimanya. Mereka dapat menghadapi kebenaran dengan tabah - ketabahan yang hanya dimiliki orang-orang yang mengharapkan kehidupan yang cerah." -- Agatha Christie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66162-reiko-had-not-kept-a-diary-and-was-now-denied</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 11:49:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Yukio Mishima]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66162-reiko-had-not-kept-a-diary-and-was-now-denied]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reiko had not kept a diary and was now denied the pleasure of assiduously rereading her record of the happiness of the past few months and consigning each page to the fire as she did so.

- Death in Midsummer and Other Stories" -- Yukio Mishima]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66167-mom-i-said-she-turned-can-i-talk-to-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 12:16:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66167-mom-i-said-she-turned-can-i-talk-to-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mom?&quot; I said. She turned. &quot;Can I talk to you about something?&quot;
  &quot;Of course, darling. Come here.&quot;
I took a few steps into the room. There was so much I wanted to say.
  &quot;I need you to be --&quot; I said, and then I started to cry.
  &quot;Be what?&quot; she said, opening her arms.
  &quot;Not sad,&quot; I said." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6267-and-by-the-way-everything-in-life-is-writable-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 12:51:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6267-and-by-the-way-everything-in-life-is-writable-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And by the way, everything in life is writable about if you have the outgoing guts to do it, and the imagination to improvise. The worst enemy to creativity is self-doubt." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15864-everyone-seems-to-have-a-clear-idea-of-how-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 12:54:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15864-everyone-seems-to-have-a-clear-idea-of-how-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone seems to have a clear idea of how other people should lead their lives, but none about his or her own." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30769-there-is-only-one-sin-and-that-is-theft-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2008 11:01:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30769-there-is-only-one-sin-and-that-is-theft-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is only one sin. and that is theft... when you tell a lie, you steal someones right to the truth." -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66808-it-was-how-wars-really-ended-dieffenbaker-supposed----not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 09:56:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66808-it-was-how-wars-really-ended-dieffenbaker-supposed----not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was how wars really ended, Dieffenbaker supposed -- not at truce tables but in cancer wards and office cafeterias and traffic jams. Wars died one tiny piece at a time, each piece something that fell like a memory, each lost like an echo that fades in winding hills. In the end even war ran up the white flag. Or so he hoped. He hoped that in the end even war surrendered." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66821-saatnya-angin-berbau-asin-datang-dari-laut-hari-ini-aku</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 10:28:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Hitoshi Ashinano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66821-saatnya-angin-berbau-asin-datang-dari-laut-hari-ini-aku]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Saatnya angin berbau asin datang dari laut.
Hari ini, aku akan bermain gekkin untukmu.
Suara denting senar melebur bersama udara, meresap dalam panca indera.
Terlihat seperti wewangian apakah nada-nada ini...
Dengan terlahirnya lagu ini, keberadaanmu mendapatkan makna baru.
Kalau bersedia, bernyanyilah bersamaku. Masih ada waktu sebelum gelap.
Waktu yang paling indah." -- Hitoshi Ashinano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18093-it-is-amazing-what-you-can-accomplish-if-you-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 10:56:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Harry S. Truman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18093-it-is-amazing-what-you-can-accomplish-if-you-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is amazing what you can accomplish if you do not care who gets the credit." -- Harry S. Truman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22131-i-believe-that-the-first-test-of-a-great-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 10:59:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by John Ruskin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22131-i-believe-that-the-first-test-of-a-great-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that the first test of a great man is his humility. I don't mean by humility, doubt of his power. But really great men have a curious feeling that the greatness is not of them, but through them. And they see something divine in every other man and are endlessly, foolishly, incredibly merciful." -- John Ruskin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6966-humility-is-just-as-much-the-opposite-of-self-abasement-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 11:00:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Dag Hammarskjöld]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6966-humility-is-just-as-much-the-opposite-of-self-abasement-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humility is just as much the opposite of self-abasement as it is of self-exaltation.  To be humble is not to make comparisons.  Secure in its reality, the self is neither better nor worse, bigger nor smaller, than anything else in the universe.  It *is*--is nothing, yet at the same time one with everything.  It is in this sense that humility is absolute self-effacement.

To be nothing in the self-effacement of humility, yet, for the sake of the task, to embody its whole weight and importance in your earing, as the one who has been called to undertake it.  To give to people, works, poetry, art, what the self can contribute, and to take, simply and freely, what belongs to it by reason of its identity.  Praise and blame, the winds of success and adversity, blow over such a life without leaving a trace or upsetting its balance." -- Dag Hammarskjöld]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3458-learning-to-believe-you-are-magnificent-and-gradually-to-discover</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 11:04:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Czesław Miłosz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3458-learning-to-believe-you-are-magnificent-and-gradually-to-discover]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Learning

To believe you are magnificent.  And gradually to discover that you are not magnificent.  Enough labor for one human life." -- Czesław Miłosz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43351-humility-is-throwing-oneself-away-in-complete-concentration-on-something</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 11:12:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43351-humility-is-throwing-oneself-away-in-complete-concentration-on-something]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humility is throwing oneself away in complete concentration on something or someone else." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5686-if-more-of-us-valued-food-and-cheer-and-song</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 04:06:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5686-if-more-of-us-valued-food-and-cheer-and-song]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If more of us valued food  and cheer and song above hoarded gold, it would be a merrier world." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60459-there-was-only-one-catch-and-that-was-catch-22-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 04:35:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60459-there-was-only-one-catch-and-that-was-catch-22-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was only one catch and that was Catch-22, which specified that a concern for one’s own safety in the face of dangers that were real and immediate was the process of a rational mind. Orr was crazy and could be grounded. All he had to do was ask; and as soon as he did, he would no longer be crazy and would have to fly more missions. Orr would be crazy to fly more missions and sane if he didn’t, but if he was sane he would have to fly them. If he flew them he was crazy and didn’t have to; but if he didn't want to he was sane and had to. Yossarian was moved very deeply by the absolute simplicity of this clause of Catch-22 and let out a respectful whistle. “That’s some catch, that Catch-22,” he observed. “It’s the best there is,” Doc Daneeka agreed." -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51479-nasib-adalah-kesunyian-masing-masing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 04:35:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Chairil Anwar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51479-nasib-adalah-kesunyian-masing-masing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nasib adalah kesunyian masing-masing" -- Chairil Anwar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171556-m-aybe-we-too-busy-being-flowers-or-fairies-or-strawberries</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 11:18:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Toni Cade Bambara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171556-m-aybe-we-too-busy-being-flowers-or-fairies-or-strawberries]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["(M)aybe we too busy being flowers or fairies or strawberries instead of something honest and worthy of respect . . . you know . . . like being people." -- Toni Cade Bambara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207032-lebih-baik-bertengkar-karena-cinta-daripada-diam-kesepian-menanggung-benci</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 18:34:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Remy Sylado]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207032-lebih-baik-bertengkar-karena-cinta-daripada-diam-kesepian-menanggung-benci]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lebih baik bertengkar karena cinta
daripada diam kesepian menanggung benci
Sebab, hidup dengan seseorang yang dicinta
memang tidak sunyi dari sakit di raga
tapi, hidup tanpa seseorang yang mencinta 
membuat orang mengundang rasa sakit di jiwa" -- Remy Sylado]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 20:10:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 20:11:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 20:29:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Insanity is doing the same thing, over and over again, but expecting different results." -- Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25838-that-s-the-way-it-is-if-you-believe-in-something</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 10:10:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juniar add a quote by Ben Okri]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25838-that-s-the-way-it-is-if-you-believe-in-something]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's the way it is. If you believe in something your very belief renders you unqualified to do it. Your earnestness will come across. Your passion will show. Your enthusiasm will make everyone nervous. And your naivety will irritate. Which means that you will become suspect. Which means you will be prone to disillusionment. Which means that you will not be able to sustain your belief in the face of all the piranha fish which nibble away at your idea and your faith, 'till only the skeleton of your dream is left. Which means that you have to become a fanatic, a fool, a joke, an embarrassment. The world - which is to say the powers that be - would listen to your ardent ideas with a stiff smile on its face, then put up impossible obstacles, watch you finally give up your cherished idea, having mangled it beyond recognition, and after you slope away in profound discouragement it will take up your idea, dust it down, give it a new spin, and hand it over to someone who doesn't believe in it at all." -- Ben Okri]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
