<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/246085-r-monaleza]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/246085-r-monaleza" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 22:13:59 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55864-the-quill-has-pricked-my-soul-and-each-word-bleeds</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 22:13:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by Mona Lisa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55864-the-quill-has-pricked-my-soul-and-each-word-bleeds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The quill has pricked my soul and each word bleeds onto the parchment of my life. My freedom is in my words, therefore, I write.

" -- Mona Lisa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55866-love-is-a-haunting-melody-that-i-have-never-mastered</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 22:14:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55866-love-is-a-haunting-melody-that-i-have-never-mastered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a haunting melody that I have never mastered, and I fear I never will." -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246-the-unexamined-life-is-not-worth-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 22:15:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by Socrates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246-the-unexamined-life-is-not-worth-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The unexamined life is not worth living." -- Socrates]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48648-once-upon-a-midnight-dreary-while-i-pondered-weak-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 22:17:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48648-once-upon-a-midnight-dreary-while-i-pondered-weak-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a midnight dreary, while I pondered, weak and weary,
Over many a quaint and curious volume of forgotten lore,
While I nodded, nearly napping, suddenly there came a tapping,
As of some one gently rapping, rapping at my chamber door.
Tis some visitor,&quot; I muttered, &quot;tapping at my chamber door —
      Only this, and nothing more.&quot;

Ah, distinctly I remember it was in the bleak December,
And each separate dying ember wrought its ghost upon the floor.
Eagerly I wished the morrow; — vainly I had sought to borrow
From my books surcease of sorrow — sorrow for the lost Lenore —
For the rare and radiant maiden whom the angels name Lenore —
      Nameless here for evermore.

And the silken sad uncertain rustling of each purple curtain
Thrilled me — filled me with fantastic terrors never felt before;
So that now, to still the beating of my heart, I stood repeating,
Tis some visitor entreating entrance at my chamber door —
Some late visitor entreating entrance at my chamber door; —
    This it is, and nothing more.&quot;

Presently my soul grew stronger; hesitating then no longer,
Sir,&quot; said I, &quot;or Madam, truly your forgiveness I implore;
But the fact is I was napping, and so gently you came rapping,
And so faintly you came tapping, tapping at my chamber door,
That I scarce was sure I heard you&quot;— here I opened wide the door; —
    Darkness there, and nothing more.

Deep into that darkness peering, long I stood there wondering, fearing,
Doubting, dreaming dreams no mortals ever dared to dream before;
But the silence was unbroken, and the stillness gave no token,
And the only word there spoken was the whispered word, &quot;Lenore?&quot;
This I whispered, and an echo murmured back the word, &quot;Lenore!&quot; —
      Merely this, and nothing more.

Back into the chamber turning, all my soul within me burning,
Soon again I heard a tapping somewhat louder than before.
Surely,&quot; said I, &quot;surely that is something at my window lattice:
Let me see, then, what thereat is, and this mystery explore —
Let my heart be still a moment and this mystery explore; —
    'Tis the wind and nothing more.&quot;

Open here I flung the shutter, when, with many a flirt and flutter,
In there stepped a stately raven of the saintly days of yore;
Not the least obeisance made he; not a minute stopped or stayed he;
But, with mien of lord or lady, perched above my chamber door —
Perched upon a bust of Pallas just above my chamber door —
    Perched, and sat, and nothing more.

Then this ebony bird beguiling my sad fancy into smiling,
By the grave and stern decorum of the countenance it wore.
Though thy crest be shorn and shaven, thou,&quot; I said, &quot;art sure no craven,
Ghastly grim and ancient raven wandering from the Nightly shore —
Tell me what thy lordly name is on the Night's Plutonian shore!&quot;
      Quoth the Raven, &quot;Nevermore.&quot;

Much I marveled this ungainly fowl to hear discourse so plainly,
Though its answer little meaning— little relevancy bore;
For we cannot help agreeing that no living human being
Ever yet was blest with seeing bird above his chamber door —
Bird or beast upon the sculptured bust above his chamber door,
      With such name as &quot;Nevermore." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55868-write-what-you-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 22:19:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55868-write-what-you-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Write what you know." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24149-the-most-important-kind-of-freedom-is-to-be-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 22:22:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by Jim MORRISON]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24149-the-most-important-kind-of-freedom-is-to-be-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most important kind of freedom is to be what you really are. You trade in your reality for a role. You trade in your sense for an act. You give up your ability to feel, and in exchange, put on a mask. There can't be any large-scale revolution until there's a personal revolution, on an individual level. It's got to happen inside first." -- Jim MORRISON]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15282-when-you-sit-right-down-in-the-middle-of-yourself</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 22:25:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by Ani DiFranco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15282-when-you-sit-right-down-in-the-middle-of-yourself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you sit right down in the middle of yourself you're gonna wanna have a comfortable chair." -- Ani DiFranco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41233-what-matters-most-is-how-well-you-walk-through-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 22:28:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by Charles Bukowski ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41233-what-matters-most-is-how-well-you-walk-through-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["what matters most is how well you walk through the fire" -- Charles Bukowski ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2798-i-like-too-many-things-and-get-all-confused-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 22:34:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2798-i-like-too-many-things-and-get-all-confused-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like too many things and get all confused and hung-up running from one falling star to another till i drop. This is the night, what it does to you. I had nothing to offer anybody except my own confusion." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49041-i-want-to-grow-i-want-to-be-better-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 22:36:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by Tupac Shakur]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49041-i-want-to-grow-i-want-to-be-better-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to grow. I want to be better. You Grow. We all grow. We're made to grow.You either evolve or you disappear." -- Tupac Shakur]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 10:54:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 10:54:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2008 09:22:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that everything happens for a reason. People change so that you can learn to let go, things go wrong so that you appreciate them when they're right, you believe lies so you eventually learn to trust no one but yourself, and sometimes good things fall apart so better things can fall together." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 07:02:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148986-you-wanna-fly-you-got-to-give-up-the-shit</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2013 09:31:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148986-you-wanna-fly-you-got-to-give-up-the-shit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You wanna fly, you got to give up the shit that weighs you down." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318981-free-yourself-from-the-complexities-and-drama-of-your-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2013 09:35:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by Steve Maraboli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318981-free-yourself-from-the-complexities-and-drama-of-your-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Free yourself from the complexities and drama of your life. Simplify. Look within. Within ourselves we all have the gifts and talents we need to fulfill the purpose we've been blessed with." -- Steve Maraboli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/513861-we-tend-to-disempower-ourselves-we-tend-to-believe-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2013 09:37:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[R. add a quote by Terence McKenna]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/513861-we-tend-to-disempower-ourselves-we-tend-to-believe-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We tend to disempower ourselves. We tend to believe that we don’t matter. And in the act of taking that idea to ourselves we give everything away to somebody else, to something else." -- Terence McKenna]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
