<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/24629-zac-frank]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/24629-zac-frank" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2011 21:38:36 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134422-i-was-supposed-to-have-a-script-and-had-mislaid</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2011 21:38:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zac add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134422-i-was-supposed-to-have-a-script-and-had-mislaid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was supposed to have a script, and had mislaid it. I was supposed to hear cues, and no longer did. I was meant to know the plot, but all I knew was what I saw: flash pictures in variable sequence, images with no 'meaning' beyond their temporary arrangement, not a movie but a cutting-room experience." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122374-the-places-we-have-known-do-not-belong-solely-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2011 21:41:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zac add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122374-the-places-we-have-known-do-not-belong-solely-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The places we have known do not belong solely to the world of space in which we situate them for our greater convenience. They were only a thin slice among contiguous impressions which formed our life at that time; the memory of a certain image is but regret for a certain moment; and houses, roads, avenues are as fleeting, alas, as the years." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94422-of-course-we-would-all-like-to-believe-in-something</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2011 21:41:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zac add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94422-of-course-we-would-all-like-to-believe-in-something]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of course we would all like to &quot;believe&quot; in something, like to assuage our private guilts in public causes, like to lose our tiresome selves; like, perhaps, to transform the white flag of defeat at home into the brave white banner of battle away from home. And of course it is all right to do that; that is how, immemorially, thing have gotten done. But I think it is all right only so long as we do not delude ourselves about what we are doing, and why. It is all right only so long as we remember that all the ad hoc committees, all the picket lines, all the brave signatures in The New York Times, all the tools of agitprop straight across the spectrum, do not confer upon anyone any ipso facto virtue. It is all right only so long as we recognize that the end may or may not be expedient, may or may not be a good idea, but in any case has nothing to do with &quot;morality.&quot; Because when we start deceiving ourselves into thinking not that we want something or need something, not that it is a pragmatic necessity for us to have it, but that it is a moral imperative that we have it, then is when we join the fashionable madmen, and then is when the thin whine of hysteria is heard in the land, and then is when we are in bad trouble. And I suspect we are already there." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55296-doubt-or-the-absence-of-faith-and-naivete-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2011 21:35:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zac add a quote by Charles Baudelaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55296-doubt-or-the-absence-of-faith-and-naivete-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Doubt, or the absence of faith and naivete, is a vice peculiar to this age, for no one is obedient nowadays; and naivete, which means the dominance of temperament in the manner, is a gift from God, possessed by very few." -- Charles Baudelaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55295-but-mostly-they-were-lies-i-told-it-wasn-t-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 14:07:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zac add a quote by Truman Capote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55295-but-mostly-they-were-lies-i-told-it-wasn-t-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But mostly they were lies I told; it wasn't my fault, I couldn't remember, because it was as though I'd been to one of those supernatural castles visited by characters in legends: once away, you do not remember, all that is left is the ghostly echo of haunting wonder." -- Truman Capote]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 12:54:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zac add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the only people for me are the mad ones, the ones who are mad to live, mad to talk, mad to be saved, desirous of everything at the same time, the ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn like fabulous yellow roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/605609-she-wanted-them-to-go-together-to-some-hopelessly-disreputable</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 16:00:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zac add a quote by Jean Stafford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/605609-she-wanted-them-to-go-together-to-some-hopelessly-disreputable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She wanted them to go together to some hopelessly disreputable bar and to console one another in the most maudlin fashion over a lengthy succession of powerful drinks of whiskey, to compare their illnesses, to marry their invalid souls for these few hours of painful communion, and to babble with rapture that they were at last, for a little while, they were no longer alone." -- Jean Stafford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8206-do-i-contradict-myself-very-well-then-i-contradict-myself</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 14:24:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zac add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8206-do-i-contradict-myself-very-well-then-i-contradict-myself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do I contradict myself? Very well, then, I contradict myself; I am large -- I contain multitudes." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629048-a-poem-compresses-much-in-a-small-space-and-adds</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 16:41:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zac add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629048-a-poem-compresses-much-in-a-small-space-and-adds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A poem compresses much in a small space and adds music, thus heightening its meaning. The city is like poetry: it compresses all life, all races and breeds, into a small island and adds music and the accompaniment of internal engines. The island of Manhattan is without any doubt the greatest human concentrate on earth, the poem whose magic is comprehensible to millions of permanent residents but whose full meaning will always remain elusive." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
