<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/246868-tim-paccione]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/246868-tim-paccione" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 11:34:47 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56088-we-all-have-the-potential-to-fall-in-love-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 11:34:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56088-we-all-have-the-potential-to-fall-in-love-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all have the potential to fall in love a thousand times in our lifetime. It's easy. The first girl I ever loved was someone I knew in sixth grade. Her name was Missy; we talked about horses. The last girl I love will be someone I haven't even met yet, probably. They all count. But there are certain people you love who do something else; they define how you classify what love is supposed to feel like. These are the most important people in your life, and you’ll meet maybe four or five of these people over the span of 80 years. But there’s still one more tier to all this; there is always one person you love who becomes that definition. It usually happens retrospectively, but it happens eventually. This is the person who unknowingly sets the template for what you will always love about other people, even if some of these loveable qualities are self-destructive and unreasonable. The person who defines your understanding of love is not inherently different than anyone else, and they’re often just the person you happen to meet the first time you really, really, want to love someone. But that person still wins. They win, and you lose. Because for the rest of your life, they will control how you feel about everyone else." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163511-though-i-obviously-have-no-proof-of-this-the-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 11:38:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163511-though-i-obviously-have-no-proof-of-this-the-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Though I obviously have no proof of this, the one aspect of life that seems clear to me is that good people do whatever they believe is the right thing to do. Being virtuous is hard, not easy. The idea of doing good things simply because you're good seems like a zero-sum game; I'm not even sure those actions would still qualify as 'good,' since they'd merely be a function of normal behavior. Regardless of what kind of god you believe in--a loving god, a vengeful god, a capricious god, a snooty beret-wearing French god, or whatever--one has to assume that you can't be penalized for doing the things you believe to be truly righteous and just. Certainly, this creates some pretty glaring problems: Hitler may have thought he was serving God. Stalin may have thought he was serving God (or something vaguely similar). I'm certain Osama bin Laden was &lt;I&gt;positive&lt;/i&gt; he was serving God. It's not hard to fathom that all of those maniacs were certain that what they were doing was right. Meanwhile, I &lt;I&gt;constantly&lt;/i&gt; do things that I &lt;I&gt;know&lt;/i&gt; are wrong; they're not on the same scale as incinerating Jews or blowing up skyscrapers, but my motivations might be worse. I have looked directly into the eyes of a woman I loved and told her lies for no reason, except that those lies would allow me to continue having sex with another woman I cared about less. This act did not kill 20 million Russian peasants, but it might be more 'diabolical' in a literal sense. If I died and found out I was going to hell and Stalin was in heaven, I would note the irony, but I couldn't complain. I don't make the fucking rules." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33631-in-and-of-itself-nothing-really-matters-what-matters-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 11:38:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33631-in-and-of-itself-nothing-really-matters-what-matters-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In and of itself, nothing really matters. What matters is that nothing is ever in and of itself." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222586-if-rain-is-god-crying-i-think-god-is-drunk</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 11:40:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222586-if-rain-is-god-crying-i-think-god-is-drunk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If rain is God crying, I think God is drunk and his girlfriend just slept with Zeus." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138055-art-and-love-are-the-same-thing-it-s-the-process</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 12:10:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138055-art-and-love-are-the-same-thing-it-s-the-process]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Art and love are the same thing: It’s the process of seeing yourself in things that are not you." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120699-but-whenever-i-meet-dynamic-nonretarded-americans-i-notice-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 12:10:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120699-but-whenever-i-meet-dynamic-nonretarded-americans-i-notice-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But whenever I meet dynamic, nonretarded Americans, I notice that they all seem to share a single unifying characteristic: the inability to experience the kind of mind-blowing, transcendent romantic relationship they perceive to be a normal part of living. And someone needs to take the fall for this. So instead of blaming no one for this (which is kind of cowardly) or blaming everyone (which is kind of meaningless), I'm going to blame John Cusack." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116991-you-used-to-be-able-to-tell-the-difference-between</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 12:10:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116991-you-used-to-be-able-to-tell-the-difference-between]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You used to be able to tell the difference between hipsters and homeless people. Now, it's between hipsters and retards. I mean, either that guy in the corner in orange safety pants holding a protest sign and wearing a top hat is mentally disabled or he is the coolest fucking guy you will ever know." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120705-being-interesting-has-been-replaced-by-being-identifiable</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 12:14:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120705-being-interesting-has-been-replaced-by-being-identifiable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being interesting has been replaced by being identifiable." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222581-i-love-the-way-music-inside-a-car-makes-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 12:14:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222581-i-love-the-way-music-inside-a-car-makes-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love the way music inside a car makes you feel invisible; if you plan the stereo at max volume, it's almost like the other people can't see into your vehicle. It tints your windows, somehow." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161278-i-remember-saying-things-but-i-have-no-idea-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 12:27:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161278-i-remember-saying-things-but-i-have-no-idea-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I remember saying things, but I have no idea what was said. It was generally a friendly conversation.” —Associated Press reporter Jack Sullivan, attempting to recount a 3 A.M. exchange we had at a dinner party and inadvertently describing the past ten years of my life." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411729-i-have-never-understood-the-concept-of-infatuation-it-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 12:38:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411729-i-have-never-understood-the-concept-of-infatuation-it-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…I have never understood the concept of infatuation. It has always been my understanding that being ‘infatuated’ with someone means you think you are in love, but you’re actually not; infatuation is (supposedly) just a foolish, fleeting feeling. But if being ‘in love’ is an abstract notion, and it’s not tangible, and there is no way to physically prove it to anyone else… well, how is being in love any different than having an infatuation? They’re both human constructions. If you think you’re in love with someone and you feel like you’re in love with someone, then you obviously are; thinking and feeling is the sum total of what love is. Why do we feel an obligation to certify emotions with some kind of retrospective, self-imposed authenticity?" -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161280-no-woman-will-ever-satisfy-me-i-know-that-now</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 12:41:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161280-no-woman-will-ever-satisfy-me-i-know-that-now]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No woman will ever satisfy me. I know that now, and I would never try to deny it. But this is actually okay, because I will never satisfy a woman, either. Should I be writing such thoughts? Perhaps not. Perhaps it’s a bad idea. I can definitely foresee a scenario where that first paragraph could come back to haunt me, especially if I somehow became marginally famous." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/400696-the-strength-of-your-memory-dictates-the-size-of-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 13:28:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/400696-the-strength-of-your-memory-dictates-the-size-of-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The strength of your memory dictates the size of your reality" -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403468-science-fiction-tends-to-be-philosophy-for-stupid-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 13:34:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403468-science-fiction-tends-to-be-philosophy-for-stupid-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Science fiction tends to be philosophy for stupid people." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/482489-when-you-start-thinking-about-what-your-life-was-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 13:36:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/482489-when-you-start-thinking-about-what-your-life-was-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you start thinking about what your life was like 10 years ago--and not in general terms, but in highly specific detail--it's disturbing to realize how certain elements of your being are completely dead. They die long before you do. It's astonishing to consider all the things from your past that used to happen all the time but (a) never happen anymore, and (b) never even cross your mind. It's almost like those things didn't happen. Or maybe it seems like they just happened to someone else. To someone you don't really know. To someone you just hung out with for one night, and now you can't even remember her name." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398528-i-ve-spent-the-last-fifteen-years-of-my-life-railing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 13:38:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398528-i-ve-spent-the-last-fifteen-years-of-my-life-railing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...I've spent the last fifteen years of my life railing against the game of soccer, an exercise that has been lauded as &quot;the sport of the future&quot; since 1977. Thankfully, that future dystopia has never come." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133215-on-the-third-play-he-dropped-back-to-pass-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 13:47:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133215-on-the-third-play-he-dropped-back-to-pass-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the third play he dropped back to pass, and it was unadulterated chaos: The pocket was immediately collapsing, people were yelling, everything was happening at the same time, and it felt like he was trying to defuse a pipe bomb while learning to speak Cantonese.&quot;

&quot;He believed it was his destiny to kill faceless foreigners for complex reasons that were beyond his control, and to deeply question the meaning of those murders, and to kill despite those questions, and to eventually understand the meaning of his own life through the battlefield executions of total strangers.&quot;

&quot;Teaching history to eighth graders is like being a tour guide for people who hate their vacation.&quot;

&quot;There is no feeling that can match the emotive intensity of an attraction devoid of explanation." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227324-a-mind-needs-books-as-a-sword-needs-a-whetstone</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 19:13:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227324-a-mind-needs-books-as-a-sword-needs-a-whetstone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A mind needs books as a sword needs a whetstone, if it is to keep its edge." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408441-a-reader-lives-a-thousand-lives-before-he-dies-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 19:13:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408441-a-reader-lives-a-thousand-lives-before-he-dies-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A reader lives a thousand lives before he dies, said Jojen. The man who never reads lives only one." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227321-never-forget-what-you-are-for-surely-the-world-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 19:13:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227321-never-forget-what-you-are-for-surely-the-world-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never forget what you are, for surely the world will not. Make it your strength. Then it can never be your weakness. Armour yourself in it, and it will never be used to hurt you." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85141-they-can-keep-their-heaven-when-i-die-i-d-sooner</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 19:15:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85141-they-can-keep-their-heaven-when-i-die-i-d-sooner]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They can keep their heaven.  When I die, I’d sooner go to Middle Earth. " -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386558-there-is-only-one-god-and-his-name-is-death</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 19:16:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by George R. R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386558-there-is-only-one-god-and-his-name-is-death]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is only one god and his name is Death. And there is only one thing we say to Death: “Not today." -- George R. R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383969-death-is-so-terribly-final-while-life-is-full-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 19:17:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383969-death-is-so-terribly-final-while-life-is-full-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death is so terribly final, while life is full of possibilities." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97184-luck-is-where-preparation-meets-opportunity</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 19:27:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Randy Pausch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97184-luck-is-where-preparation-meets-opportunity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Luck is where preparation meets opportunity. " -- Randy Pausch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104335-when-you-re-screwing-up-and-nobody-says-anything-to-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 19:27:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Randy Pausch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104335-when-you-re-screwing-up-and-nobody-says-anything-to-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you're screwing up and nobody says anything to you anymore, that means they've given up on you." -- Randy Pausch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76530-when-there-s-an-elephant-in-the-room-introduce-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 19:29:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Randy Pausch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76530-when-there-s-an-elephant-in-the-room-introduce-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When there’s an elephant in the room introduce him." -- Randy Pausch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115600-we-ve-placed-a-lot-of-emphasis-in-this-country-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 19:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Randy Pausch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115600-we-ve-placed-a-lot-of-emphasis-in-this-country-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We've placed a lot of emphasis in this country on the idea of people's rights. That's how it should be, but it makes no sense to talk about rights without also talking about responsibilities." -- Randy Pausch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498189-just-because-you-re-in-the-driver-s-seat-doesn-t-mean-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 19:43:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Randy Pausch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498189-just-because-you-re-in-the-driver-s-seat-doesn-t-mean-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just because you're in the driver's seat, doesn't mean you have to run people over." -- Randy Pausch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263081-it-is-easy-when-you-are-young-to-believe-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 19:50:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263081-it-is-easy-when-you-are-young-to-believe-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is easy, when you are young, to believe that what you desire is no less than what you deserve, to assume that if you want something badly enough, it is your God-given right to have it." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/281380-it-is-easy-when-you-are-young-to-believe-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 19:51:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/281380-it-is-easy-when-you-are-young-to-believe-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is easy, when you are young, to believe that what you desire is no less than what you deserve, to assume that if you want something badly enough , it is your God-given right to have it...I was a raw youth who mistook passion for insight and acted according to an obscure, gap-ridden logic. I thought climbing the Devils Thumb would fix all that was wrong with my life. In the end, of course, it changed almost nothing. But I came to appreciate that mountains make poor receptacles for dreams. And I lived to tell my tale." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
