<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/246917-sarah-koz]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/246917-sarah-koz" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 08:38:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142707-we-are-all-alone-born-alone-die-alone-and---</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 08:38:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142707-we-are-all-alone-born-alone-die-alone-and---]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all alone, born alone, die alone, and -- in spite of True Romance magazines -- we shall all someday look back on our lives and see that, in spite of our company, we were alone the whole way. I do not say lonely -- at least, not all the time -- but essentially, and finally, alone. This is what makes your self-respect so important, and I don't see how you can respect yourself if you must look in the hearts and minds of others for your happiness." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82085-sex-without-love-is-as-hollow-and-ridiculous-as-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 08:38:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82085-sex-without-love-is-as-hollow-and-ridiculous-as-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sex without love is as hollow and ridiculous as love without sex." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48834-there-are-times-however-and-this-is-one-of-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 08:38:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48834-there-are-times-however-and-this-is-one-of-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are times, however, and this is one of them, when even being right feels wrong. What do you say, for instance, about a generation that has been taught that rain is poison and sex is death? If making love might be fatal and if a cool spring breeze on any summer afternoon can turn a crystal blue lake into a puddle of black poison right in front of your eyes, there is not much left except TV and relentless masturbation. It's a strange world. Some people get rich and others eat shit and die." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27831-i-ve-always-considered-writing-the-most-hateful-kind-of-work</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 08:44:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27831-i-ve-always-considered-writing-the-most-hateful-kind-of-work]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've always considered writing the most hateful kind of work. I suspect it's a bit like fucking, which is only fun for amateurs. Old whores don't do much giggling." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10913-one-of-them-is-knowing-the-difference-between-morality-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 08:46:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10913-one-of-them-is-knowing-the-difference-between-morality-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of them is knowing the difference between Morality and Wisdom.  Morality is temporary, Wisdom is permanent…  Ho ho.  Take that one to bed with you tonight." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102714-to-make-a-point-of-declaring-friendship-is-to-cheapen</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 08:49:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102714-to-make-a-point-of-declaring-friendship-is-to-cheapen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To make a point of declaring friendship is to cheapen it.  For men's emotions are very rarely put into words successfully. " -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229694-i-ve-always-considered-writing-the-most-hateful-kind-of-work</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 09:02:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229694-i-ve-always-considered-writing-the-most-hateful-kind-of-work]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've always considered writing the most hateful kind of work. I suspect it's a bit like fucking — which is fun only for amateurs. Old whores don't do much giggling. Nothing is fun when you have to do it — over and over, again and again... " -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3065-the-edge-there-is-no-honest-way-to-explain-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 09:04:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3065-the-edge-there-is-no-honest-way-to-explain-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["THE EDGE, there is no honest way to explain it because the only people who really know where it is are the ones who have gone over." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59758-no-more-games-no-more-bombs-no-more-walking-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 09:14:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59758-no-more-games-no-more-bombs-no-more-walking-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No More Games. No More Bombs. No More Walking. No More Fun. No More Swimming. 67. That is 17 years past 50. 17 more than I needed or wanted. Boring. I am always bitchy. No Fun — for anybody. 67. You are getting Greedy. Act your old age. Relax — This won't hurt" -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68202-some-people-turn-sad-awfully-young-no-special-reason-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 08:01:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68202-some-people-turn-sad-awfully-young-no-special-reason-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people turn sad awfully young. No special reason, it seems, but they seem almost to be born that way. They bruise easier, tire faster, cry quicker, remember longer and, as I say, get sadder younger than anyone else in the world. I know, for I'm one of them." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107311-if-you-hide-your-ignorance-no-one-will-hit-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 08:17:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107311-if-you-hide-your-ignorance-no-one-will-hit-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you hide your ignorance, no one will hit you and you'll never learn." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154707-the-difference-between-a-non-suicide-and-an-ex-suicide-leaving-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 10:22:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Walker Percy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154707-the-difference-between-a-non-suicide-and-an-ex-suicide-leaving-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The difference between a non-suicide and an ex-suicide leaving the house for work, at eight o'clock on an ordinary morning:

The non-suicide is a little traveling suck of care, sucking care with him from the past and being sucked toward care in the future.  His breath is high in his chest.

The ex-suicide opens his front door, sits down on the steps, and laughs.  Since he has the option of being dead, he has nothing to lose by being alive.  It is good to be alive.  He goes to work because he doesn't have to." -- Walker Percy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353358-when-i-was-first-aware-that-i-had-been-laid</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 10:24:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by William Styron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353358-when-i-was-first-aware-that-i-had-been-laid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was first aware that I had been laid low by the disease, I felt a need, among other things, to register a strong protest against the word &quot;depression.&quot; Depression, most people know, used to be termed &quot;melancholia,&quot; a word which appears in English as the year 1303 and crops up more than once in Chaucer, who in his usade seemed to be aware of its pathological nuances. &quot;Melancholia&quot; would still appear to be a far more apt and evocative word for the blacker forms of the disorder, but it was usurped by a noun with a blank tonality and lacking any magisterial presence, used indifferentl to describe an economic decline or a rut in the ground, a true wimp of a word for such a major illness.

It may be that the scientist generally held responsible for its currency in modern times, a Johns Hopkins Medical School faculty member justly venerated --the Swiss-born psychiatrist Adolf Meyer -- had a tin ear for the finer rhthms of English and therefore was unaware of the semantic damage he had inflicted for such a dreadful and raging disease. Nonetheless, for over seventy-five years the word has slithered innocuously through the language like a slug, leaving little trace of its intrinsic malevolence and preventing, by its insipidity, a general awareness of the horrible intensity of the disease when out of control." -- William Styron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106139-the-good-writing-of-any-age-has-always-been-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 10:25:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by William Styron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106139-the-good-writing-of-any-age-has-always-been-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The good writing of any age has always been the product of someone's neurosis, and we'd have a mighty dull literature if all the writers that came along were a bunch of happy chuckleheads." -- William Styron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25043-you-have-to-be-an-artist-and-a-madman-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 13:05:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25043-you-have-to-be-an-artist-and-a-madman-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to be an artist and a madman, a creature of infinite melancholy, with a bubble of hot poison in your loins and a super-voluptuous flame permanently aglow in your subtle spine (oh, how you have to cringe and hide!), in order to discern at once, by ineffable signs―the slightly feline outline of a cheekbone, the slenderness of a downy limbs, and other indices which despair and shame and tears of tenderness forbid me to tabulate―the little deadly demon among the wholesome children; she stands unrecognized by them and unconscious herself of her fantastic power." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57424-and-i-still-have-other-smothered-memories-now-unfolding-themselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 13:07:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57424-and-i-still-have-other-smothered-memories-now-unfolding-themselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I still have other smothered memories, now unfolding themselves into limbless monsters of pain. Once, in a sunset-ending street of Beardsley, she turned to little Eva Rosen (I was taking both nymphets to a concert and walking behind them so close as almost to touch them with my person), she turned to Eva, and so very serenely and seriously, in answer to something the other had said about its being better to die than hear Milton Pinski; some local schoolboy she knew, talk about music, my Lolita remarked:
'You know what's so dreadful about dying is that you're completely on your own'; and it struck me, as my automaton knees went up and down, that I simply did not know a thing about my darling's mind and that quite possibly, behind the awful juvenile cliches, there was in her a garden and a twilight, and a palace gate - dim and adorable regions which happened to be lucidly and absolutely forbidden to me, in my polluted rags and miserable convulsions..." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23720-be-true-to-your-dick</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 13:08:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23720-be-true-to-your-dick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be true to your Dick." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/700443-don-t-touch-me-i-ll-die-if-you-touch-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 13:18:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/700443-don-t-touch-me-i-ll-die-if-you-touch-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't touch me; I'll die if you touch me." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/567961-how-did-it-happen-that-now-he-could-see-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 05:41:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Walker Percy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/567961-how-did-it-happen-that-now-he-could-see-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How did it happen that now he could see everything so clearly.  Something had given him leave to live in the present.  Not once in his entire life had he come to rest in the quiet center of himself but had forever cast himself from some dark past he could not remember to a future that did not exist.  Not once had he been present for his life. So his life had passed like a dream.  Is it possible for people to miss their lives the way one can miss a plane?" -- Walker Percy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24324-be-still-when-you-have-nothing-to-say-when-genuine</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 05:17:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24324-be-still-when-you-have-nothing-to-say-when-genuine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be still when you have nothing to say; when genuine passion moves you, say what you've got to say, and say it hot." -- D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/911111-she-might-be-a-little-introverted-livelier-of-movement-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 12:10:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/911111-she-might-be-a-little-introverted-livelier-of-movement-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She might be a little introverted, livelier of movement than of conversation, neither bashful nor forward, with a soul that seemed submerged, but in a radiant moistness. Opalescent on the surface but translucent in her depths…" -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/592099-almighty-god-i-am-sorry-i-am-now-an-atheist</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 07:02:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by John Fante]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/592099-almighty-god-i-am-sorry-i-am-now-an-atheist]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Almighty God, I am sorry I am now an atheist, but have You read Nietzsche?" -- John Fante]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1018866-i-ve-been-in-love-for-five-hundred-million-years</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 05:58:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1018866-i-ve-been-in-love-for-five-hundred-million-years]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been in love for five hundred million years…" -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1052188-what-she-needs-at-least-one-thing-she-needs-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 07:09:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1052188-what-she-needs-at-least-one-thing-she-needs-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What she needs, at least one thing she needs, is companionship. After all why should she eat? Who needs her to be alive? What we call psychosis is sometimes simply realism. But human beings can't live on realism alone." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1174384-knowledge-of-my-atrocious-selfishness-settled-on-me-all-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 06:15:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by John Fowles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1174384-knowledge-of-my-atrocious-selfishness-settled-on-me-all-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Knowledge of my atrocious selfishness, settled on me. All those bitter home truths she had flung at me, right from the beginning…and still loved me; was so blind that she still loved me. One day she had said: &lt;i&gt;When you love me&lt;/i&gt; (and she had not meant “make love to me”) &lt;i&gt;it’s as if God forgave me for being the mess I am;&lt;/i&gt; and I took it as chicanery, another emotional blackmail, to make me feel essential and so give me a sense of responsibility towards her." -- John Fowles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1174385-she-was-a-mirror-that-did-not-lie-whose-interest</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 06:16:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by John Fowles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1174385-she-was-a-mirror-that-did-not-lie-whose-interest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was a mirror that did not lie; whose interest in me was real; whose love was real." -- John Fowles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1234454-real-consciousness-is-touch-thought-is-getting-out-of-touch</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 13:46:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1234454-real-consciousness-is-touch-thought-is-getting-out-of-touch]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Real consciousness is touch. Thought is getting out of touch.

The crux of the whole problem lies here, in the duality of man's consciousness. Touch, the being in touch, is the basis of all consciousness, and it is the basis of enduring happiness. Thought is a secondary form of consciousness, Mind is a secondary form of existence, a getting out of touch, a standing clear, in order to come to a better adjustment in touch.

Man, poor man, has to learn to function in these two ways of consciousness. When a man is in touch, he is non-mental, his mind is quiescent, his bodily centres are active. When a man's mind is active in real mental activity, the bodily centres are quiescent, switched off, the man is out of touch. The animals remain always in touch. And man, poor modern man, with his worship of his own god, which is his own mind glorified, is permanently out of touch. To be always irrevocably in touch is to feel sometimes imprisoned. But to be permanently out of touch is at last excruciatingly painful, it is a state of being nothing, and being nowhere, and at the same time being conscious and capable of extreme discomfort and ennui." -- D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260218-the-only-real-prison-is-fear-and-the-only-real</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 06:17:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Aung San Suu Kyi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260218-the-only-real-prison-is-fear-and-the-only-real]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only real prison is fear, and the only real freedom is freedom from fear" -- Aung San Suu Kyi]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
