<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/247229-carrie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/247229-carrie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 16:07:39 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199572-you-ve-got-to-jump-off-cliffs-all-the-time-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 16:07:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199572-you-ve-got-to-jump-off-cliffs-all-the-time-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've got to jump off cliffs all the time and build your wings on the way down." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873638-in-our-culture-privacy-is-often-confused-with-secrecy-open</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 09:12:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Bell Hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873638-in-our-culture-privacy-is-often-confused-with-secrecy-open]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In our culture privacy is often confused with secrecy. Open, honest, truth-telling individuals value privacy. We all need spaces where we can be alone with thoughts and feelings - where we can experience healthy psychological autonomy and can choose to share when we want to. Keeping secrets is usually about power, about hiding and concealing information." -- Bell Hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/516826-it-still-took-years-for-me-to-let-go-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 09:13:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/516826-it-still-took-years-for-me-to-let-go-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It still took years for me to let go of learned pattern's of behavior that negated my capacity to give and receive love.  One pattern that made the practice of love especially difficult was my constantly choosing to be with men who were emotionally wounded, who were not that interested in loving, even though they desired to be loved.  I wanted to know love but was afraid to be intimate.  By choosing men who were not interested in being loving, I was able to practice giving love but always within an unfufilling context.  Naturally, my need to receive love was not met. I got what I was accustomed to getting. Care and affection, usually mingled with a degree of unkindness, neglect, and on some occasions, out right cruelty." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/731640-one-of-the-best-guides-to-how-to-be-self-loving</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 09:13:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Bell Hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/731640-one-of-the-best-guides-to-how-to-be-self-loving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the best guides to how to be self-loving is to give ourselves the love we are often dreaming about receiving from others. There was a time when I felt lousy about my over-forty body, saw myself as too fat, too this, or too that. Yet I fantasized about finding a lover who would give me the gift of being loved as I am. It is silly, isn't it, that I would dream of someone else offering to me the acceptance and affirmation I was withholding from myself. This was a moment when the maxim &quot;You can never love anybody if you are unable to love yourself&quot; made clear sense.  And I add, &quot;Do not expect to receive the love from someone else you do not give yourself." -- Bell Hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
