<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/247446-jennifer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/247446-jennifer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 23:19:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82031-if-the-day-and-night-are-such-that-you-greet</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 23:19:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82031-if-the-day-and-night-are-such-that-you-greet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the day and night are such that you greet them with joy, and life emits a fragrance like flowers and sweet-scented herbs, is more elastic, more starry, more immortal - that is your success." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82037-we-don-t-set-out-to-save-the-world-we-set</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 00:19:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Pema Chodron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82037-we-don-t-set-out-to-save-the-world-we-set]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't set out to save the world; we set out to wonder how other people are doing and to reflect on how our actions affect other people's hearts." -- Pema Chodron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369-a-human-being-is-a-part-of-the-whole-called</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 00:33:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369-a-human-being-is-a-part-of-the-whole-called]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A human being is a part of the whole called by us universe, a part limited in time and space. He experiences himself, his thoughts and feeling as something separated from the rest, a kind of optical delusion of his consciousness. This delusion is a kind of prison for us, restricting us to our personal desires and to affection for a few persons nearest to us. Our task must be to free ourselves from this prison by widening our circle of compassion to embrace all living creatures and the whole of nature in its beauty." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/827-among-those-whom-i-like-or-admire-i-can-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 00:38:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by W. H. Auden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/827-among-those-whom-i-like-or-admire-i-can-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Among those whom I like or admire, I can find no common denominator, but among those whom I love, I can; all of them make me laugh." -- W. H. Auden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2851-i-would-rather-be-ashes-than-dust-i-would-rather</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 17:16:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Jack London]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2851-i-would-rather-be-ashes-than-dust-i-would-rather]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would rather be ashes than dust!
I would rather that my spark should burn out in a brilliant blaze than it should be stifled by dry-rot.
I would rather be a superb meteor, every atom of me in magnificent glow, than a sleepy and permanent planet.
The function of man is to live, not to exist.
I shall not waste my days trying to prolong them.
I shall use my time." -- Jack London]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166384-though-farmer-troutham-had-just-hurt-him-he-was-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 00:22:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Thomas Hardy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166384-though-farmer-troutham-had-just-hurt-him-he-was-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Though Farmer Troutham had just hurt him, he was a boy who could not himself bear to hurt anything. He had never brought home a nest of young birds without lying awake in misery half the night after, and often reinstating them and the nest in their original place the next morning. He could scarcely bear to see trees cut down or lopped, from a fancy that it hurt them; and late pruning, when the sap was up and the tree bled profusely, had been a positive grief to him in his infancy. This weakness of character, as it may be called, suggested that he was the sort of man who was born to ache a good deal before the fall of the curtain upon his unnecessary life should signify that all was well with him again. He carefully picked his way on tiptoe among the earthworms, without killing a single one." -- Thomas Hardy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
