<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/247514-bob-koo]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/247514-bob-koo" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2010 12:44:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289273-the-conflict-will-always-beyond-ur-strength-the-enemy-always-pushes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2010 12:44:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bob add a quote by Francis Frangipane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289273-the-conflict-will-always-beyond-ur-strength-the-enemy-always-pushes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The conflict will always beyond ur strength.The enemy always pushes 
us beyond our personal, inbred, preset limits concerning how far we'll
go for God:&quot;Here's how far I'm going to love,this is how many times 
I'll turn the other cheek.&quot;The test kills the limits of our humanity,til we're like Christ in everything We're left with a choice:Become Christlike or gradually shrivel into superficial hypocrites: angry people who have stopped walking with God, who blame others for our bitterness." -- Francis Frangipane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/987157-emotions-are-like-a-river-flowing-out-of-one-s-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 06:43:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bob add a quote by John Piper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/987157-emotions-are-like-a-river-flowing-out-of-one-s-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Emotions are like a river flowing out of one’s heart. Form is like the riverbanks. Without them the river runs shallow and dissipates on the plain. But banks make the river run deep. Why else have humans for centuries reached for poetry when we have deep affections to express? The creation of a form happens because someone feels a passion. How ironic, then, that we often fault form when the real evil is a dry spring." -- John Piper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1008682-people-do-not-drift-toward-holiness-apart-from-grace-driven-effort</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 08:28:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bob add a quote by D. A. Carson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1008682-people-do-not-drift-toward-holiness-apart-from-grace-driven-effort]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People do not drift toward holiness. Apart from grace-driven effort, people do not gravitate toward godliness, prayer, obedience to Scripture, faith, and delight in the Lord. We drift toward compromise and call it tolerance; we drift toward disobedience and call it freedom; we drift toward superstition and call it faith. We cherish the indiscipline of lost self-control and call it relaxation; we slouch toward prayerlessness and delude ourselves into thinking we have escaped legalism; we slide toward godlessness and convince ourselves we have been liberated." -- D. A. Carson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1143078-i-recall-that-in-the-immediate-aftermath-of-those-losses</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 15:04:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bob add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1143078-i-recall-that-in-the-immediate-aftermath-of-those-losses]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I recall that in the immediate aftermath of those losses at Candlestick, I lost all healthy perspective, my ordinarily sober and sensible outlook cast to the wind like the hot dog wrappers forever swirling above the ballpark's stands. I am not proud of this. Frankly, it is embarrassing (as a graying, 48-year-old father of two, and as someone from Afghanistan, an impoverished nation unraveled by three decades of violence and human suffering) to describe the depth of emotional sting inflicted on me by those Candlestick heartbreaks. Disappointment is too bland a word, too feeble to capture the helpless despair of watching the opponent kneel in victory, the long, long offseason looming suddenly and cruelly premature." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1143080-another-wealthy-clan-member-in-the-united-arab-emirates-bought</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 15:05:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bob add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1143080-another-wealthy-clan-member-in-the-united-arab-emirates-bought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Another wealthy clan member in the United Arab Emirates bought Mr. Yao three iPads to make this feasible — but even then, it was feasible only in the technical sense. At one point, he was bringing five iPads into the shower with him, each wrapped in a plastic bag, so that none of his accounts would go inactive." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1143083-at-literary-gatherings-he-made-a-practice-of-slipping-away</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 15:06:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bob add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1143083-at-literary-gatherings-he-made-a-practice-of-slipping-away]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At literary gatherings he made a practice of slipping away from “the gaunt and great, the famed for conversation” (as he called them in a poem) to find the least important person in the room. A letter-writer in the Times of London last year recalled one such incident: Sixty years ago my English teacher brought me to London from my provincial grammar school for a literary conference. Understandably, she abandoned me for her friends when we arrived, and I was left to flounder. I was gauche and inept and had no idea what to do with myself. Auden must have sensed this because he approached me and said, “Everyone here is just as nervous as you are, but they are bluffing, and you must learn to bluff too." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1143084-in-1939-he-left-england-for-america-partly-to-escape</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 15:06:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bob add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1143084-in-1939-he-left-england-for-america-partly-to-escape]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In 1939 he left England for America, partly to escape his own public status. Six months later, after making a speech at a political meeting, he wrote to a friend: I suddenly found I could really do it, that I could make a fighting demagogic speech and have the audience roaring…. It is so exciting but so absolutely degrading; I felt just covered with dirt afterwards. He was disgusted by his early fame because he saw the mixed motives behind his image of public virtue, the gratification he felt in being idolized and admired. He felt degraded when asked to pronounce on political and moral issues about which, he reminded himself, artists had no special insight. Far from imagining that artists were superior to anyone else, he had seen in himself that artists have their own special temptations toward power and cruelty and their own special skills at masking their impulses from themselves." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1143086-the-view-that-the-citizen-and-dictator-have-nothing-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 15:07:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bob add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1143086-the-view-that-the-citizen-and-dictator-have-nothing-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The view that the citizen and dictator have nothing in common has another corollary: the view that the dictator’s victims are inherently innocent, not merely innocent victims of someone else’s evil, but innocent in everything, so that even after the murderous dictator has been destroyed, their own actions, no matter how oppressive or unjust, may not be judged by the same standard as his actions. As victims of irrational hatred, they cannot imagine themselves acting on comparable hatreds. Against this fantasy of inherent innocence, Auden recognized that victims, no matter how guiltless in their own victimization, are tempted to become victimizers in turn. As he put it briskly in a song, “Many a sore bottom finds/A sorer one to kick." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1161031-but-as-the-conflict-studies-scholar-jayne-docherty-argues-the-f-b-i-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 11:12:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bob add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1161031-but-as-the-conflict-studies-scholar-jayne-docherty-argues-the-f-b-i-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But, as the conflict-studies scholar Jayne Docherty argues, the F.B.I.’s approach was doomed from the outset. In “Learning Lessons from Waco”—one of the very best of the Mount Carmel retrospectives—Docherty points out that the techniques that work on bank robbers don’t work on committed believers. There was no pragmatism hidden below a layer of posturing, lies, and grandiosity. Docherty uses Max Weber’s typology to describe the Davidians. They were “value-rational”—that is to say, their rationality was organized around values, not goals. A value-rational person would accept his fourteen-year-old daughter’s polygamous marriage, if he was convinced that it was in fulfillment of Biblical prophecy. Because the F.B.I. could not take the faith of the Branch Davidians seriously, it had no meaningful way to communicate with them:" -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1161059-all-parenting-involves-choosing-between-the-day-why-have-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 11:44:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bob add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1161059-all-parenting-involves-choosing-between-the-day-why-have-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All parenting involves choosing between the day (why have another argument at dinner?) and the years (the child must learn to eat vegetables). Nancy’s error seems to have been that she always focussed on the day, in a ceaseless quest to keep peace in the home she shared with the hypersensitive, controlling, increasingly hostile stranger who was her son. She thought that she could keep the years at bay by making each day as good as possible, but her willingness to indulge his isolation may well have exacerbated the problems it was intended to ameliorate." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1161071-when-robinson-and-davis-take-over-at-orientation-they-bark</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 11:58:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bob add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1161071-when-robinson-and-davis-take-over-at-orientation-they-bark]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When Robinson and Davis take over at orientation, they bark at the new recruits to stand up, then issue their first command: “Smile.” Students will learn a lot of things in Strive, but the first lesson is how to smile. The first few days are devoted to it. The new class members are always confused, and then they start to smile—except for about 20 percent of the room, who stand stone-faced. Robinson calls out those who don’t smile, pulls them up to the front of the room, and says, “This is my smile crew.” He tells the rest of the room to cheer until they can get these men and women, mostly men, to finally crack a smile. The claps and hoots and whistles rise in a crescendo heard throughout the building. Meanwhile, Davis and Robinson walk up and down the line, yelling, “Smile,” and pantomiming it, using their fingers to pull the corners of their own mouths back. The reluctant recruits roll their eyes. Some get tense, their faces get stuck in passive displays of aggression, as Robinson goes up and down the line and mocks: “Is it painful? Is there a medical condition? Smile!” He and Davis continue their full-on assault of well-wishing and joking and silliness until one by one, the students fold. A smile is the Strive game face, they explain. “I’m not asking you to smile on North Monroe Street at two in the morning,” Davis says. “I’m asking you to smile in here.” It’s usually the youngest men who bow out at this stage—the 19- and 20-year-olds who are too cool to tolerate the corniness, the guys who’ve been strongly encouraged to try Strive by some parole officer or social worker attempting to keep them from spending their twenties in prison. It’s the older guys who are eager to cooperate. They’re hungry." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1182761-what-happens-to-a-man-who-loses-more-than-half</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 13:04:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bob add a quote by Billy Bob's Blues]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1182761-what-happens-to-a-man-who-loses-more-than-half]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What happens to a man who loses more than half of himself? Ron Lester has searched for the answer since December 2000, when he underwent Roux-en-Y gastric bypass surgery with a duodenal switch.1 Since he realized in the third grade that his massive girth could draw laughs, Lester knew his fate was as the funny fat guy. When he moved to Hollywood — a town where funny fat guys can become millionaires — he was an overnight success. There was one problem, though: His moneymaker was slowly killing him. With a family history of heart problems, the 500-pound Lester wasn’t long for this world. Surgery saved his life. It also ended his career.

A shrinking man with loose skin greeted casting directors expecting the funny fat guy, and Lester struggled to score roles post-op. Now living in Dallas nearly 15 years after his glory days, he is left to ponder whether choosing life was the right decision.

“Am I alive? Yes. Am I happy? No. Did I throw away my career to be skinny? Yes,” he says. “I wouldn’t do [the surgery] again. I would much rather have died happy, rich, and kept my status and gone out on top." -- Billy Bob's Blues]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1182763-the-dramatic-interplay-was-more-in-lester-s-wheelhouse-particularly-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 13:05:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bob add a quote by Billy Bob's Blues]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1182763-the-dramatic-interplay-was-more-in-lester-s-wheelhouse-particularly-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The dramatic interplay was more in Lester’s wheelhouse, particularly the scene where Billy Bob contemplates suicide. Wracked with guilt over disappointing his coach (and, in retrospect, possibly suffering from post-concussion syndrome), Billy Bob sits on the back of his pickup with his football trophies, a bottle of tequila, and a Mossberg 12-gauge pump shotgun when he’s confronted by Mox.

“Championship trophy. Steelers. We were 9. Remember this shit? Playing Pee Wee?”

“Yeah,” Mox says. “It was fun.”

“No, it wasn’t. I remember being yelled at.” Billy Bob throws the trophy. “Too fat, Billy Bob!” Bang! “Too slow and dumb!” He pulls the pump handle. Bang!

“It was great,” Robbins, the director, says. “I remember that night shooting that scene, and you don’t do that once, you do it over and over again from different angles. And he was just able to deliver that performance over and over again, and those were real tears and real emotion coming out of him.”

Lester drew on pain from his personal life, thinking of his late father and his sister Linda, who died at 35. He also pulled from his own struggles with suicide. Inconsolable after Linda passed, he had put a loaded gun to his head and pulled the trigger. Nothing happened. “God,” he says, is the only explanation.

“I actually have the bullet, still. It’s not a dud; it’s live. It just didn’t go off,” Lester says. “I was kind of dreading [that scene] because I knew where I’d go. But I’m an actor and I’m making a commitment to the character. To do that, you have to go 100 percent and just hope you pull yourself out of it." -- Billy Bob's Blues]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1182778-the-judge-asked-the-question-on-everyone-s-mind-what-possibly</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 13:10:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bob add a quote by The Suit Who Spooked the EPA]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1182778-the-judge-asked-the-question-on-everyone-s-mind-what-possibly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The judge asked the question on everyone’s mind: What possibly could have occupied his time—2½ years of absence from work? What was he doing?

“Exercising,” he said.

Doing house projects.

Beale told investigators he would usually get some reading or bicycling done, too.

There it was. John Beale lied for more than a decade and spent the spoils of his charade as anyone else would spend a lazy Sunday.

The judge gave him 32 months." -- The Suit Who Spooked the EPA]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1182786-the-toy-is-the-lodestar-of-the-child-s-survival-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 13:12:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bob add a quote by Philip Seymour Hoffman Was Right MBird]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1182786-the-toy-is-the-lodestar-of-the-child-s-survival-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The toy is the lodestar of the child’s survival.  The consequences of his failure to get his toy are disastrous.  That Hoffman’s—and anyone else’s—pursuit of glory operates in the same way is why one man’s fear of failure and striving for perfection is significant, why it is not a matter of bourgeois decadence, in a world where a million Syrian children are in exile and starving.  The Syrian child, the child lacking his toy, and the actor fear for their survival.  How will they survive?  And how will they medicate their fear?

I suppose this is the moment where I am supposed to say that fear can be conquered by trusting in the risen Lord or whatever.  But I would just as well save the reflex.  I would just as well not waste meaningless words to counter the assertion about which Hoffman was exactly right: this world is damn terrifying.  It is easy enough to say that fear is an illusion or something trumped-up when you don’t read the newspaper or have a frank conversation with your friend.  How could one not be scared in a world where your birth is the beginning of your preparation for death?  This is a world of cancer and hunger and beheadings and layoffs and heartbreak and stabbings and innumerable and head-spinning and creative forms of violence and lovelessness.  This is a world where people are still burnt alive.  That is, in this world there are people who must endure, for several hundred seconds, the sensation of a hot iron enveloping the body until they die of bleeding, inhalation, or organ failure.  What sane person would not be terrified in such a world?" -- Philip Seymour Hoffman Was Right MBird]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1200715-understanding-i-believe-is-a-unifying-force-and-unity-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 15:53:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bob add a quote by Mike Cosper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1200715-understanding-i-believe-is-a-unifying-force-and-unity-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Understanding, I believe, is a unifying force and unity is just what is unlikely to happen in a culture where people can live next to someone who fundamentally disagrees with them about life’s most important questions. Empathy says, “Okay, I don’t get understand you, but I don’t have to and I don’t have to win the argument. And don’t worry about the recycling bins while you’re out of town; I’ll take care of them." -- Mike Cosper]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
