<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/248074-shannon]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/248074-shannon" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 18:15:34 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3409-as-we-walked-i-began-to-wonder-what-the-opposite</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 18:15:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Andre Aciman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3409-as-we-walked-i-began-to-wonder-what-the-opposite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As we walked, I began to wonder what the opposite of molting was and why, unlike the body, which sheds everything, the soul cannot let go but compiles and accumulates, growing annual rings around the things it wants and dreams and remembers" -- Andre Aciman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3410-for-juliana-comes-and-she-what-i-do-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 18:16:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Andrew Marvell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3410-for-juliana-comes-and-she-what-i-do-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For Juliana comes, and she, what I do to the grass, does to my thoughts and me." -- Andrew Marvell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3411-but-what-is-certain-is-that-in-five-ten-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 18:17:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Irene Nemirovsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3411-but-what-is-certain-is-that-in-five-ten-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But what is certain is that in five, ten or twenty years, this problem unique to our time, according to him, will no longer exist, it will be replaced by others...Yet this music, the sound of this rain on the windows, the great mournful creaking of the cedar tree in the garden outside, this moment, so tender, so strange in the middle of war, this will never change, not this, this is forever." -- Irene Nemirovsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3412-he-sits-in-his-car-at-traffic-lights-on-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 18:18:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Elliot Perlman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3412-he-sits-in-his-car-at-traffic-lights-on-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He sits in his car at traffic lights on his way out sometimes and tries to estimate how many times he has sat here, waiting at these traffic lights on his way somewhere without you, hoping to meet someone with the capacity to consign you to an anecdote, to be eventually confused with others" -- Elliot Perlman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3413-i-was-never-a-man-of-great-ambition-i-cried</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 18:19:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3413-i-was-never-a-man-of-great-ambition-i-cried]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was never a man of great ambition
I cried too easily
I didn't have a head for science
Words often failed me
While others prayed I only moved my lips" -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 18:20:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I can hear my bones straining under the weight of all the lives I'm not living." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3415-being-locked-up-is-one-thing-but-to-have-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 18:21:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3415-being-locked-up-is-one-thing-but-to-have-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being locked up is one thing, but to have no concept of confinement, to be ignorant of its terms and never understand that struggle is useless - that's what hell must be like." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3416-by-night-the-skyscraper-looms-in-the-smoke-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 18:22:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Carl Sandburg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3416-by-night-the-skyscraper-looms-in-the-smoke-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By night the skyscraper looms in the smoke and the stars and has a soul." -- Carl Sandburg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3417-pulling-through-is-what-people-do-around-here-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 18:23:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Laurie Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3417-pulling-through-is-what-people-do-around-here-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pulling through is what people do around here.  There is a kind of bravery in their lives that isn't bravery at all.  It is automatic, unflinching, a mix of man and machine, consuming and unquestionable obligation meeting illness move for move in a giant even-steven game of chess - an unending round of something that looks like shadowboxing, though between love and death, which is the shadow?  'Everyone admires us for our courage,' says one man.  'They have no idea what they're talking about." -- Laurie Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3418-i-wanted-so-many-times-while-driving-to-flip-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 18:26:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3418-i-wanted-so-many-times-while-driving-to-flip-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted so many times while driving to flip, to skid and flip and fall from the car and have something happen.  I wanted to land on my head and lose half of it, or land on my legs and lose one or both.  I wanted something to happen so my choices would be fewer, so my map would have a route straight through, in red.  I wanted limitations, boundaries, to ease the burden; because the agony, Jack, when we were up there in the dark, was in the silence!  All I ever wanted was to know what to do.  In these last months I've had no clue, I've been paralyzed by the quiet, and for a moment something spoke to me, and we came here, or came to Africa, and intermittently there were answers, intermittently there was a chorus and they sang to us and pointing, and were watching and approving, but just as often there was silence, and we stood blinking under the sun, or under the black sky, and we had to think of what to do next." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3419-and-there-is-a-chance-that-everything-we-did-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 18:27:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3419-and-there-is-a-chance-that-everything-we-did-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And there is a chance that everything we did was incorrect, but stasis is itself criminal for those with the means to move, and the means to weave communion between people." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3420-even-now-all-possible-feelings-do-not-yet-exist-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 18:29:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3420-even-now-all-possible-feelings-do-not-yet-exist-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even now, all possible feelings do not yet exist, there are still those that lie beyond our capacity and our imagination.  From time to time, when a piece of music no one has ever written or a painting no one has ever painted, or something else impossible to predict, fathom or yet describe takes place, a new feeling enters the world.  And then, for the millionth time in the history of feeling, the heart surges and absorbs the impact." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3421-important-events-whether-serious-happy-or-unfortunate-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 18:30:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Irene Nemirovsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3421-important-events-whether-serious-happy-or-unfortunate-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Important events — whether serious, happy or unfortunate — do not change a man's soul, they merely bring it into relief, just as a strong gust of wind reveals the true shape of a tree when it blows off all its leaves. Such events highlight what is hidden in the shadows, they nudge the spirit towards a place where it can flourish." -- Irene Nemirovsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2203-it-is-what-you-read-when-you-don-t-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 17:16:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2203-it-is-what-you-read-when-you-don-t-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is what you read when you don't have to that determines what you will be when you can't help it." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 17:18:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41237-mom-said-that-people-are-interested-in-birds-only-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 14:27:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41237-mom-said-that-people-are-interested-in-birds-only-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mom said that people are interested in birds only in as much as they exhibit human behavior - greed and stupidity and anger - and by doing so they free us from the unique sorrow of being human...I told Mom my own theory of why we like birds - of how birds are a miracle because they prove to us there is a finer, simpler state of being which we may strive to attain." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41238-so-this-is-how-they-lived-for-some-time-theo</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 14:28:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41238-so-this-is-how-they-lived-for-some-time-theo]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So this is how they lived.  For some time Theo, like a tree living in the shadow of taller trees, found a way to live off reflected light." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41239-it-was-as-if-hannah-had-sprung-a-leak-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 14:29:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Marisha Pessl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41239-it-was-as-if-hannah-had-sprung-a-leak-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was as if Hannah had sprung a leak and her character, usually so meticulous and contained, was spilling all over the place." -- Marisha Pessl]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
