<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/248065-melissa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/248065-melissa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 18:42:22 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/515134-great-teachers-had-great-personalities-and-that-the-greatest-teachers</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 18:42:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/515134-great-teachers-had-great-personalities-and-that-the-greatest-teachers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Great teachers had great personalities and that the greatest teachers had outrageous personalities. I did not like decorum or rectitude in a classroom; I preferred a highly oxygenated atmosphere, a climate of intemperance, rhetoric, and feverish melodrama. And I wanted my teachers to make me smart. A great teacher is my adversary, my conqueror, commissioned to chastise me. He leaves me tame and grateful for the new language he has purloined from other kings whose granaries are filled and whose libraries are famous. He tells me that teaching is the art of theft: of knowing what to steal and from whom. Bad teachers do not touch me; the great ones never leave me. They ride with me during all my days, and I pass on to others what they have imparted to me. I exchange their handy gifts with strangers on trains, and I pretend the gifts are mine. I steal from the great teachers. And the truly wonderful thing about them is they would applaud my theft, laugh at the thought of it, realizing they had taught me their larcenous skills well." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11540-you-get-a-little-moody-sometimes-but-i-think-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 00:56:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11540-you-get-a-little-moody-sometimes-but-i-think-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You get a little moody sometimes but I think that's because you like to read. People that like to read are always a little fucked up." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32476-i-don-t-know-why-it-is-that-i-have-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 00:57:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32476-i-don-t-know-why-it-is-that-i-have-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don’t know why it is that I have always been happier thinking of somewhere I have been or wanted to go, than where I am at the time. I find it difficult to be happy in the present." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16718-no-story-is-a-straight-line-the-geometry-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 00:57:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16718-no-story-is-a-straight-line-the-geometry-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No story is a straight line.  The geometry of a human life is too imperfect and complex, too distorted by the laughter of time and the bewildering intricacies of fate to admit the straight line into its system of laws." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/862-music-could-ache-and-hurt-that-beautiful-music-was-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 00:57:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/862-music-could-ache-and-hurt-that-beautiful-music-was-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Music could ache and hurt, that beautiful music was a place a suffering man could hide." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224753-the-world-of-literature-has-everything-in-it-and-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 00:57:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224753-the-world-of-literature-has-everything-in-it-and-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world of literature has everything in it, and it refuses to leave 
anything out. I have read like a man on fire my whole life because the 
genius of English teachers touched me with the dazzling beauty of language. 
Because of them I rode with Don Quixote and danced with Anna Karenina at a 
ball in St. Petersburg and lassoed a steer in &quot;Lonesome Dove&quot; and had 
nightmares about slavery in &quot;Beloved&quot; and walked the streets of Dublin in 
&quot;Ulysses&quot; and made up a hundred stories in the Arabian nights and saw my 
mother killed by a baseball in &quot;A Prayer for Owen Meany.&quot; I've been in ten 
thousand cities and have introduced myself to a hundred thousand strangers 
in my exuberant reading career, all because I listened to my fabulous 
English teachers and soaked up every single thing those magnificent men and 
women had to give. I cherish and praise them and thank them for finding me 
when I was a boy and presenting me with the precious gift of the English 
language. " -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315841-here-is-all-i-ask-of-a-book--give-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 00:58:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315841-here-is-all-i-ask-of-a-book--give-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here is all I ask of a book- give me everything. Everything, and don't leave out a single word." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392913-even-today-i-hunt-for-the-fabulous-books-that-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 00:59:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392913-even-today-i-hunt-for-the-fabulous-books-that-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even today, I hunt for the fabulous books that will change me utterly.  I find myself happiest in the middle of a book which I forget that I am reading, but am instead immersed in a made-up life lived at the highest pitch." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474105-here-s-what-i-want-from-a-book-what-i-demand</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 01:00:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474105-here-s-what-i-want-from-a-book-what-i-demand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's what I want from a book, what I demand, what I pray for when I take up a novel and begin to read the first sentence: I want everything and nothing less, the full measure of a writer's heart. I want a novel so poetic that I do not have to turn to the standby anthologies of poetry to satisfy that itch for music, for perfection and economy of phrasing, for exactness of tone. Then, too, I want a book so filled with story and character that I read page after page without thinking of food or drink because a writer has possessed me, crazed with an unappeasable thirst to know what happens next." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480128-here-s-what-i-love-when-a-great-writer-turns-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 01:01:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480128-here-s-what-i-love-when-a-great-writer-turns-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's what I love: when a great writer turns me into a Jew from Chicago, a lesbian out of South Carolina, or a black woman moving into a subway entrance in Harlem. Turn me into something else, writers of the world. Make me Muslim, heretic, hermaphrodite. Put me into a crusader's armor, a cardinal's vestments. Let me feel the pygmy's heartbeat, the queen's breast, the torturer's pleasure, the Nile's taste, or the nomad's thirst. Tell me everything that I must know. Hold nothing back." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/514428-i-meditated-on-the-nature-of-friendship-as-i-practiced</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 01:01:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/514428-i-meditated-on-the-nature-of-friendship-as-i-practiced]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I meditated on the nature of friendship as I practiced the craft. My friends had always come from outside the mainstream. I had always been popular with the fifth column of my peers, those individuals who were princely in their solitude, lords of their own unpraised melancholy. Distrusting the approval of the chosen, I would take the applause of exiles anytime. My friends were all foreigners, and they wore their unbelongingness in their eyes. I hunted for that look; I saw it often, disarrayed and fragmentary and furious, and I approached every boy who invited me in." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59478-memory-in-these-incomparable-streets-in-mosaics-of-pain-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 01:02:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59478-memory-in-these-incomparable-streets-in-mosaics-of-pain-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Memory in these incomparable streets, in mosaics of pain and sweetness, was clear to me now, a unity at last. I remembered small and unimportant things from the past: the whispers of roommates during thunderstorms, the smell of brass polish on my fingertips, the first swim at Folly Beach in April, lightning over the Atlantic, shelling oysters at Bowen's Island during a rare Carolina snowstorm, pigeons strutting across the graveyard at St. Philip's, lawyers moving out of their offices to lunch on Broad Street, the darkness of reveille on cold winter mornings, regattas, the flash of bagpipers' tartans passing in review, blue herons on the marshes, the pressure of the chinstrap on my shako, brotherhood, shad roe at Henry's, camellias floating above water in a porcelain bowl, the scowl of Mark Santoro, and brotherhood again." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32484-anyone-who-knows-me-well-must-understand-and-be-sympathetic</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 01:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32484-anyone-who-knows-me-well-must-understand-and-be-sympathetic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who knows me well must understand and be sympathetic to my genuine need to be my own greatest hero. It is not a flaw of character; it is a catastrophe." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
