<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/248308-christine]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/248308-christine" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 21:48:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296620-most-of-this-world-s-misery-is-the-fruit-not-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 21:48:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Rafael Sabatini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296620-most-of-this-world-s-misery-is-the-fruit-not-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most of this world's misery is the fruit not as priests tell us of wickedness, but of stupidity....
And we know that of all stupidities he considered anger the most deplorable." -- Rafael Sabatini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427063-civilized-people-must-i-believe-satisfy-the-following-criteria-1</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 09:35:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Anton Chekhov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427063-civilized-people-must-i-believe-satisfy-the-following-criteria-1]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Civilized people must, I believe, satisfy the following criteria:

1)  They respect human beings as individuals and are therefore always tolerant, gentle, courteous and amenable ... They do not create scenes over a hammer or a mislaid eraser; they do not make you feel they are conferring a great benefit on you when they live with you, and they don't make a scandal when they leave. (...)

2)  They have compassion for other people besides beggars and cats.  Their hearts suffer the pain of what is hidden to the naked eye. (...)

3)  They respect other people's property, and therefore pay their debts.

4)  They are not devious, and they fear lies as they fear fire.  They don't tell lies even in the most trivial matters.  To lie to someone is to insult them, and the liar is diminished in the eyes of the person he lies to.  Civilized people don't put on airs; they behave in the street as they would at home, they don't show off to impress their juniors. (...)

5)  They don't run themselves down in order to provoke the sympathy of others.  They don't play on other people's heartstrings to be sighed over and cosseted ... that sort of thing is just cheap striving for effects, it's vulgar, old hat and false. (...)

6)  They are not vain.  They don't waste time with the fake jewellery of hobnobbing with celebrities, being permitted to shake the hand of a drunken [judicial orator], the exaggerated bonhomie of the first person they meet at the Salon, being the life and soul of the bar ... They regard prases like 'I am a representative of the Press!!' -- the sort of thing one only hears from [very minor journalists] -- as absurd.  If they have done a brass farthing's work they don't pass it off as if it were 100 roubles' by swanking about with their portfolios, and they don't boast of being able to gain admission to places other people aren't allowed in (...) True talent always sits in the shade, mingles with the crowd, avoids the limelight ... As Krylov said, the empty barrel makes more noise than the full one. (...)

7)  If they do possess talent, they value it ... They take pride in it ... they know they have a responsibility to exert a civilizing influence on [others] rather than aimlessly hanging out with them.  And they are fastidious in their habits. (...)

8)  They work at developing their aesthetic sensibility ... Civilized people don't simply obey their baser instincts ... they require &lt;i&gt;mens sana in corpore sano&lt;/i&gt;.

And so on.  That's what civilized people are like ... Reading &lt;i&gt;Pickwick&lt;/i&gt; and learning a speech from &lt;i&gt;Faust&lt;/i&gt; by heart is not enough if your aim is to become a truly civilized person and not to sink below the level of your surroundings.

[From a letter to Nikolay Chekhov, March 1886]" -- Anton Chekhov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/902943-while-they-were-dancing-the-buoyancy-that-the-champagne-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 08:36:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Monica Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/902943-while-they-were-dancing-the-buoyancy-that-the-champagne-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["While they were dancing, the buoyancy that the champagne had given her left her all at once, and she slumped and felt suddenly tired and miserable about all the things that Denys should have said and done and hadn't.  At the end of the dance there was one awful moment when she was bored. She didn't want to go and be kissed in the garden, she didn't want to drink any more, and Denys was in no mood for conversation; what was there to do? She was bored. It was a terrible, treacherous thought to feel like that when you were with someone you loved." -- Monica Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1275765-men-may-irritate-women-entirely-by-accident-but-i-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 15:03:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by S.E. Grove ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1275765-men-may-irritate-women-entirely-by-accident-but-i-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men may irritate women entirely by accident, but I believe they infuriate one another wholly by design." -- S.E. Grove ]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
