<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/250817-inder]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/250817-inder" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 15:19:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114885-that-is-how-life-goes--we-send-our-children-into-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 15:19:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114885-that-is-how-life-goes--we-send-our-children-into-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That is how life goes--we send our children into the wilderness. Some of them on the day they are born, it seems, for all the help we can give them. Some of them seem to be a kind of wilderness unto themselves. But there must be angels there, too, and springs of water. Even that wilderness, the very habitation of jackals, is the Lord's." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73824-man-in-good-earnest-is-a-marvellous-vain-fickle-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 13:20:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Michel de Montaigne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73824-man-in-good-earnest-is-a-marvellous-vain-fickle-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man (in good earnest) is a marvellous vain, fickle, and unstable subject, and on whom it is very hard to form any certain and uniform judgment." -- Michel de Montaigne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77196-i-had-rather-complain-of-ill-fortune-than-be-ashamed-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2008 15:22:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Michel de Montaigne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77196-i-had-rather-complain-of-ill-fortune-than-be-ashamed-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had rather complain of ill-fortune than be ashamed of victory." -- Michel de Montaigne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78760-such-as-are-in-immediate-fear-of-a-losing-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 15:54:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Michel de Montaigne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78760-such-as-are-in-immediate-fear-of-a-losing-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Such as are in immediate fear of a losing their estates, of banishment, or of slavery, live in perpetual anguish, and lose all appetite and repose; whereas such as are actually poor, slaves, or exiles, ofttimes live as merrily as other folk." -- Michel de Montaigne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9766-in-the-shop-window-you-have-promptly-identified-the-cover</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 13:02:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9766-in-the-shop-window-you-have-promptly-identified-the-cover]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the shop window you have promptly identified the cover with the title you were looking for. Following this visual trail, you have forced your way through the shop past the thick barricade of Books You Haven't Read, which are frowning at you from the tables and shelves, trying to cow you...And thus you pass the outer girdle of ramparts, but then you are attacked by the infantry of Books That If You Had More Than One Life You Would Certainly Also Read But Unfortunately Your Days Are Numbered. With a rapid maneuver you bypass them and move into the phalanxes of the Books You Mean To Read But There Are Others You Must Read First, the Books Too Expensive Now And You'll Wait Till They're Remaindered, the Books ditto When They Come Out in Paperback, Books You Can Borrow From Somebody, Books That Everybody's Read So It's As If You Had Read Them, Too. " -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65-maturity-is-a-bitter-disappointment-for-which-no-remedy-exists</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 11:50:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65-maturity-is-a-bitter-disappointment-for-which-no-remedy-exists]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maturity is a bitter disappointment for which no remedy exists, unless laughter could be said to remedy anything." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15730-dear-child-of-god-i-am-sorry-to-say-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2008 10:22:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Desmond Tutu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15730-dear-child-of-god-i-am-sorry-to-say-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dear Child of God, I am sorry to say that suffering is not optional." -- Desmond Tutu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6691-if-i-should-ever-die-god-forbid-let-this-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2008 14:59:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by kurt vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6691-if-i-should-ever-die-god-forbid-let-this-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I should ever die, God forbid, let this be my epitaph:
THE ONLY PROOF HE NEEDED
FOR THE EXISTENCE OF GOD
WAS MUSIC" -- kurt vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103656-the-old-family-carriage-and-the-two-lady-s-maids-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2008 11:08:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Anthony Trollope]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103656-the-old-family-carriage-and-the-two-lady-s-maids-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The old family carriage and the two lady's maids were there,--as necessaries of life; but London society was not within her reach. It was therefore the case that they had not heard very much about Lizzie Eustace. But they had heard something. &quot;I hope she won't be too fond of going out,&quot; said Amelia, the second girl.

&quot;Or extravagant,&quot; said Georgina, the third.

&quot;There was some story of her being terribly in debt when she married Sir Florian Eustace,&quot; said Diana, the fourth.

&quot;Frederic will be sure to see to that,&quot; said Augusta, the eldest.

&quot;She is very beautiful,&quot; said Lydia, the fifth.

&quot;And clever,&quot; said Cecilia, the sixth.

&quot;Beauty and cleverness won't make a good wife,&quot; said Amelia, who was the wise one of the family.

&quot;Frederic will be sure to see that she doesn't go wrong,&quot; said Augusta who was not wise." -- Anthony Trollope]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70980-to-have-her-meals-and-her-daily-walk-and-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2008 11:10:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Anthony Trollope]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70980-to-have-her-meals-and-her-daily-walk-and-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To have her meals, and her daily walk, and her fill of novels, and to be left alone, was all that she asked of the gods." -- Anthony Trollope]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107039-i-don-t-like-anybody-or-anything-said-lucinda-yes-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2008 16:20:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Anthony Trollope]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107039-i-don-t-like-anybody-or-anything-said-lucinda-yes-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't like anybody or anything,&quot; said Lucinda.

Yes, you do;--you like horses to ride, and dresses to wear." -- Anthony Trollope]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110674-there-was-very-much-in-the-whole-affair-of-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 19:19:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Anthony Trollope]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110674-there-was-very-much-in-the-whole-affair-of-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was very much in the whole affair of which he would not be proud as he led his bride to the altar;--but a man does not expect to get four thousand pounds a year for nothing." -- Anthony Trollope]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49016-remember-this-for-it-is-as-true-and-true-gets</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 12:44:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Ina May Gaskin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49016-remember-this-for-it-is-as-true-and-true-gets]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember this, for it is as true and true gets: Your body is not a lemon. You are not a machine. The Creator is not a careless mechanic. Human female bodies have the same potential to give birth well as aardvarks, lions, rhinoceri, elephants, moose, and water buffalo. Even if it has not been your habit throughout your life so far, I recommend that you learn to think positively about your body." -- Ina May Gaskin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117354-dear-child-of-god-i-write-these-words-because-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2008 17:11:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Desmond Tutu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117354-dear-child-of-god-i-write-these-words-because-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dear Child of God, I write these words because we all experience sadness, we all come at times to despair, and we all lose hope that the suffering in our lives and in the world will ever end. I want to share with you my faith and my understanding that this suffering can be transformed and redeemed. There is no such thing as a totally hopeless case. Our God is an expert at dealing with chaos, with brokenness, with all the worst that we can imagine. God created order out of disorder, cosmos out of chaos, and God can do so always, can do so now--in our personal lives and in our lives as nations, globally. ... Indeed, God is transforming the world now--through us--because God loves us." -- Desmond Tutu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41667-whether-i-shall-turn-out-to-be-the-hero-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 13:02:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41667-whether-i-shall-turn-out-to-be-the-hero-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whether I shall turn out to be the hero of my own life, or whether that station will be held by anybody else, these pages must show." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90487-annual-income-twenty-pounds-annual-expenditure-nineteen-six-result-happiness</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 13:03:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90487-annual-income-twenty-pounds-annual-expenditure-nineteen-six-result-happiness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Annual income twenty pounds, annual expenditure nineteen six, result happiness. Annual income twenty pounds, annual expenditure twenty pound ought and six, result misery." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159771-if-you-can-t-be-a-hero-you-can-at-least</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2009 20:54:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Ina May Gaskin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159771-if-you-can-t-be-a-hero-you-can-at-least]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can't be a hero, you can at least be funny while being a chicken." -- Ina May Gaskin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206103-but-what-is-the-sense-in-forever-speculating-what-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 15:54:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206103-but-what-is-the-sense-in-forever-speculating-what-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But what is the sense in forever speculating what might have happened had such and such a moment turned out differently? One could presumably drive oneself to distraction in this way. In any case, while it is all very well to talk of 'turning points', one can surely only recognize such moments in retrospect. Naturally, when one looks back to such instances today, they may indeed take the appearance of being crucial, precious moments in one's life; but of course, at the time, this was not the impression one had. Rather, it was as though one had available a never-ending number of days, months, years in which to sort out the vagaries of one's relationship with Miss Kenton; an infinite number of further opportunities in which to remedy the effect of this or that misunderstanding. There was surely nothing to indicate at the time that such evidently small incidents would render whole dreams forever irredeemable." -- Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97674-i-m-writing-this-in-part-to-tell-you-that-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 15:20:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97674-i-m-writing-this-in-part-to-tell-you-that-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’m writing this in part to tell you that if you ever wonder what you’ve done in your life, and everyone does wonder sooner or later, you have been God’s grace to me, a miracle, something more than a miracle. You may not remember me very well at all, and it may seem to you to be no great thing to have been the good child of an old man in a shabby little town you will no doubt leave behind. If only I had the words to tell you." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279125-it-was-a-movie-about-american-bombers-in-world-war</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2011 10:29:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279125-it-was-a-movie-about-american-bombers-in-world-war]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was a movie about American bombers in World War II and the gallant men who flew them. Seen backwards by Billy, the story went like this:  American planes, full of holes and wounded men and corpses took off backwards from an airfield in England.  Over France, a few German fighter planes flew at them backwards, sucked bullets and shell fragments from some of the planes and crewmen. They did the same for wrecked American bombers on the ground, and those planes flew up backwards to join the formation.
The formation flew backwards over a German city that was in flames.  The bombers opened their bomb bay doors, exerted a miraculous magnetism which shrunk the fires, gathered them into cylindrical steel containers , and lifted the containers into the bellies of the planes.  The containers were stored neatly in racks.  The Germans below had miraculous devices of their own, which were long steel tubes.  They used them to suck more fragments from the crewmen and planes. But there were still a few wounded Americans though and some of the bombers were in bad repair.  Over France though, German fighters came up again, made everything and everybody as good as new.
When the bombers got back to their base, the steel cylinders were taken from the racks and shipped back to the United States of America, where factories were operating night and day, dismantling the cylinders, separating the dangerous contents into minerals.   Touchingly, it was mainly women who did this work.  The minerals were then shipped to specialists in remote areas.  It was their business to put them into the ground, to hide them cleverly, so they would never hurt anybody ever again.  The American fliers turned in their uniforms, became high school kids.  And Hitler turned into a baby." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48299-experience-is-a-brutal-teacher-but-you-learn-fast</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 15:57:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by William Nicholson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48299-experience-is-a-brutal-teacher-but-you-learn-fast]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Experience is a brutal teacher, but you learn fast." -- William Nicholson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/502833-faith-is-not-an-art-faith-is-not-an-achievement</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 10:33:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Karl Barth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/502833-faith-is-not-an-art-faith-is-not-an-achievement]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Faith is not an art. Faith is not an achievement. Faith is not a good work of which some may boast while others can excuse themselves with a shrug of the shoulders for not being capable of it. It is a decisive insight of faith itself that all of us are incapable of faith in ourselves, whether we think of its preparation, beginning, continuation, or completion. In this respect believers understand unbelievers, skeptics, and atheists better than they understand themselves.  Unlike unbelievers, they regard the impossibility of faith as necessary, not accidental ..." -- Karl Barth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228530-at-the-most-we-gaze-at-it-in-wonder-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 14:14:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by W.G. Sebald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228530-at-the-most-we-gaze-at-it-in-wonder-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the most we gaze at it in wonder, a kind of wonder which in itself is a form of dawning horror, for somehow we know by instinct that outsize buildings cast the shadow of their own destruction before them, and are designed from the first with an eye to their later existence as ruins." -- W.G. Sebald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37668-you-have-enemies-good-that-means-you-ve-stood-up-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 11:32:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inder add a quote by Winston Churchill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37668-you-have-enemies-good-that-means-you-ve-stood-up-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have enemies? Good. That means you've stood up for something, sometime in your life." -- Winston Churchill]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
