<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/251035-charlie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/251035-charlie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 21:12:49 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118895-there-are-in-us-possibilities-that-take-our-breath-away</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 21:12:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlie add a quote by William James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118895-there-are-in-us-possibilities-that-take-our-breath-away]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[There are, in us] possibilities that take our breath away, and show a world wider than either physics or philistine ethics can imagine. Here is a world in which all is well, &lt;i&gt;in spite&lt;/i&gt; of certain forms of death, death of hope, death of strength, death of responsibility, of fear and wrong, death of everything that paganism, naturalism and legalism pin their trust on." -- William James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202118-wise-blood-was-written-by-an-author-congenitally-innocent-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2009 08:09:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlie add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202118-wise-blood-was-written-by-an-author-congenitally-innocent-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wise Blood was written by an author congenitally innocent of theory, but one with certain preoccupations. That belief in Christ is to some a matter of life and death has been a stumbling block for readers who would prefer to think it a matter of no great consequence. For them Hazel Motes' integrity lies in his trying with such vigor to get rid of the ragged figure who moves from tree to tree in the back of his mind. For the author Hazel's integrity lies in his not being able to. Does one's integrity ever lie in what he is not able to do? I think that usually it does, for free will does not mean one will, but many wills conflicting in one man. Freedom cannot be conceived simply. It is a mystery and one which a novel, even a comic novel, can only be asked to deepen." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182987-a-philosophical-thought-is-not-supposed-to-be-impervious-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2009 08:09:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlie add a quote by Graham Harman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182987-a-philosophical-thought-is-not-supposed-to-be-impervious-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A philosophical thought is not supposed to be impervious to all criticism; this is the error Whitehead describes of turning philosophy into geometry, and it is useful primarily as a way of gaining short-term triumphs in personal arguments that no one else cares (or even knows) about anyway. A good philosophical thought will always be subject to criticisms (as Heidegger’s or Whitehead’s best insights all are) but they are of such elegance and depth that they change the terms of debate, and function as a sort of “obligatory passage point” (Latour’s term) in the discussions that follow.

Or in other words, the reason Being and Time is still such a classic, with hundreds of thousands or millions of readers almost a century later, is not because Heidegger made “fewer mistakes” than others of his generation. Mistakes need to be cleaned up, but that is not the primary engine of personal or collective intellectual progress." -- Graham Harman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
