<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/251555-shinynickel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/251555-shinynickel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 21:41:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4490-a-man-sets-out-to-draw-the-world-as-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 21:41:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shinynickel add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4490-a-man-sets-out-to-draw-the-world-as-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man sets out to draw the world.  As the years go by, he peoples a space with images of provinces, kingdoms, mountains, bays, ships, islands, fishes, rooms, instruments, stars, horses, and individuals. A short time before he dies, he discovers that the patient labyrinth of lines traces the lineaments of his own face." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12578-in-the-critic-s-vocabulary-the-word-precursor-is-indispensable-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 21:41:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shinynickel add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12578-in-the-critic-s-vocabulary-the-word-precursor-is-indispensable-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the critic's vocabulary, the word &quot;precursor&quot; is indispensable, but it should be cleansed of all connotations of polemic or rivalry. The fact is that every writer creates his own precursors. His work modifies our conception of the past, as it will modify the future.&quot;
-- Essay: &quot;Kafka and his Precursors" -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14739-you-have-wakened-not-out-of-sleep-but-into-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 21:41:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shinynickel add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14739-you-have-wakened-not-out-of-sleep-but-into-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have wakened not out of sleep, but into a prior dream, and that dream lies within another, and so on, to infinity, which is the number of grains of sand. The path that you are to take is endless, and you will die before you have truly awakened." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160615-it-s-said-that-science-will-dehumanize-people-and-turn-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2009 10:25:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shinynickel add a quote by Jacob Bronowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160615-it-s-said-that-science-will-dehumanize-people-and-turn-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's said that science will dehumanize people and turn them into numbers. That's false, tragically false. Look for yourself. This is the concentration camp and crematorium at Auschwitz. This is where people were turned into numbers. Into this pond were flushed the ashes of some four million people. And that was not done by gas. It was done by arrogance, it was done by dogma, it was done by ignorance. When people believe that they have absolute knowledge, with no test in reality, this is how they behave. This is what men do when they aspire to the knowledge of gods.

Science is a very human form of knowledge. We are always at the brink of the known; we always feel forward for what is to be hoped. Every judgment in science stands on the edge of error and is &lt;i&gt;personal&lt;/i&gt;. Science is a tribute to what we can know although we are fallible. In the end, the words were said by Oliver Cromwell: &quot;I beseech you in the bowels of Christ: Think it possible you may be mistaken.&quot;

I owe it as a scientist to my friend Leo Szilard, I owe it as a human being to the many members of my family who died here, to stand here as a survivor and a witness. We have to cure ourselves of the itch for absolute knowledge and power. We have to close the distance between the push-button order and the human act. We have to &lt;i&gt;touch&lt;/i&gt; people." -- Jacob Bronowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422-there-are-years-that-ask-questions-and-years-that-answer</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 22:35:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shinynickel add a quote by Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422-there-are-years-that-ask-questions-and-years-that-answer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are years that ask questions and years that answer." -- Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325712-we-would-be-worse-than-we-are-without-the-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 11:24:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shinynickel add a quote by Mario Vargas Llosa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325712-we-would-be-worse-than-we-are-without-the-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We would be worse than we are without the good books we have read, more conformist, not as restless, more submissive, and the critical spirit, the engine of progress, would not even exist. Like writing, reading is a protest against the insufficiencies of life. When we look in fiction for what is missing in life, we are saying, with no need to say it or even to know it, that life as it is does not satisfy our thirst for the absolute – the foundation of the human condition – and should be better. We invent fictions in order to live somehow the many lives we would like to lead when we barely have one at our disposal." -- Mario Vargas Llosa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50677-who-has-never-killed-an-hour-not-casually-or-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 13:55:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shinynickel add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50677-who-has-never-killed-an-hour-not-casually-or-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who has never killed an hour? Not casually or without thought, but carefully: a premeditated murder of minutes. The violence comes from a combination of giving up, not caring, and a resignation that getting past it is all you can hope to accomplish. So you kill the hour. You do not work, you do not read, you do not daydream. If you sleep it is not because you need to sleep. And when at last it is over, there is no evidence: no weapon, no blood, and no body. The only clue might be the shadows beneath your eyes or a terribly thin line near the corner of your mouth indicating something has been suffered, that in the privacy of your life you have lost something and the loss is too empty to share." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78990-all-stories-are-about-wolves-all-worth-repeating-that-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2012 09:26:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shinynickel add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78990-all-stories-are-about-wolves-all-worth-repeating-that-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All stories are about wolves. All worth repeating, that is. Anything else is sentimental drivel.

All of them?

Sure, he says. Think about it. There's escaping from the wolves, fighting the wolves, capturing the wolves, taming the wolves. Being thrown to the wolves, or throwing others to the wolves so the wolves will eat them instead of you. Running with the wolf pack. Turning into a wolf. Best of all, turning into the head wolf. No other decent stories exist." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1921-tell-me-what-is-it-you-plan-to-do-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 14:10:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shinynickel add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1921-tell-me-what-is-it-you-plan-to-do-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tell me, what is it you plan to do 
with your one wild and precious life?" -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13750-if-only-it-were-all-so-simple-if-only-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 11:39:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shinynickel add a quote by Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13750-if-only-it-were-all-so-simple-if-only-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If only it were all so simple! If only there were evil people somewhere insidiously committing evil deeds, and it were necessary only to separate them from the rest of us and destroy them. But the line dividing good and evil cuts through the heart of every human being. And who is willing to destroy a piece of his own heart?" -- Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22532-own-only-what-you-can-always-carry-with-you-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 11:39:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shinynickel add a quote by Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22532-own-only-what-you-can-always-carry-with-you-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Own only what you can always carry with you: know languages, know countries, know people.  Let your memory be your travel bag." -- Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81085-you-only-have-power-over-people-as-long-as-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 11:39:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shinynickel add a quote by Alexander Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81085-you-only-have-power-over-people-as-long-as-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You only have power over people as long as you don't take everything away from them.  But when you've robbed a man of everything, he's no longer in your power--he's free again." -- Alexander Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/210116-when-you-re-cold-don-t-expect-sympathy-from-someone-who-s-warm</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 11:39:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shinynickel add a quote by Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/210116-when-you-re-cold-don-t-expect-sympathy-from-someone-who-s-warm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you're cold, don't expect sympathy from someone who's warm." -- Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
