<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/252119-matthew]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/252119-matthew" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 01:23:35 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10092-civilized-men-are-more-discourteous-than-savages-because-they-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 01:23:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Robert E. Howard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10092-civilized-men-are-more-discourteous-than-savages-because-they-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Civilized men are more discourteous than savages because they know they can be impolite without having their skulls split, as a general thing." -- Robert E. Howard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2583-you-only-live-twice-once-when-you-re-born-and-once</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 21:54:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Ian Fleming]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2583-you-only-live-twice-once-when-you-re-born-and-once]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You only live twice:
Once when you're born
And once when you look death in the face." -- Ian Fleming]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19786-tomorrow-you-re-all-going-to-wake-up-in-a-brave</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 01:22:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Stephen Colbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19786-tomorrow-you-re-all-going-to-wake-up-in-a-brave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tomorrow you're all going to wake up in a brave new world, a world where the Constitution gets trampled by an army of terrorist clones, created in a stem-cell research lab run by homosexual doctors who sterilize their instruments over burning American flags. Where tax-and-spend Democrats take all your hard-earned money and use it to buy electric cars for National Public Radio, and teach evolution to illegal immigrants. Oh, and everybody's high!" -- Stephen Colbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8051-until-a-man-is-twenty-five-he-still-thinks-every-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 01:22:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8051-until-a-man-is-twenty-five-he-still-thinks-every-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until a man is twenty-five, he still thinks, every so often, that under the right circumstances he could be the baddest motherfucker in the world. If I moved to a martial-arts monastery in China and studied real hard for ten years. If my family was wiped out by Colombian drug dealers and I swore myself to revenge. If I got a fatal disease, had one year to live, and devoted it to wiping out street crime. If I just dropped out and devoted my life to being bad." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38367-i-have-known-many-gods-he-who-denies-them-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 01:22:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Robert E. Howard and L. Sprague De Camp]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38367-i-have-known-many-gods-he-who-denies-them-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have known many gods. He who denies them is as blind as he who trusts them too deeply. I seek not beyond death. It may be the blackness averred by the Nemedian skeptics, or Crom's realm of ice and cloud, or the snowy plains and vaulted halls of the Nordheimer's Valhalla. I know not, nor do I care. Let me live deep while I live; let me know the rich juices of red meat and stinging wine on my palate, the hot embrace of white arms, the mad exultation of battle when the blue blades flame and crimson, and I am content. Let teachers and philosophers brood over questions of reality and illusion. I know this: if life is illusion, then I am no less an illusion, and being thus, the illusion is real to me. I live, I burn with life, I love, I slay, and am content." -- Robert E. Howard and L. Sprague De Camp]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30962-you-are-not-entering-this-world-in-the-usual-manner</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 21:57:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Gary Gygax]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30962-you-are-not-entering-this-world-in-the-usual-manner]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are not entering this world in the usual manner, for you are setting forth to be a Dungeon Master. Certainly there are stout fighters, mighty magic-users, wily thieves, and courageous clerics who will make their mark in the magical lands of D&amp;D adventure. You however, are above even the greatest of these, for as DM you are to become the Shaper of the Cosmos. It is you who will give form and content to the all the universe. You will breathe life into the stillness, giving meaning and purpose to all the actions which are to follow." -- Gary Gygax]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25805-it-has-been-said-that-politics-is-the-second-oldest</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 21:56:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Ronald Reagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25805-it-has-been-said-that-politics-is-the-second-oldest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It has been said that politics is the second oldest profession. I have learned that it bears a striking resemblance to the first." -- Ronald Reagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1981-my-experience-of-life-is-that-it-is-not-divided</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 01:23:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1981-my-experience-of-life-is-that-it-is-not-divided]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My experience of life is that it is not divided up into genres; it’s a horrifying, romantic, tragic, comical, science-fiction cowboy detective novel. You know, with a bit of pornography if you're lucky." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1-the-story-so-far-in-the-beginning-the-universe-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 01:23:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1-the-story-so-far-in-the-beginning-the-universe-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The story so far:
In the beginning the Universe was created.
This has made a lot of people very angry and been widely regarded as a bad move." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4696-politics-is-the-only-field-of-human-endeavor-where-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 01:24:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Kinky Friedman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4696-politics-is-the-only-field-of-human-endeavor-where-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Politics is the only field of human endeavor where the more experience you have, the worse you get." -- Kinky Friedman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19189-in-ancient-times-cats-were-worshipped-as-gods-they-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 01:24:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19189-in-ancient-times-cats-were-worshipped-as-gods-they-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In ancient times cats were worshipped as gods; they have not forgotten this." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57809-the-worthy-gm-never-purposely-kills-players-pcs-he-presents</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 01:24:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Gary Gygax]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57809-the-worthy-gm-never-purposely-kills-players-pcs-he-presents]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worthy GM never purposely kills players' PCs, He presents opportunities for the rash and unthinking players to do that all on their own." -- Gary Gygax]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13104-there-are-more-things-in-heaven-and-earth-horatio-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 01:24:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13104-there-are-more-things-in-heaven-and-earth-horatio-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are more things in Heaven and Earth, Horatio, than are dreamt of in your philosophy." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12882-now-i-have-a-cat-well-that-s-not-quite-accurate</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 22:04:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Kinky Friedman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12882-now-i-have-a-cat-well-that-s-not-quite-accurate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now I have a cat. Well, that's not quite accurate. A cat and I have each other." -- Kinky Friedman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1146-it-was-about-eleven-o-clock-in-the-morning-mid-october</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 22:04:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Raymond Chandler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1146-it-was-about-eleven-o-clock-in-the-morning-mid-october]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was about eleven o'clock in the morning, mid October, with the sun not shining and a look of hard wet rain in the clearness of the foothills. I was wearing my powder-blue suit, with dark blue shirt, tie and display handkerchief, black brogues, black wool socks with dark little clocks on them. I was neat, clean, shaved and sober, and I didn't care who knew it. I was everything the well-dressed private detective ought to be. I was calling on four million dollars." -- Raymond Chandler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81562-isn-t-it-a-bit-unnerving-that-doctors-call-what-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 22:04:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81562-isn-t-it-a-bit-unnerving-that-doctors-call-what-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn’t it a bit unnerving that doctors call what they do “practice”?" -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118135-before-a-man-s-forty-girls-cost-nothing-after-that-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 22:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Ian Fleming]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118135-before-a-man-s-forty-girls-cost-nothing-after-that-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Before a man's forty, girls cost nothing. After that you have to pay money, or tell a story. Of the two, it's the story that hurts most. Anyway I'm not forty yet." -- Ian Fleming]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62239-books-are-the-perfect-entertainment-no-commercials-no-batteries-hours</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 22:03:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62239-books-are-the-perfect-entertainment-no-commercials-no-batteries-hours]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are the perfect entertainment: no commercials, no batteries, hours of enjoyment for each dollar spent. What I wonder is why everybody doesn't carry a book around for those inevitable dead spots in life." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125106-elmore-leonard-s-ten-rules-of-writing-1-never-open-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 22:03:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Elmore Leonard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125106-elmore-leonard-s-ten-rules-of-writing-1-never-open-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Elmore Leonard's Ten Rules of Writing

1. Never open a book with weather.
2.  Avoid prologues.
3. Never use a verb other than &quot;said&quot; to carry dialogue.
4. Never use an adverb to modify the verb &quot;said”…he admonished gravely.
5. Keep your exclamation points under control. You are allowed no more than two or three per 100,000 words of prose. 
6. Never use the words &quot;suddenly&quot; or &quot;all hell broke loose.&quot;
7. Use regional dialect, patois, sparingly.
8. Avoid detailed descriptions of characters.
9. Don't go into great detail describing places and things.
10. Try to leave out the part that readers tend to skip.

My most important rule is one that sums up the 10.

If it sounds like writing, I rewrite it." -- Elmore Leonard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122130-bond-always-mistrusted-short-men-they-grew-up-from-childhood</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 22:03:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Ian Fleming]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122130-bond-always-mistrusted-short-men-they-grew-up-from-childhood]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bond always mistrusted short men. They grew up from childhood with an inferiority complex. All their lives they would strive to be big - bigger than the others who had teased them as a child. Napoleon had been short, and Hitler. It was the short men that caused all the trouble in the world." -- Ian Fleming]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63481-religion-has-convinced-people-that-there-s-an-invisible-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 22:03:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63481-religion-has-convinced-people-that-there-s-an-invisible-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Religion has convinced people that there's an invisible man ... living in the sky. Who watches everything you do every minute of every day. And the invisible man has a list of ten specific things he doesn't want you to do. And if you do any of these things, he will send you to a special place, of burning and fire and smoke and torture and anguish for you to live forever, and suffer, and suffer, and burn, and scream, until the end of time. But he loves you. He loves you. He loves you and he needs money." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1494-the-beauty-of-religious-mania-is-that-it-has-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 22:03:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1494-the-beauty-of-religious-mania-is-that-it-has-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The beauty of religious mania is that it has the power to explain everything. Once God (or Satan) is accepted as the first cause of everything which happens in the mortal world, nothing is left to chance...logic can be happily tossed out the window." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70232-when-you-re-dead-they-really-fix-you-up-i-hope</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 22:03:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70232-when-you-re-dead-they-really-fix-you-up-i-hope]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you're dead, they really fix you up. I hope to hell when I do die somebody has sense enough to just dump me in the river or something. Anything except sticking me in a goddam cemetery. People coming and putting a bunch of flowers on your stomach on Sunday, and all that crap. Who wants flowers when you're dead? Nobody." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37262-vegetarians-and-their-hezbollah-like-splinter-faction-the-vegans-are-a-persistent</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 01:24:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Anthony Bourdain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37262-vegetarians-and-their-hezbollah-like-splinter-faction-the-vegans-are-a-persistent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Vegetarians, and their Hezbollah-like splinter-faction, the vegans, are a persistent irritant to any chef worth a damn.  

To me, life without veal stock, pork fat, sausage, organ meat, demi-glace, or even stinky cheese is a life not worth living.  

Vegetarians are the enemy of everything good and decent in the human spirit, an affront to all I stand for, the pure enjoyment of food.  The body, these waterheads imagine, is a temple that should not be polluted by animal protein.  It's healthier, they insist, though every vegetarian waiter I've worked with is brought down by any rumor of a cold.  

Oh, I'll accomodate them, I'll rummage around for something to feed them, for a 'vegetarian plate', if called on to do so.  Fourteen dollars for a few slices of grilled eggplant and zucchini suits my food cost fine." -- Anthony Bourdain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82154-a-republican-stands-up-in-congress-and-says-i-got</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 01:24:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Lewis Black]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82154-a-republican-stands-up-in-congress-and-says-i-got]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A republican stands up in congress and says 'I GOT A REALLY BAD IDEA!!' and the democrat stands up after him and says 'AND I CAN MAKE IT SHITTIER!!" -- Lewis Black]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9180-stood-in-firelight-sweltering-bloodstain-on-chest-like-map-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 01:22:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9180-stood-in-firelight-sweltering-bloodstain-on-chest-like-map-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stood in firelight, sweltering. Bloodstain on chest like map of violent new continent. Felt cleansed. Felt dark planet turn under my feet and knew what cats know that makes them scream like babies in night.

Looked at sky through smoke heavy with human fat and God was not there. The cold, suffocating dark goes on forever and we are alone. Live our lives, lacking anything better to do. Devise reason later. Born from oblivion; bear children, hell-bound as ourselves, go into oblivion. There is nothing else.

Existence is random. Has no pattern save what we imagine after staring at it for too long. No meaning save what we choose to impose. This rudderless world is not shaped by vague metaphysical forces. It is not God who kills the children. Not fate that butchers them or destiny that feeds them to the dogs. It’s us. Only us. Streets stank of fire. The void breathed hard on my heart, turning its illusions to ice, shattering them. Was reborn then, free to scrawl own design on this morally blank world.

Was Rorschach.

Does that answer your Questions, Doctor?" -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253196-throw-a-stick-and-the-servile-dog-wheezes-and-pants</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 15:45:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253196-throw-a-stick-and-the-servile-dog-wheezes-and-pants]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Throw a stick, and the servile dog wheezes and pants and stumbles to bring it to you. Do the same before a cat, and he will eye you with coolly polite and somewhat bored amusement. And just as inferior people prefer the inferior animal which scampers excitedly because someone else wants something, so do superior people respect the superior animal which lives its own life and knows that the puerile stick-throwings of alien bipeds are none of its business and beneath its notice. The dog barks and begs and tumbles to amuse you when you crack the whip. That pleases a meekness-loving peasant who relishes a stimulus to his self importance. The cat, on the other hand, charms you into playing for its benefit when it wishes to be amused; making you rush about the room with a paper on a string when it feels like exercise, but refusing all your attempts to make it play when it is not in the humour. That is personality and individuality and self-respect -- the calm mastery of a being whose life is its own and not yours -- and the superior person recognises and appreciates this because he too is a free soul whose position is assured, and whose only law is his own heritage and aesthetic sense." -- H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
