<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/252720-autumn-skye-gerhard]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/252720-autumn-skye-gerhard" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 15:51:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78456-when-you-stick-a-song-on-a-tape-you-set</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 15:51:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Autumn skye add a quote by rob sheffield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78456-when-you-stick-a-song-on-a-tape-you-set]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you stick a song on a tape, you set it free." -- rob sheffield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/504662-my-sweet-little-whorish-nora-i-did-as-you-told</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 20:18:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Autumn skye add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/504662-my-sweet-little-whorish-nora-i-did-as-you-told]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My sweet little whorish Nora I did as you told me, you dirty little girl, and pulled myself off twice when I read your letter. I am delighted to see that you do like being fucked arseways. Yes, now I can remember that night when I fucked you for so long backwards. It was the dirtiest fucking I ever gave you, darling. My prick was stuck in you for hours, fucking in and out under your upturned rump. I felt your fat sweaty buttocks under my belly and saw your flushed face and mad eyes. At every fuck I gave you your shameless tongue came bursting out through your lips and if a gave you a bigger stronger fuck than usual, fat dirty farts came spluttering out of your backside. You had an arse full of farts that night, darling, and I fucked them out of you, big fat fellows, long windy ones, quick little merry cracks and a lot of tiny little naughty farties ending in a long gush from your hole. It is wonderful to fuck a farting woman when every fuck drives one out of her. I think I would know Nora’s fart anywhere. I think I could pick hers out in a roomful of farting women. It is a rather girlish noise not like the wet windy fart which I imagine fat wives have. It is sudden and dry and dirty like what a bold girl would let off in fun in a school dormitory at night. I hope Nora will let off no end of her farts in my face so that I may know their smell also.

You say when I go back you will suck me off and you want me to lick your cunt, you little depraved blackguard. I hope you will surprise me some time when I am asleep dressed, steal over to me with a whore’s glow in your slumberous eyes, gently undo button after button in the fly of my trousers and gently take out your lover’s fat mickey, lap it up in your moist mouth and suck away at it till it gets fatter and stiffer and comes off in your mouth. Sometimes too I shall surprise you asleep, lift up your skirts and open your drawers gently, then lie down gently by you and begin to lick lazily round your bush. You will begin to stir uneasily then I will lick the lips of my darling’s cunt. You will begin to groan and grunt and sigh and fart with lust in your sleep. Then I will lick up faster and faster like a ravenous dog until your cunt is a mass of slime and your body wriggling wildly.

Goodnight, my little farting Nora, my dirty little fuckbird! There is one lovely word, darling, you have underlined to make me pull myself off better. Write me more about that and yourself, sweetly, dirtier, dirtier." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10071-time-is-a-drug-too-much-of-it-kills-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 19:45:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Autumn skye add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10071-time-is-a-drug-too-much-of-it-kills-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time is a drug.  Too much of it kills you." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63117-in-the-beginning-there-was-nothing-which-exploded</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 19:45:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Autumn skye add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63117-in-the-beginning-there-was-nothing-which-exploded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the beginning there was nothing, which exploded." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27726-somewhere-something-incredible-is-waiting-to-be-known</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 19:45:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Autumn skye add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27726-somewhere-something-incredible-is-waiting-to-be-known]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Somewhere, something incredible is waiting to be known." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34999-everyone-should-be-able-to-do-one-card-trick-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 19:46:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Autumn skye add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34999-everyone-should-be-able-to-do-one-card-trick-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone should be able to do one card trick, tell two jokes, and recite three poems, in case they are ever trapped in an elevator." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
