<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/253598-amanda]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/253598-amanda" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 11:55:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1147426-although-nobody-in-the-grace-movement-is-saying-grace-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 11:55:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by D.R. Silva]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1147426-although-nobody-in-the-grace-movement-is-saying-grace-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Although nobody in the grace movement is saying grace is a license to sin (nor have they ever), it’s often assumed that, since we don’t emphasize the Law and push it on people like our accusers think we should, we must be endorsing sin and telling people it’s okay to do whatever they want. In truth, we avoid pushing the Law because we believe what scripture says: that the Law increases sin (Romans 5:20), sin gets its strength from the Law (1 Cor. 15:56), the Law is the ministry of death (2 Cor. 3:6), the Law isn’t based on faith (Gal. 3:12), and nobody can be made right with God through keeping the Law (Gal. 2:20). In fact, though many preachers will tell us today that it’s sin that separates us from God, and we need to go back to His holy Law to be reconciled, scripture actually teaches the opposite. It says that the Law is what separates people from Christ and causes them to fall from grace (Gal. 5:4). Our choice to not enforce those Laws is not because we want to see people sin, but because we want them to live free from sin. Scripture is very clear that those Laws are the very thing causing people to sin. While we receive many accusations that our grace-emphasized message is a “license to sin,” if you look at the church today, and all throughout its entire history, sin and the blatant abuse of people has always been done in the name of the Law, not in the name of grace. Nobody has ever killed anyone in the name of God’s grace, and yet countless crusades and wars have been waged in the name of upholding and enforcing those Laws. Some today are in Uganda using the law as a license to kill homosexuals.[27] Why do we ignore what scripture so clearly says about the law? “The letter kills…" -- D.R. Silva]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1151336-we-think-when-jesus-said-you-have-heard-it-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 06:10:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by D.R. Silva]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1151336-we-think-when-jesus-said-you-have-heard-it-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We think when Jesus said, “You have heard it said do not commit adultery, but if you even think about it you’re guilty,” that He was trying to get them to be more obedient to those Laws. He made those Laws impossible. He did so on purpose so they would stop trying to live up to them and put their faith in Him. He wasn’t trying to rally them up for holiness when He said, “If your right hand causes you to sin, cut it off!” He was telling them how severe the Law really is if they were going to continue trying to live by it, because they had cheapened it and made it doable, just like so many have today. Jesus was saying, “You want to gain holiness and purity that way? Cut off your hand and gouge out your eye if they cause you to sin. Because if you break even one of those Laws, you will be judged for breaking them all.”[29]" -- D.R. Silva]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
