<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/255053-michelle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/255053-michelle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 14:29:44 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4566-in-vain-have-i-struggled-it-will-not-do-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 14:29:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4566-in-vain-have-i-struggled-it-will-not-do-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In vain have I struggled. It will not do. My feelings will not be repressed. You must allow me to tell you how ardently I admire and love you." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292387-whatever-you-are-physically-male-or-female-strong-or-weak-ill</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 14:30:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Cassandra Clare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292387-whatever-you-are-physically-male-or-female-strong-or-weak-ill]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever you are physically...male or female, strong or weak, ill or healthy--all those things matter less than what your heart contains. If you have the soul of a warrior, you are a warrior. All those other things, they are the glass that contains the lamp, but &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; are the light inside." -- Cassandra Clare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/461086-we-live-and-breathe-words-it-was-books-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 14:30:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Cassandra Clare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/461086-we-live-and-breathe-words-it-was-books-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We live and breathe words. .... It was books that made me feel that perhaps I was not completely alone. They could be honest with me, and I with them. Reading your words, what you wrote, how you were lonely sometimes and afraid, but always brave; the way you saw the world, its colors and textures and sounds, I felt--I felt the way you thought, hoped, felt, dreamt. I felt I was dreaming and thinking and feeling &lt;i&gt;with&lt;/i&gt; you. I dreamed what you dreamed, wanted what you wanted--and then I realized that truly I just wanted you." -- Cassandra Clare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/514809-i-missed-you-every-hour-and-you-know-what-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 07:56:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Leigh Bardugo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/514809-i-missed-you-every-hour-and-you-know-what-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I missed you every hour. And you know what the worst part was? It caught me completely by surprise. I'd catch myself just walking around to find you, not for any reason, just out of habit, because I'd seen something that I wanted to tell you about or because I wanted to hear your voice. And then I'd realize that you weren't there anymore, and every time, &lt;em&gt;every single time&lt;/em&gt;, it was like having the wind knocked out of me. I've risked my life for you. I've walked half the length of Ravka for you, and I'd do it again and again and again just to be with you, just to starve with you and freeze with you and hear you complain about hard cheese every day. So don't tell me why we don't belong together,&quot; he said fiercely." -- Leigh Bardugo]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
