<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/255116-zack-wagoner]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/255116-zack-wagoner" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 23:45:06 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353389-words-are-pale-shadows-of-forgotten-names-as-names-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 23:45:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zack add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353389-words-are-pale-shadows-of-forgotten-names-as-names-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Words are pale shadows of forgotten names. As names have power, words have power. Words can light fires in the minds of men. Words can wring tears from the hardest hearts. There are seven words that will make a person love you. There are ten words that will break a strong man's will. But a word is nothing but a painting of a fire. A name is the fire itself." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161323-my-parents-danced-together-her-head-on-his-chest-both</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 23:46:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zack add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161323-my-parents-danced-together-her-head-on-his-chest-both]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My parents danced together, her head on his chest. Both had their eyes closed. They seemed so perfectly content. If you can find someone like that, someone who you can hold and close your eyes to the world with, then you're lucky. Even if it only lasts for a minute or a day. The image of them gently swaying to the music is how I picture love in my mind even after all these years." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278876-i-have-known-her-longer-my-smile-said-true-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 23:47:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zack add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278876-i-have-known-her-longer-my-smile-said-true-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have known her longer, my smile said.  True, you have been inside the circle of her arms, tasted her mouth, felt the warmth of her, and that is something I have never had.  But there is a part of her that is only for me.  You cannot touch it, no matter how hard you might try.  And after she has left you I will still be here, making her laugh.  My light shining in her.  I will still be here long after she has forgotten your name." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112296-chronicler-shook-his-head-and-bast-gave-a-frustrated-sigh</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 23:48:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zack add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112296-chronicler-shook-his-head-and-bast-gave-a-frustrated-sigh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chronicler shook his head and Bast gave a frustrated sigh. &quot;How about plays? Have you seen &lt;i&gt;The Ghost and the Goosegirl&lt;/i&gt; or &lt;i&gt;The Ha'penny King&lt;/i&gt;?&quot;
Chronicler frowned. &quot;Is that the one where the king sells his crown to an orphan boy?&quot;
Bast nodded. &quot;And the boy becomes a better king than the original. The goosegirl dresses like a countess and everyone is stunned by her grace and charm.&quot; He hesitated, struggling to find the words he wanted. &quot;You see, there's a fundamental connection between &lt;i&gt;seeming&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;being&lt;/i&gt;. Every Fae child knows this, but you mortals never seem to see. We understand how dangerous a mask can be. We all become what we pretend to be.&quot;
Chronicler relaxed a bit, sensing familiar ground. &quot;That's basic psychology. You dress a beggar in fine clothes, people treat him like a noble, and he lives up to their expectations.&quot;
&quot;That's only the smallest piece of it,&quot; Bast said. &quot;The truth is deeper than that. It's...&quot; Bast floundered for a moment. &quot;It's like everyone tells a story about themselves inside their own head. Always. All the time. That story makes you what you are. We build ourselves out of that story.&quot;
Frowning, Chronicler opened his mouth, but Bast held up a hand to stop him. &quot;No, listen. I've got it now. You meet a girl: shy, unassuming. If you tell her she's beautiful, she'll think you're sweet, but she won't believe you. She knows that beauty lies in your beholding.&quot; Bast gave a grudging shrug. &quot;And sometimes that's enough.&quot;
His eyes brightened. &quot;But there's a better way. You &lt;i&gt;show&lt;/i&gt; her she is beautiful. You make mirrors of your eyes, prayers of your hands against her body. It is hard, very hard, but when she truly believes you...&quot; Bast gestured excitedly. &quot;Suddenly the story she tells herself in her own head changes. She transforms. She isn't &lt;i&gt;seen as beautiful&lt;/i&gt;. She is &lt;i&gt;beautiful, seen&lt;/i&gt;.&quot;
&quot;What the hell is that supposed to mean?&quot; Chronicler snapped. &quot;You're just spouting nonsense now.&quot;
&quot;I'm spouting too much sense for you to understand,&quot; Bast said testily. &quot;But you're close enough to see my point." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169923-go-out-in-the-early-days-of-winter-after-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 23:48:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zack add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169923-go-out-in-the-early-days-of-winter-after-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Go out in the early days of winter, after the first cold snap of the season. Find a pool of water with a sheet of ice across the top, still fresh and new and clear as glass. Near the shore the ice will hold you. Slide out farther. Farther. Eventually you'll find the place where the surface just barely bears your weight. There you will feel what I felt. The ice splinters under your feet. Look down and you can see the white cracks darting through the ice like mad, elaborate spiderwebs. It is perfectly silent, but you can feel the sudden sharp vibrations through the bottoms of your feet.
That is what happened when Denna smiled at me." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
