<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/256417-kaivan-ashtiani]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/256417-kaivan-ashtiani" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 21:10:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 21:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaivan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes fate is like a small sandstorm that keeps changing directions. You change direction but the sandstorm chases you. You turn again, but the storm adjusts. Over and over you play this out, like some ominous dance with death just before dawn. Why? Because this storm isn't something that blew in from far away, something that has nothing to do with you. This storm is you. Something &lt;i&gt;inside&lt;/i&gt; of you. So all you can do is give in to it, step right inside the storm, closing your eyes and plugging up your ears so the sand doesn't get in, and walk through it, step by step. There's no sun there, no moon, no direction, no sense of time. Just fine white sand swirling up into the sky like pulverized bones. That's the kind of sandstorm you need to imagine.

An you really will have to make it through that violent, metaphysical, symbolic storm. No matter how metaphysical or symbolic it might be, make no mistake about it: it will cut through flesh like a thousand razor blades. People will bleed there, and &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; will bleed too. Hot, red blood. You'll catch that blood in your hands, your own blood and the blood of others.

And once the storm is over you won't remember how you made it through, how you managed to survive. You won't even be sure, in fact, whether the storm is really over. But one thing is certain. When you come out of the storm you won't be the same person who walked in. That's what this storm's all about." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8526-memories-warm-you-up-from-the-inside-but-they-also</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 21:10:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaivan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8526-memories-warm-you-up-from-the-inside-but-they-also]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Memories warm you up from the inside. But they also tear you apart." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1977-it-s-like-tolstoy-said-happiness-is-an-allegory-unhappiness-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 21:10:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaivan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1977-it-s-like-tolstoy-said-happiness-is-an-allegory-unhappiness-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's like Tolstoy said. Happiness is an allegory, unhappiness a &lt;i&gt;story&lt;/i&gt;." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322452-if-you-remember-me-then-i-don-t-care-if-everyone</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 21:11:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaivan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322452-if-you-remember-me-then-i-don-t-care-if-everyone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you remember me, then I don't care if everyone else forgets." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134645-lost-opportunities-lost-possibilities-feelings-we-can-never-get-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 21:11:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaivan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134645-lost-opportunities-lost-possibilities-feelings-we-can-never-get-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lost opportunities, lost possibilities, feelings we can never get back.  That's part of what it means to be alive.  But inside our heads - at least that's where I imagine it - there's a little room where we store those memories.  A room like the stacks in this library.  And to understand the workings of our own heart we have to keep on making new reference cards.  We have to dust things off every once in awhile, let in fresh air, change the water in the flower vases.  In other words, you'll live forever in your own private library." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1975-listen-up---there-s-no-war-that-will-end-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 21:11:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaivan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1975-listen-up---there-s-no-war-that-will-end-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen up - there's no war that will end all wars." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243805-silence-i-discover-is-something-you-can-actually-hear</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 21:11:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaivan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243805-silence-i-discover-is-something-you-can-actually-hear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Silence, I discover, is something you can actually hear." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78517-when-i-open-them-most-of-the-books-have-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 21:17:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaivan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78517-when-i-open-them-most-of-the-books-have-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I open them, most of the books have the smell of an earlier time leaking out between the pages - a special odor of the knowledge and emotions that for ages have been calmly resting between the covers. Breathing it in, I glance through a few pages before returning each book to its shelf." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231943-if-you-think-god-s-there-he-is-if-you-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 21:17:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaivan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231943-if-you-think-god-s-there-he-is-if-you-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you think God’s there, He is. If you don’t, He isn’t. And if that’s what God’s like, I wouldn’t worry about it." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230271-that-s-how-stories-happen-with-a-turning-point-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 21:19:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaivan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230271-that-s-how-stories-happen-with-a-turning-point-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That’s how stories happen — with a turning point, an unexpected twist. There’s only one kind of happiness, but misfortune comes in all shapes and sizes. It’s like Tolstoy said. Happiness is an allegory, unhappiness a story." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56136-hungry-man-reach-for-the-book-it-is-a-weapon</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2012 22:31:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaivan add a quote by Bertolt Brecht]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56136-hungry-man-reach-for-the-book-it-is-a-weapon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hungry man, reach for the book: it is a weapon." -- Bertolt Brecht]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25556-the-first-time-it-was-reported-that-our-friends-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2012 22:32:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaivan add a quote by Bertolt Brecht]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25556-the-first-time-it-was-reported-that-our-friends-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first time it was reported that our friends were being butchered there was a cry of horror. Then a hundred were butchered. But when a thousand were butchered and there was no end to the butchery, a blanket of silence spread. 
When evil-doing comes like falling rain, nobody calls out &quot;stop!&quot;

When crimes begin to pile up they become invisible. When sufferings become unendurable the cries are no longer heard. The cries, too, fall like rain in summer." -- Bertolt Brecht]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541442-the-worst-illiterate-is-the-political-illiterate-he-doesn-t-hear</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2012 22:34:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaivan add a quote by Bertolt Brecht]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541442-the-worst-illiterate-is-the-political-illiterate-he-doesn-t-hear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worst illiterate is the political illiterate, he doesn’t hear, doesn’t speak, nor participates in the political events. He doesn’t know the cost of life, the price of the bean, of the fish, of the flour, of the rent, of the shoes and of the medicine, all depends on political decisions. The political illiterate is so stupid that he is proud and swells his chest saying that he hates politics. The imbecile doesn’t know that, from his political ignorance is born the prostitute, the abandoned child, and the worst thieves of all, the bad politician, corrupted and flunky of the national and multinational companies." -- Bertolt Brecht]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110941-he-who-laughs-last-has-not-yet-heard-the-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 10:08:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaivan add a quote by Bertolt Brecht]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110941-he-who-laughs-last-has-not-yet-heard-the-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He who laughs last has not yet heard the bad news. " -- Bertolt Brecht]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224102-mom-says-each-of-us-has-a-veil-between-ourselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 21:28:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kaivan add a quote by Rebecca Stead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224102-mom-says-each-of-us-has-a-veil-between-ourselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mom says each of us has a veil between ourselves and the rest of the world, like a bride wears on her wedding day, except this kind of veil is invisible. We walk around happily with these invisible veils hanging down over our faces. The world is kind of blurry, and we like it that way. But sometimes our veils are pushed away for a few moments, like there's a wind blowing it from our faces. And when the veil lifts, we can see the world as it really is, just for those few seconds before it settles down again. We see all the beauty, and cruelty, and sadness, and love. But mostly we are happy not to. Some people learn to lift the veil themselves. Then they don't have to depend on the wind anymore." -- Rebecca Stead]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
