<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/256885-mahboube-mohammadi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/256885-mahboube-mohammadi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2009 10:25:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2009 10:25:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mahboube add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2009 10:25:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mahboube add a quote by Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened." -- Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87287</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2009 11:27:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mahboube add a quote by دکتر علی شریعتی]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87287]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["نامم را پدرم انتخاب کرد، نام خانوادگي ام را يکي از اجدادم! ديگر بس است! راهم را خودم انتخاب خواهم کرد." -- دکتر علی شریعتی]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102110</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2009 15:19:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mahboube add a quote by احمد شاملو]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102110]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["مرا 
تو 
بی سببی 
نيستی. 
به راستی
صلت کدام قصيده ای 
ای غزل؟ 
ستاره باران جواب کدام سلامی 
به آفتاب 
از دريچه ی تاريک؟

کلام از نگاه تو شکل می بندد.
خوشا نظر بازيا که تو آغازمی کنی!" -- احمد شاملو]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74247</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2009 11:27:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mahboube add a quote by Dr. Ali Shariati]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74247]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["اگر تنها ترین تنهاها شوم ، باز خدا هست ، او جانشین همه نداشتن هاست 
نفرین و آفرین ها بی ثمر است 
اگر تمامی خلق گرگهای هار شوند و از آسمان ، هول وکینه بر سرم بارد تو مهربان جاودان آسیب ناپذیر من هستی 
ای پناهگاه ابدی! تو می توانی جانشین همه بی پناهی ها شوی" -- Dr. Ali Shariati]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2102-love-does-not-consist-of-gazing-at-each-other-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 08:53:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mahboube add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2102-love-does-not-consist-of-gazing-at-each-other-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love does not consist of gazing at each other, but in looking outward together in the same direction." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46900-i-shall-look-at-you-out-of-the-corner-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 08:54:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mahboube add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46900-i-shall-look-at-you-out-of-the-corner-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I shall look at you out of the corner of my eye, and you will say nothing. Words are the source of misunderstandings.&quot; -from the Fox-" -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85614-people-have-forgotten-this-truth-the-fox-said-but-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 08:55:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mahboube add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85614-people-have-forgotten-this-truth-the-fox-said-but-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People have forgotten this truth,&quot; the fox said. &quot;But you mustn’t forget it. You become responsible forever for what you’ve tamed. You’re responsible for your rose." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109543-i-remembered-the-fox-one-runs-the-risk-of-crying</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 08:55:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mahboube add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109543-i-remembered-the-fox-one-runs-the-risk-of-crying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I remembered the fox. One runs the risk of crying a bit if one allows oneself to be tamed." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1816-you-may-say-i-m-a-dreamer-but-i-m-not-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2009 09:06:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mahboube add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1816-you-may-say-i-m-a-dreamer-but-i-m-not-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may say I'm a dreamer, but I'm not the only one. I hope someday you'll join us. And the world will live as one." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218420</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 09:19:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mahboube add a quote by قیصر امین پور]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218420]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["شهیدی که برخاک می‌خفت

سرانگشت در خون خود می‌زد و می‌نوشت

به امید پیروزی واقعی

نه در جنگ

که بر جنگ" -- قیصر امین پور]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231219-but-why-should-you-be-interested-in-me-good-question</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 13:08:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mahboube add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231219-but-why-should-you-be-interested-in-me-good-question]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But why should you be interested in me?&quot;
Good question. I can’t explain it myself right this moment. But maybe – just maybe – if we start getting together and talking, after a while something like Francis Lai’s soundtrack music will start playing in the background, and a whole slew of concrete reasons why I’m interested in you will line up out of nowhere. With luck, it might even snow for us." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2011 15:16:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mahboube add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
