<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/258477-allyson]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/258477-allyson" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2010 00:33:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32978-recognize-that-the-very-molecules-that-make-up-your-body</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2010 00:33:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Neil deGrasse Tyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32978-recognize-that-the-very-molecules-that-make-up-your-body]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Recognize that the very molecules that make up your body, the atoms that construct the molecules, are traceable to the crucibles that were once the centers of high mass stars that exploded their chemically rich guts into the galaxy, enriching pristine gas clouds with the chemistry of life.  So that we are all connected to each other biologically, to the earth chemically and to the rest of the universe atomically.  That’s kinda cool!  That makes me smile and I actually feel quite large at the end of that.  It’s not that we are better than the universe, we are part of the universe.  We are in the universe and the universe is in us." -- Neil deGrasse Tyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487601-finishing-a-book-is-bittersweet-you-spend-days-getting-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 22:57:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Whimsical Enlightenment]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487601-finishing-a-book-is-bittersweet-you-spend-days-getting-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finishing a book is bittersweet. You spend days getting to know the characters. Learning their nuances, their faults, their loves, their lives. They become your friends, acquaintances, enemies. And after the story ends, you miss them. You look for them in your own life, wonder where they’ve gone, you forget that they aren’t real. You fall in love with the hero and dream of him at night. The strange girl becomes your best friend. Their heartaches become your heartaches. You laugh when they laugh. And cry when they die. Eventually you realise they aren’t a part of your world, you were just briefly visiting theirs." -- Whimsical Enlightenment]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228647-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 23:10:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228647-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up. You build up all these defenses, you build up a whole suit of armor, so that nothing can hurt you, then one stupid person, no different from any other stupid person, wanders into your stupid life...You give them a piece of you. They didn't ask for it. They did something dumb one day, like kiss you or smile at you, and then your life isn't your own anymore. Love takes hostages. It gets inside you. It eats you out and leaves you crying in the darkness, so simple a phrase like 'maybe we should be just friends' turns into a glass splinter working its way into your heart. It hurts. Not just in the imagination. Not just in the mind. It's a soul-hurt, a real gets-inside-you-and-rips-you-apart pain. I hate love." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/532912-just-before-i-look-under-my-bed-i-always-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 11:57:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Graham Parke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/532912-just-before-i-look-under-my-bed-i-always-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just before I look under my bed, I always get a little cold feeling, as if part of me expects to find something staring back at me.

I've probably seen too many Hollywood movies to have any hopes of ever cultivating a healthy relationship with the underside of my bed." -- Graham Parke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40581-we-were-keeping-our-eye-on-1984-when-the-year</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 10:10:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Neil Postman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40581-we-were-keeping-our-eye-on-1984-when-the-year]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We were keeping our eye on 1984. When the year came and the prophecy didn't, thoughtful Americans sang softly in praise of themselves. The roots of liberal democracy had held. Wherever else the terror had happened, we, at least, had not been visited by [author:Orwellian|3706] nightmares.

But we had forgotten that alongside [author:Orwell|3706]'s dark vision, there was another - slightly older, slightly less well known, equally chilling: [author:Aldous Huxley|3487]'s Brave New World. Contrary to common belief even among the educated, [author:Huxley|3487] and [author:Orwell|3706] did not prophesy the same thing. [author:Orwell|3706] warns that we will be overcome by an externally imposed oppression. But in [author:Huxley|3487]'s vision, no Big Brother is required to deprive people of their autonomy, maturity and history. As he saw it, people will come to love their oppression, to adore the technologies that undo their capacities to think.

What [author:Orwell|3706] feared were those who would ban books. What [author:Huxley|3487] feared was that there would be no reason to ban a book, for there would be no one who wanted to read one. [author:Orwell|3706] feared those who would deprive us of information. [author:Huxley|3487] feared those who would give us so much that we would be reduced to passivity and egoism. [author:Orwell|3706] feared that the truth would be concealed from us. [author:Huxley|3487] feared the truth would be drowned in a sea of irrelevance. [author:Orwell|3706] feared we would become a captive culture. [author:Huxley|3487] feared we would become a trivial culture, preoccupied with some equivalent of the feelies, the orgy porgy, and the centrifugal bumblepuppy. As [author:Huxley|3487] remarked in Brave New World Revisited, the civil libertarians and rationalists who are ever on the alert to oppose tyranny &quot;&lt;i&gt;failed to take into account man's almost infinite appetite for distractions&lt;/i&gt;.&quot; In 1984, [author:Orwell|3706] added, people are controlled by inflicting pain. In Brave New World, they are controlled by inflicting pleasure. In short, [author:Orwell|3706] feared that what we fear will ruin us. [author:Huxley|3487] feared that what we desire will ruin us.

This book is about the possibility that [author:Huxley|3487], not [author:Orwell|3706], was right." -- Neil Postman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
