<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/259270-kathleen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/259270-kathleen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 21:21:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6051-if-ever-there-is-tomorrow-when-we-re-not-together-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 21:21:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6051-if-ever-there-is-tomorrow-when-we-re-not-together-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If ever there is tomorrow when we're not together... there is something you must always remember. You are braver than you believe, stronger than you seem, and smarter than you think. But the most important thing is, even if we're apart... I'll always be with you." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17521-it-s-so-hard-to-forget-pain-but-it-s-even-harder</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 21:22:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17521-it-s-so-hard-to-forget-pain-but-it-s-even-harder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's so hard to forget pain, but it's even harder to remember sweetness.  We have no scar to show for happiness. We learn so little from peace." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16831-we-all-die-the-goal-isn-t-to-live-forever-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 21:22:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16831-we-all-die-the-goal-isn-t-to-live-forever-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all die. The goal isn't to live forever, the goal is to create something that will." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22892-it-s-only-after-we-ve-lost-everything-that-we-re-free-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 21:22:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22892-it-s-only-after-we-ve-lost-everything-that-we-re-free-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's only after we've lost everything that we're free to do anything." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43717-nothing-of-me-is-original-i-am-the-combined-effort</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 21:23:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43717-nothing-of-me-is-original-i-am-the-combined-effort]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing of me is original. I am the combined effort of everyone I've ever known." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16072-the-unreal-is-more-powerful-than-the-real-because-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 21:24:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16072-the-unreal-is-more-powerful-than-the-real-because-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The unreal is more powerful than the real. Because nothing is as perfect as you can imagine it. Because its only intangible ideas, concepts, beliefs, fantasies that last. Stone crumbles. Wood rots. People, well, they die. But things as fragile as a thought, a dream, a legend, they can go on and on. If you can change the way people think. The way they see themselves. The way they see the world. You can change the way people live their lives. That's the only lasting thing you can create." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43711-most-times-it-s-just-a-lot-easier-not-to-let</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 15:18:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43711-most-times-it-s-just-a-lot-easier-not-to-let]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most times, it's just a lot easier not to let the world know what's wrong." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45462-there-are-only-patterns-patterns-on-top-of-patterns-patterns</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 15:19:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45462-there-are-only-patterns-patterns-on-top-of-patterns-patterns]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are only patterns, patterns on top of patterns, patterns that affect other patterns. Patterns hidden by patterns. Patterns within patterns. 
If you watch close, history does nothing but repeat itself. 
What we call chaos is just patterns we haven't recognized. What we call random is just patterns we can't decipher. what we can't understand we call nonsense. What we can't read we call gibberish.
There is no free will. 
There are no variables." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2070-only-after-disaster-can-we-be-resurrected-it-s-only-after</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 15:19:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2070-only-after-disaster-can-we-be-resurrected-it-s-only-after]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only after disaster can we be resurrected. It's only after you've lost everything that you're free to do anything. Nothing is static, everything is evolving, everything is falling apart." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103606-ladies-and-gentlemen-of-the-class-of-97-wear-sunscreen</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 19:55:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Mary Schmich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103606-ladies-and-gentlemen-of-the-class-of-97-wear-sunscreen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ladies and gentlemen of the class of '97:

Wear sunscreen.

If I could offer you only one tip for the future, sunscreen would be it. The long-term benefits of sunscreen have been proved by scientists, whereas the rest of my advice has no basis more reliable than my own meandering experience. I will dispense this advice now.

Enjoy the power and beauty of your youth. Oh, never mind. You will not understand the power and beauty of your youth until they've faded. But trust me, in 20 years, you'll look back at photos of yourself and recall in a way you can't grasp now how much possibility lay before you and how fabulous you really looked. You are not as fat as you imagine.

Don't worry about the future. Or worry, but know that worrying is as effective as trying to solve an algebra equation by chewing bubble gum. The real troubles in your life are apt to be things that never crossed your worried mind, the kind that blindside you at 4 p.m. on some idle Tuesday." -- Mary Schmich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:09:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't interest me what you do for a living. I want to know what you ache for, and if you dare to dream of meeting your heart's longing.
It doesn't interest me how old you are. I want to know if you will risk looking like a fool for love, for your dream, for the adventure of being alive. 
It doesn't interest me what planets are squaring your moon. I want to know if you have touched the center of your own sorrow, if you have been opened by life's betrayals or have become shriveled and closed from fear of further pain!I want to know if you can sit with pain, mine or your own, without moving to hide it or fade it, or fix it. 
I want to know if you can be with joy, mine or your own, if you can dance with wildness and let the ecstasy fill you to the tips of your fingers and toes without cautioning us to be careful, to be realistic, to remember the limitations of being human. 
It doesn't interest me if the story you are telling me is true. I want to know if you can disappoint another to be true to yourself; if you can bear the accusation of betrayal and not betray your own soul; if you can be faithlessand therefore trustworthy. 
I want to know if you can see beauty even when it's not pretty, every day,and if you can source your own life from its presence. 
I want to know if you can live with failure, yours and mine, and still stand on the edge of the lake and shout to the silver of the full moon, “Yes!”
It doesn't interest me to know where you live or how much money you have. I want to know if you can get up, after the night of grief and despair, weary and bruised to the bone, and do what needs to be done to feed the children. 
It doesn't interest me who you know or how you came to be here. I want to know if you will stand in the center of the fire with me and not shrink back. 
It doesn't interest me where or what or with whom you have studied. I want to know what sustains you, from the inside, when all else falls away. 
I want to know if you can be alone with yourself and if you truly like the company you keep in the empty moments." -- Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/457-what-matters-in-life-is-not-what-happens-to-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:13:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Gabriel Garcia Marquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/457-what-matters-in-life-is-not-what-happens-to-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What matters in life is not what happens to you but what you remember and how you remember it." -- Gabriel Garcia Marquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23281-kids-don-t-remember-what-you-try-to-teach-them-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:13:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Jim Henson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23281-kids-don-t-remember-what-you-try-to-teach-them-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Kids] don't remember what you try to teach them.  They remember what you are." -- Jim Henson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6525-living-is-like-tearing-through-a-museum-not-until-later</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:15:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6525-living-is-like-tearing-through-a-museum-not-until-later]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Living is like tearing through a museum. Not until later do you really start absorbing what you saw, thinking about it, looking it up in a book, and remembering - because you can't take it in all at once." -- Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48648-once-upon-a-midnight-dreary-while-i-pondered-weak-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:21:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48648-once-upon-a-midnight-dreary-while-i-pondered-weak-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a midnight dreary, while I pondered, weak and weary,
Over many a quaint and curious volume of forgotten lore,
While I nodded, nearly napping, suddenly there came a tapping,
As of some one gently rapping, rapping at my chamber door.
Tis some visitor,&quot; I muttered, &quot;tapping at my chamber door —
      Only this, and nothing more.&quot;

Ah, distinctly I remember it was in the bleak December,
And each separate dying ember wrought its ghost upon the floor.
Eagerly I wished the morrow; — vainly I had sought to borrow
From my books surcease of sorrow — sorrow for the lost Lenore —
For the rare and radiant maiden whom the angels name Lenore —
      Nameless here for evermore.

And the silken sad uncertain rustling of each purple curtain
Thrilled me — filled me with fantastic terrors never felt before;
So that now, to still the beating of my heart, I stood repeating,
Tis some visitor entreating entrance at my chamber door —
Some late visitor entreating entrance at my chamber door; —
    This it is, and nothing more.&quot;

Presently my soul grew stronger; hesitating then no longer,
Sir,&quot; said I, &quot;or Madam, truly your forgiveness I implore;
But the fact is I was napping, and so gently you came rapping,
And so faintly you came tapping, tapping at my chamber door,
That I scarce was sure I heard you&quot;— here I opened wide the door; —
    Darkness there, and nothing more.

Deep into that darkness peering, long I stood there wondering, fearing,
Doubting, dreaming dreams no mortals ever dared to dream before;
But the silence was unbroken, and the stillness gave no token,
And the only word there spoken was the whispered word, &quot;Lenore?&quot;
This I whispered, and an echo murmured back the word, &quot;Lenore!&quot; —
      Merely this, and nothing more.

Back into the chamber turning, all my soul within me burning,
Soon again I heard a tapping somewhat louder than before.
Surely,&quot; said I, &quot;surely that is something at my window lattice:
Let me see, then, what thereat is, and this mystery explore —
Let my heart be still a moment and this mystery explore; —
    'Tis the wind and nothing more.&quot;

Open here I flung the shutter, when, with many a flirt and flutter,
In there stepped a stately raven of the saintly days of yore;
Not the least obeisance made he; not a minute stopped or stayed he;
But, with mien of lord or lady, perched above my chamber door —
Perched upon a bust of Pallas just above my chamber door —
    Perched, and sat, and nothing more.

Then this ebony bird beguiling my sad fancy into smiling,
By the grave and stern decorum of the countenance it wore.
Though thy crest be shorn and shaven, thou,&quot; I said, &quot;art sure no craven,
Ghastly grim and ancient raven wandering from the Nightly shore —
Tell me what thy lordly name is on the Night's Plutonian shore!&quot;
      Quoth the Raven, &quot;Nevermore.&quot;

Much I marveled this ungainly fowl to hear discourse so plainly,
Though its answer little meaning— little relevancy bore;
For we cannot help agreeing that no living human being
Ever yet was blest with seeing bird above his chamber door —
Bird or beast upon the sculptured bust above his chamber door,
      With such name as &quot;Nevermore." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21262-tell-me-and-i-forget-teach-me-and-i-may</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:21:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21262-tell-me-and-i-forget-teach-me-and-i-may]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tell me and I forget, teach me and I may remember, involve me and I learn." -- Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:25:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes fate is like a small sandstorm that keeps changing directions. You change direction but the sandstorm chases you. You turn again, but the storm adjusts. Over and over you play this out, like some ominous dance with death just before dawn. Why? Because this storm isn't something that blew in from far away, something that has nothing to do with you. This storm is you. Something &lt;i&gt;inside&lt;/i&gt; of you. So all you can do is give in to it, step right inside the storm, closing your eyes and plugging up your ears so the sand doesn't get in, and walk through it, step by step. There's no sun there, no moon, no direction, no sense of time. Just fine white sand swirling up into the sky like pulverized bones. That's the kind of sandstorm you need to imagine.

An you really will have to make it through that violent, metaphysical, symbolic storm. No matter how metaphysical or symbolic it might be, make no mistake about it: it will cut through flesh like a thousand razor blades. People will bleed there, and &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; will bleed too. Hot, red blood. You'll catch that blood in your hands, your own blood and the blood of others.

And once the storm is over you won't remember how you made it through, how you managed to survive. You won't even be sure, in fact, whether the storm is really over. But one thing is certain. When you come out of the storm you won't be the same person who walked in. That's what this storm's all about." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83175-all-grown-ups-were-once-children-but-only-few-of-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:29:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83175-all-grown-ups-were-once-children-but-only-few-of-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All grown-ups were once children... but only few of them remember it." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94878-you-ll-get-mixed-up-of-course-as-you-already-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:29:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94878-you-ll-get-mixed-up-of-course-as-you-already-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You'll get mixed up, of course, as you already know. You'll get mixed up with many strange birds as you go. So be sure when you step. Step with care and great tact and remember that Life's a Great Balancing Act. Just never forget to be dexterous and deft. And never mix up your right foot with your left." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12021-when-two-people-meet-and-fall-in-love-there-s-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:29:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12021-when-two-people-meet-and-fall-in-love-there-s-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When two people meet and fall in love, there's a sudden rush of magic. Magic is just naturally present then. We tend to feed on that gratuitous magic without striving to make any more. One day we wake up and find that the magic is gone. We hustle to get it back, but by then it's usually too late, we've used it up. What we have to do is work like hell at making additional magic right from the start. It's hard work, but if we can remember to do it, we greatly improve our chances of making love stay." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33387-remember-if-you-ever-need-a-helping-hand-it-s-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:30:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Sam Levenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33387-remember-if-you-ever-need-a-helping-hand-it-s-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember, if you ever need a helping hand, it's at the end of your arm, as you get older, remember you have another hand: The first is to help yourself, the second is to help others." -- Sam Levenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133449-i-didn-t-want-to-see-her-because-it-would-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:38:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133449-i-didn-t-want-to-see-her-because-it-would-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I didn't want to see her because it would make me feel better. I came because without her, it's hard to remember who I am..." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37953-i-cannot-remember-the-books-i-ve-read-any-more-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:38:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Emerson, Ralph Waldo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37953-i-cannot-remember-the-books-i-ve-read-any-more-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot remember the books I've read any more than the meals I have eaten; even so, they have made me." -- Emerson, Ralph Waldo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3390-holding-hands-for-example-is-a-way-to-remember-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:41:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3390-holding-hands-for-example-is-a-way-to-remember-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Holding hands, for example, is a way to remember how it feels to say nothing together." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20601-when-we-die-we-will-turn-into-songs-and-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:50:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Rob Sheffield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20601-when-we-die-we-will-turn-into-songs-and-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we die, we will turn into songs, and we will hear each other and remember each other." -- Rob Sheffield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/780-some-of-you-say-joy-is-greater-than-sorrow-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:50:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/780-some-of-you-say-joy-is-greater-than-sorrow-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some of you say, “Joy is greater than sorrow,” and others say, “Nay, sorrow is the greater.”
But I say unto you, they are inseparable.
Together they come, and when one sits alone with you at your board, remember that the other is asleep upon your bed." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55006-if-i-had-a-camera-i-said-i-d-take-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:51:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55006-if-i-had-a-camera-i-said-i-d-take-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I had a camera,' I said, 'I'd take a picture of you every day. That way I'd remember how you looked every single day of your life." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4740-memory-believes-before-knowing-remembers-believes-longer-than-recollects-longer</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:51:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4740-memory-believes-before-knowing-remembers-believes-longer-than-recollects-longer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Memory believes before knowing remembers. Believes longer than recollects, longer than knowing even wonders." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218377-promise-me-you-ll-always-remember-you-re-braver-than-you-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:52:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218377-promise-me-you-ll-always-remember-you-re-braver-than-you-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Promise me you'll always remember: You're braver than you believe, and stronger than you seem, and smarter than you think." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74835-you-must-remember-family-is-often-born-of-blood-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 20:52:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Trenton Lee Stewart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74835-you-must-remember-family-is-often-born-of-blood-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must remember, family is often born of blood, but it doesn't depend on blood. Nor is it exclusive of friendship. Family members can be your best friends, you know. And best friends, whether or not they are related to you, can be your family." -- Trenton Lee Stewart]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
