<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/25964-aster]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/25964-aster" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 05:48:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27147-you-never-have-to-change-anything-you-got-up-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 05:48:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aster add a quote by Saul Bellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27147-you-never-have-to-change-anything-you-got-up-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You never have to change anything you got up in the middle of the night to write." -- Saul Bellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/461086-we-live-and-breathe-words-it-was-books-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 06:46:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aster add a quote by Cassandra Clare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/461086-we-live-and-breathe-words-it-was-books-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We live and breathe words. .... It was books that made me feel that perhaps I was not completely alone. They could be honest with me, and I with them. Reading your words, what you wrote, how you were lonely sometimes and afraid, but always brave; the way you saw the world, its colors and textures and sounds, I felt--I felt the way you thought, hoped, felt, dreamt. I felt I was dreaming and thinking and feeling &lt;i&gt;with&lt;/i&gt; you. I dreamed what you dreamed, wanted what you wanted--and then I realized that truly I just wanted you." -- Cassandra Clare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27047-let-me-live-love-and-say-it-well-in-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 06:54:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aster add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27047-let-me-live-love-and-say-it-well-in-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["let me live, love, and say it well in good sentences" -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/506145-make-up-a-story-for-our-sake-and-yours-forget</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 06:59:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aster add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/506145-make-up-a-story-for-our-sake-and-yours-forget]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Make up a story... For our sake and yours forget your name in the street; tell us what the world has been to you in the dark places and in the light. Don't tell us what to believe, what to fear. Show us belief's wide skirt and the stitch that unravels fear's caul." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26108-if-you-do-not-breathe-through-writing-if-you-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 06:59:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aster add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26108-if-you-do-not-breathe-through-writing-if-you-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you do not breathe through writing, if you do not cry out in writing, or sing in writing, then don't write, because our culture has no use for it." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/400854-i-loved-her-against-reason-against-promise-against-peace-against</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 07:36:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aster add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/400854-i-loved-her-against-reason-against-promise-against-peace-against]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I loved her against reason, against promise, against peace, against hope, against happiness, against all discouragement that could be." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182796-out-of-my-thoughts-you-are-part-of-my-existence</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 07:38:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aster add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182796-out-of-my-thoughts-you-are-part-of-my-existence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Out of my thoughts! You are part of my existence, part of myself. You have been in every line I have ever read, since I first came here, the rough common boy whose poor heart you wounded even then. You have been in every prospect I have ever seen since – on the river, on the sails of the ships, on the marshes, in the clouds, in the light, in the darkness, in the wind, in the woods, in the sea, in the streets. You have been the embodiment of every graceful fancy that my mind has ever become acquainted with. The stones of which the strongest London buildings are made, are not more real, or more impossible to displace with your hands, than your presence and influence have been to me, there and everywhere, and will be. Estella, to the last hour of my life, you cannot choose but remain part of my character, part of the little good in me, part of the evil. But, in this separation I associate you only with the good, and I will faithfully hold you to that always, for you must have done me far more good than harm, let me feel now what sharp distress I may. O God bless you, God forgive you!" -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
