<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/262542-mo]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/262542-mo" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 17:12:31 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94068-the-fact-that-certain-members-of-the-oppressor-class-join</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 17:12:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Paulo Freire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94068-the-fact-that-certain-members-of-the-oppressor-class-join]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...the fact that certain members of the oppressor class join the oppressed in their struggle for liberation, thus moving from one pole of the contradiction to the other... Theirs is a fundamental role, and has been throughout the history of this struggle. It happens, however, that as they cease to be exploiters or indifferent spectators or simply the heirs of exploitation and move to the side of the exploited, they almost always bring with them the marks of their origin: their prejudices and their deformations, which include a lack of confidence in the people's ability to think, to want, and to know.  Accordingly, these adherents to the people's cause constantly run the risk of falling into a type of generosity as malefic as that of the oppressors. The generosity of the oppressors is nourished by an unjust order, which must be maintained in order to justify that generosity. Our converts, on the other hand, truly desire to transform the unjust order; but because of their background they believe that they must be the executors of the transformation. They talk about the people, but they do not trust them; and trusting the people is the indispensable precondition for revolutionary change. A real humanist can be identified more by his trust in the people, which engages him in their struggle, than by a thousand actions in their favor without that trust." -- Paulo Freire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20686-the-oppressors-do-not-favor-promoting-the-community-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 17:20:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Paulo Freire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20686-the-oppressors-do-not-favor-promoting-the-community-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The oppressors do not favor promoting the community as a whole, but rather selected leaders." -- Paulo Freire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328134-socialism-never-took-root-in-america-because-the-poor-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2011 21:13:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328134-socialism-never-took-root-in-america-because-the-poor-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Socialism never took root in America because the poor see themselves not as an exploited proletariat but as temporarily embarrassed millionaires." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/929-whatever-you-can-do-or-dream-you-can-begin-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 12:49:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Johann Wolfgang von Goethe ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/929-whatever-you-can-do-or-dream-you-can-begin-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever you can do or dream you can, begin it. Boldness has genius, power and magic in it!" -- Johann Wolfgang von Goethe ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361858-he-s-not-perfect-you-aren-t-either-and-the-two-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 13:43:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361858-he-s-not-perfect-you-aren-t-either-and-the-two-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He’s not perfect. You aren’t either, and the two of you will never be perfect. But if he can make you laugh at least once, causes you to think twice, and if he admits to being human and making mistakes, hold onto him and give him the most you can. He isn’t going to quote poetry, he’s not thinking about you every moment, but he will give you a part of him that he knows you could break. Don’t hurt him, don’t change him, and don’t expect for more than he can give. Don’t analyze. Smile when he makes you happy, yell when he makes you mad, and miss him when he’s not there. Love hard when there is love to be had. Because perfect guys don’t exist, but there’s always one guy that is perfect for you." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/529962-whether-or-not-they-exist-we-are-slaves-to-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 05:52:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/529962-whether-or-not-they-exist-we-are-slaves-to-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whether or not they exist we are slaves to  our gods." -- Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335571-once-you-learn-to-read-you-will-be-forever-free</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 11:26:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Frederick Douglass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335571-once-you-learn-to-read-you-will-be-forever-free]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once you learn to read, you will be forever free." -- Frederick Douglass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45989-let-me-give-you-a-word-of-the-philosophy-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 11:27:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Frederick Douglass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45989-let-me-give-you-a-word-of-the-philosophy-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me give you a word of the philosophy of reform. The whole history of the progress of human liberty shows that all concessions yet made to her august claims, have been born of earnest struggle. The conflict has been exciting, agitating, all-absorbing, and for the time being, putting all other tumults to silence. It must do this or it does nothing. If there is no struggle there is no progress. Those who profess to favor freedom and yet depreciate agitation, are men who want crops without plowing up the ground, they want rain without thunder and lightening. They want the ocean without the awful roar of its many waters.&quot; 
  
&quot;This struggle may be a moral one, or it may be a physical one, and it may be both moral and physical, but it must be a struggle. Power concedes nothing without a demand. It never did and it never will. Find out just what any people will quietly submit to and you have found out the exact measure of injustice and wrong which will be imposed upon them, and these will continue till they are resisted with either words or blows, or with both. The limits of tyrants are prescribed by the endurance of those whom they oppress. In the light of these ideas, Negroes will be hunted at the North, and held and flogged at the South so long as they submit to those devilish outrages, and make no resistance, either moral or physical. Men may not get all they pay for in this world; but they must certainly pay for all they get. If we ever get free from the oppressions and wrongs heaped upon us, we must pay for their removal. We must do this by labor, by suffering, by sacrifice, and if needs be, by our lives and the lives of others." -- Frederick Douglass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145749-to-hell-with-luck-i-ll-bring-the-luck-with-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 09:54:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by The Old Man and the Sea,  Ernest Hemingway. ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145749-to-hell-with-luck-i-ll-bring-the-luck-with-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To hell with luck. I'll bring the luck with me." -- The Old Man and the Sea,  Ernest Hemingway. ]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
