<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/263150-tracy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/263150-tracy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 May 2012 16:38:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185805-because-nerds-like-us-are-allowed-to-be-unironically-enthusiastic</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2012 16:38:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185805-because-nerds-like-us-are-allowed-to-be-unironically-enthusiastic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…because nerds like us are allowed to be unironically enthusiastic about stuff… Nerds are allowed to love stuff, like jump-up-and-down-in-the-chair-can’t-control-yourself love it. Hank, when people call people nerds, mostly what they’re saying is ‘you like stuff.’ Which is just not a good insult at all. Like, ‘you are too enthusiastic about the miracle of human consciousness’." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492120-as-a-quick-aside-let-me-observe-that-in-moments</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 17:11:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Amor Towles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492120-as-a-quick-aside-let-me-observe-that-in-moments]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As a quick aside, let me observe that in moments of high emotion....if the next thing you're going to say makes you feel better, then it's probably the wrong thing to say. This is one of the finer maxims that I've discovered in life. And you can have it, since it's been of no use to me." -- Amor Towles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36554-the-secret-to-getting-ahead-is-getting-started</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 17:11:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36554-the-secret-to-getting-ahead-is-getting-started]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The secret to getting ahead is getting started." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371653-first-lord-no-tattoos-may-neither-chinese-symbol-for-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 19:41:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371653-first-lord-no-tattoos-may-neither-chinese-symbol-for-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First, Lord: No tattoos. May neither Chinese symbol for truth nor Winnie-the-Pooh holding the FSU logo stain her tender haunches.

May she be Beautiful but not Damaged, for it’s the Damage that draws the creepy soccer coach’s eye, not the Beauty.

When the Crystal Meth is offered, May she remember the parents who cut her grapes in half And stick with Beer.

Guide her, protect her

When crossing the street, stepping onto boats, swimming in the ocean, swimming in pools, walking near pools, standing on the subway platform, crossing 86th Street, stepping off of boats, using mall restrooms, getting on and off escalators, driving on country roads while arguing, leaning on large windows, walking in parking lots, riding Ferris wheels, roller-coasters, log flumes, or anything called “Hell Drop,” “Tower of Torture,” or “The Death Spiral Rock ‘N Zero G Roll featuring Aerosmith,” and standing on any kind of balcony ever, anywhere, at any age.

Lead her away from Acting but not all the way to Finance. Something where she can make her own hours but still feel intellectually fulfilled and get outside sometimes And not have to wear high heels.

What would that be, Lord? Architecture? Midwifery? Golf course design? I’m asking You, because if I knew, I’d be doing it, Youdammit.

May she play the Drums to the fiery rhythm of her Own Heart with the sinewy strength of her Own Arms, so she need Not Lie With Drummers.

Grant her a Rough Patch from twelve to seventeen. Let her draw horses and be interested in Barbies for much too long, For childhood is short – a Tiger Flower blooming Magenta for one day – And adulthood is long and dry-humping in cars will wait.

O Lord, break the Internet forever, That she may be spared the misspelled invective of her peers And the online marketing campaign for Rape Hostel V: Girls Just Wanna Get Stabbed.

And when she one day turns on me and calls me a Bitch in front of Hollister, Give me the strength, Lord, to yank her directly into a cab in front of her friends, For I will not have that Shit. I will not have it.

And should she choose to be a Mother one day, be my eyes, Lord, that I may see her, lying on a blanket on the floor at 4:50 A.M., all-at-once exhausted, bored, and in love with the little creature whose poop is leaking up its back.

“My mother did this for me once,” she will realize as she cleans feces off her baby’s neck. “My mother did this for me.” And the delayed gratitude will wash over her as it does each generation and she will make a Mental Note to call me. And she will forget. But I’ll know, because I peeped it with Your God eyes." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372991-don-t-waste-your-energy-trying-to-educate-or-change-opinions</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 19:41:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372991-don-t-waste-your-energy-trying-to-educate-or-change-opinions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don’t waste your energy trying to educate or change opinions; go over, under, through, and opinions will change organically when you’re the boss. Or they won’t. Who cares? Do your thing, and don’t care if they like it." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1-the-story-so-far-in-the-beginning-the-universe-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 12:42:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1-the-story-so-far-in-the-beginning-the-universe-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The story so far:
In the beginning the Universe was created.
This has made a lot of people very angry and been widely regarded as a bad move." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/459853-there-will-come-a-time-when-all-of-us-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2012 16:38:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/459853-there-will-come-a-time-when-all-of-us-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There will come a time when all of us are dead.  All of us.  There will come a time when there are no human beings remaining to remember that anyone ever existed or that our species ever did anything.  There will be no one left to remember Aristotle or Cleopatra, let alone you.  Everything that we did and built and wrote and thought and discovered will be forgotten and all of this will have been for naught.  Maybe that time is coming soon and maybe it is millions of years away, but even if we survive the collapse of our sun, we will not survive forever.  There was time before organisms experienced consciousness, and there will be time after.  And if the inevitability of human oblivion worries you, I encourage you to ignore it.  God knows that’s what everyone else does." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234429-adult-librarians-are-like-lazy-bakers-their-patrons-want-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2012 21:09:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234429-adult-librarians-are-like-lazy-bakers-their-patrons-want-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Adult librarians are like lazy bakers: their patrons want a jelly doughnut, so they give them a jelly doughnut. Children’s librarians are ambitious bakers: 'You like the jelly doughnut? I’ll get you a jelly doughnut. But you should try my cruller, too. My cruller is gonna blow your mind, kid." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124077-you-are-pure-hearted-branza-and-lovely-and-you-have-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2012 17:43:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Margo Lanagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124077-you-are-pure-hearted-branza-and-lovely-and-you-have-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are pure-hearted, Branza, and lovely, and you have never done a moment's wrong.  But you are a living creature, born to make a real life, however it cracks your heart.  However sweet that other place was, it was not real.  It was an artifact of your mam's imagination; it was a dream of hers and a desire; you could not have stayed there forever and called yourself alive.  Now you are in the true world, and a great deal more is required of you.  Here you must befriend real wolves, and lure real birds down from the sky.  Here you must endure real people around you, and we are not uniformly kind; we are damaged and impulsive, each in our own way.  It is harder.  It is not safe.  But it is what you were born to. (357)" -- Margo Lanagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283964-anyone-who-never-met-a-man-he-didn-t-like-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2012 18:19:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Michael Zadoorian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283964-anyone-who-never-met-a-man-he-didn-t-like-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who never met a man he didn't like just isn't trying hard enough." -- Michael Zadoorian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282996-you-spend-your-life-so-worried-about-what-others-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2012 18:19:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Michael Zadoorian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282996-you-spend-your-life-so-worried-about-what-others-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You spend your life so worried about what others think, when in reality, people mostly don't think. On the few occasions when they do, true, it is often something bad, but one has to at least admire the fact that they're thinking at all." -- Michael Zadoorian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/594379-no-no-it-s-not-all-random-if-it-really-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 17:12:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by R.J. Palacio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/594379-no-no-it-s-not-all-random-if-it-really-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["no, no, it's not all random, if it really was all random, the universe would abandon us completely. and the universe doesn't. it takes care of its most fragile creations in ways we can't see. like with parents who adore you blindly. and a big sister who feels guilty for being human over you. and a little gravelly-voiced kid whose friends have left him over you. and even a pink-haired girl who carries your picture in her wallet. maybe it is a lottery, but the universe makes it all even out in the end. the universe takes care of all its birds." -- R.J. Palacio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/544416-august-pullman-s-precept-everyone-in-the-world-should-get-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 17:13:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by R.J. Palacio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/544416-august-pullman-s-precept-everyone-in-the-world-should-get-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["AUGUST PULLMAN'S PRECEPT
Everyone in the world should get a standing ovation at least once in their life because we all overcometh the world. - Auggie" -- R.J. Palacio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10317-francois-rabelais-he-was-a-poet-and-his-last-words</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 17:16:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10317-francois-rabelais-he-was-a-poet-and-his-last-words]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Francois Rabelais. He was a poet. And his last words were &quot;I go to seek a Great Perhaps.&quot; That's why I'm going. So I don't have to wait until I die to start seeking a Great Perhaps." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244724-maybe-our-favorite-quotations-say-more-about-us-than-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 17:17:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244724-maybe-our-favorite-quotations-say-more-about-us-than-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe our favorite quotations say more about us than about the stories and people we're quoting." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57214-saying-i-notice-you-re-a-nerd-is-like-saying-hey</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 06:36:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57214-saying-i-notice-you-re-a-nerd-is-like-saying-hey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Saying 'I notice you're a nerd' is like saying, 'Hey, I notice that you'd rather be intelligent than be stupid, that you'd rather be thoughtful than be vapid, that you believe that there are things that matter more than the arrest record of Lindsay Lohan. Why is that?' In fact, it seems to me that most contemporary insults are pretty lame. Even 'lame' is kind of lame. Saying 'You're lame' is like saying 'You walk with a limp.' Yeah, whatever, so does 50 Cent, and he's done all right for himself." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171327-it-was-one-of-those-humid-days-when-the-atmosphere</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 08:36:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171327-it-was-one-of-those-humid-days-when-the-atmosphere]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was one of those humid days when the atmosphere gets confused. Sitting on the porch, you could feel it: the air wishing it was water." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1046427-and-looking-at-one-single-label-on-a-jar-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 08:33:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1046427-and-looking-at-one-single-label-on-a-jar-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And looking at one single label on a jar, he felt himself gone round the calendar to the private day this summer when he had looked at the circling world and found himself at its center.

The word on the jar was RELISH.

And he was glad that he had decided to live." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
