<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/264037-tra-kay]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/264037-tra-kay" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 16:21:22 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64411-i-think-that-in-all-descriptions-of-the-good-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 16:21:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64411-i-think-that-in-all-descriptions-of-the-good-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think that in all descriptions of the good life here on earth we must assume a certain basis of animal vitality and animal instinct; without this, life becomes tame and uninteresting. Civilization should be something added to this, not substituted for it; the ascetic saint and the detached sage fail in this respect to be complete human beings. A small number of them may enrich a community; but a world composed of them would die of boredom." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13099-now-in-their-love-which-was-stronger-there-were-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 16:21:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by T.H. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13099-now-in-their-love-which-was-stronger-there-were-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now, in their love, which was stronger, there were the seeds of hatred and fear and confusion growing at the same time: for love can exist with hatred, each preying on the other, and this is what gives it its greatest fury." -- T.H. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64412-a-drop-of-water-is-not-immortal-it-can-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 03:25:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64412-a-drop-of-water-is-not-immortal-it-can-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A drop of water is not immortal; it can be resolved into oxygen and hydrogen. If, therefore, a drop of water were to maintain that it had a quality of aqueousness which would survive its dissolution we should be inclined to be skeptical. In like manner we know that the brain is not immortal..." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39541-these-people-fail-to-realize-that-it-is-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 01:41:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39541-these-people-fail-to-realize-that-it-is-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These people fail to realize that it is on the inside that God must be defended, not on the outside. They should direct their anger at themselves. For evil in the open is but evil from within that has been let out. The main battlefield for good is not the open ground of the public arena but the small clearing of each heart." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95947-we-stepped-outside-rather-hurriedly-and-down-the-street-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 22:00:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Richard Brautigan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95947-we-stepped-outside-rather-hurriedly-and-down-the-street-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We stepped outside rather hurriedly and down the street to anonymous sanctuary among the buildings of San Francisco.
&quot;Promise me till your dying day, you'll believe that a Mellon was a Confederate general. It's the truth. That God-damn book lies! There was a Confederate general in my family!&quot;
&quot;I promise,&quot; I said and it was a promise that was kept." -- Richard Brautigan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93604-i-fell-asleep-reading-a-dull-book-and-i-dreamed</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 01:24:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Heinrich Heine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93604-i-fell-asleep-reading-a-dull-book-and-i-dreamed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I fell asleep reading a dull book, and I dreamed that I was reading on, so I awoke from sheer boredom. " -- Heinrich Heine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101538-nothing-any-man-can-do-will-improve-that-genius-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2008 01:28:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Aleister Crowley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101538-nothing-any-man-can-do-will-improve-that-genius-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing any man can do will improve that genius; but the genius needs his mind, and he can broaden that mind, fertilize it with knowledge of all kinds, improve its powers of expression; supply the genius, in short, with an orchestra instead of a tin whistle. All our little great men, our one-poem poets, our one-picture painters, have merely failed to perfect themselves as instruments. The Genius who wrote The Ancient Mariner is no less sublime than he who wrote The Tempest; but Coleridge had some incapacity to catch and express the thoughts of his genius - was ever such wooden stuff as his conscious work? - while Shakespeare had the knack of acquiring the knowledge necessary to the expression of every conceivable harmony, and his technique was sufficiently fluent to transcribe with ease." -- Aleister Crowley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103558-more-on-topic-the-best-group-of-japanese-speakers-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 23:17:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Khatz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103558-more-on-topic-the-best-group-of-japanese-speakers-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["More on topic, the best group of Japanese speakers on the planet, a group many call “the Japanese”, just happen to spend more time hearing and reading Japanese than any other group. But there’s nothing special about this group of people; when a Japanese person speaks Japanese to you, what she is demonstrating is nothing more than the result of dedication, albeit often unwitting dedication. Whether you are Japanese by default (born and raised in Japan) or by choice, it doesn’t matter, your path and your task are essentially the same: SHOW UP." -- Khatz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103559-if-there-are-prodigies-no-one-will-call-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 23:30:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Khatz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103559-if-there-are-prodigies-no-one-will-call-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[" If there are prodigies, no one will call us out for not trying because they’re not trying either, and because we have created a condition that can only be fulfilled by accident of birth, our excuse is airtight: we can go about being mediocre for the rest of our lives, blameless." -- Khatz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107906-to-be-pleasant-gentle-calm-and-self-possessed-this-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2008 20:35:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Murasaki Shikibu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107906-to-be-pleasant-gentle-calm-and-self-possessed-this-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["    To be pleasant, gentle, calm and self-possessed: this is the basis of good taste and charm in a woman. No matter how amorous or passionate you may be, as long as you are straightforward and refrain from causing others embarrassment, no one will mind. But women who are too vain and act pretentiously, to the extent that they make others feel uncomfortable, will themselves become the object of attention; and once that happens, people will find fault with whatever they say or do; whether it be how they enter a room, how they sit down, how they stand up or how they take their leave. Those who end up contradicting themselves and those who disparage their companions are also carefully watched and listened to all the more. As long as you are free from such faults, people will surely refrain from listening to tittle-tattle and will want to show you sympathy, if only for the sake of politeness.
    I am of the opinion that when you intentionally cause hurt to another, or indeed if you do ill through mere thoughtless behavior, you fully deserve to be censured in public. Some people are so good-natured that they can still care for those who despise them, but I myself find it very difficult. Did the Buddha himself in all his compassion ever preach that one should simply ignore those who slander the Three Treasures? How in this sullied world of ours can those who are hard done by be expected to reciprocate in kind?" -- Murasaki Shikibu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108123-the-woman-was-silent-her-eyes-on-the-floor-shimamura</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 16:19:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Yasunari Kawabata]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108123-the-woman-was-silent-her-eyes-on-the-floor-shimamura]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The woman was silent, her eyes on the floor. Shimamura had come to a point where he knew he was only parading his masculine shamelessness, and yet it seemed likely enough that the woman was familiar with the failing and need not be shocked by it. He looked at her. Perhaps it was the rich lashes of the downcast eyes that made her face seem warm and sensuous. She shook her head very slightly, and again a faint blush spread over her face." -- Yasunari Kawabata]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108184-but-even-more-than-her-diary-shimamura-was-surprised-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 17:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Yasunari Kawabata]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108184-but-even-more-than-her-diary-shimamura-was-surprised-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But even more than her diary, Shimamura was surprised at her statement that she had carefully cataloged every novel and short story she had read since she was fifteen or sixteen. The record already filled ten notebooks.
&quot;You write down your criticisms, do you?&quot;
&quot;I could never do anything like that. I just write down the author and the characters and how they are related to each other. That is about all.&quot;
&quot;But what good does it do?&quot;
&quot;None at all.&quot;
&quot;A waste of effort.&quot;
&quot;A complete waste of effort,&quot; she answered brightly, as though the admission meant little to her. She gazed solemnly at Shimamura, however.
A complete waste of effort. For some reason Shimamura wanted to stress the point. But, drawn to her at that moment, he felt a quiet like the voice of the rain flow over him. He knew well enough that for her it was in fact no waste of effort, but somehow the final determination that it was had the effect of distilling and purifying the woman's existence." -- Yasunari Kawabata]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108942-eighteen-thousand-miles-from-the-moon-is-some-slide-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2008 20:27:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Winsor McCay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108942-eighteen-thousand-miles-from-the-moon-is-some-slide-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eighteen thousand miles from the moon is some slide, but I'll get up there again some way!" -- Winsor McCay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109819-the-bond-between-husband-and-wife-is-a-strong-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 23:57:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Murasaki Shikibu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109819-the-bond-between-husband-and-wife-is-a-strong-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The bond between husband and wife is a strong one. Suppose the man had hunted her out and brought her back. The memory of her acts would still be there, and inevitably, sooner or later, it would be cause for rancor. When there are crises, incidents, a woman should try to overlook them, for better or for worse, and make the bond into something durable. The wounds will remain, with the woman and with the man, when there are crises such as I have described. It is very foolish for a woman to let a little dalliance upset her so much that she shows her resentment openly. He has his adventures--but if he has fond memories of their early days together, his and hers, she may be sure that she matters. A commotion means the end of everything. She should be quiet and generous, and when something comes up that quite properly arouses her resentment she should make it known by delicate hints. The man will feel guilty and with tactful guidance he will mend his ways. Too much lenience can make a woman seem charmingly docile and trusting, but it can also make her seem somewhat wanting in substance. We have had instances enough of boats abandoned to the winds and waves.
It may be difficult when someone you are especially fond of, someone beautiful and charming, has been guilty of an indiscretion, but magnanimity produces wonders. They may not always work, but generosity and reasonableness and patience do on the whole seem best." -- Murasaki Shikibu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110015-the-hanging-gate-of-something-like-trelliswork-was-propped-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 16:37:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Murasaki Shikibu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110015-the-hanging-gate-of-something-like-trelliswork-was-propped-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The hanging gate, of something like trelliswork, was propped on a pole, and he could see that the house was tiny and flimsy. He felt a little sorry for the occupants of such a place--and then asked himself who in this world had a temporary shelter.

[Anonymous, Kokinshuu 987:
Where in all this world shall I call home?
A temporary shelter is my home.]

A hut, a jeweled pavilion, they were the same. A pleasantly green vine was climbing a board wall. The white flowers, he said to himself, had a rather self-satisfied look about them.
'I needs must ask the lady far yonder,&quot; he said, as if to himself.

[Anonymous, Kokinshuu 1007:
I needs must ask the lady far yonder
What flower it is off there that blooms so white.]

An attendant came up, bowing deeply. &quot;The white flowers far off yonder are known as 'evening faces,&quot; he said. &quot;A very human sort of name--and what a shabby place they have picked to bloom in.&quot;
It was as the man said. The neighborhood was a poor one, chiefly of small houses. Some were leaning precariously, and there were &quot;evening faces&quot; at the sagging eaves.
A hapless sort of flower. Pick one off for me, will you?&quot;
The man went inside the raised gate and broke off a flower. A pretty little girl in long, unlined yellow trousers of raw silk came out through a sliding door that seemed too good for the surroundings. Beckoning to the man, she handed him a heavily scented white fan.
Put it on this. It isn't much of a fan, but then it isn't much of a flower either." -- Murasaki Shikibu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110651-well-i-thought-america-s-not-stingy-with-its-bombs</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 16:41:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Shizuko Go]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110651-well-i-thought-america-s-not-stingy-with-its-bombs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, I thought, America's not stingy with its bombs." -- Shizuko Go]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110668-i-was-surprised-to-find-authors-like-kaizan-nakazato-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 18:12:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Shizuko Go]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110668-i-was-surprised-to-find-authors-like-kaizan-nakazato-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was surprised to find authors like Kaizan Nakazato and Sanjugo Naoki in a corner of the bookcase where I've never noticed them before. I dip into a book, and if it's dull I go straight onto the next. I never used to do that--even if I was bored I'd plod on to the end. But, look, if I'm to die at any moment, there's no sense being in the middle of a boring book, is there?" -- Shizuko Go]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110669-these-days-even-plain-tea-has-become-a-treat-hasn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 18:15:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Shizuko Go]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110669-these-days-even-plain-tea-has-become-a-treat-hasn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These days, even plain tea has become a treat, hasn't it?" -- Shizuko Go]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110690-there-is-no-shame-in-impulse</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 22:14:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110690-there-is-no-shame-in-impulse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no shame in impulse." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112146-from-the-time-when-the-exercise-of-the-intellect-became</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2008 22:09:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Alexis de Tocqueville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112146-from-the-time-when-the-exercise-of-the-intellect-became]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From the time when the exercise of the intellect became a source of strength and of wealth, we see that every addition to science, every fresh truth, and every new idea became a germ of power placed within the reach of the people. Poetry, eloquence, and memory, the graces of the mind, the fire of imagination, depth of thought, and all the gifts which Heaven scatters at a venture turned to the advantage of democracy; and even when they were in the possession of its adversaries, they still served its cause by throwing into bold relief the natural greatness of man. Its conquests spread, therefore, with those of civilization and knowledge; and literature became an arsenal open to all, where the poor and the weak daily resorted for arms." -- Alexis de Tocqueville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112265-all-stories-teach-whether-the-storyteller-intends-them-to-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 13:06:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112265-all-stories-teach-whether-the-storyteller-intends-them-to-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All stories teach, whether the storyteller intends them to or not. They teach the world we create. They teach the morality we live by. They teach it much more effectively than moral precepts and instructions." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112266-stories-are-the-most-important-thing-in-the-world-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 13:07:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112266-stories-are-the-most-important-thing-in-the-world-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories are the most important thing in the world. Without stories, we wouldn't be human beings at all." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112267-make-this-the-golden-rule-the-equivalent-of-the-hippocratic</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 13:09:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112267-make-this-the-golden-rule-the-equivalent-of-the-hippocratic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Make this the golden rule, the equivalent of the Hippocratic oath: Everything we ask a child to do should be worth doing." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112270-i-m-for-open-mindedness-and-tolerance-i-m-against-any-form-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 13:23:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112270-i-m-for-open-mindedness-and-tolerance-i-m-against-any-form-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm for open-mindedness and tolerance. I'm against any form of fanaticism, fundamentalism or zealotry, and this certainty of 'We have the truth.' The truth is far too large and complex. Nobody has the truth." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10111-we-don-t-need-a-list-of-rights-and-wrongs-tables</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 13:25:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10111-we-don-t-need-a-list-of-rights-and-wrongs-tables]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don’t need a list of rights and wrongs, tables of dos and don’ts: we need books, time, and silence. &lt;I&gt;Thou shalt not&lt;/I&gt; is soon forgotten, but &lt;I&gt;Once upon a time&lt;/I&gt; lasts forever." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112393-the-road-was-frozen-the-village-lay-quiet-under-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 02:43:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Yasunari Kawabata]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112393-the-road-was-frozen-the-village-lay-quiet-under-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The road was frozen. The village lay quiet under the cold sky. Komako hitched up the skirt of her kimono and tucked it into her obi. The moon shone like a blade frozen in blue ice." -- Yasunari Kawabata]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120517-the-greatest-of-warriors-can-fight-on-behalf-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 14:36:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Barry Wolfenden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120517-the-greatest-of-warriors-can-fight-on-behalf-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greatest of warriors can fight on behalf of the most banal of countries; the most masterful of poets can have the plainest woman as their muse." -- Barry Wolfenden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143166-i-know-i-have-a-pretty-good-sense-for-music</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 17:33:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143166-i-know-i-have-a-pretty-good-sense-for-music]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know I have a pretty good sense for music, but she was better than me. I used to think it was such a waste! I thought, ‘If only she had started out with a good teacher and gotten the proper training, she’d be so much further along!’ But I was wrong about that. She was not the kind of child who could stand proper training. There just happen to be people like that. They’re blessed with this marvelous talent, but they can’t make the effort to systematize it. They end up squandering it in little bits and pieces. I’ve seen my share of people like that. At first you think they’re amazing. Like, they can sight-read some terrifically difficult piece and do a damn good job playing it all the way through. You see them do it, and you’re overwhelmed. you think, ‘I could never do that in a million years.’ But that’s as far as they go. They can’t take it any further. And why not? Because they won’t put in the effort. Because they haven’t had the discipline pounded into them. They’ve been spoiled. They have just enough talent so they’ve been able to play things well without any effort and they’ve had people telling them how great they are from the time they’re little, so hard work looks stupid to them. They’ll take some piece another kid has to work on for three weeks and polish it off in half the time, so the teacher figures they’ve put enough into it and lets them go to the next thing. And they do that in half the time and go on to the next piece. They never find out what it means to be hammered by the teacher; they lose out on a certain element required or character building. It’s a tragedy." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143216-and-well-mine-are-kind-of-on-the-heavy-side</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 20:20:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143216-and-well-mine-are-kind-of-on-the-heavy-side]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And, well, mine are kind of on the heavy side anyway. The first day or two, I don't want to do ANYTHING. Make sure you keep away from me then.'
I'd like to, but how can I tell?' I asked.
O.K., I'll wear a hat for a couple of days after my period starts. A red one. That should work,' she said with a laugh. 'If you see me on the street and I'm wearing a red hat, don't talk to me, just run away." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143231-i-go-to-a-bookstore-and-select-a-new-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2009 02:07:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tra-Kay add a quote by Ariel Dingus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143231-i-go-to-a-bookstore-and-select-a-new-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I go to a bookstore and select a new friend to screw around with for a few hours and then grope intermittently when the mood strikes...to abandon them is just...mean." -- Ariel Dingus]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
