<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/264033-kira]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/264033-kira" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 13:31:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111051-i-have-for-the-first-time-found-what-i-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 13:31:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kira add a quote by Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111051-i-have-for-the-first-time-found-what-i-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have for the first time found what I can truly love–I have found you. You are my sympathy–my better self–my good angel–I am bound to you with a strong attachment. I think you good, gifted, lovely: a fervent, a solemn passion is conceived in my heart; it leans to you, draws you to my centre and spring of life, wrap my existence about you–and, kindling in pure, powerful flame, fuses you and me in one." -- Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1-the-story-so-far-in-the-beginning-the-universe-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 15:06:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kira add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1-the-story-so-far-in-the-beginning-the-universe-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The story so far:
In the beginning the Universe was created.
This has made a lot of people very angry and been widely regarded as a bad move." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50677-who-has-never-killed-an-hour-not-casually-or-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 15:07:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kira add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50677-who-has-never-killed-an-hour-not-casually-or-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who has never killed an hour? Not casually or without thought, but carefully: a premeditated murder of minutes. The violence comes from a combination of giving up, not caring, and a resignation that getting past it is all you can hope to accomplish. So you kill the hour. You do not work, you do not read, you do not daydream. If you sleep it is not because you need to sleep. And when at last it is over, there is no evidence: no weapon, no blood, and no body. The only clue might be the shadows beneath your eyes or a terribly thin line near the corner of your mouth indicating something has been suffered, that in the privacy of your life you have lost something and the loss is too empty to share." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53166-the-best-fantasy-is-written-in-the-language-of-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 08:22:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kira add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53166-the-best-fantasy-is-written-in-the-language-of-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best fantasy is written in the language of dreams. It is alive as dreams are alive, more real than real ... for a moment at least ... that long magic moment before we wake.

     Fantasy is silver and scarlet, indigo and azure, obsidian veined with gold and lapis lazuli. Reality is plywood and plastic, done up in mud brown and olive drab. Fantasy tastes of habaneros and honey, cinnamon and cloves, rare red meat and wines as sweet as summer. Reality is beans and tofu, and ashes at the end. Reality is the strip malls of Burbank, the smokestacks of Cleveland, a parking garage in Newark. Fantasy is the towers of Minas Tirith, the ancient stones of Gormenghast, the halls of Camelot. Fantasy flies on the wings of Icarus, reality on Southwest Airlines. Why do our dreams become so much smaller when they finally come true?

     We read fantasy to find the colors again, I think. To taste strong spices and hear the songs the sirens sang. There is something old and true in fantasy that speaks to something deep within us, to the child who dreamt that one day he would hunt the forests of the night, and feast beneath the hollow hills, and find a love to last forever somewhere south of Oz and north of Shangri-La.

     They can keep their heaven. When I die, I'd sooner go to middle Earth." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1924-books-are-the-ultimate-dumpees-put-them-down-and-they-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2012 15:31:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kira add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1924-books-are-the-ultimate-dumpees-put-them-down-and-they-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are the ultimate Dumpees: put them down and they’ll wait for you forever; pay attention to them and they always love you back." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485711-my-thoughts-are-stars-i-cannot-fathom-into-constellations</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2012 15:34:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kira add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485711-my-thoughts-are-stars-i-cannot-fathom-into-constellations]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My thoughts are stars I cannot fathom into constellations." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/593452-there-s-a-right-thing-to-do-holden-said-you-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 08:16:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kira add a quote by James S.A. Corey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/593452-there-s-a-right-thing-to-do-holden-said-you-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's a right thing to do,&quot; Holden said.
&quot;You don't have a right thing, friend,&quot; Miller said. &quot;You've got a whole plateful of maybe a little less wrong." -- James S.A. Corey]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
