<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/264400-elizabeth]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/264400-elizabeth" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2012 11:30:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2229-to-be-hopeful-in-bad-times-is-not-just-foolishly</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2012 11:30:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2229-to-be-hopeful-in-bad-times-is-not-just-foolishly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["TO BE HOPEFUL in bad times is not just foolishly romantic. It is based on the fact that human history is a history not only of cruelty, but also of compassion, sacrifice, courage, kindness.
What we choose to emphasize in this complex history will determine our lives. If we see only the worst, it destroys our capacity to do something. If we remember those times and places—and there are so many—where people have behaved magnificently, this gives us the energy to act, and at least the possibility of sending this spinning top of a world in a different direction.
And if we do act, in however small a way, we don’t have to wait for some grand utopian future. The future is an infinite succession of presents, and to live now as we think human beings should live, in defiance of all that is bad around us, is itself a marvelous victory." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214717-we-don-t-have-to-engage-in-grand-heroic-actions-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2012 11:33:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214717-we-don-t-have-to-engage-in-grand-heroic-actions-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't have to engage in grand, heroic actions to participate in the process of change. Small acts, when multiplied by millions of people, can transform the world." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241462-there-are-no-faster-or-firmer-friendships-than-those-formed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 19:42:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Irving Stone]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241462-there-are-no-faster-or-firmer-friendships-than-those-formed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are no faster or firmer friendships than those formed between people who love the same books." -- Irving Stone]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140448-the-place-god-calls-you-to-is-the-place-where</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 13:55:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140448-the-place-god-calls-you-to-is-the-place-where]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The place God calls you to is the place where your deep gladness and the world’s deep hunger meet." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17916-i-m-worried-that-students-will-take-their-obedient-place-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 06:59:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17916-i-m-worried-that-students-will-take-their-obedient-place-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm worried that students will take their obedient place in society and look to become successful cogs in the wheel - let the wheel spin them around as it wants without taking a look at what they're doing. I'm concerned that students not become passive acceptors of the official doctrine that's handed down to them from the White House, the media, textbooks, teachers and preachers." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88590-the-challenge-remains-on-the-other-side-are-formidable-forces</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 07:03:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88590-the-challenge-remains-on-the-other-side-are-formidable-forces]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The challenge remains.  On the other side are formidable forces: money, political power, the major media.  On our side are the people of the world and a power greater than money or weapons: the truth.
Truth has a power of its own.  Art has a power of its own.  That age-old lesson – that everything we do matters – is the meaning of the people’s struggle here in the United States and everywhere.  A poem can inspire a movement.  A pamphlet can spark a revolution.  Civil disobedience can arouse people and provoke us to think, when we organize with one another, when we get involved, when we stand up and speak out together, we can create a power no government can suppress.  We live in a beautiful country.  But people who have no respect for human life, freedom, or justice have taken it over.  It is now up to all of us to take it back." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107221-the-cry-of-the-poor-is-is-not-always-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 07:04:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107221-the-cry-of-the-poor-is-is-not-always-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The cry of the poor is is not always just, but if you don't listen to it, you will never know what justice is." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
