<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/266227-jennifer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/266227-jennifer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 14:19:03 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7097-now-i-was-the-only-one-left-i-thought-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 14:19:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Perry Moore  (Hero)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7097-now-i-was-the-only-one-left-i-thought-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now I was the only one left.  I thought about what I was going to say: Oh, hi there, I'm Thom.  I just want to say what an honor it is to be a part of this prestigious team.  A leader that wants to kick my ass, some bitchy girl with a major attitude problem, a geriatric precog, a guy who should probably be quarantined at the Center for Disease Control, and me, just your average, ordinary, gay teen superhero.  Surely we're what the founding members had in mind when they banded together to form the world's premier superhero group. What's not to be excited about?

     &quot;I'm Thom.&quot; I scratched a dry patch above my elbow.  &quot;I can heal things.  Sometimes." -- Perry Moore  (Hero)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11027-culture-clash-dylan-says-when-i-meet-his-mother-today</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 06:09:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Sonya Sones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11027-culture-clash-dylan-says-when-i-meet-his-mother-today]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Culture Clash

Dylan says
when I meet his mother today
I shouldn't mention
that I'm Jewish.

I say
okay, but can I 
tell her about
the HIV postive thing?

He gives me a look.
I give him one back" -- Sonya Sones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30009-but-for-me-if-we-re-talking-about-romance-cassettes-wipe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2008 17:18:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Rob Sheffield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30009-but-for-me-if-we-re-talking-about-romance-cassettes-wipe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But for me, if we're talking about romance, cassettes wipe the floor with MP3s.  This has nothing to do with superstition, or nostalgia. MP3s buzz straight to your brain.  That's part of what I love about them.  But the rhythm of the mix tape is the rhythm of romance, the analog hum of a physical connection between two sloppy human bodies.  The cassette is full of tape hiss and room tone; it's full of wasted space, unnecessary noise.  Compared to the go-go-go rhythm of an MP3, mix tapes are hopelessly inefficient.  You go back to a cassette the way a detective sits and pours drinks for the elderly motel clerk who tells stories about the old days--you know you might be somewhat bored, but there might be a clue in there somewhere.  And if there isn't, what the hell? It's not a bad time.  You know you will waste time.  You  plan on it." -- Rob Sheffield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35512-i-believe-that-when-people-die-they-go-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 20:14:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Dara Horn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35512-i-believe-that-when-people-die-they-go-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that when people die, they go to the same place as all the people who haven’t yet been born.  That’s why it’s called the world to come, because that’s where they make the new souls for the future.  And the reward when good people die” – her mother paused, swallowed, paused again – “the reward when good people die is that they get to help make the people in their families who haven’t been born yet.  They pick out what kinds of traits they want the new people to have – they give them all the raw material of their souls, like their talents and their brains and their potential.  Of course it’s up to the new ones, once they’re born, what they’ll use and what they won’t, but that’s what everyone who dies is doing, I think.  They get to decide what kind of people the new ones might be able to become." -- Dara Horn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 20:15:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to write the book that wants to be written. And if the book will be too difficult for grown-ups, then you write it for children." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25748-like-90-percent-of-the-television-they-watch-it-comes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 15:31:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25748-like-90-percent-of-the-television-they-watch-it-comes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like 90 percent of the television they watch, it comes from the south and is shown dubbed into Yiddish.  It concerns the adventures of a pair of children with Jewish names who look like they might be part Indian and have no visible parents.  They do have a crystalline magical dragon scale that they wish on in order to travel to a land of pastel dragons, each distinguished by its color and its particular brand of imbecility.  Little by little, the children spend more and more time with their magical dragon scale until one day they travel off to the land of rainbow idiocy and never return; their bodies are found by the night manager of their cheap flop, each with a bullet in the back of the head.  Maybe, Landsman thinks, something gets lost in the translation." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23330-i-thought-marcus-was-going-to-be-in-my-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 05:10:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Megan McCafferty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23330-i-thought-marcus-was-going-to-be-in-my-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I thought Marcus was going to be in my life forever. Then I thought I was wrong. Now he’s back. But this time I know what’s certain: Marcus will be gone again, and back again and again and again because nothing is permanent. Especially people. Strangers become friends. Friends become lovers. Lovers become strangers. Strangers become friends once more, and over and over. Tomorrow, next week, fifty years from now, I know I’ll get another one-word postcard from Marcus, because this one doesn’t have a period signifying the end of the sentence.

Or the end of anything at all." -- Megan McCafferty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115245-what-i-bring-to-the-interview-is-respect-the-person</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2008 04:41:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Studs Terkel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115245-what-i-bring-to-the-interview-is-respect-the-person]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I bring to the interview is respect.  The person recognizes that you respect them because you're listening.  Because you're listening, they feel good about talking to you.  When someone tells me a thing that happened, what do I feel inside? I want to get the story out. It's for the person who reads it to have the feeling . . . In most cases the person I encounter is not a celebrity; rather the ordinary person.  &quot;Ordinary&quot; is a word I loathe.  It has a patronizing air.  I have come across ordinary people who have done extraordinary things. (p. 176)" -- Studs Terkel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259736-some-years-ago-a-psychiatrist-had-told-me-that-finding</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 05:11:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by George Chesbro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259736-some-years-ago-a-psychiatrist-had-told-me-that-finding]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some years ago a psychiatrist had told me that finding out things other people didn't want known was my way of trying to stay even with a society filled with people bigger than I was.  The remark had been meant to startle, to provoke insight, and eventually to alter my behavior.
     Instead, I'd simply found that I thoroughly agreed with him and had gone out after a private investigator's license.
     [Dr. Robert Frederickson AKA Mongo]" -- George Chesbro]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
