<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/268147-sarah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/268147-sarah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 21:54:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223963-there-are-only-so-many-times-that-you-can-utter</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 21:54:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223963-there-are-only-so-many-times-that-you-can-utter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are only so many times that you can utter ‘It does not hurt’ before it begins to hurt even more than the hurt. You become enlightened of the feeling of feeling hurt, which is worse, I am certain, than the existent hurt." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295254-usually-adult-males-who-are-unable-to-make-emotional-connections</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 21:56:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295254-usually-adult-males-who-are-unable-to-make-emotional-connections]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Usually adult males who are unable to make emotional connections with the women they choose to be intimate with are frozen in time, unable to allow themselves to love for fear that the loved one will abandon them.  If the first woman they passionately loved, the mother, was not true to her bond of love, then how can they trust that their partner will be true to love. Often in their adult relationships these men act out again and again to test their partner's love. While the rejected adolescent boy imagines that he can no longer receive his mother's love because he is not worthy, as a grown man he may act out in ways that are unworthy and yet demand of the woman in his life that she offer him unconditional love. This testing does not heal the wound of the past, it merely reenacts it, for ultimately the woman will become weary of being tested and end the relationship, thus reenacting the abandonment.  This drama confirms for many men that they cannot put their trust in love. They decide that it is better to put their faith in being powerful, in being dominant." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295257-often-men-who-have-been-emotionally-neglected-and-abused-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 21:58:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295257-often-men-who-have-been-emotionally-neglected-and-abused-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Often men who have been emotionally neglected and abused as children by dominating mothers bond with assertive women, only to have their childhood feelings of being engulfed surface.  While they could not 'smash their mommy' and still receive love, they find that they can engage in intimate violence with partners who respond to their acting out by trying harder to connect with them emotionally, hoping that the love offered in the present will heal the wounds of the past.  If only one party in the relationship is working to create love, to create the space of emotional connection, the dominator model remains in place and the relationship just becomes a site for continuous power struggle." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
