<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/26852-eric]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/26852-eric" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 11:04:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176300-which-so-incorruptibly-reduced-a-reality-to-its-color-content</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 11:04:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176300-which-so-incorruptibly-reduced-a-reality-to-its-color-content]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["which so incorruptibly reduced a reality to its color content that it resumed a new existence in a beyond of color, without any previous memories." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5015-what-did-nabokov-and-joyce-have-in-common-apart-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 10:04:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5015-what-did-nabokov-and-joyce-have-in-common-apart-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What did Nabokov and Joyce have in common, apart from the poor teeth and the great prose? Exile, and decades of near pauperism. A compulsive tendency to overtip. An uxoriousness that their wives deservedly inspired. More than that, they both lived their lives 'beautifully'--not in any Jamesian sense (where, besides, ferocious solvency would have been a prerequisite), but in the droll fortitude of their perseverance. They got the work done, with style." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213364-above-my-cradle-loomed-the-bookcase-where-latin-ashes-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 23:16:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Charles Baudelaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213364-above-my-cradle-loomed-the-bookcase-where-latin-ashes-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Above my cradle loomed the bookcase where/ Latin ashes and the dust of Greece/ mingled with novels, history, and verse/ in one dark Babel. I was folio-high/ when I first heard the voices." -- Charles Baudelaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221157-and-i-reminded-myself-that-the-reproach-of-intellectualism-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 10:44:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Marguerite Yourcenar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221157-and-i-reminded-myself-that-the-reproach-of-intellectualism-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...and I reminded myself that the reproach of intellectualism is often directed at the most sensitive natures, those most ardently alive, those obliged by their frailty or their excess of strength constantly to resort to the arduous disciplines of the mind." -- Marguerite Yourcenar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232678-this-furtive-childhood-this-concealed-degradation-is-ready-to-explode</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2010 15:53:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Witold Gombrowicz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232678-this-furtive-childhood-this-concealed-degradation-is-ready-to-explode]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...this furtive childhood, this concealed degradation is ready to explode your systems sooner or later." -- Witold Gombrowicz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256970-until-the-fear-of-catastrophe-amends-or-catastrophe-itself-destroys</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2010 14:23:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Reinhold Niebuhr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256970-until-the-fear-of-catastrophe-amends-or-catastrophe-itself-destroys]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...until the fear of catastrophe amends, or catastrophe itself destroys..." -- Reinhold Niebuhr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260989-much-fuss-has-been-made-over-the-idea-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 08:14:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260989-much-fuss-has-been-made-over-the-idea-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Much fuss has been made over the idea of the frontier, as though it were a line advancing east to west, but the West was settled piece meal, and Indians fled in many directions to escape the tightening noose of the railroad lines and towns." -- Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275666-old-men-old-men-old-men-medals-medals-medals-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 13:03:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Marina Tsvetaeva]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275666-old-men-old-men-old-men-medals-medals-medals-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Old men, old men, old men. Medals, medals, medals. Not a brow without a furrow, not a breast without a star. My brother and husband are uniquely-young here. The grouping of young Grand Dukes doesn't count because a grouping is just what they are: a marble bas-relief. Today the whole old-age of Russia seems to have flowed into this place in homage to the eternal youth of Greece. A living lesson of history and philosophy: this is what time does with people, this is what it does--with gods. This is what time does with a man, this is what (a glance at the statues) art does. And, the last lesson: this is what time does with a man; this is what a man does with time. But because of my youth I don't think about that, I feel only a cold shudder. (&quot;The Opening of the Museum&quot;)" -- Marina Tsvetaeva]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292048-we-all-thought-richmond-protected-as-it-was-by-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:07:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Robert E. Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292048-we-all-thought-richmond-protected-as-it-was-by-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all thought Richmond, protected as it was by our splendid fortifications and defended by our army of veterans, could not be taken.  Yet Grant turned his face to our Capital, and never turned it away until we had surrendered.  Now, I have carefully searched the military records of both ancient and modern history, and have never found Grant's superior as a general.  I doubt that his superior can be found in all history." -- Robert E. Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295735-the-metaphor-is-perhaps-the-most-fruitful-power-of-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 09:00:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by José Ortega y Gasset]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295735-the-metaphor-is-perhaps-the-most-fruitful-power-of-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The metaphor is perhaps the most fruitful power of man. Its efficacy verges on magic, and it seems a tool for creation which God forgot inside one of His creatures when He made him." -- José Ortega y Gasset]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303879-there-never-will-be-anything-more-interesting-than-that-american</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 10:46:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Gertrude Stein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303879-there-never-will-be-anything-more-interesting-than-that-american]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There never will be anything more interesting than that American Civil War." -- Gertrude Stein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155686-a-raznochinets-needs-no-memory-it-is-enough-for-him-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 22:41:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Osip Mandelstam]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155686-a-raznochinets-needs-no-memory-it-is-enough-for-him-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A  raznochinets needs no memory—it is enough for him to tell of the books he has read, and his biography is done." -- Osip Mandelstam]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315592-i-find-more-and-more-that-i-am-a-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2010 18:32:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Edmund Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315592-i-find-more-and-more-that-i-am-a-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I find more and more that I am a man of the 1920s. I still expect something exciting. Drinks, animated conversation, gaiety: the uninhibited exchange of ideas." -- Edmund Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/379710-poor-little-place-he-murmured-with-a-sigh-she-heard</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2011 11:27:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/379710-poor-little-place-he-murmured-with-a-sigh-she-heard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Poor little place,' he murmured with a sigh. She heard him. He said the most melancholy things, but she noticed that directly he had said them he always seemed more cheerful than usual. All this phrase-making was a game, she thought, for if she had said half what he said, she would have blown her brains out by now." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31093-you-should-approach-joyce-s-ulysses-as-the-illiterate-baptist-preacher</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 13:25:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by william faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31093-you-should-approach-joyce-s-ulysses-as-the-illiterate-baptist-preacher]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You should approach Joyce's Ulysses as the illiterate Baptist preacher approaches the Old Testament: with faith." -- william faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427863-how-soon-indeed-are-human-things-forgotten-as-we-meet</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2011 12:27:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by William James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427863-how-soon-indeed-are-human-things-forgotten-as-we-meet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How soon, indeed, are human things forgotten! As we meet here this morning, the Southern sun is shining on their place of burial, and the waves sparkling and the sea-gulls circling around Fort Wagner's ancient site. But the great earthworks and their thundering cannon, the commanders and their followers, the wild assault and repulse that for a brief space made night hideous on that far-off evening, have all sunk into the blue gulf of the past, and for the majority of this generation are hardly more than an abstract name, a picture, a tale that is told. Only when some yellow-bleached photograph of a soldier of the 'sixties comes into our hands, with that odd and vivid look of individuality due to the moment when it was taken, do we realize the concreteness of that by-gone history, and feel how interminable to the actors in them were those leaden-footed hours and years." -- William James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/452037-the-great-bulk-of-the-legal-voters-of-the-south</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 11:32:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Ulysses S. Grant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/452037-the-great-bulk-of-the-legal-voters-of-the-south]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The great bulk of the legal voters of the South were men who owned no slaves; their homes were generally in the hills and poor country; their facilities for educating their children, even up to the point of reading and writing, were very limited; their interest in the contest was very meagre--what there was, if they had been capable of seeing it, was with the North; they too needed emancipation." -- Ulysses S. Grant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/452912-at-the-constitutional-convention-the-states-were-divided-into-different</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 11:50:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by James Madison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/452912-at-the-constitutional-convention-the-states-were-divided-into-different]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...[at the Constitutional Convention] the States were divided into different interests not by their difference of size, but principally from their having or not having slaves. It did not lie between the large and small States: it lay between the Northern and Southern." -- James Madison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464506-the-pollution-of-american-space-brutalizes-the-senses-making-gray-neurotics</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2011 07:35:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Susan Sontag]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464506-the-pollution-of-american-space-brutalizes-the-senses-making-gray-neurotics]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...the pollution of American space...brutalizes the senses, making gray neurotics of most of us, and perverse spiritual athletes and strident self-transcenders of the best of us." -- Susan Sontag]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491899-baudelaire-had-supper-at-the-table-next-to-ours-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 11:28:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Edmond De Goncourt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491899-baudelaire-had-supper-at-the-table-next-to-ours-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Baudelaire had supper at the table next to ours. He was without a cravat, his shirt open at the neck and his head shaved, just as if he were to be guillotined. A single affectation: his little hands washed and cared for, the nails kept scrupulously clean. The face of a maniac, a voice that cuts like a knife, and a precise elocution that tries to copy Saint-Just and succeeds." -- Edmond De Goncourt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/496858-there-was-a-distinct-class-of-these-gentlemen-tramps-young</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 13:40:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by George Santayana]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/496858-there-was-a-distinct-class-of-these-gentlemen-tramps-young]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was a distinct class of these gentlemen tramps, young men no longer young, who wouldn't settle down, who disliked polite society and the genteel conventions, but hadn't enough intelligence or enough conceit to think themselves transcendentalists or poets, in the style of Thoreau or of Walt Whitman." -- George Santayana]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/499934-little-phoebe-was-one-of-those-persons-who-possess-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 06:51:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Nathaniel Hawthorne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/499934-little-phoebe-was-one-of-those-persons-who-possess-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Little Phoebe was one of those persons who possess, as their exclusive patrimony, the gift of practical arrangement. It is a kind of natural magic that enables these favored ones to bring out the hidden capabilities of things around them; and particularly to give a look of comfort and habitableness to any place which, for however brief a period, may happen to be their home. A wild hut of underbrush, tossed together by wayfarers through the primitive forest, would acquire the home aspect by one night's lodging of such a woman, and would retain it long after her quiet figure had disappeared into the surrounding shade." -- Nathaniel Hawthorne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/503529-captain-jack-that-volatile-modoc-seems-to-have-been-handled</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 16:03:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Evan S. Connell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/503529-captain-jack-that-volatile-modoc-seems-to-have-been-handled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Captain Jack, that volatile Modoc, seems to have been handled still more causally. After being hanged and buried, Jack was exhumed, embalmed, and exhibited at carnivals: admission ten cents. How many instances of such sensibility one chooses to catalogue may be limited by the amount of time spent turning over musty pages. During the seventeenth century, Robert Cavalier, Sieur de La Salle, came upon a wood plank near the ruins of Ft. Crèvecoeur deep in the wilderness of the New World, upon which a French deserter had printed: NOUS SOMMES TOUS SAUVAGES" -- Evan S. Connell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/523870-most-i-loved-james-baldwin-s-essays-there-was-to-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 20:26:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Richard Rodriguez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/523870-most-i-loved-james-baldwin-s-essays-there-was-to-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most, I loved James Baldwin's essays. There was to a Baldwin essay a metropolitan elegance I envied, a refusal of the livid. In Baldwin I found a readiness to rise to prophetic wrath, something like those ministers, and yet, once more, to bend down in tenderness, to call grown men and women &quot;baby&quot; (a whiff of the theater). Watching Baldwin on television—I will always consider the fifties to have been a sophisticated time—fixed for me what being a writer must mean. Arching eyebrows intercepted ironies, parenthetically declared fouls; mouthfuls of cigarette smoke shot forth ribbons of exactitude." -- Richard Rodriguez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/532846-one-of-picton-s-officers-fell-asleep-the-instant-the-halt</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 11:58:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by John Keegan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/532846-one-of-picton-s-officers-fell-asleep-the-instant-the-halt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of Picton's officers fell asleep the instant the halt was sounded and did not think of food until later in the night, when he woke to eat some chops cooked in the breastplate of a dead cuirassier (meat fried in a breastplate was very much &lt;i&gt;à la mode&lt;/i&gt; in the Waterloo campaign, rather as rats spitted on a bayonet were to be in 1871 or champagne exhumed from chateau gardens in 1914)." -- John Keegan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/547564-i-have-two-foes-in-the-world-twins-inextricably-interrelated</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 20:37:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Marina Tsvetaeva]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/547564-i-have-two-foes-in-the-world-twins-inextricably-interrelated]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have two foes in the world, twins inextricably interrelated -- the hunger of the hungry and the glut of the glutted!" -- Marina Tsvetaeva]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123791-but-we-had-with-us-to-keep-and-to-care</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 07:10:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Joshua Lawrence Chamberlain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123791-but-we-had-with-us-to-keep-and-to-care]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But we had with us, to keep and to care for, more than five hundred bruised bodies of men- men made in the image of God, marred by the hand of man and must we say in the name of God?  And where is the reckoning for such things?  And who is answerable?  One might almost shrink from the sound of his own voice, which had launched into the palpitating air words of order- do we call it? - fraught with such ruin. Was it God's command we heard or His forgiveness we must forever implore?" -- Joshua Lawrence Chamberlain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/558807-that-ambiguous-area-of-culture-where-something-unfailingly-political-though</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 09:33:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Roland Barthes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/558807-that-ambiguous-area-of-culture-where-something-unfailingly-political-though]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...that ambiguous area of culture where something unfailingly political, though separate from the political choices of the day, infiltrates judgment and language." -- Roland Barthes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/563450-he-preferred-always-the-more-to-the-less-remote-what-seeming</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 21:38:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Walter Pater]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/563450-he-preferred-always-the-more-to-the-less-remote-what-seeming]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He...preferred always the more to the less remote, what, seeming exceptional, was an instance of law more refined..." -- Walter Pater]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/477731-i-am-reading-six-books-at-once-the-only-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 10:40:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eric add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/477731-i-am-reading-six-books-at-once-the-only-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am reading six books at once, the only way of reading; since, as you will agree, one book is only a single unaccompanied note, and to get the full sound, one needs ten others at the same time." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
