<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/270012-rachele]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/270012-rachele" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 May 2012 10:13:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196631-sometimes-i-think-if-i-had-to-choose-between-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2012 10:13:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Sara Gruen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196631-sometimes-i-think-if-i-had-to-choose-between-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I think if I had to choose between an ear of corn or making love to a woman, I'd choose the corn." -- Sara Gruen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145470-but-it-did-not-all-happen-in-a-day-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2012 10:14:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Jack London]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145470-but-it-did-not-all-happen-in-a-day-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But it did not all happen in a day, this giving over of himself, body and soul, to the man-animals. He could not immediately forego his wild heritage and his memories of the Wild. There were days when he crept to the edge of the forest and stood and listened to something calling him far and away." -- Jack London]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290767-what-i-need-is-the-dandelion-in-the-spring-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2012 10:15:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290767-what-i-need-is-the-dandelion-in-the-spring-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I need is the dandelion in the spring. The bright yellow that means rebirth instead of destruction. The promise that life can go on, no matter how bad our losses. That it can be good again." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522431-i-learned-long-ago-not-to-restrict-the-world-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 09:55:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Elizabeth C. Mock]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522431-i-learned-long-ago-not-to-restrict-the-world-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I learned long ago not to restrict the world into what I believe to be possible, because that is precisely when the world surprises me." -- Elizabeth C. Mock]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431616-never-give-up-hope-and-look-for-the-rainbows-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 19:58:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Nonna Bannister]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431616-never-give-up-hope-and-look-for-the-rainbows-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never give up hope, and look for the rainbows and happiness!" -- Nonna Bannister]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/356151-i-imagined-myself-as-frida-to-diego-both-muse-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 16:32:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by patti smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/356151-i-imagined-myself-as-frida-to-diego-both-muse-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I imagined myself as Frida to Diego, both muse and maker. I dreamed of meeting an artist to love and support and work with side by side." -- patti smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335913-yet-you-could-feel-a-vibration-in-the-air-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 15:55:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Patti Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335913-yet-you-could-feel-a-vibration-in-the-air-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yet you could feel a vibration in the air, a sense of hastening. It had started with the moon, inaccessible poem that it was. Now men had walked upon it, rubber treads on a pearl of the gods. Perhaps it was an awareness of time passing, the last summer of the decade. Sometimes I just wanted to raise my hands and stop. But stop what? Maybe just growing up." -- Patti Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/463890-there-is-no-sunrise-so-beautiful-that-it-is-worth</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 16:18:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Mindy Kaling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/463890-there-is-no-sunrise-so-beautiful-that-it-is-worth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no sunrise so beautiful that it is worth waking me up to see it." -- Mindy Kaling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/471108-later-when-you-re-grown-up-you-realize-you-never-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 16:19:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Mindy Kaling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/471108-later-when-you-re-grown-up-you-realize-you-never-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Later, when you're grown up, you realize you never really get to hang out with your family.  You pretty much have only eighteen years to spend with them full time, and that's it." -- Mindy Kaling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7511-i-saw-my-life-branching-out-before-me-like-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 14:40:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7511-i-saw-my-life-branching-out-before-me-like-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I saw my life branching out before me like the green fig tree in the story. From the tip of every branch, like a fat purple fig, a wonderful future beckoned and winked. One fig was a husband and a happy home and children, and another fig was a famous poet and another fig was a brilliant professor, and another fig was Ee Gee, the amazing editor, and another fig was Europe and Africa and South America, and another fig was Constantin and Socrates and Attila and a pack of other lovers with queer names and offbeat professions, and another fig was an Olympic lady crew champion, and beyond and above these figs were many more figs I couldn't quite make out. I saw myself sitting in the crotch of this fig tree, starving to death, just because I couldn't make up my mind which of the figs I would choose. I wanted each and every one of them, but choosing one meant losing all the rest, and, as I sat there, unable to decide, the figs began to wrinkle and go black, and, one by one, they plopped to the ground at my feet." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23327-that-s-one-of-the-reasons-i-never-wanted-to-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 14:41:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23327-that-s-one-of-the-reasons-i-never-wanted-to-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That’s one of the reasons I never wanted to get married. The last thing I wanted was infinite security and to be the place an arrow shoots off from. I wanted change and excitement and to shoot off in all directions myself, like the colored arrows from a Fourth of July rocket." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300754-she-was-like-a-real-strawberry-in-a-roomful-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 14:42:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Jillian Lauren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300754-she-was-like-a-real-strawberry-in-a-roomful-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was like a real strawberry in a roomful of strawberry Pop-Tarts." -- Jillian Lauren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391476-but-i-tell-you-one-thing-i-don-t-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 14:43:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Rebecca Skloot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391476-but-i-tell-you-one-thing-i-don-t-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I tell you one thing, I don't want to be immortal if it mean living forever, cause then everybody else just die and get old in front of you while you stay the same, and that's just sad." -- Rebecca Skloot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/458016-she-s-the-most-important-person-in-the-world-and-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 14:43:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Rebecca Skloot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/458016-she-s-the-most-important-person-in-the-world-and-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She's the most important person in the world and her family living in poverty. If our mother is so important to science, why can't we get health insurance?" -- Rebecca Skloot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225444-more-girls-were-killed-in-the-last-50-years-precisely</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 15:21:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Nicholas D. Kristof]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225444-more-girls-were-killed-in-the-last-50-years-precisely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["More girls were killed in the last 50 years, precisely because they were girls, than men killed in all the wars in the 20th century. More girls are killed in this routine gendercide in any one decade than people were slaughtered in all the genocides of the 20th century.

The equivalent of 5 jumbo jets worth of women die in labor each day... life time risk of maternal death is 1,000x higher in a poor country than in the west. That should be an international scandal." -- Nicholas D. Kristof]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873530-we-have-a-racially-based-justice-system-that-overpunishes-fails</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2013 10:46:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Piper Kerman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873530-we-have-a-racially-based-justice-system-that-overpunishes-fails]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have a racially based justice system that overpunishes, fails to rehabilitate, and doesn't make us safer." -- Piper Kerman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381019-any-place-then-can-become-a-cemetery-all-it-takes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2013 10:47:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Karen Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381019-any-place-then-can-become-a-cemetery-all-it-takes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any place, then, can become a cemetery. All it takes is your body. It's not fair, I think, and I get this petulant wish for ugly flowers and mourners, my mother's old familiar grief. Somebody I love to tend my future grave. Probably this is the wrong thing to be wishing for." -- Karen Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/510296-all-i-ever-really-want-to-know-is-how-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2013 10:48:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Miranda July]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/510296-all-i-ever-really-want-to-know-is-how-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All I ever really want to know is how other people are making it through life—where do they put their body, hour by hour, and how do they cope inside of it." -- Miranda July]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10942-to-the-person-in-the-bell-jar-blank-and-stopped</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2013 10:49:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10942-to-the-person-in-the-bell-jar-blank-and-stopped]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To the person in the bell jar, blank and stopped as a dead baby, the world itself is a bad dream." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143324-we-all-want-to-be-stars-the-idea-of-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2013 15:07:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Tonya Hurley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143324-we-all-want-to-be-stars-the-idea-of-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all want to be stars.  The idea of being revered and envied must be encoded somewhere deep in our DNA.  So must the desire to revere and envy others we imagine to be better, more accepted, and more popular than we are.  The only problem is that the most necessary qualities required to be a celebrity -- self-absorption, egomania, shamelessness -- are the least attractive in a friend." -- Tonya Hurley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227687-now-should-we-treat-women-as-independent-agents-responsible-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 10:37:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Jessica Valenti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227687-now-should-we-treat-women-as-independent-agents-responsible-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now, should we treat  women as independent agents, responsible for themselves? Of course. But being responsible has nothing to do with being raped. Women don’t get raped because they were drinking or took drugs. Women do not get raped because they weren’t careful enough. Women get raped because &lt;i&gt;someone raped them.&lt;/i&gt;" -- Jessica Valenti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186473-the-desirable-virgin-is-sexy-but-not-sexual-she-s-young</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 10:37:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Jessica Valenti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186473-the-desirable-virgin-is-sexy-but-not-sexual-she-s-young]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The desirable virgin is sexy but not sexual. She's young, white, and skinny. She's a cheerleader, a babysitter; she's accessible and eager to please (remember those ethics of passivity!). She's never a woman of color. SHe's never a low-income girl or a fat girl.  She's never disabled. &quot;Virgin&quot; is a designation for those who meet a certain standard of what women, especially young women, are supposed to look like. As for how these young women are supposed to act? A blank slate is best." -- Jessica Valenti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/424160-the-hope-i-have-for-women-that-we-can-start</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 10:37:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Jessica Valenti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/424160-the-hope-i-have-for-women-that-we-can-start]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["..the hope I have for women: that we can start to see ourselves-and encourage men to see us-as more than just the sum of our sexual parts: not as virgins or whores, as mothers or girlfriends, or as existing only in relation to men, but as people with independent desires, hopes and abilities. But I know that this can't happen as long as American culture continues to inundate us with gender-role messages that place everyone-men and women-in an unnatural hierarchical order that's impossible to maintain without strife. For women to move forward, and for men to break free, we need to overcome the masculinity status quo-together." -- Jessica Valenti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/424162-when-women-s-sexuality-is-imagined-to-be-passive-or-dirty</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 10:37:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Jessica Valenti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/424162-when-women-s-sexuality-is-imagined-to-be-passive-or-dirty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When women's sexuality is imagined to be passive or &quot;dirty,&quot; it also means that men's sexuality is automatically positioned as aggressive and right-no matter what form it takes. And when one of the conditions of masculinity, a concept that is already so fragile in men's minds, is that men dissociate from women and prove their manliness through aggression, we're encouraging a culture of violence and sexuality that's detrimental to both men and women." -- Jessica Valenti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/648556-what-s-the-difference-between-venerating-women-for-being-fuckable-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 10:37:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Jessica Valenti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/648556-what-s-the-difference-between-venerating-women-for-being-fuckable-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What’s the difference between venerating women for being fuckable and putting them on a purity pedestal? In both cases, women’s worth is contingent upon their ability to please men and to shape their sexual identities around what men want." -- Jessica Valenti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/693099-making-women-the-sexual-gatekeepers-and-telling-men-they-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 10:37:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Jessica Valenti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/693099-making-women-the-sexual-gatekeepers-and-telling-men-they-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Making women the sexual gatekeepers and telling men they just can't help themselves not only drives home the point that women's sexuality is unnatural, but also sets up a disturbing dynamic in which women are expected to be responsible for men's sexual behavior." -- Jessica Valenti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/621365-idea-at-play-here-is-that-of-morality-when-young</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 10:37:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Jessica Valenti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/621365-idea-at-play-here-is-that-of-morality-when-young]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...idea at play here is that of “morality.” When young women are taught about morality, there’s not often talk of compassion, kindness, courage, or integrity. There is, however, a lot of talk about hymens" -- Jessica Valenti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728350-girls-going-wild-aren-t-damaging-a-generation-of-women-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 10:38:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Jessica Valenti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728350-girls-going-wild-aren-t-damaging-a-generation-of-women-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Girls “going wild” aren’t damaging a generation of women, the myth of sexual purity is. The lie of virginity—the idea that such a thing even exists—is ensuring that young women’s perception of themselves is inextricable from their bodies, and that their ability to be moral actors is absolutely dependent on their sexuality. It’s time to teach our daughters that their ability to be good people depends on their being good people , not on whether or not they’re sexually active…so while young women are subject to overt sexual messages everyday, they’re simultaneously being taught—by the people who are supposed to care for their personal and moral development, no less—that their only real worth is their virginity and ability to remain “pure”." -- Jessica Valenti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/558998-sex-for-pleasure-for-fun-or-even-for-building-relationships</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 10:38:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Jessica Valenti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/558998-sex-for-pleasure-for-fun-or-even-for-building-relationships]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sex for pleasure, for fun, or even for building relationships is completely absent from our national conversation.  Yet taking the joy out of sexuality is a surefire way to ensure not that young women won't have sex, but rather that they'll have it without pleasure." -- Jessica Valenti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/380136-whether-it-appears-in-a-story-about-a-man-killing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 10:38:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachele add a quote by Jessica Valenti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/380136-whether-it-appears-in-a-story-about-a-man-killing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whether it appears in a story about a man killing his girlfriend while calling her a whore or in trying to battle conservative claims that emergency contraception or the HPV vaccine will make girls promiscuous, the purity myth in America underlies more misogyny than most people would like to admit" -- Jessica Valenti]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
