<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/27056-ainsley]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/27056-ainsley" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 07:58:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47075-we-slept-in-the-same-bed-there-was-never-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 07:58:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47075-we-slept-in-the-same-bed-there-was-never-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We slept in the same bed.
There was never a right time to say it.
It was always unnecessary.
The books in my father's shed were sighing.
The sheets were rising and falling around me with Anna's breathing.
I thought about waking her.
but it was unnecessary.
There would be other nights.
And how can you say I love you to someone you love?
I rolled onto my side and fell asleep next to her.
Here is the point of everything I have been trying to tell you...
It's always necessary.
I love you,..." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6463-i-ve-learned-that-you-can-tell-a-lot-about-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 07:58:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6463-i-ve-learned-that-you-can-tell-a-lot-about-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that you can tell a lot about a person by the way (s)he handles these three things: a rainy day, lost luggage, and tangled Christmas tree lights." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82453-she-said-it-out-loud-the-words-distributed-into-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 07:58:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82453-she-said-it-out-loud-the-words-distributed-into-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She said it out loud, the words distributed into a room that was full of cold air and books. Books everywhere! Each wall was armed with overcrowded yet immaculate shelving. It was barely possible to see paintwork. There were all different styles and sizes of lettering on the spines of the black, the red, the gray, the every-colored books. It was one of the most beautiful things Liesel Meminger had ever seen.

With wonder, she smiled.

That such a room existed!" -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135497-you-know-your-problem-quentin-you-keep-expecting-people-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 07:57:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135497-you-know-your-problem-quentin-you-keep-expecting-people-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know your problem, Quentin? You keep expecting people not to be themselves. I mean, I could hate you for being massively unpunctual and for never being interested in anything other than Margo Roth Spiegelman, and for, like, never asking me about how it's going with my girlfriend - but I don't give a shit, man, because you're you. My parents have a shit ton of black Santas, but that's okay. They're them. I'm too obsessed with a reference website to answer my phone sometimes when my friends call, or my girlfriend. That's okay, too. That's me. You like me anyway. And I like you. You're funny, and you're smart, and you may show up late, but you always show up eventually." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24168-life-can-be-wildly-tragic-at-times-and-i-ve-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2008 08:09:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Katharine Hepburn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24168-life-can-be-wildly-tragic-at-times-and-i-ve-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life can be wildly tragic at times, and I've had my share. But whatever happens to you, you have to keep a slightly comic attitude. In the final analysis, you have got not to forget to laugh." -- Katharine Hepburn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7128-never-be-bullied-into-silence-never-allow-yourself-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2008 08:11:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Harvey Fierstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7128-never-be-bullied-into-silence-never-allow-yourself-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never be bullied into silence. Never allow yourself to be made a victim. Accept no one's definition of your life, but define yourself." -- Harvey Fierstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24172-we-danced-too-wild-and-we-sang-too-long-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2008 08:12:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Pearl Cleage]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24172-we-danced-too-wild-and-we-sang-too-long-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We danced too wild, and we sang too long, and we hugged too hard, and we kissed too sweet, and howled just as loud as we wanted to howl, because by now we were all old enough to know that what looks like crazy on an ordinary day looks a lot like love if you catch it in the moonlight." -- Pearl Cleage]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/769-books-are-the-quietest-and-most-constant-of-friends-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2008 08:14:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Charles W. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/769-books-are-the-quietest-and-most-constant-of-friends-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are the quietest and most constant of friends; they are the most accessible and wisest of counselors, and the most patient of teachers." -- Charles W. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1420-i-wanted-a-perfect-ending-now-i-ve-learned-the-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2008 08:16:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Gilda Radner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1420-i-wanted-a-perfect-ending-now-i-ve-learned-the-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted a perfect ending. Now I've learned, the hard way, that some poems don't rhyme, and some stories don't have a clear beginning, middle, and end. Life is about not knowing, having to change, taking the moment and making the best of it, without knowing what's going to happen next.
Delicious Ambiguity." -- Gilda Radner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24180-if-we-could-read-the-secret-history-of-our-enemies</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2008 08:24:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Henry Wadsworth Longfellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24180-if-we-could-read-the-secret-history-of-our-enemies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we could read the secret history of our enemies, we should find in each man's life sorrow and suffering enough to disarm all hostility." -- Henry Wadsworth Longfellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3823-you-gain-strength-courage-and-confidence-by-every-experience-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2008 08:25:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3823-you-gain-strength-courage-and-confidence-by-every-experience-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You gain strength, courage and confidence by every experience in which you really stop to look fear in the face. You are able to say to yourself, 'I have lived through this horror. I can take the next thing that comes along.' You must do the thing you think you cannot do." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24182-just-thinking-about-a-friend-makes-you-want-to-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2008 08:26:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24182-just-thinking-about-a-friend-makes-you-want-to-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just thinking about a friend makes you want to do a happy dance, because a friend is someone who loves you in spite of your faults." -- Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1071-never-doubt-that-a-small-group-of-thoughtful-committed-citizens</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2008 08:33:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Margaret Mead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1071-never-doubt-that-a-small-group-of-thoughtful-committed-citizens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never doubt that a small group of thoughtful, committed, citizens can change the world. Indeed, it is the only thing that ever has." -- Margaret Mead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44852-all-of-them-all-except-phineas-constructed-at-infinite-cost</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 07:58:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by John Knowles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44852-all-of-them-all-except-phineas-constructed-at-infinite-cost]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All of them, all except Phineas, constructed at infinite cost to themselves these Maginot Lines against this enemy they thought they saw across the frontier, this enemy who never attacked that way-if he ever attacked at all; if he was indeed the enemy." -- John Knowles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19119-of-all-the-preposterous-assumptions-of-humanity-over-humanity-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 19:14:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19119-of-all-the-preposterous-assumptions-of-humanity-over-humanity-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of all the preposterous assumptions of humanity over humanity, nothing exceeds most of the criticisms made on the habits of the poor by the well-housed, well- warmed, and well-fed." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/504703-i-was-blind-and-heart-broken-and-didn-t-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 07:44:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/504703-i-was-blind-and-heart-broken-and-didn-t-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was blind and heart broken and didn't want to do anything and Gus burst into my room and shouted, &quot;I have wonderful news!&quot; And I was like, &quot;I don't really want to hear wonderful news right now,&quot; and Gus said, &quot;This is wonderful news you want to hear,&quot; and I asked him, &quot;Fine, what is it?&quot; and he said, &quot;You are going to live a good and long life filled with great and terrible moments that you cannot even imagine yet!" -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492965-i-imagined-the-augustus-waters-analysis-of-that-comment-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 07:44:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492965-i-imagined-the-augustus-waters-analysis-of-that-comment-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I imagined the Augustus Waters analysis of that comment: If I am playing basketball in heaven, does that imply a physical location of a heaven containing physical basketballs? Who makes the basketballs in question? Are there less fortunate souls in heaven who work in a celestial basketball factory so that I can play? Or did an omnipotent God create the basketballs out of the vacuum of space? Is this heaven in some kind of unobservable universe where the laws of physics don't apply, and if so, why in the hell would I be playing basketball when I could be flying or reading or looking at beautiful people or something else I actually enjoy? It's almost as if the way you imagine my dead self says more about you than either the person I was or whatever I am now." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275699-each-javelin-round-costs-80-000-and-the-idea-that-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2012 19:32:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Sebastian Junger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275699-each-javelin-round-costs-80-000-and-the-idea-that-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each Javelin round costs $80,000, and the idea that it's fired by a guy who doesn't make that in a year at a guy who doesn't make that in a lifetime is somehow so outrageous it almost makes the war seem winnable." -- Sebastian Junger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97674-i-m-writing-this-in-part-to-tell-you-that-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 20:45:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97674-i-m-writing-this-in-part-to-tell-you-that-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’m writing this in part to tell you that if you ever wonder what you’ve done in your life, and everyone does wonder sooner or later, you have been God’s grace to me, a miracle, something more than a miracle. You may not remember me very well at all, and it may seem to you to be no great thing to have been the good child of an old man in a shabby little town you will no doubt leave behind. If only I had the words to tell you." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2177-i-am-enough-of-an-artist-to-draw-freely-upon</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 07:57:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2177-i-am-enough-of-an-artist-to-draw-freely-upon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am enough of an artist to draw freely upon my imagination. Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24178-never-never-never-believe-any-war-will-be-smooth-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2008 08:23:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Winston Churchill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24178-never-never-never-believe-any-war-will-be-smooth-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never, never, never believe any war will be smooth and easy, or that anyone who embarks on the strange voyage can measure the tides and hurricanes he will encounter. The statesman who yields to war fever must realize that once the signal is given, he is no longer the master of policy but the slave of unforeseeable and uncontrollable events. " -- Winston Churchill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8727-life-isn-t-about-finding-yourself-life-is-about-creating-yourself</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2008 08:25:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8727-life-isn-t-about-finding-yourself-life-is-about-creating-yourself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life isn't about finding yourself. Life is about creating yourself." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/856205-what-was-unfolding-in-mumbai-was-unfolding-elsewhere-too-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 10:01:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Katherine Boo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/856205-what-was-unfolding-in-mumbai-was-unfolding-elsewhere-too-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What was unfolding in Mumbai was unfolding elsewhere, too. In the age of global market capitalism, hopes and grievances were narrowly conceived, which blunted a sense of common predicament. Poor people didn't unite; they competed ferociously amongst themselves for gains as slender as they were provisional. And this undercity strife created only the faintest ripple in the fabric of the society at large. The gates of the rich, occasionally rattled, remained unbreached. The politicians held forth on the middle class. The poor took down one another, and the world's great, unequal cities soldiered on in relative peace." -- Katherine Boo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/923820-for-the-past-two-weeks-he-s-been-feeling-so-superior</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 09:56:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ainsley add a quote by Ben Fountain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/923820-for-the-past-two-weeks-he-s-been-feeling-so-superior]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the past two weeks he's been feeling so superior and smart because of all the things he knows from the war, but forget it, they are the ones in charge, these saps, these innocents, their homeland dream is the dominant force. His reality is their reality's bitch; what they don't know is more powerful than all the things he knows, and yet he's lived what he's lived and knows what he knows, which means what, something terrible and possibly fatal, he suspects. To learn what you have to learn at the war, to do what you have to do, does this make you the enemy of all that sent you to the war?

Their reality dominates, except for this: It can't save you. It won't stop any bombs or bullets. He wonders if there's a saturation point, a body count that will finally blow the homeland dream to smithereens. How much reality can unreality take?" -- Ben Fountain]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
