<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/270540-rory]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/270540-rory" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 14:15:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27147-you-never-have-to-change-anything-you-got-up-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 14:15:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rory add a quote by Saul Bellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27147-you-never-have-to-change-anything-you-got-up-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You never have to change anything you got up in the middle of the night to write." -- Saul Bellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31427-language-is-courage-the-ability-to-conceive-a-thought-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2011 19:42:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rory add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31427-language-is-courage-the-ability-to-conceive-a-thought-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Language is courage: the ability to conceive a thought, to speak it, and by doing so to make it true." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11895-one-final-paragraph-of-advice-do-not-burn-yourselves-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 23:06:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rory add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11895-one-final-paragraph-of-advice-do-not-burn-yourselves-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One final paragraph of advice: do not burn yourselves out. Be as I am - a reluctant enthusiast....a part-time crusader, a half-hearted fanatic. Save the other half of yourselves and your lives for pleasure and adventure. It is not enough to fight for the land; it is even more important to enjoy it. While you can. While it’s still here. So get out there and hunt and fish and mess around with your friends, ramble out yonder and explore the forests, climb the mountains, bag the peaks, run the rivers, breathe deep of that yet sweet and lucid air, sit quietly for a while and contemplate the precious stillness, the lovely, mysterious, and awesome space. Enjoy yourselves, keep your brain in your head and your head firmly attached to the body, the body active and alive, and I promise you this much; I promise you this one sweet victory over our enemies, over those desk-bound men and women with their hearts in a safe deposit box, and their eyes hypnotized by desk calculators. I promise you this; You will outlive the bastards." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12675-after-all-reading-is-arguably-a-far-more-creative-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 13:08:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rory add a quote by Jasper Fforde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12675-after-all-reading-is-arguably-a-far-more-creative-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After all, reading is arguably a far more creative and imaginative process than writing; when the reader creates emotion in their head, or the colors of the sky during the setting sun, or the smell of a warm summer's breeze on their face, they should reserve as much praise for themselves as they do for the writer - perhaps more." -- Jasper Fforde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117959-if-the-real-world-were-a-book-it-would-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 02:24:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rory add a quote by Jasper Fforde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117959-if-the-real-world-were-a-book-it-would-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the real world were a book, it would never find a publisher.  Overlong, detailed to the point of distraction-and ultimately, without a major resolution." -- Jasper Fforde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10894-so-we-dream-on-thus-we-invent-our-lives-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 23:25:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rory add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10894-so-we-dream-on-thus-we-invent-our-lives-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So we dream on.  Thus we invent our lives.  We give ourselves a sainted mother, we make our father a hero; and someone’s older brother and someone’s older sister – they become our heroes too.  We invent what we love and what we fear.  There is always a brave lost brother – and a little lost sister, too.  We dream on and on: the best hotel, the perfect family, the resort life.  And our dreams escape us almost as vividly as we can imagine them…  That’s what happens, like it or not.  And because that’s what happens, this is what we need: we need a good, smart bear…  Coach Bob knew it all along: you’ve got to get obsessed and stay obsessed. You have to keep passing the open windows." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200931-a-friend-came-to-visit-james-joyce-one-day-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 21:08:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rory add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200931-a-friend-came-to-visit-james-joyce-one-day-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A friend came to visit James Joyce one day and found the great man sprawled across his writing desk in a posture of utter despair.

James, what’s wrong?' the friend asked. 'Is it the work?'

Joyce indicated assent without even raising his head to look at his friend. Of course it was the work; isn’t it always?

How many words did you get today?' the friend pursued.

Joyce (still in despair, still sprawled facedown on his desk): 'Seven.'

Seven? But James… that’s good, at least for you.'

Yes,' Joyce said, finally looking up. 'I suppose it is… but I don’t know what order they go in!" -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32194-work-is-about-a-search-for-daily-meaning-as-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 12:34:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rory add a quote by Studs Terkel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32194-work-is-about-a-search-for-daily-meaning-as-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Work is about a search for daily meaning as well as daily bread, for recognition as well as cash, for astonishment rather than torpor; in short, for a sort of life rather than a Monday through Friday sort of dying." -- Studs Terkel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76236-that-s-the-thing-about-books-they-let-you-travel-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 00:24:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rory add a quote by Jhumpa Lahiri]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76236-that-s-the-thing-about-books-they-let-you-travel-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's the thing about books. They let you travel without moving your feet." -- Jhumpa Lahiri]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
