<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/270891-julia-hotopp]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/270891-julia-hotopp" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 10:07:25 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67157-to-understand-all-is-to-forgive-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 10:07:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67157-to-understand-all-is-to-forgive-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To understand all is to forgive all." -- Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224537-you-re-going-to-pass-something-down-no-matter-what-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 14:30:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224537-you-re-going-to-pass-something-down-no-matter-what-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're going to pass something down no matter what you do or if you do nothing. Even if you let yourself go fallow, the weeds will grow and the brambles. Something will grow." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21627-the-best-thing-for-being-sad-replied-merlin-beginning-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 08:59:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by T.H. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21627-the-best-thing-for-being-sad-replied-merlin-beginning-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best thing for being sad,&quot; replied Merlin, beginning to puff and blow, &quot;is to learn something. That's the only thing that never fails. You may grow old and trembling in your anatomies, you may lie awake at night listening to the disorder of your veins, you may miss your only love, you may see the world about you devastated by evil lunatics, or know your honour trampled in the sewers of baser minds. There is only one thing for it then — to learn. Learn why the world wags and what wags it. That is the only thing which the mind can never exhaust, never alienate, never be tortured by, never fear or distrust, and never dream of regretting. Learning is the only thing for you. Look what a lot of things there are to learn." -- T.H. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/557176-he-saw-her-as-the-passionate-spirit-of-innocent-youth</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 09:07:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by T.H. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/557176-he-saw-her-as-the-passionate-spirit-of-innocent-youth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He saw her as the passionate spirit of innocent youth, now beleaguered by the trick which is played on youth - the trick of treachery in the body, which turns flesh into green bones. Her stupid finery was not vulgar to him, but touching. The girl was still there, still appealing from behind the breaking barricade of rouge. She had made the brave protest: I will not be vanquished. Under the clumsy coquetry, the undignified clothes, there was the human cry for help. The young eyes were puzzled, saying: It is I, inside here - what have they done to me? I will not submit. Some part of her spirit knew that the powder was making a guy of her, and hated it, and tried to hold her lover with the eyes alone. They said: Don't look at all this. Look at me. I am still here, in the eyes. Look at me, here in the prison, and help me out. Another part said: I am not old, it is illusion. I am beautifully made-up. See, I will perform the movements of youth. I will defy the enormous army of age." -- T.H. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
