<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/271179-nathan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/271179-nathan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 17:15:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/582791-we-shall-not-cease-from-exploration-and-the-end-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 17:15:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/582791-we-shall-not-cease-from-exploration-and-the-end-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We shall not cease from exploration
And the end of all our exploring
Will be to arrive where we started
And know the place for the first time. 
Through the unknown, unremembered gate
When the last of earth left to discover
Is that which was the beginning;
At the source of the longest river
The voice of the hidden waterfall
And the children in the apple-tree 
Not known, because not looked for
But heard, half-heard, in the stillness
Between two waves of the sea." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/582787-now-you-see-we-are-all-fugitives-we-have-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 17:15:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by A. A. Attanasio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/582787-now-you-see-we-are-all-fugitives-we-have-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now you see. We are all fugitives. We have always been fugitives from the void. Whatever comfort, whatever power we gain from outside of ourselves diminishes us -- because comfort and power, unless they are won from the void inside of us, are illusions that make us forget the emptyness that carries us. When we forget that, we believe we deserve comfort and power and so are capable of any evil. We deserve nothing but what we make of ourselves. We deserve nothing else. And when we understand that, then nothing is enough." -- A. A. Attanasio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5911-this-is-the-true-joy-in-life-the-being-used</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 17:15:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5911-this-is-the-true-joy-in-life-the-being-used]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is the true joy in life, the being used for a purpose recognized by yourself as a mighty one; the being thoroughly worn out before you are thrown on the scrap heap; the being a force of Nature instead of a feverish selfish little clod of ailments and grievances complaining that the world will not devote itself to making you happy." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190560-we-can-make-our-minds-so-like-still-water-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 17:15:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by William Butler Yeats]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190560-we-can-make-our-minds-so-like-still-water-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can make our minds so like still water that beings gather about us that they may see, it may be, their own images, and so live for a moment with a clearer, perhaps even with a fiercer life because of our quiet." -- William Butler Yeats]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199329-when-health-is-absent-wisdom-cannot-reveal-itself-art-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 17:15:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Herophilus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199329-when-health-is-absent-wisdom-cannot-reveal-itself-art-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When health is absent, wisdom cannot reveal itself, art cannot manifest, strength cannot fight, wealth becomes useless, and intelligence cannot be applied." -- Herophilus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2125-did-you-ever-want-to-set-someone-s-head-on-fire</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 17:01:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Warren Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2125-did-you-ever-want-to-set-someone-s-head-on-fire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did you ever want to set someone's head on fire, just to see what it looked like? Did you ever stand in the street and think to yourself, I could make that nun go blind just by giving her a kiss? Did you ever lay out plans for stitching babies and stray cats into a Perfect New Human? Did you ever stand naked surrounded by people who want your gleaming sperm, squirting frankincense, soma and testosterone from every pore? If so, then you're the bastard who stole my drugs Friday night. And I'll find you. Oh, yes." -- Warren Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205281-dance-like-you-re-stamping-on-a-human-face-forever-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 17:01:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Warren Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205281-dance-like-you-re-stamping-on-a-human-face-forever-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dance like you're stamping on a human face forever, love like you've been in a serious car crash that minced the front of your brain, stab like no one can arrest you, and live like there's no such thing as God." -- Warren Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40330-if-you-believe-that-your-thoughts-originate-inside-your-brain</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 17:01:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Warren Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40330-if-you-believe-that-your-thoughts-originate-inside-your-brain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you believe that your thoughts originate inside your brain, do you also believe that television shows are made inside your television set?" -- Warren Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169553-you-want-to-know-about-voting-i-m-here-to-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 17:01:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Warren Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169553-you-want-to-know-about-voting-i-m-here-to-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You want to know about voting. I'm here to tell you about voting. Imagine you're locked in a huge underground night-club filled with sinners, whores, freaks and unnameable things that rape pitbulls for fun. And you ain't allowed out until you all vote on what you're going to do tonight. You like to put your feet up and watch &quot;Republican Party Reservation&quot;. They like to have sex with normal people using knives, guns, and brand new sexual organs you did not even know existed. So you vote for television, and everyone else, as far as your eye can see, votes to fuck you with switchblades. That's voting. You're welcome." -- Warren Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 17:04:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 17:05:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things need not have happened to be true. Tales and dreams are the shadow-truths that will endure when mere facts are dust and ashes, and forgot." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1344-only-the-phoenix-rises-and-does-not-descend-and-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 17:07:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1344-only-the-phoenix-rises-and-does-not-descend-and-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only the phoenix rises and does not descend. And everything changes. And nothing is truly lost." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/582790-at-the-still-point-of-the-turning-world-neither-flesh</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 17:14:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/582790-at-the-still-point-of-the-turning-world-neither-flesh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the still point of the turning world.  Neither flesh nor fleshless;
Neither from nor towards; at the still point, there the dance is,
But neither arrest nor movement.  And do not call it fixity, 
Where past and future are gathered.  Neither movement from nor towards,
Neither ascent nor decline.  Except for the point, the still point,
There would be no dance, and there is only the dance." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 12:41:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/794121-in-the-two-years-after-no-logo-came-out-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2014 12:24:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Naomi Klein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/794121-in-the-two-years-after-no-logo-came-out-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the two years after No Logo came out, I went to dozens of teach-ins and conferences, some of them attended by thousands of people (tens of thousands in the case of the World Social Forum), that were exclusively devoted to popular education about the inner workings of global finance and trade. No topic was too arcane: the science of genetically modified foods, trade-related intellectual property rights, the fine print of bilateral trade deals, the patenting of seeds, the truth about certain carbon sinks. I sensed in these rooms a hunger for knowledge that I have never witnessed in any university class. It was as if people understood, all at once, that gathering this knowledge was crucial to the survival not just of democracy but of the planet. Yes, this was complicated, but we embraced that complexity because we were finally looking at systems, not just symbols." -- Naomi Klein]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
