<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/271213-diana]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/271213-diana" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 13:02:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43334-i-love-you-also-means-i-love-you-more-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 13:02:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43334-i-love-you-also-means-i-love-you-more-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you also means I love you more than anyone loves you, or has loved you, or will love you, and also, I love you in a way that no one loves you, or has loved you, or will love you, and also, I love you in a way that I love no one else, and never have loved anyone else, and never will love anyone else." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7692-if-there-is-no-love-in-the-world-we-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7692-if-there-is-no-love-in-the-world-we-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there is no love in the world, we will make a new world, and we will give it walls, and we will furnish it with soft, red interiors, from the inside out, and give it a knocker that resonates like a diamond falling to a jeweller's felt so that we should never hear it. Love me, because love doesn't exist, and I have tried everything that does." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12278-i-think-and-think-and-think-i-ve-thought-myself-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 13:00:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12278-i-think-and-think-and-think-i-ve-thought-myself-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think and think and think, I‘ve thought myself out of happiness one million times, but never once into it." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38963-the-earth-is-a-very-small-stage-in-a-vast</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 13:00:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38963-the-earth-is-a-very-small-stage-in-a-vast]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The earth is a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena. Think of the rivers of blood spilled by all those generals and emperors so that in glory and in triumph they could become the momentary masters of a fraction of a dot. Think of the endless cruelties visited by the inhabitants of one corner of the dot on scarcely distinguishable inhabitants of some other corner of the dot. How frequent their misunderstandings, how eager they are to kill one another, how fervent their hatreds. Our posturings, our imagined self-importance, the delusion that we have some privileged position in the universe, are challenged by this point of pale light. Our planet is a lonely speck in the great enveloping cosmic dark. In our obscurity -- in all this vastness -- there is no hint that help will come from elsewhere to save us from ourselves. It is up to us. It's been said that astronomy is a humbling, and I might add, a character-building experience. To my mind, there is perhaps no better demonstration of the folly of human conceits than this distant image of our tiny world. To me, it underscores our responsibility to deal more kindly and compassionately with one another and to preserve and cherish that pale blue dot, the only home we've ever known." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83017-i-like-to-see-people-reunited-i-like-to-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 13:00:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83017-i-like-to-see-people-reunited-i-like-to-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like to see people reunited, I like to see people run to each other, I like the kissing and the crying, I like the impatience, the stories that the mouth can't tell fast enough, the ears that aren't big enough, the eyes that can't take in all of the change, I like the hugging, the bringing together, the end of missing someone." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485711-my-thoughts-are-stars-i-cannot-fathom-into-constellations</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 13:00:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485711-my-thoughts-are-stars-i-cannot-fathom-into-constellations]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My thoughts are stars I cannot fathom into constellations." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105554-but-some-people-can-t-tell-where-it-hurts-they-can-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105554-but-some-people-can-t-tell-where-it-hurts-they-can-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But some people can't tell where it hurts. They can't calm down. They can't ever stop howling." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105195-a-truth-should-exist-it-should-not-be-used-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105195-a-truth-should-exist-it-should-not-be-used-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A truth should exist,
it should not be used
like this. If I love you

is that a fact or a weapon?" -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115376-tell-me-how-all-this-and-love-too-will-ruin</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Richard Siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115376-tell-me-how-all-this-and-love-too-will-ruin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tell me how all this, and love too, will ruin us.
These, our bodies, possessed by light.
Tell me we'll never get used to it." -- Richard Siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/535169-he-feels-as-if-he-is-floating-and-she-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/535169-he-feels-as-if-he-is-floating-and-she-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He feels as if he is floating, and she is weighting him to earth; he would like to put his arms around her and his face in her apron, and rest there listening to her heartbeat. But he doesn't want to mess her up, get blood all down the front of her." -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things need not have happened to be true. Tales and dreams are the shadow-truths that will endure when mere facts are dust and ashes, and forgot." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148505-the-heart-lies-and-the-head-plays-tricks-on-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148505-the-heart-lies-and-the-head-plays-tricks-on-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The heart lies and the head plays tricks on us, but the eyes see true.  Look with your eyes.  Hear with your ears.  Taste with your mouth.  Smell with your nose.  Feel with your skin.  Then comes the thinking, afterward, and in a way knowing the truth." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1398-i-love-deadlines-i-love-the-whooshing-noise-they-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 13:01:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1398-i-love-deadlines-i-love-the-whooshing-noise-they-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love deadlines. I love the whooshing noise they make as they go by." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176322-did-you-like-question-ten-moony-asked-sirius-as-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 13:01:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176322-did-you-like-question-ten-moony-asked-sirius-as-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did you like question ten, Moony?&quot; asked Sirius as they emerged into the entrance hall.
&quot;Loved it,&quot; said Lupin briskly. &quot;Give five signs that identify the werewolf. Excellent question.&quot;
&quot;D'you think you managed to get all the signs?&quot; said James in tones of mock concern.
&quot;Think I did,&quot; said Lupin seriously, as they joined the crowd thronging around the front doors eager to get out into the sunlit grounds. &quot;One: He's sitting on my chair. Two: He's wearing my clothes. Three: His name's Remus Lupin..." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357113-living-alone-november-whispered-is-a-skill-like-running-long</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357113-living-alone-november-whispered-is-a-skill-like-running-long]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Living alone,' November whispered, 'is a skill, like running long distance or programming old computers.  You have to know parameters, protocols.  You have to learn them so well that they become like a language: to have music always so that the silence doesn't overwhelm you, to perform your work exquisitely well so that your time is filled.  You have to allow yourself to open up until you are the exact size of the place you live, no more or else you get restless. No less, or else you drown.  There are rules; there are ways of being and not being." -- Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357115-for-grace-may-only-be-found-briefly-and-always-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 08:00:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357115-for-grace-may-only-be-found-briefly-and-always-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...For grace may only be found briefly, and always in the midst of madness." -- Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357112-if-he-closed-his-eyes-he-could-dwell-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357112-if-he-closed-his-eyes-he-could-dwell-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If he closed his eyes he could dwell in the circuit of air that had once held her, he could hold his breath and be inside her again, within the close and burning borders of her- she stood here, washed her hair in this sink, wrote upon this wall, ate roasted chicken at this table.  There was no place he could enter where she had not also been, her echoes hanging in the air like pages hung to dry.  No place that did not suppurate in her absence, which was not ringed with the light of her old selves, like film burned with a cigarette." -- Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/272135-he-quirked-an-eyebrow-briefly-slightly-in-such-a-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/272135-he-quirked-an-eyebrow-briefly-slightly-in-such-a-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He quirked an eyebrow briefly, slightly, in such a way that no one afterwards might be able to safely accuse him of having done it. Sei knew the look. Names are meaningless, plosives and breath, but those who liked the slope of her waist often made much of hers, which denoted purity, clarity—as though it had any more in the way of depth than others. They wondered, all of them, if she really was pure, as pure as her name announced her to be, all white banners and hymeneal grace." -- Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40152-he-smiled-understandingly-much-more-than-understandingly-it-was-one-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40152-he-smiled-understandingly-much-more-than-understandingly-it-was-one-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He smiled understandingly-much more than understandingly. It was one of those rare smiles with a quality of eternal reassurance in it, that you may come across four or five times in life. It faced--or seemed to face--the whole eternal world for an instant, and then concentrated on you with an irresistible prejudice in your favor. It understood you just as far as you wanted to be understood, believed in you as you would like to believe in yourself, and assured you that it had precisely the impression of you that, at your best, you hoped to convey." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299816-one-ought-not-to-judge-her-all-children-are-heartless</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299816-one-ought-not-to-judge-her-all-children-are-heartless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One ought not to judge her: all children are Heartless. They have not grown a heart yet, which is why they can climb high trees and say shocking things and leap so very high grown-up hearts flutter in terror. Hearts weigh quite a lot. That is why it takes so long to grow one. But, as in their reading and arithmetic and drawing, different children proceed at different speeds. (It is well known that reading quickens the growth of a heart like nothing else.) Some small ones are terrible and fey, Utterly Heartless. Some are dear and sweet and Hardly Heartless At All. September stood very generally in the middle on the day the Green Wind took her, Somewhat Heartless, and Somewhat Grown." -- Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1230-a-day-without-laughter-is-a-day-wasted</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Nicolas Chamfort]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1230-a-day-without-laughter-is-a-day-wasted]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A day without  laughter is a day wasted." -- Nicolas Chamfort]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't see things as they are, we see them as we are." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3420-even-now-all-possible-feelings-do-not-yet-exist-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3420-even-now-all-possible-feelings-do-not-yet-exist-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even now, all possible feelings do not yet exist, there are still those that lie beyond our capacity and our imagination.  From time to time, when a piece of music no one has ever written or a painting no one has ever painted, or something else impossible to predict, fathom or yet describe takes place, a new feeling enters the world.  And then, for the millionth time in the history of feeling, the heart surges and absorbs the impact." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322817-she-knows-what-it-means-oh-wonderfully-bright-at-6</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322817-she-knows-what-it-means-oh-wonderfully-bright-at-6]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She &lt;i&gt;knows&lt;/i&gt; what it means. Oh, wonderfully bright at 6 a.m., yes, wonderfully clear for an &lt;i&gt;hour&lt;/i&gt;. But the shorter the days, the longer the nights, the darker the house, the easier it is, the easier it is, the easier it is, to mistake a shadow for the writing on the wall, the sound of overland footsteps for the distant crack of thunder, and the midnight chime of a New Year clock for the bell that tolls the end of the world." -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193706-she-hopes-for-nothing-except-fine-weather-and-a-resolution</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193706-she-hopes-for-nothing-except-fine-weather-and-a-resolution]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She hopes for nothing except fine weather and a resolution. She wants to end properly, like a good sentence. " -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158552-science-is-magic-that-works</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158552-science-is-magic-that-works]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Science is magic that works." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103751-that-is-part-of-the-beauty-of-all-literature-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103751-that-is-part-of-the-beauty-of-all-literature-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That is part of the beauty of all literature. You discover that your longings are universal longings, that you're not lonely and isolated from anyone. You belong." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71213-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-who-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71213-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-who-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time there was a boy who loved a girl, and her laughter was a question he wanted to spend his whole life answering." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15404-perhaps-one-did-not-want-to-be-loved-so-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 12:59:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15404-perhaps-one-did-not-want-to-be-loved-so-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps one did not want to be loved so much as to be understood." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
