<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/271691-edna-lyn]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/271691-edna-lyn" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2009 11:14:08 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/168019-sometimes-you-read-a-book-so-special-that-you-want</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2009 11:14:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/168019-sometimes-you-read-a-book-so-special-that-you-want]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes you read a book so special that you want to carry it around with you for months after you've finished just to stay near it." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360-good-friends-good-books-and-a-sleepy-conscience-this-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 18:03:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360-good-friends-good-books-and-a-sleepy-conscience-this-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good friends, good books, and a sleepy conscience: this is the ideal life." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 18:04:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always imagined that Paradise will be a kind of library." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 18:05:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many books, so little time." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3549-there-is-never-a-time-or-place-for-true-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 18:05:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3549-there-is-never-a-time-or-place-for-true-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is never a time or place for true love. It happens accidentally, in a heartbeat, in a single flashing, throbbing moment." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244512-i-look-down-at-our-knees-slightly-touching-jeans-against</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 12:40:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Simone Elkeles ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244512-i-look-down-at-our-knees-slightly-touching-jeans-against]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I look down at our knees, slightly touching. Jeans against jeans. Does she notice the heat transferring from her body to mine? Does she even realize what she's doing to me? I know, I know. I'm not a virgin and the slightest touch of a girl's knee is driving me insane. I don't even know what I'm feeling for Maggie, I just know that I'm &lt;i&gt;feeling&lt;/i&gt;. It's something I've tried to avoid and deny until yesterday, when I held her in my arms while her tears spilled onto my shirt.

God, our knees touching isn't enough. I need more.

She's knotting her fingers together on her lap as if she doesn't know what to do with them. I want to touch her, but what if she pulls away&amp;nbsp;like before? I've never been such a wuss with a girl in my life.

I bite my bottom lip as I slide my hand about millionth of a millimeter closer to her hand.

She doesn't seem fazed so I move closer. And closer.

When the tips of my fingers touch her wrist, she freezes. But she doesn't jerk her hand away. &lt;i&gt;God, her skin is so soft&lt;/i&gt;, I think as my fingers trail a path from her wrist to her knuckles to her smooth, manicured nails.

I swear touching her like this is driving me nuts. It's more erotic, more intense than any other time with Kendra. I feel awkward and&amp;nbsp;inexperienced as a freshman again. I look up. Everyone else is oblivious to the intensity of emotions running rampant in the back of the public bus.

When I look back down at my hand covering hers, I'm grateful she hasn't come to her senses and pulled away. As if she knows my&amp;nbsp;thoughts, we both turn our hands at the same time so our hands are palm against palm...finger against finger. Her hand is dwarfed against mine. It makes her seem more delicate and petite than I'd realize. I feel a need to protect her and be her champion should she ever need one.

With a slight shift of my hand, I lace my fingers through hers.

I'm holding hands. With Maggie Armstrong.

I'm not even going to think about how wrong it is because it feels so right. She's avoided looking right at me, but now she turns her head&amp;nbsp;and our eyes lock. God, how come I never noticed before how long her lashes were and how her brown eyes have specks of gold that sparkle when the sun shine on them?

The bus stops suddenly and I look out the window. It's our stop. She must have realized this because she pulls her hand away from mine and stands. I follow behind, still reeling." -- Simone Elkeles ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/796-classic---a-book-which-people-praise-and-don-t-read</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 12:43:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/796-classic---a-book-which-people-praise-and-don-t-read]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Classic' - a book which people praise and don't read." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247196-well-sometimes-i-worry-that-my-whole-life-will-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 17:46:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Julia Hoban]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247196-well-sometimes-i-worry-that-my-whole-life-will-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, sometimes I worry that my whole life will be based about what's comfortable and easy. I'll care too much about what makes me feel good to ever really reach for anything. And then I worry that even if I do, I won't succeed." -- Julia Hoban]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220028-every-story-is-part-of-a-whole-entire-life-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 17:47:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Sarah Ockler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220028-every-story-is-part-of-a-whole-entire-life-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every story is part of a whole, entire life, you know? Happy and sad and tragic and whatever, but an entire life. And books let you know them." -- Sarah Ockler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155008-i-realize-now-that-dying-is-easy-living-is-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 09:42:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Gayle Forman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155008-i-realize-now-that-dying-is-easy-living-is-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I realize now that dying is easy. Living is hard." -- Gayle Forman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177359-it-s-okay-he-tells-me-if-you-want-to-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 09:43:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Gayle Forman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177359-it-s-okay-he-tells-me-if-you-want-to-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's okay,' he tells me. 'If you want to go. Everyone wants you to stay. I want you to stay more than I've ever wanted anything in my life.' His voice cracks with emotion. He stops, clears his throat, takes a breath, and continues. 'But that's what I want and I could see why it might not be what you want. So I just wanted to tell you that I understand if you go. It's okay if you have to leave us. It's okay if you want to stop fighting.'

For the first time since I realized that Teddy was gone, too, I feel something unclench. I feel myself breathe. I know that Gramps can't be that late-inning pinch hitter I'd hoped for. He won't unplug my breathing tube or overdoes me with morphine or anything like that. But this is the first time today that anyone has acknowledged what I have lost. I know that the social worker warned Gran and Gramps not to upset me, but Gramps's recognition, and the permission he just offered me--it feels like a gift.

Gramps doesn't leave me. He slumps back into the chair. It's quiet now. So quiet you can almost hear other people's dreams. So quiet that you can almost hear me tell Gramps, 'Thank you." -- Gayle Forman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177362-sometimes-you-make-choices-in-life-and-sometimes-choices-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 09:43:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Gayle Forman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177362-sometimes-you-make-choices-in-life-and-sometimes-choices-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes you make choices in life and sometimes choices make you." -- Gayle Forman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237546-if-you-stay-i-ll-do-whatever-you-want-i-ll-quit</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 09:45:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Gayle Forman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237546-if-you-stay-i-ll-do-whatever-you-want-i-ll-quit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you stay, I'll do whatever you want. I'll quit the band, go with you to New York. But if you need me to go away, I'll do that, too. I was talking to Liz and she said maybe coming back to your old life would be too painful, that maybe it'd be easier for you to erase us. And that would suck, but I'd do it. I can lose you like that if I don't lose you today. I'll let you go. If you stay." -- Gayle Forman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366064-you-don-t-share-me-you-own-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 20:06:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Gayle Forman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366064-you-don-t-share-me-you-own-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t share me. You own me." -- Gayle Forman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367283-you-is-all-i-can-manage-to-choke-out-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 20:15:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Gayle Forman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367283-you-is-all-i-can-manage-to-choke-out-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You?' is all I can manage to choke out.

'Always me,' she replies softly, bashfully. 'Who else?" -- Gayle Forman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367284-and-then-adam-wilde-shows-up-at-carnegie-hall-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 20:20:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Gayle Forman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367284-and-then-adam-wilde-shows-up-at-carnegie-hall-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And then Adam Wilde shows up at Carnegie Hall on the biggest night of my career, and it felt like more than a coincidence. It felt like a gift. From them. For my first recital ever, they gave me a cello. And for this one, they gave me you." -- Gayle Forman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398565-sometimes-there-is-such-beauty-in-awkwardness</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 13:06:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Ruta Sepetys]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398565-sometimes-there-is-such-beauty-in-awkwardness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes there is such beauty in awkwardness." -- Ruta Sepetys]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290322-we-walk-alone-through-this-world-but-if-we-re-lucky</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 15:43:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Paullina Simons]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290322-we-walk-alone-through-this-world-but-if-we-re-lucky]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We walk alone through this world, but if we're lucky, we have a moment of belonging to something, to someone, that sustains us through a lifetime of loneliness." -- Paullina Simons]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/693649-and-what-is-there-to-be-joyful-about-i-asked</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 18:55:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Fisher Amelie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/693649-and-what-is-there-to-be-joyful-about-i-asked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And what is there to be joyful about?&quot;  I asked honestly, thinking on the images of dead children curled into themselves at the village.  Another burst of silent tears streamed down.

&quot;Life, Sophie.  They still live.  They breathe, they love each other, they find joy in the world around them for no other reason than because they are children.  They are resilient.  They will always rise above.  Always.  It is a curious facet of the innocent young." -- Fisher Amelie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/693656-no-one-can-know-sincere-happiness-sophie-without-first-having</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 18:55:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Fisher Amelie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/693656-no-one-can-know-sincere-happiness-sophie-without-first-having]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one can know sincere happiness, Sophie, without first having known sorrow.  One can never appreciate the enormity and rareness of such a fiery bliss without seeing misery, however unfair that may be." -- Fisher Amelie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/694948-vanity-s-a-debilitating-affliction-you-re-so-absorbed-in-yourself-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 18:55:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Fisher Amelie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/694948-vanity-s-a-debilitating-affliction-you-re-so-absorbed-in-yourself-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Vanity's a debilitating affliction. You’re so absorbed in yourself it’s impossible to love anyone other than oneself, leaving you weak without realization of it. It’s quite sad. You’ve no idea what you’re missing either. You will never know real love and your life will pas you by." -- Fisher Amelie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155757-i-ve-always-envied-people-who-sleep-easily-their-brains-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 19:00:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by David Benioff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155757-i-ve-always-envied-people-who-sleep-easily-their-brains-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've always envied people who sleep easily. Their brains must be cleaner, the floorboards of the skull well swept, all the little monsters closed up in a steamer trunk at the foot of the bed." -- David Benioff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158016-talent-must-be-a-fanatical-mistress-she-s-beautiful-when-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 19:01:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by David Benioff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158016-talent-must-be-a-fanatical-mistress-she-s-beautiful-when-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Talent must be a fanatical mistress. She's beautiful; when you're with her, people watch you, they notice. But she bangs on your door at odd hours, and she disappears for long stretches, and she has no patience for the rest of your existence; your wife, your children, your friends. She is the most thrilling evening of your week, but some day she will leave you for good. One night, after she's been gone for years, you will see her on the arm of a younger man, and she will pretend not to recognize you." -- David Benioff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169813-there-are-a-few-moments-in-your-life-when-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 19:01:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by David Benioff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169813-there-are-a-few-moments-in-your-life-when-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are a few moments in your life when you are truly and completely happy, and you remember to give thanks. Even as it happens you are nostalgic for the moment, you are tucking it away in your scrapbook." -- David Benioff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204518-truth-might-be-stranger-than-fiction-but-it-needs-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 19:01:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by David Benioff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204518-truth-might-be-stranger-than-fiction-but-it-needs-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Truth might be stranger than fiction, but it needs a better editor. " -- David Benioff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/628423-people-like-to-say-love-is-unconditional-but-it-s-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 19:01:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Katja Millay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/628423-people-like-to-say-love-is-unconditional-but-it-s-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People like to say love is unconditional, but it's not, and even if it was unconditional, it's still never free. There's always an expectation attached. They always want something in return. Like they want you to be happy or whatever and that makes you automatically responsible for their happiness because they won't be happy unless you are ... I just don't want that responsibility." -- Katja Millay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/628629-daylight-won-t-protect-you-from-anything-bad-things-happen-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 19:01:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Katja Millay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/628629-daylight-won-t-protect-you-from-anything-bad-things-happen-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Daylight won’t protect you from anything.  Bad things happen all the time; they don’t wait until after dinner" -- Katja Millay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/633294-there-are-so-many-things-that-can-break-you-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 19:01:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Katja Millay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/633294-there-are-so-many-things-that-can-break-you-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are so many things that can break you if there's nothing to hold you together." -- Katja Millay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/639430-i-know-at-that-moment-what-he-s-given-me-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 19:01:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Katja Millay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/639430-i-know-at-that-moment-what-he-s-given-me-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know at that moment what he's given me and it isn't a chair.  It's an invitation, a welcome, the knowledge that I am accepted here.  He hasn't given me a place to sit.  He's given me a place to belong." -- Katja Millay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/634737-i-live-in-a-world-without-magic-or-miracles-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 19:01:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edna Lyn add a quote by Katja Millay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/634737-i-live-in-a-world-without-magic-or-miracles-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I live in a world without magic or miracles. A place where there are no clairvoyants or shapeshifters, no angels or superhuman boys to save you. A place where people die and music disintegrates and things suck." -- Katja Millay]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
