<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/272905-yuval]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/272905-yuval" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 09:40:17 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211851-only-in-chaos-are-we-conceivable</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 09:40:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yuval add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211851-only-in-chaos-are-we-conceivable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only in chaos are we conceivable." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7147-you-must-have-chaos-within-you-to-give-birth-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 06:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yuval add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7147-you-must-have-chaos-within-you-to-give-birth-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must have chaos within you to give birth to a dancing star." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41372-did-it-matter-then-she-asked-herself-walking-towards-bond</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 20:54:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yuval add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41372-did-it-matter-then-she-asked-herself-walking-towards-bond]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did it matter then, she asked herself, walking towards Bond Street, did it matter that she must inevitably cease completely? All this must go on without her; did she resent it; or did it not become consoling to believe that death ended absolutely?" -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53773-the-inferno-of-the-living-is-not-something-that-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 09:41:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yuval add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53773-the-inferno-of-the-living-is-not-something-that-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The inferno of the living is not something that will be; if there is one, it is what is already here, the inferno where we live every day, that we form by being together. There are two ways to escape suffering it. The first is easy for many: accept the inferno and become such a part of it that you can no longer see it. The second is risky and demands constant vigilance and apprehension: seek and learn to recognize who and what, in the midst of inferno, are not inferno, then make them endure, give them space." -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87968-we-are-continually-overflowing-toward-those-who-preceded-us-toward</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 09:41:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yuval add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87968-we-are-continually-overflowing-toward-those-who-preceded-us-toward]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["we are continually overflowing toward those who preceded us, toward our origin, and toward those who seemingly come after us. ... It is our task to imprint this temporary, perishable earth into ourselves so deeply, so painfully and passionately, that its essence can rise again “invisibly,” inside us. We are the bees of the invisible. We wildly collect the honey of the visible, to store it in the great golden hive of the invisible." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47143-all-artforms-are-in-the-service-of-the-greatest-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 09:41:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yuval add a quote by Bertolt Brecht]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47143-all-artforms-are-in-the-service-of-the-greatest-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All artforms are in the service of the greatest of all arts: the art of living." -- Bertolt Brecht]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16462-i-leave-sisyphus-at-the-foot-of-the-mountain-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 09:41:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yuval add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16462-i-leave-sisyphus-at-the-foot-of-the-mountain-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I leave Sisyphus at the foot of the mountain. One always finds one's burden again. But Sisyphus teaches the higher fidelity that negates the gods and raises rocks. He too concludes that all is well. This universe henceforth without a master seems to him neither sterile nor futile. Each atom of that stone, each mineral flake of that night-filled mountain, in itself, forms a world. The struggle itself toward the heights is enough to fill a man's heart. One must imagine Sisyphus happy." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44499-i-should-like-to-know-which-is-worse-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 09:41:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yuval add a quote by Voltaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44499-i-should-like-to-know-which-is-worse-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I should like to know which is worse: to be ravished a hundred times by pirates, and have a buttock cut off, and run the gauntlet of the Bulgarians, and be flogged and hanged in an auto-da-fe, and be dissected, and have to row in a galley -- in short, to undergo all the miseries we have each of us suffered -- or simply to sit here and do nothing?'
That is a hard question,' said Candide." -- Voltaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102629-the-only-true-voyage-the-only-bath-in-the-fountain</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 09:40:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yuval add a quote by Proust, Marcel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102629-the-only-true-voyage-the-only-bath-in-the-fountain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only true voyage, the only bath in the Fountain of Youth, would be not to visit strange lands but to possess other eyes, to see the universe through the eyes of another, of a hundred others, to see the hundred universes that each of them sees, that each of them is; and this we do [with great artists]; with artists like these we do really fly from star to star. " -- Proust, Marcel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69159-work-is-love-made-visible-and-if-you-can-t-work</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 09:39:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yuval add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69159-work-is-love-made-visible-and-if-you-can-t-work]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Work is love made visible. And if you can't work with love, but only with distaste, it is better that you should leave your work and sit at the gate of the temple and take alms of the people who work with joy" -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207439-what-is-the-purpose-of-writing-music-one-is-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 09:39:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yuval add a quote by John Cage]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207439-what-is-the-purpose-of-writing-music-one-is-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is the purpose of writing music? One is, of course, not dealing with purposes but dealing with sounds. Or the answer must take the form of a paradox: a purposeful purposeless or a purposeless play. This play, however, is an affirmation of life--not an attempt to bring order out of chaos nor to suggest improvements in creation, but simply a way of waking up to the very life we’re living, which is so excellent once one gets one’s mind and one’s desires out of its way and lets it act of its own accord." -- John Cage]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
