<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/272909-blair]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/272909-blair" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 07:45:28 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214743-an-anxiety-with-no-object-or-purpose-in-the-present</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 07:45:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214743-an-anxiety-with-no-object-or-purpose-in-the-present]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An anxiety with no object or purpose in the present, and in the future nothing but endless sacrifice, by means of which he would attain nothing - that was what his days on earth held in store for him... What good was life to him? What prospects did he have? What did he have to strive for? Was he to live merely in order to exist? But a thousand times before he had been ready to give up his existence for an idea, for a hope, even for an imagining. Existence on its own had never been enough for him; he had always wanted more than that. Perhaps it was merely the strength of his own desires that made him believe he was a person to whom more was allowed than others." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66336-pain-and-suffering-are-always-inevitable-for-a-large-intelligence</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 07:45:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66336-pain-and-suffering-are-always-inevitable-for-a-large-intelligence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pain and suffering are always inevitable for a large intelligence and a deep heart. The really great men must, I think, have great sadness on earth." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167493-being-alone-is-not-the-most-awful-thing-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 07:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Zoë Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167493-being-alone-is-not-the-most-awful-thing-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being alone is &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; the most awful thing in the world. You visit your museums and cultivate your interests and remind yourself how lucky you are not to be one of those spindly Sudanese children with flies beading their mouths. You make out To Do lists - reorganise linen cupboard, learn two sonnets. You dole out little treats to yourself - slices of ice-cream cake, concerts at Wigmore Hall. And then, every once in a while, you wake up and gaze out of the window at another bloody daybreak, and think, &lt;i&gt;I cannot do this anymore. I cannot pull myself together again and spend the next fifteen hours of wakefulness fending off the fact of my own misery&lt;/i&gt;.

People like Sheba think that they know what it's like to be lonely. They cast their minds back to the time they broke up with a boyfriend in 1975 and endured a whole month before meeting someone new. Or the week they spent in a Bavarian steel town when they were fifteen years old, visiting their greasy-haired German pen pal and discovering that her hand-writing was the best thing about her. But about the drip drip of long-haul, no-end-in-sight solitude, they know nothing. They don't know what it is to construct an entire weekend around a visit to the laundrette. Or to sit in a darkened flat on Halloween night, because you can't bear to expose your bleak evening to a crowd of jeering trick-or-treaters. Or to have the librarian smile pityingly and say, ‘Goodness, you're a quick reader!’ when you bring back seven books, read from cover to cover, a week after taking them out. They don't know what it is to be so chronically untouched that the accidental brush of a bus conductor's hand on your shoulder sends a jolt of longing straight to your groin. I have sat on park benches and trains and schoolroom chairs, feeling the great store of unused, objectless love sitting in my belly like a stone until I was sure I would cry out and fall, flailing, to the ground. About all of this, Sheba and her like have no clue." -- Zoë Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427495-he-was-someone-who-had-to-live-alone-someone-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 04:36:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by John Burnside]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427495-he-was-someone-who-had-to-live-alone-someone-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was someone who &lt;I&gt;had&lt;/i&gt; to live alone, someone who found it difficult to be with others for any length of time, because he only had one mode - that discreet art of withdrawal which had, no doubt, taken him years to perfect. He had no other strategies for getting along with people and, though his colleagues probably saw this as the mark of a gentle, erudite, considerate soul, I was suddenly able to see right through it. Not because I was so very perceptive, but because I was so like him. He had been living in that one mode for so long, he had almost forgotten about it, but I was a near-beginner, and for me it was painfully obvious." -- John Burnside]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484472-i-knew-that-to-find-and-to-feel-yoav-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 05:52:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484472-i-knew-that-to-find-and-to-feel-yoav-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I knew that to find and to feel Yoav again would be terribly painful, because of what had become of him, and because of what I knew he could ignite in me, a vitality that was excruciating because like a flare it lit up the emptiness inside me and exposed what I always secretly knew about myself: how much time I’d spent being only partly alive, and how easily I’d accepted a lesser life." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204283-i-performed-the-part-of-an-odd-quiet-woman-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 04:36:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Margaret Cezair-Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204283-i-performed-the-part-of-an-odd-quiet-woman-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I performed the part of an odd, quiet woman, and performed it to everyone's satisfaction. When others slept, I was awake; when they woke, they found me quietly occupied. I took walks by myself. I read and sewed or sat in the garden with my own self for company. I was not missed. I have never been missed. I had all the manners and necessities of other women of my society, yet I was without society.

... I simply surrendered to that brute unhappiness which had always been close at hand. I no longer made the effort to appear civil, for by then I loathed civilisation from the bottom of my heart. Solitude, after a while, becomes the worst kind of savagery." -- Margaret Cezair-Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381062-even-if-i-did-speak-irish-i-d-always-be-considered</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 04:36:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Brian Friel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381062-even-if-i-did-speak-irish-i-d-always-be-considered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even if I did speak Irish, I’d always be considered an outsider here, wouldn’t I? I may learn the password but the language of the tribe will always elude me, won’t it? The private core will always be ...hermetic, won’t it?" -- Brian Friel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/490056-like-most-music-that-affects-me-deeply-i-would-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 16:00:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/490056-like-most-music-that-affects-me-deeply-i-would-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like most music that affects me deeply, I would never listen to it while others were around, just as I would not pass on a book that I especially loved to another. I am embarrassed to admit this, knowing that it reveals some essential lack or selfishness in my nature, and aware that it runs contrary to the instincts of most, whose passion for something leads them to want to share it, to ignite a similar passion in others, and that without the benefit of such enthusiasm I would still be ignorant of many of the books and much of the music I love most... But rather than an expansion, I've always felt a diminishment of my own pleasure when I've invited someone else to take part in it, a rupture in the intimacy I felt with the work, an invasion of privacy. It is worst when someone else picks up the copy of a book I've just been enthralled by and begins casually to thumb through the pages." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161212-mister-teatime-had-a-truly-brilliant-mind-but-it-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 16:00:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161212-mister-teatime-had-a-truly-brilliant-mind-but-it-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mister Teatime had a truly brilliant mind, but it was brilliant like a fractured mirror, all marvellous facets and rainbows but, ultimately, also something that was broken." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232951-yesterday-when-we-were-packing-julius-asked-me-if-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 16:00:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Anne Fine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232951-yesterday-when-we-were-packing-julius-asked-me-if-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yesterday, when we were packing, Julius asked me,

&quot;If you could rub Tulip out of your past life, would you do it?&quot;

And I had to shake my head. I can't regret the times we had together. Sometimes I worry I won't have times like that again, that there will be no lit nights, no incandescent days. But I know it's not true. There can be colour in a million ways. I know I'll find it on my own." -- Anne Fine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408386-if-you-want-to-know-what-s-in-motherhood-for-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 15:59:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Caitlin Moran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408386-if-you-want-to-know-what-s-in-motherhood-for-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to know what's in motherhood for you, as a woman, then - in truth - it's nothing you couldn't get from, say, reading the 100 greatest books in human history; learning a foreign language well enough to argue in it; climbing hills; loving recklessly; sitting quietly, alone, in the dawn; drinking whisky with revolutionaries; learning to do close-hand magic; swimming in a river in winter; growing foxgloves, peas and roses; calling your mum; singing while you walk; being polite; and always, always helping strangers. No one has ever claimed for a moment that childless men have missed out on a vital aspect of their existence, and were the poorer, and crippled by it." -- Caitlin Moran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227694-whenever-i-tell-people-i-m-a-misanthrope-they-react-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 01:24:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Charlie Brooker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227694-whenever-i-tell-people-i-m-a-misanthrope-they-react-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever I tell people I'm a misanthrope they react as though that's a bad thing, the idiots. I live in London, for God's sake. Have you walked down Oxford Street recently? Misanthropy's the only thing that gets you through it. It's not a personality flaw, it's a skill.

It's nothing to do with sheer numbers. Move me to a remote cottage in the Hebrides and I'd learn to despise the postman, even if he only visited once a year. I can't abide other people, with their stink and their noise and their irritating ringtones. Bill Hicks called the human race 'a virus with shoes', and if you ask me he was being unduly hard on viruses; I'd consider a career in serial killing if the pay wasn't so bad." -- Charlie Brooker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/490055-politics-boring-politics-is-history-on-the-wing-what-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 01:24:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Robert Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/490055-politics-boring-politics-is-history-on-the-wing-what-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Politics? Boring? Politics is history on the wing! What other sphere of human activity calls forth all that is most noble in men's souls, and all that is most base? Or has such excitement? Or more vividly exposes our strengths and weaknesses? Boring? You might as well say that life itself is boring!" -- Robert Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/428040-the-problem-with-the-world-is-that-the-intelligent-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 01:24:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/428040-the-problem-with-the-world-is-that-the-intelligent-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem with the world is that the intelligent people are full of doubts, while the stupid ones are full of confidence." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/490050-alone-in-my-room-wrapped-in-a-blanket-i-whimpered</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 02:10:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/490050-alone-in-my-room-wrapped-in-a-blanket-i-whimpered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alone in my room, wrapped in a blanket, I whimpered and talked aloud to myself, recalling the lost glory of my youth when I considered myself, and was considered by others, a bright and capable person. It seemed that was all gone now." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224787-he-who-does-not-understand-your-silence-will-probably-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 01:24:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224787-he-who-does-not-understand-your-silence-will-probably-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He who does not understand your silence will probably not understand your words." -- Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157357-the-woman-who-follows-the-crowd-will-usually-go-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 01:24:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157357-the-woman-who-follows-the-crowd-will-usually-go-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The woman who follows the crowd will usually go no further than the crowd. The woman who walks alone is likely to find herself in places no one has ever been before." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/448425-and-all-i-loved-i-loved-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 16:05:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Blair add a quote by Edgar Allen Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/448425-and-all-i-loved-i-loved-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And all I loved, I loved alone." -- Edgar Allen Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
