<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/273009-daniel-farias]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/273009-daniel-farias" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:03:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:03:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10722-i-love-you-as-certain-dark-things-are-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:03:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10722-i-love-you-as-certain-dark-things-are-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you as certain dark things are to be loved, 
in secret, between the shadow and the soul." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361858-he-s-not-perfect-you-aren-t-either-and-the-two-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:03:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361858-he-s-not-perfect-you-aren-t-either-and-the-two-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He’s not perfect. You aren’t either, and the two of you will never be perfect. But if he can make you laugh at least once, causes you to think twice, and if he admits to being human and making mistakes, hold onto him and give him the most you can. He isn’t going to quote poetry, he’s not thinking about you every moment, but he will give you a part of him that he knows you could break. Don’t hurt him, don’t change him, and don’t expect for more than he can give. Don’t analyze. Smile when he makes you happy, yell when he makes you mad, and miss him when he’s not there. Love hard when there is love to be had. Because perfect guys don’t exist, but there’s always one guy that is perfect for you." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:08:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know you're in love when you can't fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:08:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:08:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54-don-t-walk-behind-me-i-may-not-lead-don-t-walk</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:08:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54-don-t-walk-behind-me-i-may-not-lead-don-t-walk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't walk behind me; I may not lead. Don't walk in front of me; I may not follow. Just walk beside me and be my friend." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:08:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one can make you feel inferior without your consent." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16949-a-friend-is-someone-who-knows-all-about-you-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:08:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16949-a-friend-is-someone-who-knows-all-about-you-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A friend is someone who knows all about you and still loves you." -- Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:09:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:09:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be yourself in a world that is constantly trying to make you something else is the greatest accomplishment." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48851-i-have-always-essentially-been-waiting-waiting-to-become-something</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 12:25:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Shauna Niequist]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48851-i-have-always-essentially-been-waiting-waiting-to-become-something]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always, essentially, been waiting. Waiting to become something else, waiting to be that person I always thought I was on the verge of becoming, waiting for that life I thought I would have. In my head, I was always one step away. In high school, I was biding my time until I could become the college version of myself, the one my mind could see so clearly. In college, the post-college “adult” person was always looming in front of me, smarter, stronger, more organized. Then the married person, then the person I’d become when we have kids. For twenty years, literally, I have waited to become the thin version of myself, because that’s when life will really begin.
And through all that waiting, here I am. My life is passing, day by day, and I am waiting for it to start. I am waiting for that time, that person, that event when my life will finally begin.
I love movies about “The Big Moment” – the game or the performance or the wedding day or the record deal, the stories that split time with that key event, and everything is reframed, before it and after it, because it has changed everything. I have always wanted this movie-worthy event, something that will change everything and grab me out of this waiting game into the whirlwind in front of me. I cry and cry at these movies, because I am still waiting for my own big moment. I had visions of life as an adventure, a thing to be celebrated and experienced, but all I was doing was going to work and coming home, and that wasn’t what it looked like in the movies.
John Lennon once said, “Life is what happens when you’re busy making other plans.” For me, life is what was happening while I was busy waiting for my big moment. I was ready for it and believed that the rest of my life would fade into the background, and that my big moment would carry me through life like a lifeboat.
The Big Moment, unfortunately, is an urban myth. Some people have them, in a sense, when they win the Heisman or become the next American Idol. But even that football player or that singer is living a life made up of more than that one moment. Life is a collection of a million, billion moments, tiny little moments and choices, like a handful of luminous, glowing pearl. It takes so much time, and so much work, and those beads and moments are so small, and so much less fabulous and dramatic than the movies.
But this is what I’m finding, in glimpses and flashes: this is it. This is it, in the best possible way. That thing I’m waiting for, that adventure, that move-score-worthy experience unfolding gracefully. This is it. Normal, daily life ticking by on our streets and sidewalks, in our houses and apartments, in our beds and at our dinner tables, in our dreams and prayers and fights and secrets – this pedestrian life is the most precious thing any of use will ever experience." -- Shauna Niequist]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464400-to-say-that-one-waits-a-lifetime-for-his-soulmate</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 12:26:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Criss Jami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464400-to-say-that-one-waits-a-lifetime-for-his-soulmate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To say that one waits a lifetime for his soulmate to come around is a paradox. People eventually get sick of waiting, take a chance on someone, and by the art of commitment become soulmates, which takes a lifetime to perfect." -- Criss Jami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/415056-waiting-hurts-forgetting-hurts-but-not-knowing-which-decision-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 12:26:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by José N. Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/415056-waiting-hurts-forgetting-hurts-but-not-knowing-which-decision-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Waiting hurts. Forgetting hurts. But not knowing which decision to take can sometimes be the most painful..." -- José N. Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146171-i-have-noticed-that-the-people-who-are-late-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 12:27:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by E. V. Lucas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146171-i-have-noticed-that-the-people-who-are-late-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have noticed that the people who are late are often so much jollier than the people who have to wait for them." -- E. V. Lucas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208767-we-have-to-heal-our-wounded-world-the-chaos-despair</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 09:15:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Michael  Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208767-we-have-to-heal-our-wounded-world-the-chaos-despair]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have to heal our wounded world. The chaos, despair, and senseless destruction we see today are a result of the alienation that people feel from each other and their environment." -- Michael  Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7125-poetry-heals-the-wounds-inflicted-by-reason</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 09:16:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Novalis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7125-poetry-heals-the-wounds-inflicted-by-reason]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Poetry heals the wounds inflicted by reason." -- Novalis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251459-transformation-is-my-favorite-game-and-in-my-experience-anger</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 09:17:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Jason Mraz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251459-transformation-is-my-favorite-game-and-in-my-experience-anger]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Transformation is my favorite game and in my experience, anger and frustration are the result of you not being authentic somewhere in your life or with someone in your life. Being fake about anything creates a block inside of you. Life can’t work for you if you don’t show up as you." -- Jason Mraz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103315-the-wound-is-the-place-where-the-light-enters-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 09:19:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103315-the-wound-is-the-place-where-the-light-enters-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The wound is the place where the Light enters you." -- Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160951-we-are-all-wounded-but-wounds-are-necessary-for-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 09:20:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Bo Sanchez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160951-we-are-all-wounded-but-wounds-are-necessary-for-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all wounded. But wounds are necessary for his healing light to enter into our beings. Without wounds and failure and frustrations and defeats, there will be no opening for his brilliance to tickle in and invade our lives. Failures in life are courses with very high tuition fees, so I don't cut classes and miss my lessons: on humility, on patience, on hope, on asking others for help, on listening to God, on trying again and again and again." -- Bo Sanchez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97169-god-uses-broken-things-it-takes-broken-soil-to-produce</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 09:20:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Vance Havner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97169-god-uses-broken-things-it-takes-broken-soil-to-produce]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God uses broken things. It takes broken soil to produce a crop, broken clouds to give rain, broken grain to give bread, broken bread to give strength. It is the broken alabaster box that gives forth perfume. It is Peter, weeping bitterly, who returns to greater power than ever." -- Vance Havner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/735181-the-worst-kind-of-brokenness-is-the-kind-that-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 09:20:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Amy Neftzger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/735181-the-worst-kind-of-brokenness-is-the-kind-that-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worst kind of brokenness is the kind that you don’t know you have." -- Amy Neftzger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/703230-until-we-learn-to-love-others-as-ourselves-it-s-difficult</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 09:21:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Richard Rohr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/703230-until-we-learn-to-love-others-as-ourselves-it-s-difficult]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until we learn to love others as ourselves, it's difficult to blame broken people who desperately try to affirm themselves when no one else will." -- Richard Rohr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93331-i-finally-understood-what-true-love-meant-love-meant-that-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 09:20:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93331-i-finally-understood-what-true-love-meant-love-meant-that-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I finally understood what true love meant...love meant that you care for another person's happiness more than your own, no matter how painful the choices you face might be." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208156-sometimes-you-have-to-be-apart-from-people-you-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 09:21:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208156-sometimes-you-have-to-be-apart-from-people-you-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes you have to be apart from people you love, but that doesn't make you love them any less. Sometimes you love them more." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137748-the-best-love-is-the-kind-that-awakens-the-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 09:22:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137748-the-best-love-is-the-kind-that-awakens-the-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best love is the kind that awakens the soul and makes us reach for more, that plants a fire in our hearts and brings peace to our minds. And that's what you've given me. That's what I'd hoped to give you forever" -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181075-my-daddy-said-that-the-first-time-you-fall-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 09:22:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181075-my-daddy-said-that-the-first-time-you-fall-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My daddy said, that the first time you fall in love, it changes you forever and no matter how hard you try, that feeling just never goes away." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100309-if-conversation-was-the-lyrics-laughter-was-the-music-making</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 09:22:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100309-if-conversation-was-the-lyrics-laughter-was-the-music-making]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If conversation was the lyrics, laughter was the music, making time spent together a melody that could be replayed over and over without getting stale." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221732-romance-is-thinking-about-your-significant-other-when-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 09:23:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by nicholas sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221732-romance-is-thinking-about-your-significant-other-when-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Romance is thinking about your significant other, when you are supposed to be thinking about something else." -- nicholas sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
