<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/273054-ryan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/273054-ryan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 13:31:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62430-the-right-to-pursue-happiness-sends-me-and-other-americans</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 13:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Lynne Tillman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62430-the-right-to-pursue-happiness-sends-me-and-other-americans]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The right to pursue happiness sends me and other Americans, even here where we are meant to resist outside temptation, on a hunt for it. If I’m not hungry, I might seek other forms of happiness, or pleasure, which is part of my American birthright, though the most misconceived notion of them or the most difficult to realize; I can pursue several means and ways to be happy, if I am able to forget what makes me habitually sad." -- Lynne Tillman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62432-the-spiritualist-or-the-idealist-believes-in-a-spiritual-essence</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 13:34:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Joseph Dietzgen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62432-the-spiritualist-or-the-idealist-believes-in-a-spiritual-essence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The spiritualist or the idealist believes in a spiritual essence of force; spiritual, that is to say phantomatic, inexplicable. The man of materialist science is an unbeliever. Nowhere does a scientific justification exist either for belief or unbelief. Materialism has the advantage that it is not seeking the transcendental, the essence, the cause, the force behind phenomena nor that beyond matter. But when he misconstrues the distinction between force and matter, when he denies the existence of the whole problem, he merely slips around behind idealism. The materialist asserts the real indivisibility of matter and force and to explain their seperation, gives value solely to &quot;an exterior reason, born of the need for systemisation of our consciousness." -- Joseph Dietzgen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62439-o-gods-if-any-gods-will-listen-i-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 13:41:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Ovid]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62439-o-gods-if-any-gods-will-listen-i-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["O gods, \ If any gods will listen, I deserve \ Punishment surely, I do not refuse it, \ But lest, in living, I offend the living, Offend the dead in death, drive me away \ From either realm, change me somehow, refuse me \ Both life and death!
     -- Myrrha, before being transformed into a tree" -- Ovid]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62441-a-guy-is-on-the-radio-talking-about-the-war</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 13:45:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Noah Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62441-a-guy-is-on-the-radio-talking-about-the-war]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A guy is on the radio talking about the war.
Speculating.
Speculating.
Speculating.
He says in less than two hours, we shall fight to preserve freedom.
Freedom.
America wants to give another country freedom.
That doesn't sound that bad, or does it." -- Noah Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65162-yes-montriveau-went-on-in-an-unsteady-voice-this-catholic</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2008 12:04:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Honoré de Balzac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65162-yes-montriveau-went-on-in-an-unsteady-voice-this-catholic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yes,' Montriveau went on in an unsteady voice, 'this Catholic faith to which you wish to convert me is a lie that men make for themselves; hope is a lie at the expense of the future; pride, a lie between us and our fellows; and pity, and prudence, and terror are cunning lies. And now my happiness is to be one more lying delusion; I am expected to delude myself, to be willing to give gold coin for silver to the end. If you can so easily dispense with my visits; if you confess me neither as your friend nor your love, you do not care for me! And I, poor fool that I am, tell myself this, and know it, and love you!" -- Honoré de Balzac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66411-his-francisco-goya-s-debt-to-the-christianity-of-the-eighteenth</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 06:32:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Andre Malraux]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66411-his-francisco-goya-s-debt-to-the-christianity-of-the-eighteenth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His [Francisco Goya's] debt to the Christianity of the eighteenth century is contained in the idea that politics was just adopting from the Gospels: the conviction that man has a right to justice. Such a statement would seem utterly conceited to a Roman, who would doubtless have looked upon the &lt;i&gt;Disasters&lt;/i&gt; as we look upon photographs of the amphitheatre...But if Goya thought that man has not come onto the earth to be cut to pieces he thought that he must have come here for something. Is it to live in joy and honour? Not only that; it is to come to terms with the world. And the message he never ceased to preach, a message underlined by war, is that man only comes to terms with the world by blinding himself with childishness." -- Andre Malraux]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77717-objectivism-is-the-getting-rid-of-the-lyrical-interference-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 05:06:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Charles Olson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77717-objectivism-is-the-getting-rid-of-the-lyrical-interference-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Objectivism is the getting rid of the lyrical interference of the individual as ego, of the “subject” and his soul, that peculiar presumption by which western man has interposed himself between what he is as a creature of nature (with certain instructions to carry out) and those other creations of nature which we may, with no derogation, call objects. For a man is himself an object, whatever he may take to be his advantages, the more likely to recognize himself as such the greater his advantages, particularly at that moment that he achieves an humilitas sufficient to make him of use. It comes to this: the use of a man, by himself and thus by others, lies in how he conceives his relation to nature, that force to which he owes his somewhat small existence. If he sprawl, he shall find little to sing but himself, and shall sing, nature has such paradoxical ways, by way of artificial forms outside of himself. But if he stays inside himself, if he is contained within his nature as he is participant in the larger force, he will be able to listen, and his hearing through himself will give him secrets objects share. And by an inverse law his shapes will make their own way. It is in this sense that the projective act, which is the artist’s act in the larger field of objects, leads to dimensions larger than the man. For a man’s problems, the moment he takes speech up in all its fullness, is to give his work his seriousness, a seriousness sufficient to cause the thing he makes to try to take its place alongside the things of nature. This is not easy." -- Charles Olson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117961-christ-represents-originally-1-men-before-god-2-god-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 10:56:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Karl Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117961-christ-represents-originally-1-men-before-god-2-god-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Christ represents originally: 1) men before God; 2) God for men; 3) men to man.

Similarly, money represents originally, in accordance with the idea of money: 1) private property for private property; 2) society for private property; 3) private property for society.

But Christ is alienated God and alienated man. God has value only insofar as he represents Christ, and man has value only insofar as he represents Christ. It is the same with money." -- Karl Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117962-creatures-naturally-hate-their-fellow-creatures-and-whenever-their-own-interest</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 11:00:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Giacomo Leopardi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117962-creatures-naturally-hate-their-fellow-creatures-and-whenever-their-own-interest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Creatures naturally hate their fellow-creatures, and whenever their own interest requires it, harm them. We cannot therefore avoid hatred and injuries from men, while to a great extent we can avoid their scorn. This is why there is usually little point in the respect which young people and those new to the world pay to those they come across, not through mean-mindedness or any other form of self-interest, but through a benevolent desire not to provoke enmity and to win hearts. They do not fulfill this desire, and in some ways they harm their own repute, because the person who is so respected comes to have a greater idea of himself, and he who pays the respect a lesser idea of himself. He who does not look to men for usefulness or fame, should not look for love either, since he will not obtain it. If he wants my opinion, he should preserve his own dignity completely, giving to everyone no more than his due. Thus he will be somewhat more hated and persecuted than otherwise, but not often despised." -- Giacomo Leopardi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117963-with-the-plundered-people-transferring-their-energies-into-relaxed-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 11:06:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Peter Weiss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117963-with-the-plundered-people-transferring-their-energies-into-relaxed-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With the plundered people transferring their energies into relaxed and receptive thoughts, degradation and lust for power produced art." -- Peter Weiss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124033-youth-is-in-revolt-but-this-is-only-the-eternal</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 11:15:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by U.N.E.F. Strasbourg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124033-youth-is-in-revolt-but-this-is-only-the-eternal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Youth is in revolt, but this is only the eternal revolt of youth; every generation espouses &quot;good causes,&quot; only to forget them when &quot;the young man begins the serious business of production and is given concrete and real social aims,&quot; After the social scientists come the journalists with their verbal inflation. The revolt is contained by overexposure: we are given it to contemplate so that we shall forget to participate." -- U.N.E.F. Strasbourg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126318-this-usually-happens-in-the-white-collar-classes-these-people-take</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 16:45:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Noah Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126318-this-usually-happens-in-the-white-collar-classes-these-people-take]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["this usually happens in the white-collar classes: These people take to worshipping pointlessness. Examples are Twin Peaks, Christo's artwork, and academic liberal politics. But a strange thing happens; these people view their ultra pointlessness as a way of being like God." -- Noah Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130557-curious-the-prince-continued-after-a-deep-silence-is-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2009 15:31:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Friedrich Schiller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130557-curious-the-prince-continued-after-a-deep-silence-is-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Curious,' the Prince continued, after a deep silence, 'is it possible never to have known something, never to have missed it in its absence -- and a few moments later to live in and for that single experience alone? Can a single moment make a man so different from himself? It would be just as impossible for me to return to the joys and wishes of yesterday morning as it would for me to return to the games of childhood, now that I have seen &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; object, now that &lt;i&gt;her&lt;/i&gt; image dwells here -- and I have this living, overpowering feeling within me: from now on you can love nothing other than &lt;i&gt;her&lt;/i&gt;, and in this world nothing else will ever have any effect on you." -- Friedrich Schiller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147150-freedom-is-the-dream-you-dream-while-putting-thought-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2009 08:21:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Giacomo Leopardi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147150-freedom-is-the-dream-you-dream-while-putting-thought-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Freedom is the dream you dream
While putting thought in chains again --" -- Giacomo Leopardi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161075-i-say-i-can-not-identify-that-thing-which-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2009 12:41:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161075-i-say-i-can-not-identify-that-thing-which-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I say, I can not identify that thing which is called happiness, that thing whose token is a laugh, or a smile, or a silent serenity on the lip. I may have been happy, but it is not in my conscious memory now. Nor do I feel a longing for it, as though I had never had it; my spirit seeks different food from happiness, for I think I have a suspicion of what it is. I have suffered wretchedness, but not because of the absence of happiness, and without praying for happiness. I pray for peace -- for motionlessness -- for the feeling of myself, as of some plant, absorbing life without seeking it, and existing without individual sensation. I feel that there can be no perfect peace in individualness. Therefore, I hope one day to feel myself drank up into the pervading spirit animating all things. I feel I am an exile here. I still go straying." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162848-people-quickly-grow-accustomed-to-being-the-slaves-of-mystery</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 10:17:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Guillaume Apollinaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162848-people-quickly-grow-accustomed-to-being-the-slaves-of-mystery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People quickly grow accustomed to being the slaves of mystery." -- Guillaume Apollinaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173485-the-brevity-of-life-the-failing-of-the-senses-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2009 14:00:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Nicholas Copernicus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173485-the-brevity-of-life-the-failing-of-the-senses-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The brevity of life, the failing of the senses, the numbness of indifference and unprofitable occupations allow us to know very little. And again and again swift oblivion, the thief of knowledge and the enemy of memory, makes a void of the mind, in the course of time, even what we learn we lose." -- Nicholas Copernicus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293553-work-on-good-prose-has-three-steps-a-musical-stage</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 20:12:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Walter Benjamin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293553-work-on-good-prose-has-three-steps-a-musical-stage]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Work on good prose has three steps: a musical stage when it is composed, an architectonic one when it is built, and a textile one when it is woven." -- Walter Benjamin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
