<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/27347-sam]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/27347-sam" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2009 21:09:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135510-knowledge-is-the-harvest-of-attention</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2009 21:09:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sam add a quote by Charles Olson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135510-knowledge-is-the-harvest-of-attention]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Knowledge is the harvest of attention" -- Charles Olson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13522-cultural-analysis-is-intrinsically-incomplete-and-worse-than-that-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2009 21:09:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sam add a quote by Clifford Geertz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13522-cultural-analysis-is-intrinsically-incomplete-and-worse-than-that-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cultural analysis is intrinsically incomplete. And, worse than that, the more deeply it goes the less complete it is." -- Clifford Geertz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119196-sight-isolates-sound-incorporates-whereas-sight-situates-the-observer-outside</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2009 21:12:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sam add a quote by Walter J. Ong]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119196-sight-isolates-sound-incorporates-whereas-sight-situates-the-observer-outside]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sight isolates, sound incorporates. Whereas sight situates the observer outside what he views, at a distance, sound pours into the hearer. Vision dissects, as Merleau-Ponty has observed (1961). Vision comes to a human being from one direction at a time: to look at a room or a landscape, I must move my eyes around from one part to another. When I hear, however, I gather sound simultaneously from every directions at once; I am at the center of my auditory world, which envelopes me, establishing me at a kind of core of sensation and existence... You can immerse yourself in hearing, in sound. There is no way to immerse yourself similarly in sight. 
    By contrast with vision, the dissecting sense, sound is thus a unifying sense. A typical visual ideal is clarity and distinctness, a taking apart. The auditory ideal, by contrast, is harmony, a putting together.
   Interiority and harmony are characteristics of human consciousness. The consciousness of each human person is totally interiorized, known to the person from the inside and inaccessible to any other person directly from the inside. Everyone who says 'I' means something different by it from what every other person means. What is 'I' to me is only 'you' to you...
    In a primary oral culture, where the word has its existence only in sound... the phenomenology of sound enters deeply into human beings' feel for existence, as processed by the spoken word. For the way in which the word is experienced is always momentous in psychic life." -- Walter J. Ong]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63954-a-klee-painting-named-angelus-novus-shows-an-angel-looking</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 20:06:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sam add a quote by Walter Benjamin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63954-a-klee-painting-named-angelus-novus-shows-an-angel-looking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A Klee painting named 'Angelus Novus' shows an angel looking as though he is about to move away from something he is fixedly contemplating. His eyes are staring, his mouth is open, his wings are spread. This is how one pictures the angel of history. His face is turned toward the past. Where we perceive a chain of events, he sees one single catastrophe which keeps piling wreckage upon wreckage and hurls it in front of his feet. The angel would like to stay, awaken the dead, and make whole what has been smashed. But a storm is blowing from Paradise; it has got caught in his wings with such violence that the angel can no longer close them. This storm irresistibly propels him into the future to which his back is turned, while the pile of debris before him grows skyward. This storm is what we call progress." -- Walter Benjamin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177235-the-pure-products-of-america-go-crazy-no-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2009 16:27:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sam add a quote by William Carlos Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177235-the-pure-products-of-america-go-crazy-no-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The pure products of America
go crazy...

...[] No one 
to witness
and adjust, no one to drive the car" -- William Carlos Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
