<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/274891-whitney]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/274891-whitney" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 09:50:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425928-i-envied-women-with-signature-hair-dos-signature-perfumes-signature-sign-offs</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 09:50:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by Emma Forrest]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425928-i-envied-women-with-signature-hair-dos-signature-perfumes-signature-sign-offs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I envied women with signature hair-dos, signature perfumes, signature sign-offs. Novelists who tell Vogue Magazine: “I can’t live without my Smythson notebook, Pomegranate Noir cologne by Jo Malone and Frette sheets”. In the grip of madness, materialism begins to look like an admirable belief system." -- Emma Forrest]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/307083-love-opens-the-doors-into-everything-as-far-as-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 20:32:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by May Sarton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/307083-love-opens-the-doors-into-everything-as-far-as-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love opens the doors into everything, as far as I can see, including and perhaps most of all, the door into one's own secret, and often terrible and frightening, real self." -- May Sarton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10795-don-t-own-so-much-clutter-that-you-will-be-relieved</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 09:50:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10795-don-t-own-so-much-clutter-that-you-will-be-relieved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't own so much clutter that you will be relieved to see your house catch fire." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28585-we-women-have-lived-too-much-with-closure-if-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 20:32:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by Carolyn G. Heilbrun]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28585-we-women-have-lived-too-much-with-closure-if-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We women have lived too much with closure: &quot;If he notices me, if I marry him, if I get into college, if I get this work accepted, if I get this job&quot; -- there always seems to loom the possibility of something being over, settled, sweeping clear the way for contentment. This is the delusion of a passive life. When the hope for closure is abandoned, when there is an end to fantasy, adventure for women will begin." -- Carolyn G. Heilbrun]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311416-in-the-earliest-years-when-you-could-still-drive-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 09:51:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311416-in-the-earliest-years-when-you-could-still-drive-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the earliest years, when you could still drive a Volvo 240 without feeling self-conscious, the collective task in Ramsey Hill was to relearn certain life skills that your own parents had fled to the suburbs specifically to unlearn, like how to interest the local cops in actually doing their job, and how to protect a bike from a highly motivated thief, and when to bother rousting a drunk from your lawn furniture, and how to encourage feral cats to shit in somebody else’s children’s sandbox, and how to determine whether a public school sucked too much to bother trying to fix it." -- Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38844-loneliness-is-the-poverty-of-self-solitude-is-richness-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 20:32:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by May Sarton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38844-loneliness-is-the-poverty-of-self-solitude-is-richness-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Loneliness is the poverty of self; solitude is richness of self." -- May Sarton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218028-i-ve-learned-to-write-the-truth-but-to-do-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 09:50:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by Pat Murphy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218028-i-ve-learned-to-write-the-truth-but-to-do-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned to write the truth. But to do that, I had to figure out what the truth was-and I had to realize that the truth isn't always the same for everyone. I had to realize that my truth may not be the same as your truth." -- Pat Murphy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171501-why-dream-life-is-a-difficult-assignment-we-are-fragile</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 09:50:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by Susan Ariel Rainbow Kennedy (SARK)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171501-why-dream-life-is-a-difficult-assignment-we-are-fragile]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why Dream?

Life is a difficult assignment. We are fragile creatures, expected to function at high rates of speed, and asked to accomplish great and small things each day. These daily activities take enormous amounts of energy. Most things are out of our control. We are surrounded by danger, frustration, grief, and insanity as well as love, hope, ecstasy, and wonder. Being fully human is an exercise in humility, suffering, grace, and great humor. Things and people all around us die, get broken, or are lost. There is no safety or guarantees.

The way to accomplish the assignment of truly living is to engage fully, richly, and deeply in the living of your dreams. We are made to dream and to live those dreams." -- Susan Ariel Rainbow Kennedy (SARK)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24729-there-are-it-seems-two-muses-the-muse-of-inspiration</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 06:38:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24729-there-are-it-seems-two-muses-the-muse-of-inspiration]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are, it seems, two muses: the Muse of Inspiration, who gives us inarticulate visions and desires, and the Muse of Realization, who returns again and again to say &quot;It is yet more difficult than you thought.&quot; This is the muse of form. It may be then that form serves us best when it works as an obstruction, to baffle us and deflect our intended course. It may be that when we no longer know what to do, we have come to our real work and when we no longer know which way to go, we have begun our real journey. The mind that is not baffled is not employed. The impeded stream is the one that sings." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/758-whether-we-and-our-politicians-know-it-or-not-nature</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 06:38:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/758-whether-we-and-our-politicians-know-it-or-not-nature]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whether we and our politicians know it or not, Nature is party to all our deals and decisions, and she has more votes, a longer memory, and a sterner sense of justice than we do." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24671-lovers-must-not-like-usurers-live-for-themselves-alone-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 06:40:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24671-lovers-must-not-like-usurers-live-for-themselves-alone-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lovers must not, like usurers, live for themselves alone. They must finally turn from their gaze at one another back toward the community. If they had only themselves to consider, lovers would not need to marry, but they must think of others and of other things. They say their vows to the community as much as to one another, and the community gathers around them to hear and to wish them well, on their behalf and its own. It gathers around them because it understands how necessary, how joyful, and how fearful this joining is. These lovers, pledging themselves to one another &quot;until death,&quot; are giving themselves away, and they are joined by this as no law or contract could join them. Lovers, then, &quot;die&quot; into their union with one another as a soul &quot;dies&quot; into its union with God. And so here, at the very heart of community life, we find not something to sell as in the public market but this momentous giving. If the community cannot protect this giving, it can protect nothing..." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134218-a-corporation-essentially-is-a-pile-of-money-to-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 06:40:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134218-a-corporation-essentially-is-a-pile-of-money-to-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A corporation, essentially, is a pile of money to which a number of persons have sold their moral allegiance." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169049-do-unto-those-downstream-as-you-would-have-those-upstream</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 06:40:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169049-do-unto-those-downstream-as-you-would-have-those-upstream]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do unto those downstream as you would have those upstream do unto you." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120099-i-dislike-the-thought-that-some-animal-has-been-made</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 06:41:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120099-i-dislike-the-thought-that-some-animal-has-been-made]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I dislike the thought that some animal has been made miserable to feed me.  If I am going to eat meat, I want it to be from an animal that has lived a pleasant, uncrowded life outdoors, on bountiful pasture, with good water nearby and trees for shade." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51717-and-in-some-of-the-people-of-the-town-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 06:42:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Whitney add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51717-and-in-some-of-the-people-of-the-town-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["and in some of the people of the town and community surrounding it, one of the characteristic diseases of the twentieth century was making its way: the suspicion that they would be greatly improved if they were somewhere else." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
