<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/274842-emily]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/274842-emily" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 10:48:12 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329779-childhood-it-was-like-trying-to-chart-an-entire-continent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 10:48:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Edward Docx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329779-childhood-it-was-like-trying-to-chart-an-entire-continent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Childhood: it was like trying to chart an entire continent by the brief flare of a firework. Except that you had no idea that this was your only chance to explore for free, and instead you spent the five seconds of precious light gawping at the sky, stuffing treacle into your mouth. And then it went dark again." -- Edward Docx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329780-the-past-was-not-always-past-enough-here-it-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 10:48:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Michelle de Kretser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329780-the-past-was-not-always-past-enough-here-it-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The past was not always past enough here. It was like living in a house acquired for its clean angles and gleaming appliances, and discovering a bricked-up foor at which, faint but insistent, the sound of knocking could be heard." -- Michelle de Kretser]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329778-male-fantasies-male-fantasies-is-everything-run-by-male-fantasies</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 10:48:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329778-male-fantasies-male-fantasies-is-everything-run-by-male-fantasies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Male fantasies, male fantasies, is everything run by male fantasies? Up on a pedestal or down on your knees, it's all a male fantasy: that you're strong enough to take what they dish out, or else too weak to do anything about it. Even pretending you aren't catering to male fantasies is a male fantasy: pretending you're unseen, pretending you have a life of your own, that you can wash your feet and comb your hair unconscious of the ever-present watcher peering through the keyhole, peering through the keyhole in your own head, if nowhere else. You are a woman with a man inside watching a woman. You are your own voyeur." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329781-she-has-gone-back-to-brooklyn-her-mother-would-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 10:42:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Colm Toibín]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329781-she-has-gone-back-to-brooklyn-her-mother-would-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She has gone back to Brooklyn,' her mother would say. And, as the train rolled past Macmire Bridge on its way towards Wexford, Eilis imagined the years already when these words would come to mean less and less to the man who heard them and would come to mean more and more to herself. She almost smiled at the thought of it, then closed her eyes and tried to imagine nothing more." -- Colm Toibín]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329785-and-as-the-music-ended-he-saw-her-like-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 10:55:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329785-and-as-the-music-ended-he-saw-her-like-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And as the music ended, he saw her, like a woman in a romance, pull from her cotton sleeve a note that she pushed into his breast pocket. It would burn there unread for another hour as he danced and talked with in-laws who did not matter to him, who got in the way, whose bloodline connection to him or his wife he could not care less about. Everything that was important to him existed suddenly in the potency of Marie-Neige. He could tell what the shallow freize of the wedding party that surrounded them would continue to be, and yet the one he knew best-he could not conceive how she would behave or respond to him in a week, or even in an hour. She had stepped into more than his arms for a dance, had waited for the precise seconds so it was possible and socially forgivable-the sunlit wedding procession, the eternal meal-and she had passed him a billet-doux as if they were within a Dumas. The note she had written said 'Good-bye.' Then it said 'Hello.' And then it reminded him that 'A message sent by pigeon to The Hague can sometimes change everything.' She had, like one of those partially villainous and always evolving heroines, turned his heart over on the wrong day." -- Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329791-he-is-thinking-about-asymmetry-this-is-a-world-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 11:11:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Paul Murray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329791-he-is-thinking-about-asymmetry-this-is-a-world-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He is thinking about asymmetry. This is a world, he is thinking, where you can lie in bed, listening to a song as you dream about someone you love, and your feelings and the music will resonate so powerfully and completely that it seems impossible that the beloved, whoever and wherever he or she might be, should not know, should not pick up this signal as it pulsates from your heart, as if you and the music and the love and the whole universe have merged into one force that can be chanelled out into the darkness to bring them this message. But, in actuality, not only will he or she not know, there is nothing to stop that other person from lying on his or her bed at the exact moment listening to the exact same song and thinking about someone else entirely-from aiming those identical feelings in some completely opposite direction, at some totally other person, who may in turn be lying in the dark thinking of another person still, a fourth, who is thinking of a fifth, and so on, and so on, so that rather than a universe of neatly reciprocating pairs, love and love-returned fluttering through space nicely and symmetrically like so many pairs of butterfly wings, instead we get chains of yearning, which sprawl and meander and culminate in an infinite number of dead ends." -- Paul Murray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329792-with-the-engine-stalled-we-would-notice-the-deep-silence</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 11:17:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Orhan Pamuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329792-with-the-engine-stalled-we-would-notice-the-deep-silence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With the engine stalled, we would notice the deep silence reigning in the park around us, in the summer villa before us, in the world everywhere. We would listen enchanted to the whirring of an insect beginning vernal flight before the onset of spring, and we would know what a wondrous thing it was to be alive in a park on a spring day in Istanbul." -- Orhan Pamuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299197-he-went-on-for-some-time-while-i-sat-listening</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 11:23:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299197-he-went-on-for-some-time-while-i-sat-listening]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He went on for some time while I sat listening in silence because I knew he was right, and like two people who have loved each other however imperfectly, who have tried to make a life together, however imperfectly, who have lived side by side and watched the wrinkles slowly form at the corner of the other's eyes, and watched a little drop of gray, as if poured from a jug, drop into the other's skin and spread itself evenly, listening to the other's coughs and sneezes and little collected mumblings, like two people who'd had one idea together and slowly allowed that idea to be replaced with two separate, less hopeful, less ambitious ideas, we spoke deep into the night, and the next day, and the next night. For forty days and forty nights, I want to say, but the fact of the matter is it only took three. One of us had loved the other more perfectly, had watched the other more closely, and one of us listened and the other hadn't, and one of us held on to the ambition of the one idea far longer than was reasonable, whereas the other, passing a garbage can one night, had casually thrown it away." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329795-my-hand-reaches-for-his-eye-he-does-not-pull</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 11:27:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Hilary Thayer Hamann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329795-my-hand-reaches-for-his-eye-he-does-not-pull]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My hand reaches for his eye. He does not pull away but breathes into my touch. His normal lid drifts closed, and beneath my fingertips the distended one throbs, as if the eye below is straining to see. In his heart there is a girl; she is me. No contract keeps her; she goes with him, she goes alone, precipice to precipice, on every ledge agreeing again to leap. She is with him, she has been with him, every minute. No one can know what we know. Just us. If you listen, you can hear it. In the wide sound of the rain-us." -- Hilary Thayer Hamann]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
