<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/275400-laurie-neighbors]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/275400-laurie-neighbors" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 13:57:02 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/950542-that-imperial-guard-which-poets-and-humanists-mount-in-relay</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 13:57:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurie add a quote by Marguerite Yourcenar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/950542-that-imperial-guard-which-poets-and-humanists-mount-in-relay]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...that imperial guard which poets and humanists mount in relay around any great memory." -- Marguerite Yourcenar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218352-freedom-for-the-wolves-has-often-meant-death-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 10:54:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurie add a quote by Isaiah Berlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218352-freedom-for-the-wolves-has-often-meant-death-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Freedom for the wolves has often meant death to the sheep." -- Isaiah Berlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/776778-i-was-really-into-communal-living-and-we-were-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 12:19:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurie add a quote by Michelle Tea]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/776778-i-was-really-into-communal-living-and-we-were-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["i was really into communal living and we were all /
such free spirits, crossing the country we were /
nomads and artists and no one ever stopped / to think about how the one working class housemate / was whoring to support a gang of upper middle class / deadheads with trust fund safety nets and connecticut / childhoods, everyone was too busy processing their isms / to deal with non-issues like class....and it’s just so cool / how none of them have hang-ups about / sex work they’re all real / open-minded real / revolutionary you know / the legal definition of pimp is / one who lives off the earnings of / a prostitute, one or five or / eight and i’d love to stay and / eat some of the stir fry i’ve been cooking / for y’all but i’ve got to go fuck / this guy so we can all get stoned and / go for smoothies tomorrow, save me / some rice, ok?" -- Michelle Tea]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/504958-opening-is-an-essential-feature-of-univocity-the-nomadic-distributions</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 12:21:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurie add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/504958-opening-is-an-essential-feature-of-univocity-the-nomadic-distributions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Opening is an essential feature of univocity. The nomadic distributions or crowned anarchies in the univocal stand opposed to the sedentary distribution of analogy. Only there does the cry resound: ‘Everything is equal!’ and ‘Everything returns!’. However, this ‘Everything is equal!’ and ‘Everything returns!’ can be said only at the point in which the extremity of difference is reached. A single and same voice for the whole thousand-voiced multiple, a single and same Ocean for all the drops, a single clamour of Being for all beings: on the condition that each being, each drop, and each voice has reached the state of excess – in other words, the difference which displaces and disguises them and, in turning upon the mobile cusp, causes them to return." -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/945592-prefer-what-is-positive-and-multiple-difference-over-uniformity-flows</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 12:25:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurie add a quote by Michel Foucault]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/945592-prefer-what-is-positive-and-multiple-difference-over-uniformity-flows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Prefer what is positive and multiple, difference over uniformity, flows over unities, mobile arrangements over systems. Believe that what is productive is not sedentary but nomadic." -- Michel Foucault]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/883227-all-those-summer-drives-no-matter-where-i-was-going</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 12:27:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurie add a quote by Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/883227-all-those-summer-drives-no-matter-where-i-was-going]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All those summer drives, no matter where I was going, to a person, a project, an adventure, or home, alone in the car with my social life all before and behind me, I was suspended in the beautiful solitude of the open road, in a kind of introspection that only outdoor space generates, for inside and outside are more intertwined than the usual distinctions allow. The emotion stirred by the landscape is piercing, a joy close to pain when the blue is deepest on the horizon or the clouds are doing those spectacular fleeting things so much easier to recall than to describe. Sometimes I thought of my apartment in San Francisco as only a winter camp and home as the whole circuit around the West I travel a few times a year and myself as something of a nomad (nomads, contrary to current popular imagination, have fixed circuits and stable relationships to places; they are far from beign the drifters and dharma bums that the word nomad often connotes nowadays). This meant that it was all home, and certainly the intense emotion that, for example, the sequence of mesas alongside the highway for perhaps fifty miles west of Gallup, N.M., and a hundred miles east has the power even as I write to move me deeply, as do dozens of other places, and I have come to long not to see new places but to return and know the old ones more deeply, to see them again. But if this was home, then I was both possessor of an enchanted vastness and profoundly alienated." -- Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497724-leave-the-door-open-for-the-unknown-the-door-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 12:28:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurie add a quote by Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497724-leave-the-door-open-for-the-unknown-the-door-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Leave the door open for the unknown, the door into the dark. That’s where the most important things come from, where you yourself came from, and where you will go." -- Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541073-the-art-is-not-one-of-forgetting-but-letting-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 12:28:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurie add a quote by Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541073-the-art-is-not-one-of-forgetting-but-letting-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The art is not one of forgetting but letting go. And when everything else is gone, you can be rich in loss." -- Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/545950-getting-lost-was-not-a-matter-of-geography-so-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 12:29:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurie add a quote by Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/545950-getting-lost-was-not-a-matter-of-geography-so-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Getting lost was not a matter of geography so much as identity, a passionate desire, even an urgent need, to become no one and anyone, to shake off the shackles that remind you who you are, who others think you are." -- Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/794059-solitude-in-the-city-is-about-the-lack-of-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 12:30:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurie add a quote by Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/794059-solitude-in-the-city-is-about-the-lack-of-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Solitude in the city is about the lack of other people or rather their distance beyond a door or wall, but in remote places it isn’t an absence but the presence of something else, a kind of humming silence in which solitude seems as natural to your species as to any other, words strange rocks you may or may not turn over." -- Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/883225-there-are-fossils-of-seashells-high-in-the-himalayas-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 12:32:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurie add a quote by Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/883225-there-are-fossils-of-seashells-high-in-the-himalayas-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are fossils of seashells high in the Himalayas; what was and what is are different things." -- Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
