<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/275577-krystle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/275577-krystle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 11:10:32 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16454-you-re-going-to-come-across-people-in-your-life-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 11:10:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16454-you-re-going-to-come-across-people-in-your-life-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're going to come across people in your life who will say all the right words at all the right times. But in the end, it's always their actions you should judge them by. It's actions, not words, that matter." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7040-a-good-friend-will-always-stab-you-in-the-front</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 11:11:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7040-a-good-friend-will-always-stab-you-in-the-front]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A good friend will always stab you in the front." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13641-imagine-yourself-as-a-living-house-god-comes-in-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 11:12:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13641-imagine-yourself-as-a-living-house-god-comes-in-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine yourself as a living house. God comes in to rebuild that house. At first, perhaps, you can understand what He is doing. He is getting the drains right and stopping the leaks in the roof and so on; you knew that those jobs needed doing and so you are not surprised. But presently He starts knocking the house about in a way that hurts abominably and does not seem to make any sense. What on earth is He up to? The explanation is that He is building quite a different house from the one you thought of - throwing out a new wing here, putting on an extra floor there, running up towers, making courtyards. You thought you were being made into a decent little cottage: but He is building a palace. He intends to come and live in it Himself." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26110-you-wouldn-t-worry-so-much-about-what-others-think-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 11:13:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26110-you-wouldn-t-worry-so-much-about-what-others-think-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You wouldn't worry so much about what others think of you if you realized how seldom they do." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7139-do-not-let-your-fire-go-out-spark-by-irreplaceable</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 11:13:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7139-do-not-let-your-fire-go-out-spark-by-irreplaceable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not let your fire go out, spark by irreplaceable spark in the hopeless swamps of the not-quite, the not-yet, and the not-at-all. Do not let the hero in your soul perish in lonely frustration for the life you deserved and have never been able to reach. The world you desire can be won. It exists.. it is real.. it is possible.. it's yours." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6463-i-ve-learned-that-you-can-tell-a-lot-about-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 11:15:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6463-i-ve-learned-that-you-can-tell-a-lot-about-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that you can tell a lot about a person by the way (s)he handles these three things: a rainy day, lost luggage, and tangled Christmas tree lights." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27292-i-love-sleep-my-life-has-the-tendency-to-fall</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 11:17:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27292-i-love-sleep-my-life-has-the-tendency-to-fall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love sleep. My life has the tendency to fall apart when I'm awake, you know?" -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97759-i-knew-in-the-silence-that-followed-that-anything-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 11:24:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97759-i-knew-in-the-silence-that-followed-that-anything-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I knew, in the silence that followed, that anything could happen here. It might be too late: again, I might have missed my chance. But I would at least know I tried, that I took my heart and extended my hand, whatever the outcome.
&quot;Okay,&quot; he said. He took a breath. &quot;What would you do, if you could do anything?&quot;
I took a step toward him, closing the space between us. &quot;This,&quot; I said. And then I kissed him." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125322-that-was-the-thing-you-never-got-used-to-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 11:25:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125322-that-was-the-thing-you-never-got-used-to-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That was the thing. You never got used to it, the idea of someone being gone. Just when you think it's reconciled, accepted, someone points it out to you, and it just hits you all over again, that shocking." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111431-but-i-d-long-ago-learned-not-to-be-picky-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 11:37:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111431-but-i-d-long-ago-learned-not-to-be-picky-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I'd long ago learned not to be picky in farewells. They weren't guaranteed or promised. 
You were lucky, more than blessed, if you got a good-bye at all." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67443-what-i-want-is-to-be-needed-what-i-need</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 11:57:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67443-what-i-want-is-to-be-needed-what-i-need]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I want is to be needed. What I need is to be indispensable to somebody. Who I need is somebody that will eat up all my free time, my ego, my attention. Somebody addicted to me. A mutual addiction." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171785-you-couldn-t-just-pick-and-choose-at-will-when-someone</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 12:11:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171785-you-couldn-t-just-pick-and-choose-at-will-when-someone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You couldn't just pick and choose at will when someone depended on you, or loved you. It wasn't like a light switch, easy to turn on or off. If you were in, you were in. Out, you were out." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175760-he-was-not-my-boyfriend-on-the-other-hand-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 12:13:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175760-he-was-not-my-boyfriend-on-the-other-hand-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was not my boyfriend. On the other hand, he wasn't just a friend either. Instead, our relationship was elastic, stretching between those two extremes depending on who else was around, how much either of us had to drink, and other varying factors. This was exactly what I wanted, as commitments had never really been my thing. And it wasn't like it was hard, either. The only trick was never giving more than you were willing to lose." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205021-i-was-not-weak-i-did-not-cry-but-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 12:22:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Alysha Speer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205021-i-was-not-weak-i-did-not-cry-but-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was not weak; I did not cry.  But it hurt me, more in a kind of refreshing, thrilling way, than a kind of pain that would cripple me and send me away crying.  My fingernails dug into the palms of my hands, and my teeth bit into my lips, my knees were locked, but I could not faint." -- Alysha Speer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6130-a-woman-should-have-enough-money-within-her-control</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 12:26:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Pamela Redmond Satran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6130-a-woman-should-have-enough-money-within-her-control]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  enough money within her control to move out
  and rent a place of her own even if she never wants
  to or needs to...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  something perfect to wear if the employer or date of her
  dreams wants to see her in an hour...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ...
  a youth she's content to leave behind....
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a past juicy enough that she's looking forward to
  retelling it in her old age....
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE .....
  a set of screwdrivers, a cordless drill, and a black
  lace bra...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  one friend who always makes her laugh... and one who
  lets her cry...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a good piece of furniture not previously owned by anyone
  else in her family...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  eight matching plates, wine glasses with stems, and a
  recipe for a meal that will make her guests feel honored...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a feeling of control over her destiny...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  how to fall in love without losing herself..
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  HOW TO QUIT A JOB,
  BREAK UP WITH A LOVER,
  AND CONFRONT A FRIEND WITHOUT RUINING THE FRIENDSHIP...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  when to try harder... and WHEN TO WALK AWAY...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  that she can't change the length of her calves,
  the width of her hips, or the nature of her parents..
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  that her childhood may not have been perfect...but it's over...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  what she would and wouldn't do for love or more...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  how to live alone... even if she doesn't like it...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  whom she can trust,
  whom she can't,
  and why she shouldn't
  take it personally...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  where to go...
  be it to her best friend's kitchen table...
  or a charming inn in the woods...
  when her soul needs soothing...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  what she can and can't accomplish in a day...
  a month...and a year..." -- Pamela Redmond Satran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14471-many-people-need-desperately-to-receive-this-message-i-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 12:27:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14471-many-people-need-desperately-to-receive-this-message-i-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many people need desperately to receive this message: 'I feel and think much as you do, care about many of the things you care about, although most people do not care about them. You are not alone." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150710-in-time-the-hurt-began-to-fade-and-it-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 12:33:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150710-in-time-the-hurt-began-to-fade-and-it-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In time, the hurt began to fade and it was easier to just let it go. At least I thought it was. But in every boy I met in the next few years, I found myself looking for you, and when the feelings got too strong, I'd write you another letter. But I never sent them for fear of what I might find. By then, you'd gone on with your life and I didn't want to think about you loving someone else. I wanted to remember us like we were that summer. I didn't ever want to lose that." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181075-my-daddy-said-that-the-first-time-you-fall-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 12:34:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181075-my-daddy-said-that-the-first-time-you-fall-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My daddy said, that the first time you fall in love, it changes you forever and no matter how hard you try, that feeling just never goes away." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165016-i-lost-you-once-i-think-i-can-do-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 12:36:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165016-i-lost-you-once-i-think-i-can-do-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I lost you once, I think I can do it again." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99661-the-truly-faithless-one-is-the-one-who-makes-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 12:40:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99661-the-truly-faithless-one-is-the-one-who-makes-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truly faithless one is the one who makes love to only a fraction of you. And denies the rest." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350-i-with-a-deeper-instinct-choose-a-man-who-compels</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 12:40:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350-i-with-a-deeper-instinct-choose-a-man-who-compels]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I, with a deeper instinct, choose a man who compels my strength, who makes enormous demands on me, who does not doubt my courage or my toughness, who does not believe me naïve or innocent, who has the courage to treat me like a woman." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119899-i-do-not-want-to-be-the-leader-i-refuse</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 12:41:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119899-i-do-not-want-to-be-the-leader-i-refuse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not want to be the leader. I refuse to be the leader. I want to live darkly and richly in my femaleness. I want a man lying over me, always over me. His will, his pleasure, his desire, his life, his work, his sexuality the touchstone, the command, my pivot. I don’t mind working, holding my ground intellectually, artistically; but as a woman, oh, God, as a woman I want to be dominated. I don’t mind being told to stand on my own feet, not to cling, be all that I am capable of doing, but I am going to be pursued, fucked, possessed by the will of a male at his time, his bidding." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139391-he-who-had-done-more-than-any-human-being-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 12:42:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139391-he-who-had-done-more-than-any-human-being-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He, who had done more than any human being to draw her out of the caves of her secret, folded life, now threw her down into deeper recesses of fear and doubt.  The fall was greater than she had ever known, because she had ventured so far into emotion and had abandoned herself to it." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27611-aim-high-but-do-not-aim-so-high-that-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 12:44:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27611-aim-high-but-do-not-aim-so-high-that-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Aim high, but do not aim so high that you totally miss the target. What really matters is that he will love you, that he will respect you, that he will honor you, that he will be absolutely true to you, that he will give you the freedom of expression and let you fly in the development of your own talents. He is not going to be perfect, but if he is kind and thoughtful, if he knows how to work and earn a living, if he is honest and full of faith, the chances are you will not go wrong, that you will be immensely happy." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4798-you-miss-one-hundred-percent-of-the-shots-you-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 12:46:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Wayne Gretzky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4798-you-miss-one-hundred-percent-of-the-shots-you-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You miss one hundred percent of the shots you don't take." -- Wayne Gretzky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103292-dare-i-say-i-miss-him-i-do-i-miss</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 12:49:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103292-dare-i-say-i-miss-him-i-do-i-miss]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dare I say I miss him? I do. I miss him. I still see him in my dreams. They are nightmares mostly, but nightmares tinged with love.

I still cannot understand how he could abandon me so unceremoniously, without any sort of goodbye, without looking back even once. That pain is like an axe that chops at my heart." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29837-the-one-thing-you-can-t-take-away-from-me-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 13:09:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29837-the-one-thing-you-can-t-take-away-from-me-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The one thing you can’t take away from me is the way I choose to respond to what you do to me. The last of one’s freedoms is to choose one’s attitude in any given circumstance." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 13:28:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65817-i-think-if-i-ve-learned-anything-about-friendship-it-s-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 13:28:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Jon Katz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65817-i-think-if-i-ve-learned-anything-about-friendship-it-s-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think if I've learned anything about friendship, it's to hang in, stay connected, fight for them, and let them fight for you. Don't walk away, don't be distracted, don't be too busy or tired, don't take them for granted. Friends are part of the glue that holds life and faith together. Powerful stuff." -- Jon Katz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111423-we-can-t-expect-everybody-to-be-there-for-us-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 13:31:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krystle add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111423-we-can-t-expect-everybody-to-be-there-for-us-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can't expect everybody to be there for us, all at once.  So it's a lucky thing that really, all you need is someone. " -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
