<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/276143-linda]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/276143-linda" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 12:08:03 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6650-if-by-the-quarter-of-the-twentieth-century-godliness-wasn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 12:08:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6650-if-by-the-quarter-of-the-twentieth-century-godliness-wasn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If by the quarter of the twentieth century godliness wasn’t next to something more interesting than cleanliness, it might be time to reevaluate our notions of godliness." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6652-humans-have-evolved-to-their-relatively-high-state-by-retaining</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 12:08:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6652-humans-have-evolved-to-their-relatively-high-state-by-retaining]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humans have evolved to their relatively high state by retaining the immature characteristics of their ancestors. Humans are the most advanced of mammals – although a case could be made for the dolphins – because they seldom grow up. Behavioral traits such as curiosity about the world, flexibility of response, and playfulness are common to practically all young mammals but are usually rapidly lost with the onset of maturity in all but humans. Humanity has advanced, when it has advanced, not because it has been sober, responsible and cautious, but because it has been playful, rebellious, and immature." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 15:10:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the only people for me are the mad ones, the ones who are mad to live, mad to talk, mad to be saved, desirous of everything at the same time, the ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn like fabulous yellow roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4959-you-don-t-have-to-burn-books-to-destroy-a-culture</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 12:11:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4959-you-don-t-have-to-burn-books-to-destroy-a-culture]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't have to burn books to destroy a culture. Just get people to stop reading them." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6653-have-i-said-anything-i-started-out-to-say-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 12:12:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6653-have-i-said-anything-i-started-out-to-say-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have I said anything I started out to say about being good? God, I don’t know. A stranger is shot in the street, you hardly move to help. But if half an hour before, you spent just ten minutes with the fellow and knew a little about him and his family, you might just jump in front of his killer and try to stop it. Really knowing is good. Not knowing, or refusing to know, is bad, or amoral, at least. You can’t act if you don’t know. Acting without knowing takes you right off the cliff." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6654-every-age-every-culture-every-custom-and-tradition-has-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 12:14:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Herman Hese]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6654-every-age-every-culture-every-custom-and-tradition-has-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every age, every culture, every custom and tradition has its own character, its own weakness and its own strength, its beauties and ugliness; accepts certain sufferings as matters of course, puts up patiently with certain evils. Human life is reduced to real suffering, real hell, only when two ages, two cultures and religions overlap. A man of the Classical Age who had to live in medieval times would suffocate miserably just as a savage does in the midst of our civilization. Now there are times when a whole generation is caught in this way between two ages, two modes of life, with the consequence that it loses all power to understand itself and has no standard, no security, no simple acquiescence. Naturally, everyone does not feel this equally strongly. A nature such as Nietzsche’s had to suffer our present ills more than a generation in advance. What he had to go through alone and misunderstood, thousands suffer today." -- Herman Hese]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6655-don-t-go-around-saying-the-world-owes-you-a-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 12:17:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6655-don-t-go-around-saying-the-world-owes-you-a-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don’t go around saying the world owes you a living. The world owes you nothing. It was here first." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6656-it-has-been-said-the-truth-will-make-men-free</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 12:20:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Anton LaVey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6656-it-has-been-said-the-truth-will-make-men-free]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It has been said, 'the truth will make men free.' The truth alone has never made anyone free. It is only doubt which will bring mental emancipation." -- Anton LaVey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32379-a-stranger-is-shot-in-the-street-you-hardly-move</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 09:31:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32379-a-stranger-is-shot-in-the-street-you-hardly-move]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A stranger is shot in the street, you hardly move to help. But if, half an hour before, you spent just ten minutes with the fellow and knew a little about him and his family, you might just jump in front of his killer and try to stop it. Really knowing is good. Not knowing, or refusing to know is bad, or amoral, at least. You can’t act if you don’t know." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
