<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/276512-susan-h]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/276512-susan-h" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 09:55:19 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12109-works-of-art-in-my-opinion-are-the-only-objects</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 09:55:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by E. M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12109-works-of-art-in-my-opinion-are-the-only-objects]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Works of art, in my opinion, are the only objects in the material universe to possess internal order, and that is why, though I don't believe that only art matters, I do believe in Art for Art's sake." -- E. M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110682-if-miss-honeychurch-ever-takes-to-live-as-she-plays</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 09:55:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110682-if-miss-honeychurch-ever-takes-to-live-as-she-plays]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If Miss Honeychurch ever takes to live as she plays, it will be very exciting--both for us and for her." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95217-spoon-feeding-in-the-long-run-teaches-us-nothing-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 09:56:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95217-spoon-feeding-in-the-long-run-teaches-us-nothing-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Spoon feeding in the long run teaches us nothing but the shape of the spoon." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5907-our-imagination-flies----we-are-its-shadow-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 10:08:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5907-our-imagination-flies----we-are-its-shadow-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our imagination flies -- we are its shadow on the earth." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329452-beside-mama-in-my-own-folding-chair-with-my-feet</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 12:16:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Katherine Dunn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329452-beside-mama-in-my-own-folding-chair-with-my-feet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beside Mama, in my own folding chair, with my feet sticking out in front of me, I thought about my own innards.  Just a few months before I'd had no idea whether my reproductive equipment worked. There was no evidence. But that week I had become a full-fledged bleeder and was still absorbed by this first change in myself that I had ever noticed. The click and buzz of my synapses kept making the same connection.  If you can change, you can also end. Death had always been a theory to me.  Now I knew.  The terror hurt good and I nursed it and played it like a loose tooth." -- Katherine Dunn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39240-we-should-write-as-we-dream-we-should-even-try</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 09:01:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Helene Cixous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39240-we-should-write-as-we-dream-we-should-even-try]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We should write as we dream; we should even try and write, we should all do it for ourselves, it’s very healthy, because it’s the only place where we never lie. At night we don’t lie. Now if we think that our whole lives are built on lying-they are strange buildings-we should try and write as our dreams teach us; shamelessly, fearlessly, and by facing what is inside very human being-sheer violence, disgust, terror, shit, invention, poetry. In our dreams we are criminals; we kill, and we kill with a lot of enjoyment. But we are also the happiest people on earth; we make love as we never make love in life." -- Helene Cixous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120433-in-his-youth-he-had-believed-everything-was-possible-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 17:36:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Glen David Gold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120433-in-his-youth-he-had-believed-everything-was-possible-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In his youth, [he] had believed everything was possible.  Then in grief, he believed everything was impossible.  And now. . . he felt that when you had lived enough of your life, there was no difference between the two." -- Glen David Gold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361392-there-were-never-moments-in-your-life-when-you-actually</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 17:36:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Glen David Gold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361392-there-were-never-moments-in-your-life-when-you-actually]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There were never moments in your life when you actually saw something end, for whether you knew it or not something else was always flowering. Never a disappearance, always a transformation." -- Glen David Gold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42591-for-me-forgiveness-and-compassion-are-always-linked-how-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2012 08:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42591-for-me-forgiveness-and-compassion-are-always-linked-how-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For me, forgiveness and compassion are always linked: how do we hold people accountable for wrongdoing and yet at the same time remain in touch with their humanity enough to believe in their capacity to be transformed?" -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229213-he-said-with-sort-of-a-little-derisive-smile-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2012 10:22:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Nelson Algren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229213-he-said-with-sort-of-a-little-derisive-smile-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...he said, with sort of a little derisive smile, &quot;How can you walk down the street with all this stuff going on inside you?&quot; I said, &quot;I don't know how you can walk down the street with nothing going on inside you." -- Nelson Algren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139712-there-is-a-story-of-a-woman-running-away-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 09:26:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139712-there-is-a-story-of-a-woman-running-away-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a story of a woman running away from tigers. She runs and runs and the tigers are getting closer and closer. When she comes to the edge of a cliff, she sees some vines there, so she climbs down and holds on to the vines. Looking down, she sees that there are tigers below her as well. She then notices that a mouse is gnawing away at the vine to which she is clinging. She also sees a beautiful little bunch of strawberries close to her, growing out of a clump of grass. She looks up and she looks down. She looks at the mouse. Then she just takes a strawberry, puts it in her mouth, and enjoys it thoroughly. Tigers above, tigers below. This is actually the predicament that we are always in, in terms of our birth and death. Each moment is just what it is. It might be the only moment of our life; it might be the only strawberry we’ll ever eat. We could get depressed about it, or we could finally appreciate it and delight in the preciousness of every single moment of our life." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61787-i-would-always-rather-be-happy-than-dignified</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2013 12:51:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61787-i-would-always-rather-be-happy-than-dignified]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would always rather be happy than dignified." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/580418-so-successfully-have-we-disguised-from-ourselves-the-intensity-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 21:57:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Tennessee Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/580418-so-successfully-have-we-disguised-from-ourselves-the-intensity-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So successfully have we disguised from ourselves the intensity of our own feelings, the sensibility of our own hearts, that plays in the tragic tradition have begun to seem untrue. For a couple of hours we may surrender ourselves to a world of fiercely illuminated values in conflict, but when the stage is covered and the auditorium lighted, almost immediately there is a recoil of disbelief. &quot;Well, well!&quot; we say as we shuffle back up the aisle, while the play dwindles behind us with the sudden perspective of an early Chirico painting. By the time we have arrived at Sardi's, if not as soon as we pass beneath the marquee, we have convinced ourselves once more that life has as little resemblance to the curiously stirring and meaningful occurrences on the stage as a jingle has to an elegy of Rilke." -- Tennessee Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/580420-the-great-and-only-possible-dignity-of-man-lies-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 21:57:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Susan add a quote by Tennessee Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/580420-the-great-and-only-possible-dignity-of-man-lies-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The great and only possible dignity of man lies in his power deliberately to choose certain moral values by which to live as steadfastly as if he, too, like a character in a play, were immured against the corrupting rush of time. Snatching the eternal out of the desperately fleeting is the great magic trick of human existence. As far as we know, as far as there exists any kind of empiric evidence, there is no way to beat the beat the game of &lt;i&gt;being&lt;/i&gt; against &lt;i&gt;non-being&lt;/i&gt;, in which non-being is the predestined victor on realistic levels." -- Tennessee Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
