<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/276781-amy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/276781-amy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 21:32:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93471-we-know-that-god-is-everywhere-but-certainly-we-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 21:32:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93471-we-know-that-god-is-everywhere-but-certainly-we-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We know that God is everywhere; but certainly we feel His presence most when His works are on the grandest scale spread before us; and it is in the unclouded night-sky, where His worlds wheel their silent course, that we read clearest His infinitude, His omnipotence, His omnipresence." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26219-fantasy-is-escapist-and-that-is-its-glory-if-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 20:10:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26219-fantasy-is-escapist-and-that-is-its-glory-if-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fantasy is escapist, and that is its glory. If a soldier is imprisioned by the enemy, don't we consider it his duty to escape?. . .If we value the freedom of mind and soul, if we're partisans of liberty, then it's our plain duty to escape, and to take as many people with us as we can!" -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224102-mom-says-each-of-us-has-a-veil-between-ourselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 13:45:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Rebecca Stead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224102-mom-says-each-of-us-has-a-veil-between-ourselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mom says each of us has a veil between ourselves and the rest of the world, like a bride wears on her wedding day, except this kind of veil is invisible. We walk around happily with these invisible veils hanging down over our faces. The world is kind of blurry, and we like it that way. But sometimes our veils are pushed away for a few moments, like there's a wind blowing it from our faces. And when the veil lifts, we can see the world as it really is, just for those few seconds before it settles down again. We see all the beauty, and cruelty, and sadness, and love. But mostly we are happy not to. Some people learn to lift the veil themselves. Then they don't have to depend on the wind anymore." -- Rebecca Stead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117433-forget-conventionalisms-forget-what-the-world-thinks-of-you-stepping</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 12:03:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Susan B. Anthony]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117433-forget-conventionalisms-forget-what-the-world-thinks-of-you-stepping]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Forget conventionalisms; forget what the world thinks of you stepping out of your place; think your best thoughts, speak your best words, work your best works, looking to your own conscience for approval." -- Susan B. Anthony]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1027961-she-liked-time-at-the-edges-of-things----the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 12:21:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Nicola Griffith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1027961-she-liked-time-at-the-edges-of-things----the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She liked time at the edges of things -- the edge of the crowd, the edge of the pool, the edge of the wood -- where all must pass but none quite belonged." -- Nicola Griffith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84171-critics-who-treat-adult-as-a-term-of-approval-instead</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 23:04:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84171-critics-who-treat-adult-as-a-term-of-approval-instead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Critics who treat 'adult' as a term of approval, instead of as a merely descriptive term, cannot be adult themselves. To be concerned about being grown up, to admire the grown up because it is grown up, to blush at the suspicion of being childish; these things are the marks of childhood and adolescence. And in childhood and adolescence they are, in moderation, healthy symptoms. Young things ought to want to grow. But to carry on into middle life or even into early manhood this concern about being adult is a mark of really arrested development. When I was ten, I read fairy tales in secret and would have been ashamed if I had been found doing so. Now that I am fifty I read them openly. When I became a man I put away childish things, including the fear of childishness and the desire to be very grown up." -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 23:07:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to write the book that wants to be written. And if the book will be too difficult for grown-ups, then you write it for children." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
