<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/277087-greyor]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/277087-greyor" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 08:41:55 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1683-that-is-not-dead-which-can-eternal-lie-and-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 08:41:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Howard Phillips Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1683-that-is-not-dead-which-can-eternal-lie-and-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That is not dead which can eternal lie,
And with strange aeons even death may die." -- Howard Phillips Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2774-i-can-t-think-of-any-greater-happiness-than-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2007 02:02:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2774-i-can-t-think-of-any-greater-happiness-than-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can’t think of any greater happiness than to be with you all the time, without interruption, endlessly, even though I feel that here in this world there’s no undisturbed place for our love, neither in the village nor anywhere else; and I dream of a grave, deep and narrow, where we could clasp each other in our arms as with clamps, and I would hide my face in you and you would hide your face in me, and nobody would ever see us any more." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2775-when-all-the-other-animals-downcast-looked-upon-the-earth</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2007 02:30:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Publius Ovidius Naso]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2775-when-all-the-other-animals-downcast-looked-upon-the-earth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When all the other animals, downcast looked upon the earth, he [Prometheus] gave a face raised on high to man, and commanded him to see the sky and raise his high eyes to the stars." -- Publius Ovidius Naso]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13813-and-the-night-was-comfortably-warm-as-the-soft-filtered</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2008 21:52:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Hubert Selby Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13813-and-the-night-was-comfortably-warm-as-the-soft-filtered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...and the night was comfortably warm as the soft filtered light continued to push the darkness into the shadows as they held each other and kissed and pushed each others darkness into the corner, believing in each others light, each others dream." -- Hubert Selby Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13814-hunc-igitur-terrorem-animi-tenebrasque-necessest-non-radii-solis-neque</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2008 21:56:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Lucretius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13814-hunc-igitur-terrorem-animi-tenebrasque-necessest-non-radii-solis-neque]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["hunc igitur terrorem animi tenebrasque necessest
non radii solis neque lucida tela diei
discutiant, sed naturae species ratioque.
(1.146ff.)

Therefore it is necessary that neither the rays of the sun nor the shining spears of Day should shatter this terror and darkness of the mind, but the aspect and reason of nature..." -- Lucretius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13816-a-heap-of-broken-images-where-the-sun-beats-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2008 21:59:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13816-a-heap-of-broken-images-where-the-sun-beats-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A heap of broken images, where the sun beats,
And the dead tree gives no shelter, the cricket no relief,
And the dry stone no sound of water. Only
There is shadow under this red rock,
(Come in under the shadow of this red rock),
And I will show you something different from either
Your shadow at morning striding behind you
Or your shadow at evening rising to meet you;
I will show you fear in a handful of dust." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13817-we-had-loved-them-and-that-they-hadn-t-heard-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2008 22:00:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13817-we-had-loved-them-and-that-they-hadn-t-heard-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We had loved them, and that they hadn't heard us calling, still do not hear us... calling them out of those rooms where they went to be alone for all time, alone in suicide, which is deeper than death, and where we will never find the pieces to put them back together." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13820-all-is-forgotten-in-the-stone-halls-of-the-dead</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2008 22:01:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13820-all-is-forgotten-in-the-stone-halls-of-the-dead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All is forgotten in the stone halls of the dead. These are the rooms of ruin where the spiders spin and the great circuits fall quiet, one by one..." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157136-the-witch-approached-it-and-pared-its-edges-with-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 17:07:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Lord Dunsany]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157136-the-witch-approached-it-and-pared-its-edges-with-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The witch approached it and pared its edges with a sword that she drew from her thigh. Then she sat down beside it on the earth and sang to it while it cooled. Not like the runes that enraged the flames was the song she sang to the sword: she whose curses had blasted the fire till it shrivelled big logs of oak crooned now a melody like a wind in summer blowing from wild wood gardens that no man tended, down valleys loved once by children, now lost to them but for dreams, a song of such memories as lurk and hide along the edges of oblivion, now flashing from beautiful years of glimpse of some golden moment, now passing swiftly out of remembrance again, to go back to the shades of oblivion, and leaving on the mind those faintest traces of little shining feet which when dimly perceived by us are called regrets. She sang of old Summer noons in the time of harebells: she sang on that high dark heath a song that seemed so full of mornings and evenings preserved with all their dews by her magical craft from days that had else been lost, that Alveric wondered of each small wandering wing, that her fire had lured from the dusk, if this were the ghost of some day lost to man, called up by the force of her song from times that were fairer." -- Lord Dunsany]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157137-and-the-sword-that-had-visited-earth-from-so-far</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 17:09:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Lord Dunsany]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157137-and-the-sword-that-had-visited-earth-from-so-far]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the sword that had visited Earth from so far away smote like the falling of thunderbolts; and green sparks rose from the armour, and crimson as sword met sword; and thick elvish blood moved slowly, from wide slits, down the cuirass; and Lirazel gazed in awe and wonder and love; and the combatants edged away fighting into the forest; and branches fell on them hacked off by their fight; and the runes in Alveric's far-travelled sword exulted, and roared at the elf-knight; until in the dark of the wood, amongst branches severed from disenchanted trees, with a blow like that of a thunderbolt riving an oak tree, Alveric slew him." -- Lord Dunsany]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157896-and-little-he-knew-of-the-things-that-ink-may</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 17:15:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Lord Dunsany]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157896-and-little-he-knew-of-the-things-that-ink-may]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And little he knew of the things that ink may do, how it can mark a dead man's thought for the wonder of later years, and tell of happening that are gone clean away, and be a voice for us out of the dark of time, and save many a fragile thing from the pounding of heavy ages; or carry to us, over the rolling centuries, even a song from lips long dead on forgotten hills." -- Lord Dunsany]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159490-slitscan-s-audience-is-best-visualized-as-a-vicious-lazy-profoundly</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2009 23:18:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by William Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159490-slitscan-s-audience-is-best-visualized-as-a-vicious-lazy-profoundly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Slitscan's audience] is best visualized as a vicious, lazy, profoundly ignorant, perpetually hungry organism craving the warm god-flesh of the anointed. Personally I like to imagine something the size of a baby hippo, the color of a week-old boiled potato, that lives by itself, in the dark, in a double-wide on the outskirts of Topeka. It's covered with eyes and it sweats constantly. The sweat runs into those eyes and makes them sting. It has no mouth, Laney, no genitals, and can only express its mute extremes of murderous rage and infantile desire by changing the channels on a universal remote. Or by voting in presidential elections." -- William Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417346-but-i-called-as-we-came-near-to-one-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 10:42:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Lord Dunsany]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417346-but-i-called-as-we-came-near-to-one-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I called, as we came near, to one who stood beside the water's edge, asking him what men did in Astahahn and what their merchandise was, and with whom they traded. He said, &quot;Here we have fettered and manacled Time, who would otherwise slay the gods.&quot; I asked him what gods they worshipped in that city, and he said, &quot;All those gods whom Time has not yet slain.&quot; (from &quot;Idle Days on the River Yann&quot;)" -- Lord Dunsany]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419766-she-knows-now-absolutely-hearing-the-white-noise-that-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 23:00:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by William Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419766-she-knows-now-absolutely-hearing-the-white-noise-that-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She knows, now, absolutely, hearing the white noise that is London, that Damien's theory of jet lag is correct: that her mortal soul is leagues behind her, being reeled in on some ghostly umbilical down the vanished wake of the plane that brought her here, hundreds of thousands of feet above the Atlantic. Souls can't move that quickly, and are left behind, and must be awaited, upon arrival, like lost luggage." -- William Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/477292-gold-is-gold-everywhere-fungible-and-indifferent-but-when-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 17:53:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/477292-gold-is-gold-everywhere-fungible-and-indifferent-but-when-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["‎...Gold is gold everywhere, fungible and indifferent. But when a disk of gold is stamped by a coiner with certain pompous words and the picture of a King, it takes on added value -- seigneurage. It has that value only in that people believe that it does -- it is a shared phant'sy." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/514468-by-what-seemed-then-and-still-seems-a-chance-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 08:15:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Arthur Machen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/514468-by-what-seemed-then-and-still-seems-a-chance-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By what seemed then and still seems a chance, the suggestion of a moment’s idle thought followed up upon familiar lines and paths that I had tracked a hundred times already, the great truth burst upon me, and I saw, mapped out in lines of light, a whole world, a sphere unknown; continents and islands, and great oceans in which no ship has sailed (to my belief) since a Man first lifted up his eyes and beheld the sun, and the stars of heaven, and the quiet earth beneath." -- Arthur Machen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521882-for-there-upon-a-bed-of-soft-wool-lay-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2012 21:22:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Arthur Machen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521882-for-there-upon-a-bed-of-soft-wool-lay-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For there upon a bed of soft wool lay the most splendid jewel, a jewel such as Dyson had never dreamed of, and within it shone the blue of far skies, and the green of the sea by the shore, and the red of the ruby, and deep violet rays, and in the middle of all it seemed aflame as if a fountain of fire rose up, and fell, and rose again with sparks like stars for drops." -- Arthur Machen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/534904-the-tower-he-would-come-to-the-dark-tower-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 22:46:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/534904-the-tower-he-would-come-to-the-dark-tower-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Tower. He would come to the Dark Tower and there he would sing their names; there he would sing their names; there he would sing all their names. The sun stained the east a dusky rose, and at last Roland, no longer the last gunslinger but one of the last three, slept and dreamed his angry dreams through which there ran only that one soothing blue thread: There I will sing all their names!" -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/558364-when-i-read-a-novel-that-i-really-like-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 13:22:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/558364-when-i-read-a-novel-that-i-really-like-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I read a novel that I really like, I feel as if I am in direct, personal communication with the author. I feel as if the author and I are on the same wavelength mentally, that we have a lot in common with each other, and that we could have an interesting conversation, or even a friendship, if the circumstances permitted it. When the novel comes to an end, I feel a certain letdown, a loss of contact. It is natural to want to recapture that feeling by reading other works by the same author, or by corresponding with him/her directly." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/564900-eddie-cried-out-but-his-cry-was-lost-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 22:14:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/564900-eddie-cried-out-but-his-cry-was-lost-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Eddie] cried out but his cry was lost in the golden blast of some tremendous horn. It came from the top of the Tower, and seemed to fill the world. As that note of warning held and drew out over the field where he stood, blackness welled from the windows which girdled the Tower. It overspilled them and spread across the sky in flaggy streams which came together and formed a growing blotch of darkness. It did not look like a cloud; it looked like a tumor hanging over the earth. The sky was blotted out. And, he saw, it was not a cloud or a tumor but a shape, some tenebrous, cyclopean shape racing toward the place where he stood." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243641-three-or-four-times-only-in-my-youth-did-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 09:39:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243641-three-or-four-times-only-in-my-youth-did-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Three or four times only in my youth did I glimpse the Joyous Isles, before they were lost to fogs, depressions, cold fronts, ill winds, and contrary tides... I mistook them for adulthood. Assuming they were a fixed feature in my life's voyage, I neglected to record their latitude, their longitude, their approach. Young ruddy fool. What wouldn't I give now for a never-changing map of the ever-constant ineffable? To possess, as it were, an atlas of clouds." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/909340-the-usual-mixture-of-rooms-and-squares-and-streets-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 20:10:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/909340-the-usual-mixture-of-rooms-and-squares-and-streets-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The usual mixture of rooms and squares and streets that is the mark of the Land of the Dead. Streets lead into kitchens and bedrooms, so no area is completely private or completely public." -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/909346-a-writer-s-will-is-the-winds-of-dead-calm-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 20:14:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/909346-a-writer-s-will-is-the-winds-of-dead-calm-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A writer's will is the winds of dead calm in the Western Lands. Point way out he can start stirring of the sail. Writer, where are you going? To write. Here we are in texts already written on the sky. Where he doesn't need to write anymore. A slight seismic with the cat book. Always remember, the work is the mainsail to reach the Western Lands. The texts sing. Everything is grass and bushes, a desert or a maze of texts. Here you are ... never use the same door twice. Sky in all directions ... on the word for word. The word for word is word. The western sail stirs candles on 1920 country club table. Each page is a door to everything is permitted. The fragile lifeboat between this and that. Your words are the sails." -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1159231-in-the-wide-land-under-a-tender-lucid-evening-sky</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 08:48:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greyor add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1159231-in-the-wide-land-under-a-tender-lucid-evening-sky]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the wide land under a tender lucid evening sky, a cloud drifting westward amid a pale green sea of heaven, they stood together, children that had erred." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
