<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/278908-heather]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/278908-heather" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 09:17:45 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111453-after-three-years-down-here-i-ve-not-learned-too-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 09:17:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by N.D. Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111453-after-three-years-down-here-i-ve-not-learned-too-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After three years down here, I've not learned too much. But one thing I do know is that our bellies aren't big enough for revenge. It turns sour and eats you up. We'll get out, but we'll get out for the sun, the moon, and mothers, not for small-souled enemies, though we'll deal with them when we get there." -- N.D. Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111444-stealing-ideas-from-contemporaries-is-rude-and-tasteless-stealing-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 00:12:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by N.D. Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111444-stealing-ideas-from-contemporaries-is-rude-and-tasteless-stealing-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stealing ideas from contemporaries is rude and tasteless. Stealing from the long dead is considered literary and admirable. The same is true of grave-robbing. Loot your local cemetery and find yourself mired in social awkwardness. But unearth the tomb of an ancient king and you can feel free to pop off his toe rings. You'll probably end up on a book tour, or bagging an honorary degree or two." -- N.D. Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164509-give-me-priests-give-me-men-with-feathers-in-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 16:19:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by N.D. Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164509-give-me-priests-give-me-men-with-feathers-in-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Give me priests. Give me men with feathers in their hair, or tall domed hats, female oracles in caves, servants of the python, smoking weed and reading palms. A gypsy fortuneteller with a foot-peddle ouija board and a gold fish bowl for a crystal ball knows more about the world than many of the great thinkers of the West. Mumbling priests swinging stink cans on their chains and even witch doctors conjuring up curses with a well-buried elephant tooth have a better sense of their places in the world. They know this universe is brimming with magic, with life and riddles and ironies. They know that the world might eat them, and no encyclopedia could stop it" -- N.D. Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167441-imagine-a-poem-written-with-such-enormous-three-dimensional-words-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2009 21:12:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by N.D. Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167441-imagine-a-poem-written-with-such-enormous-three-dimensional-words-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine a poem written with such enormous three-dimensional words that we had to invent a smaller word to reference each of the big ones; that we had to rewrite the whole thing in shorthand, smashing it into two dimensions, just to talk about it. Or don’t imagine it. Look outside. Human language is our attempt at navigating God’s language; it is us running between the lines of His epic, climbing on the vowels and building houses out of the consonants." -- N.D. Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
