<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/279397-donna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/279397-donna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 12:34:47 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38657-courage-doesn-t-always-roar-sometimes-courage-is-the-little-voice</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 12:34:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Donna add a quote by Mary Anne Radmacher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38657-courage-doesn-t-always-roar-sometimes-courage-is-the-little-voice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Courage doesn't always roar.  Sometimes courage is the little voice at the end of the day that says I'll try again tomorrow." -- Mary Anne Radmacher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51192-do-not-place-the-words-of-anyone-above-the-feelings</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 15:20:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Donna add a quote by Seth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51192-do-not-place-the-words-of-anyone-above-the-feelings]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not place the words of ANYONE above the feelings of your own being. You can learn much from others, but the deepest knowledge must come from within yourself." -- Seth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217291-i-believe-in-kindness-also-in-mischief-also-in-singing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 17:21:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Donna add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217291-i-believe-in-kindness-also-in-mischief-also-in-singing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in kindness. Also in mischief. Also in singing, especially when singing is not necessarily prescribed." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113317-when-it-s-over-i-want-to-say-all-my-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 17:21:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Donna add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113317-when-it-s-over-i-want-to-say-all-my-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When it's over, I want to say: all my life
I was a bride married to amazement.
I was the bridegroom, taking the world into my arms. 

When it is over, I don't want to wonder
if I have made of my life something particular, and real.
I don't want to find myself sighing and frightened,
or full of argument. 

I don't want to end up simply having visited this world." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398408-i-want-to-think-again-of-dangerous-and-noble-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 17:23:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Donna add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398408-i-want-to-think-again-of-dangerous-and-noble-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to think again of dangerous and noble things.
 I want to be light and frolicsome.
 I want to be improbable beautiful and afraid of nothing,
 as though I had wings." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155872-ten-times-a-day-something-happens-to-me-like-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 17:23:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Donna add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155872-ten-times-a-day-something-happens-to-me-like-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ten times a day something happens to me like this - some strengthening throb of amazement - some good sweet empathic ping and swell.   This is the first, the wildest and the wisest thing I know:  that the soul exists and is built entirely out of attentiveness." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260390-the-most-regretful-people-on-earth-are-those-who-felt</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 17:24:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Donna add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260390-the-most-regretful-people-on-earth-are-those-who-felt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most regretful people on earth are those who felt the call to creative work, who felt their own creative power restive and uprising, and gave to it neither power nor time." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/628760-you-are-where-you-need-to-be-just-take-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 10:53:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Donna add a quote by Lana Parrilla]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/628760-you-are-where-you-need-to-be-just-take-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are where you need to be. Just take a deep breath." -- Lana Parrilla]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308324-no-one-rises-above-who-he-or-she-has-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 18:04:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Donna add a quote by Guy Finley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308324-no-one-rises-above-who-he-or-she-has-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one rises above who he or she has been without first having fallen down. The best time - in fact, the only time - to make a real change in your life is in the moment of seeing the need for it. He who hesitates always gets lost in the hundred reasons why tomorrow is a better day to get started." -- Guy Finley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180253-what-s-the-first-sign-of-a-lurking-hidden-expectation-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 18:05:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Donna add a quote by Guy Finley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180253-what-s-the-first-sign-of-a-lurking-hidden-expectation-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What's the first sign of a lurking, hidden expectation you didn't know you had? Pain! People don't do what we want, things don't happen quickly enough, the weather doesn't cooperate, our bodies don't cooperate. Why are these moments so painful? Because our minds are focused on a static, unchanging, me-centric picture while the dynamic unfolding of a broader life continues around us. There is nothing wrong with expectations per se, as it's appropriate to set goals and work, properly, towards their fruition. But the instant we feel pain over life not going &quot;my way,&quot; our expectations have clearly taken an improper turn. Any moment you feel resistance or pain, look for -- and then let go of -- the hidden expectation. Practice giving yourself over to what &quot;you&quot; don't want. Let the line at the store be long. Let the other person interrupt you. Let the nervousness make you shake. Be where your body is, not where your mind is trying to take you." -- Guy Finley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51301-people-generally-see-what-they-look-for-and-hear-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2013 11:09:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Donna add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51301-people-generally-see-what-they-look-for-and-hear-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People generally see what they look for, and hear what they listen for." -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/826565-the-dance-between-darkness-and-light-will-always-remain-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2013 19:25:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Donna add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/826565-the-dance-between-darkness-and-light-will-always-remain-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The dance between darkness and light will always remain— the stars and the moon will always need the darkness to be seen, the darkness will just not be worth having without the moon and the stars." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3823-you-gain-strength-courage-and-confidence-by-every-experience-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 14:00:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Donna add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3823-you-gain-strength-courage-and-confidence-by-every-experience-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You gain strength, courage and confidence by every experience in which you really stop to look fear in the face. You are able to say to yourself, 'I have lived through this horror. I can take the next thing that comes along.' You must do the thing you think you cannot do." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 16:10:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Donna add a quote by Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't interest me what you do for a living. I want to know what you ache for, and if you dare to dream of meeting your heart's longing.
It doesn't interest me how old you are. I want to know if you will risk looking like a fool for love, for your dream, for the adventure of being alive. 
It doesn't interest me what planets are squaring your moon. I want to know if you have touched the center of your own sorrow, if you have been opened by life's betrayals or have become shriveled and closed from fear of further pain!I want to know if you can sit with pain, mine or your own, without moving to hide it or fade it, or fix it. 
I want to know if you can be with joy, mine or your own, if you can dance with wildness and let the ecstasy fill you to the tips of your fingers and toes without cautioning us to be careful, to be realistic, to remember the limitations of being human. 
It doesn't interest me if the story you are telling me is true. I want to know if you can disappoint another to be true to yourself; if you can bear the accusation of betrayal and not betray your own soul; if you can be faithlessand therefore trustworthy. 
I want to know if you can see beauty even when it's not pretty, every day,and if you can source your own life from its presence. 
I want to know if you can live with failure, yours and mine, and still stand on the edge of the lake and shout to the silver of the full moon, “Yes!”
It doesn't interest me to know where you live or how much money you have. I want to know if you can get up, after the night of grief and despair, weary and bruised to the bone, and do what needs to be done to feed the children. 
It doesn't interest me who you know or how you came to be here. I want to know if you will stand in the center of the fire with me and not shrink back. 
It doesn't interest me where or what or with whom you have studied. I want to know what sustains you, from the inside, when all else falls away. 
I want to know if you can be alone with yourself and if you truly like the company you keep in the empty moments." -- Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405314-and-i-found-that-i-can-do-it-if-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 16:10:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Donna add a quote by Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405314-and-i-found-that-i-can-do-it-if-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I found that I can do it if I choose to - I can stay awake and let the sorrows of the world tear me apart and then allow the joys to put me back together different from before but whole once again." -- Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429275-you-cannot-trade-the-courage-needed-to-live-every-moment</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 16:10:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Donna add a quote by Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429275-you-cannot-trade-the-courage-needed-to-live-every-moment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You cannot trade the courage needed to live every moment for immunity from life's sorrows. We may say we know this but ours is the culture of the deal-making mind. From infancy, we have breathed in the belief that there is always a deal to be made, a bargain to be struck. Eventually, we believe, if we do the right thing, if we are good enough, clever enough, sincere enough, work hard enough, we will be rewarded. There are different verses to this song - if you are sorry for your sins and try hard not to sin again, you will go to heaven; if you do your daily practise, clean up your diet, heal your inner child, ferret out all your emotional issue's, focus your intent, come into alignment with the world around you, hone your affirmations, find and listen to the voice of your higher self, you will be rewarded with vibrant health, abundant prosperity, loving relations and inner peace - in other words, heaven!
We know that what we do and how we think affects the quality of our lives. Many things are clearly up to us. And many others are not. I can see no evidence that the universe works on a simple meritocratic system of cause and effect. Bad things happen to good people - all the time. Monetary success does come to some who do not do what they love, as well as to some who are unwilling or unable to see the harm they do to the planet or others. Illness and misfortune come to some who follow their soul's desire. Many great artist's have been poor. Great teachers have lived in obscurity.
My invitation, my challenge to you here, is to journey into a deeper intimacy with the world and your life without any promise of safety or guarantee of reward beyond the intrinsic value of full participation." -- Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
