<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/280054-elizabeth]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/280054-elizabeth" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 06:09:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/805806-most-people-live-their-entire-lives-with-their-clothes-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 06:09:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Sheila Heti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/805806-most-people-live-their-entire-lives-with-their-clothes-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most people live their entire lives with their clothes on, and even if they wanted to, couldn't take them off. Then there are those who cannot put them on. They are the ones who live their lives not just as people but as examples of people. They are destined to expose every part of themselves, so the rest of us can know what it means to be a human.

Most people lead their private lives. They have been given a natural modesty that feels to them like morality, but it's not -- it's luck. They shake their heads at the people with their clothes off rather than learning about human life from their example, but they are wrong to act so superior. Some of us have to be naked, so the rest can be exempted by fate." -- Sheila Heti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181932-it-is-very-frustrating-not-to-be-understood-in-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2009 12:17:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181932-it-is-very-frustrating-not-to-be-understood-in-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is very frustrating not to be understood in this world. If you say one thing and keep being told that you mean something else, it can make you want to scream. But somewhere in the world there is a place for all of us, whether you are an electric form of decoration, peppermint-scented sweet, a source of timber, or a potato pancake." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27484-maybe-if-everyone-walked-around-being-in-touch-with-each</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 12:51:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Michelle Tea]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27484-maybe-if-everyone-walked-around-being-in-touch-with-each]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe if everyone walked around being in touch with each other's hidden pain it could work out and even be beautiful, but it doesn't feel safe to be the only compassionate person on the planet." -- Michelle Tea]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383096-if-we-remain-grotesquely-unequal-we-shall-lose-all-sense</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 06:25:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Tony Judt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383096-if-we-remain-grotesquely-unequal-we-shall-lose-all-sense]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we remain grotesquely unequal, we shall lose all sense of fraternity: and fraternity, for all its fatuity as a political objective, turns out to be the necessary condition of politics itself." -- Tony Judt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27488-then-he-gave-her-a-kiss-on-the-forehead-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 12:58:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27488-then-he-gave-her-a-kiss-on-the-forehead-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then he gave her a kiss on the forehead that felt like a baptism and she wept like a baby." -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49743-if-at-moments-the-facts-seem-to-alter-with-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 10:26:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Ursula K. LeGuin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49743-if-at-moments-the-facts-seem-to-alter-with-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...If at moments the facts seem to alter with an altered voice, why then you can choose the fact you like best; yet none of them are false, and it is all one story." -- Ursula K. LeGuin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70958-straight-people-are-the-most-pathetic-of-all-i-ve-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 10:26:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Sarah Schulman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70958-straight-people-are-the-most-pathetic-of-all-i-ve-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Straight people are the most pathetic of all. I’ve never seen such a miserable group of people in my life. They don’t know anything about themselves" -- Sarah Schulman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134947-they-looked-at-each-other-for-a-while-their-gazes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 10:26:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Brock Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134947-they-looked-at-each-other-for-a-while-their-gazes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They looked at each other for a while their gazes steady, unblinking. It was the way people stare at each other not when they're in love but afterward, when they finally realize all the many horrible and beautiful things locked up within that love." -- Brock Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132311-once-i-was-a-master-at-recycling-leftovers-now-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 10:26:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Jean-Dominique Bauby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132311-once-i-was-a-master-at-recycling-leftovers-now-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once, I was a master at recycling leftovers. Now I cultivate the art of simmering memories." -- Jean-Dominique Bauby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5454-i-hate-america-i-hate-this-country-it-s-just-big</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 10:26:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Tony Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5454-i-hate-america-i-hate-this-country-it-s-just-big]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hate America. I hate this country. It’s just big ideas, and stories, and people dying, and people like you. The white cracker who wrote the national anthem knew what he was doing. He set the word 'free' to a note so high nobody can reach it. That was deliberate. Nothing on earth sounds less like freedom to me. You come to room 1013 over at the hospital, I'll show you America. Terminal, crazy and mean. I live in America, that’s hard enough, I don’t have to love it. You do that. Everybody’s got to love something." -- Tony Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607107-the-women-say-that-they-could-not-eat-hare-veal</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 10:27:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Monique Wittig]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607107-the-women-say-that-they-could-not-eat-hare-veal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The women say that they could not eat hare veal or fowl, they say that they could not eat animals, but man, yes, they may. He says to them throwing his head back with pride, poor wretches of women, if you eat him who will go to work in the fields, who will produce food consumer goods, who will make the aeroplanes, who will pilot them, who will provide the spermatozoa, who will write the books, who in fact will govern? Then the women laugh, baring their teeth to the fullest extent." -- Monique Wittig]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383094-we-no-longer-have-political-movement-while-thousands-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 10:27:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Tony Judt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383094-we-no-longer-have-political-movement-while-thousands-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We no longer have political movement. While thousands of us may come together for a rally or march, we are bound together on such occasions by a single shared interest. Any effort to convert such interests into collective goals is usually undermined by the fragmented individualism of our concerns. Laudable goals - fighting climate change, opposing war, advocating public healthcare or penalizing bankers - are united by nothing more than the expression of emotion. In our political as in our economic lives, we have become consumers: choosing from a broad gamut of competing objectives, we find it hard to imagine ways or reasons to combine these into a coherent whole. We must do better than this." -- Tony Judt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383097-whatever-americans-fondly-believe-their-government-has-always-had-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 10:27:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Tony Judt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383097-whatever-americans-fondly-believe-their-government-has-always-had-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever Americans fondly believe, their government has always had its fingers in the economic pie. What distinguishes the USA from every other developed country has been the widespread belief to the contrary." -- Tony Judt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383100-familiarity-reduces-insecurity-so-we-feel-more-comfortable-describing-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 10:27:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Tony Judt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383100-familiarity-reduces-insecurity-so-we-feel-more-comfortable-describing-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Familiarity reduces insecurity, so we feel more comfortable describing and combating the risks we think we understand: terrorists, immigrants, job loss or crime. But the true sources of insecurity in decades to come will be those that most of us cannot define: dramatic climate change and its social and environmental effects; imperial decline and its attendant 'small wars'; collective political impotence in the face of distant upheavals with disruptive local impact. These are the threats that chauvinist politicians will be best placed to exploit, precisely because they lead so readily to anger and humiliation." -- Tony Judt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/881205-it-was-not-the-case-that-one-thing-morphed-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 15:30:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Rachel Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/881205-it-was-not-the-case-that-one-thing-morphed-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was not the case that one thing morphed into another, child into woman. You remained the person you were before things happened to you. The person you were when you thought a small cut string could determine the course of a year. You also became the person to whom certain things happened. Who passed into the realm where you no longer questioned the notion of being trapped in one form. You took on that form, that identity, hoped for its recognition from others, hoped someone would love it and you." -- Rachel Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/899729-the-desire-for-love-is-universal-but-that-has-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 15:30:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Rachel Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/899729-the-desire-for-love-is-universal-but-that-has-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The desire for love is universal but that has never meant it’s worthy of respect. It’s not admirable to want love, it just is." -- Rachel Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/881209-but-i-had-seen-the-night-i-met-her-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 15:30:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Rachel Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/881209-but-i-had-seen-the-night-i-met-her-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I had seen, the night I met her, that her beauty was going to leave her like it does all women. For the face, time relays some essential message, and time is the message. It takes things away. But its passage, its damages, are all we have. Without it, there's nothing." -- Rachel Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/622632-you-have-to-know-where-the-funny-is-and-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 15:31:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Sheila Heti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/622632-you-have-to-know-where-the-funny-is-and-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to know where the funny is, and if you know where the funny is, you know everything." -- Sheila Heti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/881202-people-who-are-harder-to-love-pose-a-challenge-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 09:30:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Rachel Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/881202-people-who-are-harder-to-love-pose-a-challenge-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People who are harder to love pose a challenge, and the challenge makes them easier to love. You're driven to love them. People who want their love easy don't really want love." -- Rachel Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/805828-later-giddle-s-response-when-i-told-her-i-was-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 09:30:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Rachel Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/805828-later-giddle-s-response-when-i-told-her-i-was-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["(Later, Giddle's response when I told her I was in love: &quot;Oh God, I'm so sorry. Love is awful. It ruins every normal thing, everything but itself. It makes you crazy and for nothing, because it's so disappointing. But good luck with that.&quot;)" -- Rachel Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/944903-a-funny-thing-about-women-and-machines-the-combination-made</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 09:31:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Rachel Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/944903-a-funny-thing-about-women-and-machines-the-combination-made]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A funny thing about women and machines: the combination made made curious. They seemed to think it had something to do with them." -- Rachel Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1049389-causation-extraction-makes-jack-a-dull-reader</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 19:33:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Rabih Alameddine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1049389-causation-extraction-makes-jack-a-dull-reader]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Causation extraction makes Jack a dull reader." -- Rabih Alameddine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1049403-when-i-read-a-book-i-try-my-best-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 19:37:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Rabih Alameddine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1049403-when-i-read-a-book-i-try-my-best-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I read a book, I try my best, not always successfully, to let the wall crumble just a bit, the barricade that separates me from the book. I try to be involved. 
I am Raskalnikov. I am K. I am Humbert and Lolita. 
I am you.
If you read these pages and think I'm the way I am because I lived through a civil war, you can't feel my pain. If you believe you're not like me because one woman, and only one, Hannah, chose to be my friend, then you're unable to empathize." -- Rabih Alameddine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1049415-i-slipped-into-art-to-escape-life-i-sneaked-off</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 19:44:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Rabih Alameddine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1049415-i-slipped-into-art-to-escape-life-i-sneaked-off]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I slipped into art to escape life. I sneaked off into literature." -- Rabih Alameddine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1049417-i-thought-every-person-should-live-for-art-not-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 19:45:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Rabih Alameddine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1049417-i-thought-every-person-should-live-for-art-not-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I thought every person should live for art, not just me, and furthermore, why would I want to be normal? Why would I want to be stupid like everyone else?" -- Rabih Alameddine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1049419-i-know-you-think-you-love-art-because-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 19:48:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Rabih Alameddine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1049419-i-know-you-think-you-love-art-because-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know. You think you love art because you have a sensitive soul. 

Isn't a sensitive soul simply a means of transforming a deficiency into proud disdain?

You think art has meaning. You think you're not like me." -- Rabih Alameddine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/887207-there-s-so-much-beauty-in-this-world-that-it-s-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 14:26:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Sheila Heti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/887207-there-s-so-much-beauty-in-this-world-that-it-s-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's so much beauty in this world that it's hard to begin. There are no words with which to express my gratitude at having been given this one chance to live - if not Live. Let other people frequent the nightclubs in their tight-ass skirts and Live. I'm just sitting here, vibrating in my apartment, at having been given this one chance to live." -- Sheila Heti]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
