<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/282010-luna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/282010-luna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 19:48:17 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1387-life-is-pain-highness-anyone-who-says-differently-is-selling</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 19:48:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1387-life-is-pain-highness-anyone-who-says-differently-is-selling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is pain, highness. Anyone who says differently is selling something." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51541-he-held-up-a-book-then-i-m-going-to-read</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 19:51:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51541-he-held-up-a-book-then-i-m-going-to-read]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He held up a book then. “I'm going to read it to you for relax.”
“Does it have any sports in it?”
“Fencing. Fighting. Torture. Poison. True Love. Hate. Revenge. Giants. Hunters. Bad men. Good men. Beautifulest Ladies. Snakes. Spiders... Pain. Death. Brave men. Cowardly men. Strongest men. Chases. Escapes. Lies. Truths. Passion. Miracles.”
“Sounds okay,” I said and I kind of closed my eyes." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75949-there-have-been-five-great-kisses-since-1642-b-c-before-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 19:52:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75949-there-have-been-five-great-kisses-since-1642-b-c-before-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There have been five great kisses since 1642 B.C...(before then couples hooked thumbs.) And the precise rating of kisses is a terribly difficult thing, often leading to great controversy.... Well, this one left them all behind." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72109-my-westley-will-come-for-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 19:52:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72109-my-westley-will-come-for-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My Westley will come for me." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134416-i-m-going-to-tell-you-something-once-and-then-whether</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 19:55:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134416-i-m-going-to-tell-you-something-once-and-then-whether]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’m going to tell you something once and then whether you die is strictly up to you,&quot; Westley said, lying pleasantly on the bed. &quot;What I’m going to tell you is this: drop your sword, and if you do, then I will leave with this baggage here&quot;—he glanced at Buttercup—&quot;and you will be tied up but not fatally, and will be free to go about your business. And if you choose to fight, well, then, we will not both leave alive.&quot;

You are only alive now because you said 'to the pain.' I want that phrase explained.&quot;

My pleasure. To the pain means this: if we duel and you win, death for me. If we duel and I win, life for you. But life on my terms. The first thing you lose will be your feet. Below the ankle. You will have stumps available to use within six months. Then your hands, at the wrists. They heal somewhat quicker. Five months is a fair average. Next your nose. No smell of dawn for you. Followed by your tongue. Deeply cut away. Not even a stump left. And then your left eye—&quot;

And then my right eye, and then my ears, and shall we get on with it?&quot; the Prince said.

Wrong!&quot; Westley’s voice rang across the room. &quot;Your ears you keep, so that every shriek of every child shall be yours to cherish—every babe that weeps in fear at your approach, every woman that cries 'Dear God, what is that thing?' will reverberate forever with your perfect ears. That is what 'to the pain' means. It means that I leave you in anguish, in humiliation, in freakish misery until you can stand it no more; so there you have it, pig, there you know, you miserable vomitous mass, and I say this now, and live or die, it’s up to you: Drop your sword!&quot;

The sword crashed to the floor." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 19:57:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 19:57:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fairy tales are more than true: not because they tell us that dragons exist, but because they tell us that dragons can be beaten." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16261-life-is-a-disease-sexually-transmitted-and-invariably-fatal</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 19:58:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16261-life-is-a-disease-sexually-transmitted-and-invariably-fatal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is a disease: sexually transmitted, and invariably fatal." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37817-you-get-what-anybody-gets---you-get-a-lifetime</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 19:59:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37817-you-get-what-anybody-gets---you-get-a-lifetime]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You get what anybody gets - you get a lifetime." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1344-only-the-phoenix-rises-and-does-not-descend-and-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 19:59:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1344-only-the-phoenix-rises-and-does-not-descend-and-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only the phoenix rises and does not descend. And everything changes. And nothing is truly lost." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 20:00:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May your coming year be filled with magic and dreams and good madness. I hope you read some fine books and kiss someone who thinks you're wonderful, and don't forget to make some art -- write or draw or build or sing or live as only you can. And I hope, somewhere in the next year, you surprise yourself." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11285-god-does-not-play-dice-with-the-universe-he-plays</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 20:00:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11285-god-does-not-play-dice-with-the-universe-he-plays]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God does not play dice with the universe; He plays an ineffable game of His own devising, which might be compared, from the perspective of any of the other players [i.e. everybody], to being involved in an obscure and complex variant of poker in a pitch-dark room, with blank cards, for infinite stakes, with a Dealer who won't tell you the rules, and who &lt;i&gt;smiles all the time&lt;/i&gt;." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42627-most-people-don-t-realize-how-important-librarians-are-i-ran</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 20:00:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42627-most-people-don-t-realize-how-important-librarians-are-i-ran]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most people don't realize how important librarians are. I ran across a book recently which suggested that the peace and prosperity of a culture was solely related to how many librarians it contained. Possibly a slight overstatement. But a culture that doesn't value its librarians doesn't value ideas and without ideas, well, where are we?" -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46677-i-would-like-to-see-anyone-prophet-king-or-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 20:01:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46677-i-would-like-to-see-anyone-prophet-king-or-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would like to see anyone, prophet, king or God, convince a thousand cats to do the same thing at the same time." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44282-when-we-hold-each-other-in-the-darkness-it-doesn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 20:02:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44282-when-we-hold-each-other-in-the-darkness-it-doesn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we hold each other, in the darkness, it doesn't make the darkness go away. The bad things are still out there. The nightmares still walking. When we hold each other we feel not safe, but better. &quot;It's all right&quot; we whisper, &quot;I'm here, I love you.&quot; and we lie: &quot;I'll never leave you.&quot; For just a moment or two the darkness doesn't seem so bad." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116439-it-doesn-t-matter-that-you-didn-t-believe-in-us-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 20:19:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116439-it-doesn-t-matter-that-you-didn-t-believe-in-us-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't matter that you didn't believe in us,&quot; said Mr. Ibis. &quot;We believed in you." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413047-everybody-has-a-secret-world-inside-of-them-i-mean</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 14:29:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413047-everybody-has-a-secret-world-inside-of-them-i-mean]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody has a secret world inside of them. I mean everybody. All of the people in the whole world, I mean everybody — no matter how dull and boring they are on the outside. Inside them they've all got unimaginable, magnificent, wonderful, stupid, amazing worlds... Not just one world. Hundreds of them. Thousands, maybe." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132670-i-hope-you-will-have-a-wonderful-year-that-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 20:26:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132670-i-hope-you-will-have-a-wonderful-year-that-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hope you will have a wonderful year, that you'll dream dangerously and outrageously, that you'll make something that didn't exist before you made it, that you will be loved and that you will be liked, and that you will have people to love and to like in return. And, most importantly (because I think there should be more kindness and more wisdom in the world right now), that you will, when you need to be, be wise, and that you will always be kind." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125778-have-you-ever-spent-days-and-days-and-days-making</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 20:26:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125778-have-you-ever-spent-days-and-days-and-days-making]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever spent days and days and days making up flavors of ice cream that no one's ever eaten before? Like chicken and telepone ice cream? Green mouse ice cream was the worst. I didn't like that at all." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13371-every-time-you-do-a-good-deed-you-shine-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 20:29:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by charles de lint]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13371-every-time-you-do-a-good-deed-you-shine-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every time you do a good deed you shine the light a little farther into the dark. And the thing is, when you're gone that light is going to keep shining on, pushing the shadows back." -- charles de lint]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32502-i-finally-figured-out-that-i-m-solitary-by-nature-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 20:30:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Charles de Lint]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32502-i-finally-figured-out-that-i-m-solitary-by-nature-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I finally figured out that I’m solitary by nature, but at the same time I know so many people; so many people think they own a piece of me. They shift and move under my skin, like a parade of memories that simply won’t go away. It doesn’t matter where I am, or how alone--I always have such a crowded head." -- Charles de Lint]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89794-all-my-life-i-ve-wanted-to-be-the-kid-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 20:31:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Charles de Lint]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89794-all-my-life-i-ve-wanted-to-be-the-kid-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All my life I've wanted to be the kid who gets to cross over into the magical kingdom. I devoured those books by C.S. Lewis and William Dunthorn, Ellen Wentworth, Susan Cooper, and Alan Garner. When I could get them from the library, I read them out of order as I found them, and then in order, and then reread them all again, many times over. Because even when I was a child I knew it wasn't simply escape that lay on the far side of the borders of fairyland. Instinctively I knew crossing over would mean more than fleeing the constant terror and shame that was mine at that time of my life. There was a knowledge – an understanding hidden in the marrow of my bones that only I can access ― telling me that by crossing over, I'd be coming home.
  That's the reason I’ve yearned so desperately to experience the wonder, the mystery, the beauty of that world beyond the World As It Is. It's because I know that somewhere across the border there's a place for me. A place of safety and strength and learning, where I can become who I'm supposed to be. I've tried forever to be that person here, but whatever I manage to accomplish in the World As It Is only seems to be an echo of what I could be in that other place that lies hidden somewhere beyond the borders." -- Charles de Lint]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7507-remember-to-always-be-yourself-unless-you-suck</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 11:55:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7507-remember-to-always-be-yourself-unless-you-suck]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember to always be yourself. Unless you suck." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5954-there-s-stories-and-then-there-s-stories-the-ones-with-any</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 12:20:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Charles de Lint]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5954-there-s-stories-and-then-there-s-stories-the-ones-with-any]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's stories and then there's stories. The ones with any worth change your life forever, perhaps only in a small way, but once you've heard them, they are forever a part of you. You nurture them and pass them on, and the giving only makes you feel better. The others are just words on a page." -- Charles de Lint]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67188-i-do-believe-in-an-everyday-sort-of-magic---</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 12:20:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Charles de Lint]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67188-i-do-believe-in-an-everyday-sort-of-magic---]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do believe in an everyday sort of magic -- the inexplicable connectedness we sometimes experience with places, people, works of art and the like; the eerie appropriateness of moments of synchronicity; the whispered voice, the hidden presence, when we think we're alone." -- Charles de Lint]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32497-she-had-felt-straight-away-that-she-wasn-t-meeting-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 12:22:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Charles de Lint]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32497-she-had-felt-straight-away-that-she-wasn-t-meeting-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[She] had felt straight away that she wasn’t meeting a new friend, but recognizing an old one." -- Charles de Lint]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75731-there-was-too-much-going-on-here----too-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 12:24:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Charles de Lint]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75731-there-was-too-much-going-on-here----too-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was too much going on here -- too much that strayed from odd all the way over into seriously weird." -- Charles de Lint]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54567-i-write-to-give-myself-strength-i-write-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 13:15:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54567-i-write-to-give-myself-strength-i-write-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I write to give myself strength. I write to be the characters that I am not. I write to explore all the things I'm afraid of. " -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2538-people-love-a-happy-ending-so-every-episode-i-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 13:15:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2538-people-love-a-happy-ending-so-every-episode-i-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People love a happy ending. So every episode, I will explain once again that I don't like people. And then Mal will shoot someone. Someone we like. And their puppy." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9067-two-roads-diverged-in-a-wood-and-i-took-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 13:15:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9067-two-roads-diverged-in-a-wood-and-i-took-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two roads diverged in a wood, and I took the road less traveled by and they CANCELLED MY FRIKKIN' SHOW. I totally shoulda took the road that had all those people on it. Damn." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
