<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/283390-courtney]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/283390-courtney" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 11:35:22 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/439072-i-cry-a-lot-because-i-miss-people-they-die</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 11:35:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Maurice Sendak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/439072-i-cry-a-lot-because-i-miss-people-they-die]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cry a lot because I miss people. They die and I can't stop them. They leave me and I love them more." -- Maurice Sendak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215777-i-have-always-believed-in-the-principle-that-immediate-survival</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 02:53:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Jack McClelland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215777-i-have-always-believed-in-the-principle-that-immediate-survival]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always believed in the principle that immediate survival is more important than long-term survival." -- Jack McClelland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/272166-when-i-was-a-kid--10-11-12-13--the-thing-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 02:53:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Fiona Apple]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/272166-when-i-was-a-kid--10-11-12-13--the-thing-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was a kid--10, 11, 12, 13--the thing I wanted most in the world was a best friend. I wanted to be important to people; to have people that understood me. I wanted to just be close to somebody. And back then, a thought would go through my head almost constantly: &quot;There's never gonna be a room someplace where there's a group of people sitting around, having fun, hanging out, where one of them goes, 'You know what would be great? We should call Fiona. Yeah, that would be good.' That'll never happen. There's nothing interesting about me.&quot; I just felt like I was a sad little boring thing." -- Fiona Apple]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268325-the-thing-he-said-aloud-did-not-succeed</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 02:53:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Tony Burgess]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268325-the-thing-he-said-aloud-did-not-succeed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The thing he said aloud did not succeed." -- Tony Burgess]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271608-loving-someone-always-requires-you-to-not-love-others</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 02:53:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Koushun Takami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271608-loving-someone-always-requires-you-to-not-love-others]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Loving someone always requires you to not love others." -- Koushun Takami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259629-she-needs-you-dad-julia-says-she-has-unfinished-business</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 02:53:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Joey Comeau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259629-she-needs-you-dad-julia-says-she-has-unfinished-business]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She needs you, Dad,&quot; Julia says.  &quot;She has unfinished business in this world.&quot;

&quot;What is the matter with you?&quot;  Charlie asks his daughter.  &quot;Any sane person would have told me to go to the doctor.  I'm seeing a headless apparition every day.  Maybe my medications are conflicting.  You should see the list of side effects on this stuff." -- Joey Comeau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274190-but-i-think-cybil-was-my-biggest-fan-she-cut</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 02:53:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Blake Nelson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274190-but-i-think-cybil-was-my-biggest-fan-she-cut]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I think Cybil was my biggest fan. She cut out my articles and hung them in her locker and we were always cracking up how if you wrote the simplest, most obvious thing in the world people thought you were a genius." -- Blake Nelson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165956-sometimes-it-seems-so-easy-to-make-people-happy-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2009 18:00:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by C.K. Kelly Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165956-sometimes-it-seems-so-easy-to-make-people-happy-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes it seems so easy to make people happy that I wonder why I don't do it more often." -- C.K. Kelly Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215353-it-has-been-our-experience-that-american-houses-insist-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 23:44:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Jack McClelland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215353-it-has-been-our-experience-that-american-houses-insist-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It has been our experience that American houses insist on very comprehensive editing;  that English houses as a rule require little or none and are inclined to go along with the author's script almost without query.  The Canadian practice is just what you would expect--a middle-of-the-road course.  We think the Americans edit too heavily and interfere with the author's rights.  We think that the English publishers don't take enough editorial responsibility.  Naturally, then, we consider our editing to be just about perfect.  There's no doubt about it, we Canadians are a superior breed! (in a letter to author Margaret Laurence, dated May, 1960)" -- Jack McClelland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215805-i-would-not-employ-an-author-to-referee-a-ping-pong</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 20:31:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Jack McClelland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215805-i-would-not-employ-an-author-to-referee-a-ping-pong]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would not employ an author to referee a Ping-Pong match.  By their very nature they are biased and bloody-minded.  Better put a fox in a henhouse than to ask an author to judge his peers. (in a letter to the Governor General about the GA's Literary Awards &amp; his issue--among others--with the judging system, 1981)" -- Jack McClelland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217016-this-is-the-best-night-of-my-life-raffy-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2009 02:30:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217016-this-is-the-best-night-of-my-life-raffy-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is the best night of my life,&quot; Raffy says, crying.
&quot;Raffy, half our House has burnt down,&quot; I say wearily.  &quot;We don't have a kitchen.&quot;
&quot;Why do you always have to be so pessimistic?&quot;  she asks.  &quot;We can double up in our rooms and have a barbecue every night like the Cadets.&quot;
Silently I vow to keep Raffy around for the rest of my life." -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220998-a-piece-of-me-is-gone-she-told-me-once</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 17:35:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220998-a-piece-of-me-is-gone-she-told-me-once]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A piece of me is gone,&quot; she told me once while we were bra shopping.  &quot;I think we're made up of all these different pieces and every time someone goes, you're left with less of yourself." -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205579-what-i-sometimes-mistake-for-ecstasy-is-simply-the-absence</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 02:40:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Sarah Kane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205579-what-i-sometimes-mistake-for-ecstasy-is-simply-the-absence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I sometimes mistake for ecstasy is simply the absence of grief." -- Sarah Kane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260313-i-think-it-would-be-cool-if-we-wore-suits</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 21:07:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Joey Comeau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260313-i-think-it-would-be-cool-if-we-wore-suits]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think it would be cool if we wore suits while we committed these violent acts of retribution. Not fancy suits. No. Cheap suits that we won't mind ruining. Then if we're caught by the police, well, think how amazing we'll look! All bloody and torn and grizzled.

Plus, suits look official. They would add an air of credibility to our campaign of blood drenched disproportionate responses." -- Joey Comeau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268323-in-spite-of-the-three-hours-i-spent-combing-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 04:21:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Tony Burgess]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268323-in-spite-of-the-three-hours-i-spent-combing-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In spite of the three hours I spent combing over the details, I have, to this day, a very persistent certainty that hidden inside me is the revolting knowledge of days when I wasn't quite myself.  I now suspect that my inexplicable bouts of exhaustion are due to the massive effort of keeping those days behind me." -- Tony Burgess]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278738-to-answer-your-question-as-honestly-as-i-can-i-ve</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 11:50:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Ryan North]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278738-to-answer-your-question-as-honestly-as-i-can-i-ve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To answer your question as honestly as I can, I've wanted since I was very little to not have to worry about money. I've never been poverty-level poor (I mean, there's been years where I've been officially beneath the poverty line, but that wasn't poverty: that was being a student and living the Student Lifestyle), but I've been in a place where you know you can't afford a better-quality food, where you can't do certain things because of money, and I'd prefer not to have those problems if I can. I sort of have troubles with money in general, with how it determines so much of our lives but with how we all try to ignore it, but I would like to be (and stay) in a place where I can pick up some new comics and games and not worry about how much they cost.

This is terrible; you're asking me where I want to be in the future, what I want my life to be like, and the only thing I can tell you is &quot;Man, all I know is I don't want to be POOR." -- Ryan North]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/285140-it-s-not-a-bad-thing-to-be-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 01:49:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Koushun Takami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/285140-it-s-not-a-bad-thing-to-be-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not a bad thing to be loved." -- Koushun Takami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315040-there-s-something-not-quite-christian-about-it-tony-said-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 23:49:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Joey Comeau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315040-there-s-something-not-quite-christian-about-it-tony-said-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's something not quite Christian about it,&quot; Tony said. He sat back in his chair and looked up to where his Bible sat on the shelf. &quot;I can't put my finger on why exactly, but it doesn't seem right for a couple of young ladies to be out there in the middle of the night, obsessing over their telescopes." -- Joey Comeau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/332388-it-s-hard-to-imagine-talking-to-lucy-but-i-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 20:36:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Blake Nelson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/332388-it-s-hard-to-imagine-talking-to-lucy-but-i-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's hard to imagine talking to Lucy. But I can imagine sleeping with her. I have been imagining it quite regularly. I can't stop imagining it. Maybe it's time for my first Lucy Branch, my first truly physical relationship. And why do I assume it would be a bad thing? Maybe it's better with someone different from you. I could teach her how fluorocarbons affect the ozone. She could teach me about oral sex.

We would both become better people." -- Blake Nelson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369047-as-a-young-man-just-beginning-to-publish-some-short</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 01:42:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369047-as-a-young-man-just-beginning-to-publish-some-short]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As a young man just beginning to publish some short fiction in the t&amp;a magazines, I was fairly optimistic about my chances of getting published; I knew that I had some game, as the basketball players say these days, and I also felt that time was on my side; sooner or later the best-selling writers of the sixties and seventies would either die or go senile, making room for newcomers like me." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357051-the-scariest-moment-is-always-just-before-you-start-after</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 02:05:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357051-the-scariest-moment-is-always-just-before-you-start-after]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The scariest moment is always just before you start. After that, things can only get better." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390938-my-theory-was-that-if-i-behaved-like-a-confident</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2011 04:55:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Dawn French]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390938-my-theory-was-that-if-i-behaved-like-a-confident]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My theory was that if I &lt;I&gt;behaved&lt;/I&gt; like a confident, cheerful person, eventually I would buy it myself, and become that.  I always had traces of strength somewhere inside me, it wasn't fake, it was just a way of summoning my courage to the fore and not letting any creeping self-doubt hinder my adventures.  This method worked then, and it works now.  I tell myself that I am the sort of person who can open a one-woman play in the West End, so I do. I am the sort of person who has several companies, so I do. I am the sort of person WHO WRITES A BOOK! So I do. It's the process of having faith in the self you don't quite know you are yet, if you see what I mean.  Believing that you will find the strength, the means somehow, and trusting in that, although your legs are like jelly.  You can still walk on them and you will find the bones as you walk.  Yes, that's it.  The further I walk, the stronger I become.  So unlike the real lived life, where the further you walk, the more your hips hurt." -- Dawn French]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402645-ruby-told-me-it-didn-t-matter-what-a-boy-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2011 13:07:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Nova Ren Suma]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402645-ruby-told-me-it-didn-t-matter-what-a-boy-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ruby told me it didn't matter what a boy was thinking about you so long as you had a good hold on what you were thinking about him." -- Nova Ren Suma]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/426161-my-friends-love-is-better-than-anger-hope-is-better</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 18:22:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Jack Layton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/426161-my-friends-love-is-better-than-anger-hope-is-better]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My friends, love is better than anger. Hope is better than fear. Optimism is better than despair. So let us be loving, hopeful and optimistic. And we'll change the world." -- Jack Layton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449928-we-are-what-we-love-we-are-the-things-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 01:42:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Daisy Whitney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449928-we-are-what-we-love-we-are-the-things-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are what we love.  We are the things, the people, the ideas we spend our days with.  They center us, they drive us, they define us to our very core.
Without them, we are empty." -- Daisy Whitney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/463143-i-want-to-only-imagine-things-not-know-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 22:40:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Katie Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/463143-i-want-to-only-imagine-things-not-know-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to only imagine things, not know them." -- Katie Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467203-what-are-you-burning-on-a-glance-just-some-papers</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 22:57:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Adele Griffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467203-what-are-you-burning-on-a-glance-just-some-papers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What are you burning?&quot; On a glance, just some papers.
&quot;I write in a journal.&quot; He spoke below his breath, so that his words weren't quite for me. &quot;Because I like to see everything written down. So that I know it really happened. That I wasn't just making it up. Then I read it and memorize it. And then I have to destroy the hard evidence.&quot;
I thought of my own journal, the muddle of every page. All those unfiltered, lunatic letters to Sean Ryan.
&quot;What is it, exactly, that you need to destroy?&quot;
&quot;Everything that I don't want to be true." -- Adele Griffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/477641-it-was-weird-because-my-first-couple-stories-had-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 11:35:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Blake Nelson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/477641-it-was-weird-because-my-first-couple-stories-had-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was weird because my first couple stories had been so easy. Now it was like, the more you did it, the harder it became. But in another way, it was addicting. It was like gambling, every time you'd start another one you'd think &lt;I&gt;this time I'm going to get it right....&lt;/I&gt;" -- Blake Nelson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/478784-when-i-lose-my-temper-honey-you-can-t-find-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 11:35:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Ava Gardner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/478784-when-i-lose-my-temper-honey-you-can-t-find-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I lose my temper, honey, you can't find it any place." -- Ava Gardner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/404406-god-knows-i-ve-got-so-many-frailties-myself-i-ought</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 11:35:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Ava Gardner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/404406-god-knows-i-ve-got-so-many-frailties-myself-i-ought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God knows I've got so many frailties myself, I ought to be able to understand and forgive them in others. But I don't." -- Ava Gardner]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
