<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/283835-paul]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/283835-paul" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 06:49:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6309-in-my-thinking-church-doesn-t-exist-for-the-benefit-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 06:49:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paul add a quote by Brian McLaren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6309-in-my-thinking-church-doesn-t-exist-for-the-benefit-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In my thinking, church doesn't exist for the benefit of its members. It exists to equip its members for the benefit of the world." -- Brian McLaren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 06:13:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paul add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467-life-is-what-happens-to-you-while-you-re-busy-making</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 06:14:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paul add a quote by Allen Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467-life-is-what-happens-to-you-while-you-re-busy-making]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is what happens to you while you're busy making other plans." -- Allen Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 06:14:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paul add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opposite of love is not hate, it's indifference. The opposite of art is not ugliness, it's indifference. The opposite of faith is not heresy, it's indifference. And the opposite of life is not death, it's indifference." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 06:15:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paul add a quote by Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Insanity is doing the same thing, over and over again, but expecting different results." -- Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16949-a-friend-is-someone-who-knows-all-about-you-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 06:19:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paul add a quote by Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16949-a-friend-is-someone-who-knows-all-about-you-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A friend is someone who knows all about you and still loves you." -- Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104737-not-deciding-to-act-would-be-identical-with-deciding-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2008 05:29:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paul add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104737-not-deciding-to-act-would-be-identical-with-deciding-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...not deciding to act would be identical with deciding not to act." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186405-nothing-fires-the-warrior-s-heart-more-with-courage-than-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 14:12:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paul add a quote by Steven Pressfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186405-nothing-fires-the-warrior-s-heart-more-with-courage-than-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing fires the warrior’s heart more with courage than to find himself and his comrades at the point of annihilation, at the brink of being routed and overrun, and then to dredge not merely from one’s own bowels or guts but from one’s discipline and training the presence of mind not to panic, not to yield to the possession of despair, but instead to complete those homely acts of order which Dienekes had ever declared the supreme accomplishment of the warrior: to perform the commonplace under far-from-commonplace conditions." -- Steven Pressfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298871-for-what-can-be-more-noble-than-to-slay-oneself</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 14:15:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paul add a quote by Steven Pressfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298871-for-what-can-be-more-noble-than-to-slay-oneself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For what can be more noble than to slay oneself? Not literally. Not with a blade in the guts. But to extinguish the selfish self within, that part which looks only to its own preservation, to save its own skin. That, I saw, was the victory you Spartans had gained over yourselves. That was the glue. It was what you had learned and it made me stay, to learn it too." -- Steven Pressfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22248-change-will-not-come-if-we-wait-for-some-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 14:41:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paul add a quote by Barack Obama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22248-change-will-not-come-if-we-wait-for-some-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Change will not come if we wait for some other person, or if we wait for some other time.  We are the ones we've been waiting for.  We are the change that we seek." -- Barack Obama]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44541-laws-and-principles-are-not-for-the-times-when-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 13:28:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paul add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44541-laws-and-principles-are-not-for-the-times-when-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Laws and principles are not for the times when there is no temptation: they are for such moments as this, when body and soul rise in mutiny against their rigour ... If at my convenience I might break them, what would be their worth?" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116668-i-have-now-been-married-ten-years-i-know-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 13:33:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paul add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116668-i-have-now-been-married-ten-years-i-know-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have now been married ten years. I know what it is to live entirely for and with what I love best on earth. I hold myself supremely blest - blest beyond what language can express; because I am my husband's life as fully as he is mine. No woman was ever nearer to her mate than I am: ever more absolutely bone of his bone and flesh of his flesh. I know no weariness of my Edward's society: he knows none of mine, any more than we each do the pulsation of the heart that beats in our separate bosoms; consequently, we are ever together. To be together is for us to be at once free as in solitude, as gay as in company. We talk, I believe, all day long: to talk to each other is but more animated and an audible thinking. All my confidence is bestowed on him, all his confidence is devoted to me; we are precisely suited in character - perfect concord is the result." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/679-war-is-an-ugly-thing-but-not-the-ugliest-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2014 05:36:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paul add a quote by John Stuart Mill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/679-war-is-an-ugly-thing-but-not-the-ugliest-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["War is an ugly thing, but not the ugliest of things: the decayed and degraded state of moral and patriotic feeling which thinks that nothing is worth a war, is much worse. When a people are used as mere human instruments for firing cannon or thrusting bayonets, in the service and for the selfish purposes of a master, such war degrades a people. A war to protect other human beings against tyrannical injustice; a war to give victory to their own ideas of right and good, and which is their own war, carried on for an honest purpose by their free choice, — is often the means of their regeneration. A man who has nothing which he is willing to fight for, nothing which he cares more about than he does about his personal safety, is a miserable creature who has no chance of being free, unless made and kept so by the exertions of better men than himself. As long as justice and injustice have not terminated their ever-renewing fight for ascendancy in the affairs of mankind, human beings must be willing, when need is, to do battle for the one against the other." -- John Stuart Mill]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
