<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/283881-kate]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/283881-kate" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2010 08:08:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214197-this-pause-in-time-within-time-when-did-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2010 08:08:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Muriel Barbery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214197-this-pause-in-time-within-time-when-did-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This pause in time, within time ... When did I first experience the exquisite sense of surrender that is only possible with another person?  The peace of mind one experiences on one's own, one's certainty of self in the serenity of solitude, are nothing in comparison to the release and openness and fluency one shares with another, in close companionship ..." -- Muriel Barbery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267658-about-once-or-twice-every-month-i-engage-in-public</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 09:50:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267658-about-once-or-twice-every-month-i-engage-in-public]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["About once or twice every month I engage in public debates with those whose pressing need it is to woo and to win the approval of supernatural beings. Very often, when I give my view that there is no supernatural dimension, and certainly not one that is only or especially available to the faithful, and that the natural world is wonderful enough—and even miraculous enough if you insist—I attract pitying looks and anxious questions. How, in that case, I am asked, do I find meaning and purpose in life? How does a mere and gross materialist, with no expectation of a life to come, decide what, if anything, is worth caring about?

Depending on my mood, I sometimes but not always refrain from pointing out what a breathtakingly insulting and patronizing question this is. (It is on a par with the equally subtle inquiry: Since you don't believe in our god, what stops you from stealing and lying and raping and killing to your heart's content?) Just as the answer to the latter question is: self-respect and the desire for the respect of others—while in the meantime it is precisely those who think they have divine permission who are truly capable of any atrocity—so the answer to the first question falls into two parts. A life that partakes even a little of friendship, love, irony, humor, parenthood, literature, and music, and the chance to take part in battles for the liberation of others cannot be called 'meaningless' except if the person living it is also an existentialist and elects to call it so. It could be that all existence is a pointless joke, but it is not in fact possible to live one's everyday life as if this were so. Whereas if one sought to define meaninglessness and futility, the idea that a human life should be expended in the guilty, fearful, self-obsessed propitiation of supernatural nonentities… but there, there. Enough." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178306-life-has-no-meaning-each-of-us-has-meaning-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 09:50:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178306-life-has-no-meaning-each-of-us-has-meaning-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life has no meaning. Each of us has meaning and we bring it to life. It is a waste to be asking the question when you are the answer." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279323-we-modern-human-beings-are-looking-at-life-trying-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 12:01:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279323-we-modern-human-beings-are-looking-at-life-trying-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We modern human beings are looking at life, trying to make some sense of it; observing a 'reality' that often seems to be unfolding in a foreign tongue--only we've all been issued the wrong librettos.  For a text, we're given the Bible.  Or the Talmud or the Koran.  We're given Time magazine, and Reader's Digest, daily papers, and the six o'clock news; we're given schoolbooks, sitcoms, and revisionist histories; we're given psychological counseling, cults, workshops, advertisements, sales pitches, and authoritative pronouncements by pundits, sold-out scientists, political activists, and heads of state.  Unfortunately, none of these translations bears more than a faint resemblance to what is transpiring in the true theater of existence, and most of them are dangerously misleading.  We're attempting to comprehend the spiraling intricacies of a magnificently complex tragicomedy with librettos that describe the barrom melodramas or kindergarten skits.  And when's the last time you heard anybody bitch about it to the management?" -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53414-writing-is-like-driving-at-night-in-the-fog-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 13:47:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by E.L. Doctorow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53414-writing-is-like-driving-at-night-in-the-fog-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing is like driving at night in the fog. You can only see as far as your headlights, but you can make the whole trip that way." -- E.L. Doctorow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/562108-but-i-can-stop-on-any-corner-at-the-intersection</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 13:51:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by E.L. Doctorow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/562108-but-i-can-stop-on-any-corner-at-the-intersection]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I can stop on any corner at the intersection of two busy streets, and before me are thousands of lives headed in all four directions, uptown downtown east and west, on foot, on bikes, on in-line skates, in buses, strollers, cars, trucks, with the subway rumble underneath my feet... and how can I not know I am momentarily part of the most spectacular phenomenon in the unnatural world? ...The city may begin from a marketplace, a trading post, the confluence of waters, but it secretly depends on the human need to walk among strangers." -- E.L. Doctorow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185805-because-nerds-like-us-are-allowed-to-be-unironically-enthusiastic</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 18:26:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185805-because-nerds-like-us-are-allowed-to-be-unironically-enthusiastic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…because nerds like us are allowed to be unironically enthusiastic about stuff… Nerds are allowed to love stuff, like jump-up-and-down-in-the-chair-can’t-control-yourself love it. Hank, when people call people nerds, mostly what they’re saying is ‘you like stuff.’ Which is just not a good insult at all. Like, ‘you are too enthusiastic about the miracle of human consciousness’." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
