<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/284005-rebecca]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/284005-rebecca" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 May 2014 14:58:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142160-when-god-wants-a-great-work-done-in-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2014 14:58:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rebecca add a quote by E.T. Sullivan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142160-when-god-wants-a-great-work-done-in-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When God wants a great work done in the world or a great wrong righted, he goes about it in a very unusual way. He doesn’t stir up His earthquakes or send forth his thunderbolts. Instead, he has a helpless baby born, perhaps in some simple home of some obscure mother. And then God puts the idea into the mother’s heart, and she puts it into the baby’s mind. And then God waits. The greatest forces of the world are not the earthquakes and thunderbolts. The greatest forces in the world are babies." -- E.T. Sullivan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265334-a-baby-is-god-s-opinion-that-life-should-go-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 04:43:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rebecca add a quote by Carl Sandburg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265334-a-baby-is-god-s-opinion-that-life-should-go-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A baby is God's opinion that life should go on. A book that does nothing to you is dead. A baby, whether it does anything to you, represents life. If a bad fire should break out in this house and I had my choice of saving the library or the babies, I would save what is alive. Never will a time come when the most marvelous recent invention is as marvelous as a newborn baby. The finest of our precision watches, the most super-colossal of our supercargo plants, don't compare with a newborn baby in the number and ingenuity of coils and springs, in the flow and change of chemical solutions, in timing devices and interrelated parts that are irreplaceable. A baby is very modern. Yet it is also the oldest of the ancients. A baby doesn't know he is a hoary and venerable antique — but he is. Before man learned how to make an alphabet, how to make a wheel, how to make a fire, he knew how to make a baby — with the great help of woman, and his God and Maker." -- Carl Sandburg]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
