<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/285229-johanna-dieterich]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/285229-johanna-dieterich" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2010 16:01:28 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123464-the-reason-people-find-it-so-hard-to-be-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2010 16:01:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Johanna Dieterich add a quote by Marcel Pagnol  ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123464-the-reason-people-find-it-so-hard-to-be-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The reason people find it so hard to be happy is that they always see the past better than it was, the present worse than it is, and the future less resolved than it will be." -- Marcel Pagnol  ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2010 22:27:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Johanna Dieterich add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the world were merely seductive, that would be easy. If it were merely challenging, that would be no problem. But I arise in the morning torn between a desire to improve the world and a desire to enjoy the world. This makes it hard to plan the day." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7522-much-as-i-hate-to-stand-out-in-a-crowd</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2007 14:42:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Johanna Dieterich add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7522-much-as-i-hate-to-stand-out-in-a-crowd]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Much as I hate to stand out in a crowd, I have this terrible occasional compulsion to make myself a source of merriment for the world, and I had come close to sealing new heights with a Russian hat. Now, clearly, that would be unnecessary." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9612-well-i-mean-yes-idealism-yes-the-dignity-of-pure</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 20:37:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Johanna Dieterich add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9612-well-i-mean-yes-idealism-yes-the-dignity-of-pure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, I mean, yes idealism, yes the dignity of pure research, yes the pursuit of truth in all its forms, but there comes a point I'm afraid where you begin to suspect that the entire multidimensional infinity of the Universe is almost certainly being run by a bunch of maniacs. And if it comes to a choice between spending yet another ten million years finding that out, and on the other hand just taking the money and running, then I for one could do with the exercise." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11095-as-much-as-i-admire-and-value-intellectualism-and-experimentation</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 08:40:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Johanna Dieterich add a quote by Myla Goldberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11095-as-much-as-i-admire-and-value-intellectualism-and-experimentation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As much as I admire and value intellectualism and experimentation, I've discovered that unless a book has a throbbing heart as well as a sexy brain, I feel like the story is a specimen in a sealed glass jar and not a living, breathing creature I want to take by the hand and talk to for hours on end." -- Myla Goldberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2499-there-are-two-motives-for-reading-a-book-one-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 12:58:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Johanna Dieterich add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2499-there-are-two-motives-for-reading-a-book-one-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two motives for reading a book; one, that you enjoy it; the other, that you can boast about it." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78158-i-can-never-read-all-the-books-i-want-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 13:05:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Johanna Dieterich add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78158-i-can-never-read-all-the-books-i-want-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can never read all the books I want; I can never be all the people I want and live all the lives I want. I can never train myself in all the skills I want. And why do I want? I want to live and feel all the shades, tones and variations of mental and physical experience possible in life. And I am horribly limited." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83017-i-like-to-see-people-reunited-i-like-to-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2010 15:50:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Johanna Dieterich add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83017-i-like-to-see-people-reunited-i-like-to-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like to see people reunited, I like to see people run to each other, I like the kissing and the crying, I like the impatience, the stories that the mouth can't tell fast enough, the ears that aren't big enough, the eyes that can't take in all of the change, I like the hugging, the bringing together, the end of missing someone." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213589-someday-you-ll-remember-what-i-said-and-you-ll-thank-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 02:39:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Johanna Dieterich add a quote by Betty Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213589-someday-you-ll-remember-what-i-said-and-you-ll-thank-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Someday you'll remember what I said and you'll thank me for it.&quot;

Francie wished adults would stop telling her that. Already the load of thanks in the future was weighing her down. She figured she'd have to spend the best years of her womanhood hunting up people to tell them that they were right and to thank them." -- Betty Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
