<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/285596-john]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/285596-john" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 19:17:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35757-wherever-you-go-in-the-galaxy-you-can-find-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 19:17:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Robert Sheckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35757-wherever-you-go-in-the-galaxy-you-can-find-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wherever you go in the galaxy, you can find a food business, a house-building business, a war business, a peace business, a governing business, and so forth.  And, of course, a God business, which is called 'religion,' and which is a particularly reprehensible line of endeavor.  " -- Robert Sheckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35759-there-are-things-than-cannot-ever-occur-with-any-precision</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 19:19:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Bruno Schulz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35759-there-are-things-than-cannot-ever-occur-with-any-precision]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are things than cannot ever occur with any precision.  They are too big and too magnificent to be contained in mere facts.  They are merely trying to occur, they are checking whether the ground of reality can carry them.  And they quickly withdraw, fearing to loose their integrity in the frailty of realization.  " -- Bruno Schulz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35760-an-event-may-be-small-and-insignificant-in-its-origin</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 19:21:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Bruno Schulz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35760-an-event-may-be-small-and-insignificant-in-its-origin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An event may be small and insignificant in its origin , and yet, when drawn close to one’s eye, it may open in its center an infinite and radiant perspective because a higher order of being is trying to express itself in it and irradiates it violently." -- Bruno Schulz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35761-for-overstrong-was-the-command-to-hold-fast-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 19:24:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Hermann Broch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35761-for-overstrong-was-the-command-to-hold-fast-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["… for overstrong was the command to hold fast to each smallest particle of time, to the smallest particle of every circumstance, and to embody all of them in memory as if they could be preserved in memory through all deaths for all times." -- Hermann Broch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39505-and-taking-her-friend-s-hand-she-put-it-on-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 10:37:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Guy de Maupassant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39505-and-taking-her-friend-s-hand-she-put-it-on-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And taking her friend’s hand, she put it on her breast, on that firm round covering of a woman’s heart which the male often finds so satisfying that he makes no attempt to find what lies beneath it." -- Guy de Maupassant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40773-we-contrast-the-urban-and-the-natural-but-that-s-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 07:33:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Robert Charles Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40773-we-contrast-the-urban-and-the-natural-but-that-s-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We contrast the urban and the natural, but that’s a contemporary myth.  We’re animals, after all; our cities are organic products, fully as “natural” (whatever that word really means) as a termite hill or a rabbit warren.  But how much more interesting: how much more complex, dressed in the intricacies and exfoliations of human culture, simple patterns iterated into infinite variation.  And full of secrets, beyond counting." -- Robert Charles Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45274-between-shame-and-shamelessness-lies-the-axis-upon-which-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 09:54:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45274-between-shame-and-shamelessness-lies-the-axis-upon-which-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Between shame and shamelessness lies the axis upon which we turn; meteorological conditions at both these poles are of the most extreme, ferocious type.  Shamelessness, shame: the roots of violence." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76285-no-intellect-is-needed-to-see-those-figures-who-wait</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 17:52:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Gene Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76285-no-intellect-is-needed-to-see-those-figures-who-wait]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No intellect is needed to see those figures who wait beyond the void of death – every child is aware of them, blazing with glories dark or bright, wrapped in authority older than the universe.  They are the stuff of our earliest dreams, as of our dying visions.  Rightly we feel our lives guided by them, and rightly too we feel how little we matter to them, the builders of the unimaginable, the fighters of wars beyond the totality of existence.

The difficulty lies in learning that we ourselves encompass forces equally great.  We say, “I will,” and “I will not,” and imagine ourselves (though we obey the orders of some prosaic person every day) our own masters, when the truth is that our masters are sleeping.  One wakes within us and we are ridden like beasts, though the rider is but some hitherto unguessed part of ourselves." -- Gene Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85061-man-acquired-a-soul-and-he-must-fight-with-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2008 11:55:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Etienne Leroux]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85061-man-acquired-a-soul-and-he-must-fight-with-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man acquired a soul and he must fight with all the powers at his disposal to protect that soul against the monster in his dark past." -- Etienne Leroux]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85062-society-is-helpless-without-its-champion-said-dr-johns-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2008 11:56:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Etienne Leroux]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85062-society-is-helpless-without-its-champion-said-dr-johns-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Society is helpless without its champion,&quot; said Dr. Johns.  &quot;The more it itself employs its own will toward order, the more it is removed from the soil in which it roots; its freedom of will becomes a source of transgression against its deep-rooted instincts.  In its dilemma it needs a crucifixion, someone to die in the name of chaos, a sacrifice of atonement to protect it against the primitive powers that threaten to falsify its order." -- Etienne Leroux]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112410-i-had-the-whole-road-to-myself-for-no-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 06:46:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112410-i-had-the-whole-road-to-myself-for-no-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had the whole road to myself, for no one was yet stirring, and I walked on, with a slouching, dogged gait.  The gray shooting-jacket was on my back, and from the end of my brother’s rifle hung a small bundle of my clothes.  My fingers worked moodily at the stock and trigger, and I thought that this indeed was the way to begin life, with a gun in your hand!" -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114076-and-even-as-this-old-guide-book-boasts-of-the-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 18:04:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114076-and-even-as-this-old-guide-book-boasts-of-the-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And even as this old guide-book boasts of the, to us, insignificant Liverpool of fifty years ago, the New York guidebooks are now vaunting of the magnitude of a town, whose future inhabitants, multitudinous as the pebbles on the beach, and girdled in with high walls and towers, flanking endless avenues of opulence and taste, will regard all our Broadways and Bowerys as but the paltry nucleus to their Nineveh.  From far up the Hudson, beyond Harlem River where the young saplings are now growing, that will overarch their lordly mansions with broad boughs, centuries old; they may send forth explorers to penetrate into the then obscure and smoky alleys of the Fifth Avenue and Fourteenth Street; and going still farther south, may exhume the present Doric Custom-house, and quote it as a proof that their high and mighty metropolis enjoyed a Hellenic antiquity." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137121-on-the-other-hand-it-will-be-equally-forgotten-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 10:42:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Alexander Hamilton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137121-on-the-other-hand-it-will-be-equally-forgotten-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the other hand, it will be equally forgotten that the vigor of government is essential to the security of liberty; that, in the contemplation of a sound and well-informed judgment, their interest can never be separated; and that a dangerous ambition more often lurks behind the specious mask of zeal for the rights of the people than under the forbidden appearance of zeal for the firmness and efficiency of government. History will teach us that the former has been found a much more certain road to the introduction of despotism than the latter, and that of those men who have overturned the liberties of republics, the greatest number have begun their career by paying an obsequious court to the people; commencing demagogues, and ending tyrants.
" -- Alexander Hamilton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149006-when-the-tragedies-of-others-become-for-us-diversions-sad</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2009 09:32:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Lucius Shepard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149006-when-the-tragedies-of-others-become-for-us-diversions-sad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the tragedies of others become for us diversions, sad stories with which to enthrall our friends, interesting bits of data to toss out at cocktail parties, a means of presenting a pose of political concern, or whatever…when this happens we commit the gravest of sins, condemn ourselves to ignominy, and consign the world to a dangerous course.  We begin to justify our casual overview of pain and suffering by portraying ourselves as do-gooders incapacitated by the inexorable forces of poverty, famine, and war.  “What can I do?” we say, “I’m only one person, and these things are beyond my control.  I care about the world’s trouble, but there are no solutions.”  Yet no matter how accurate this assessment, most of us are relying on it to be true, using it to mask our indulgence, our deep-seated lack of concern, our pathological self-involvement." -- Lucius Shepard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169865-to-my-mind-a-well-developed-sense-of-humor-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 10:17:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Thomas Ligotti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169865-to-my-mind-a-well-developed-sense-of-humor-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To my mind, a well-developed sense of humor is the surest indication of a person's humanity, no matter how black and bitter that humor may be." -- Thomas Ligotti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175252-woe-to-he-who-checkmates-his-opponents-at-last-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 08:43:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Jedediah Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175252-woe-to-he-who-checkmates-his-opponents-at-last-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Woe to he who checkmates his opponents at last, only to discover they have been playing cribbage." -- Jedediah Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175253-if-you-are-not-setting-a-trap-then-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 08:44:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Jedediah Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175253-if-you-are-not-setting-a-trap-then-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are not setting a trap, then you are probably walking into one.  It is the mark of the master to do both at once." -- Jedediah Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175254-the-coded-message-is-a-lifeless-thing-mummified-and-entombed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 08:44:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Jedediah Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175254-the-coded-message-is-a-lifeless-thing-mummified-and-entombed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The coded message is a lifeless thing, mummified and entombed.  To the would-be cryptologist we must offer the same advice we would give the grave-robber, the spelunker, and the sorcerer of legend: beware what you dig up; it is yours." -- Jedediah Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175255-it-is-not-enough-to-say-that-you-have-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 08:45:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Jedediah Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175255-it-is-not-enough-to-say-that-you-have-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not enough to say that you have had a hunch.  Once written down, most such inklings reveal themselves for what they are: something to be tossed into a wishing well, not into a file." -- Jedediah Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175256-the-expert-detective-s-pursuit-will-go-unnoticed-but-not-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 08:45:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Jedediah Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175256-the-expert-detective-s-pursuit-will-go-unnoticed-but-not-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The expert detective’s pursuit will go unnoticed, but not because he is unremarkable.  Rather, like the suspect’s shadow, he will appear as though he is meant to be there." -- Jedediah Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260377-saimun-pondered-how-come-that-when-something-is-difficult-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 06:57:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Mochtar Lubis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260377-saimun-pondered-how-come-that-when-something-is-difficult-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Saimun pondered.  How come that when something is difficult to get or you don’t have it, and you just get a chance to taste it for a moment, a small matter can become so big, doubling, trebling, growing ever larger?  This morning one kretek cigarette dominated his whole soul.  As if his life depended on one cigarette and if he could get that cigarette his life would be prolonged, as it were, for ever.  One cigarette could fulfill his existence." -- Mochtar Lubis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318153-the-truth-is-not-always-useful-not-always-good-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 19:40:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Iain M. Banks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318153-the-truth-is-not-always-useful-not-always-good-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is not always useful, not always good.  It’s like putting your faith in water.  Yes, we need the rain, but too much can sweep you away in a flood and drown you.  Like all great natural, elemental forces, the truth needs to be channeled, managed, controlled and intelligently, morally allocated." -- Iain M. Banks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318157-anyone-could-say-that-a-miracle-is-something-impossible-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 19:51:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Michael Cisco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318157-anyone-could-say-that-a-miracle-is-something-impossible-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone could say that a miracle is something impossible, but they say it thoughtlessly, mindlessly, because most people have such weak imaginations they couldn’t possibly understand what they’re saying when they say that a miracle is something impossible.  Ask anyone what that means, what it means to see a miracle, and they will say that it’s something impossible, but they mean that a miracle is something formerly believed to be impossible that turns out not to be, not to be impossible, in other words, but possible after all.  If this were really true, then miracles would be the most ordinary things in the world, the most uninspiring things in the world, and what can one expect from people who have never been anything but ordinary and uninspired." -- Michael Cisco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/343400-what-would-the-daughters-of-the-rich-do-with-themselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 08:15:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Angela Carter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/343400-what-would-the-daughters-of-the-rich-do-with-themselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What would the daughters of the rich do with themselves if the poor ceased to exist?" -- Angela Carter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371274-i-don-t-live-by-the-fuckin-dow-jones-anymore-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 18:36:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Minister Faust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371274-i-don-t-live-by-the-fuckin-dow-jones-anymore-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't live by the fuckin Dow Jones anymore. I live by the Tao, Jones." -- Minister Faust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393284-helping-other-people-is-a-drug-so-dangerous-that-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 06:39:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Penelope Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393284-helping-other-people-is-a-drug-so-dangerous-that-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Helping other people is a drug so dangerous that there is no cure short of total abstention." -- Penelope Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494543-i-like-to-talk-about-america-it-s-so-mysterious</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 18:06:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Robert Ashley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494543-i-like-to-talk-about-america-it-s-so-mysterious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like to talk about America. It's so mysterious." -- Robert Ashley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644242-i-got-my-face-close-up-to-the-man-still</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 19:18:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Daniel Woodrell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644242-i-got-my-face-close-up-to-the-man-still]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I got my face close up to the man still standing. I let him understand that there was oodles of danger in me; my head wobbled loose, three ticks off center. This scary face is all them such as me has to show this other world, the world in charge of our world, that musters any authority, gets any reluctant respect at all. If us lower elements didn't show our teeth plenty and act fast to bite, we'd just be soft, loamy dirt anybody could walk on, anytime, and you know they would, too, since even &lt;i&gt;with&lt;/i&gt; a show of teeth there's a grassless path worn clear across our brains and backs." -- Daniel Woodrell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644248-i-think-one-of-our-cardinal-fuckups-is-how-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 19:24:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Daniel Woodrell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644248-i-think-one-of-our-cardinal-fuckups-is-how-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think one of our cardinal fuckups is how we insist that even vicious whimsical crazy shit needs to make sense, add up, belong to a reason. We lay this pain on ourselves--there must be a reason behind this horror, there must, but I ain't adequate to findin' it, and that's my fault, so torture me some more." -- Daniel Woodrell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/691641-without-ever-exactly-putting-his-mind-to-it-he-s-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 07:12:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ben Fountain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/691641-without-ever-exactly-putting-his-mind-to-it-he-s-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without ever exactly putting his mind to it, he's come to believe that loss is the standard trajectory.  Something new appears in the world-a baby, say, or a car or a house, or an individual shows some special talent-with luck and huge expenditures of soul and effort you might keep the project stoked for a while, but eventually, ultimately, its going down.  This is a truth so brutally self-evident that he can't fathom why it's not more widely percieved, hence his contempt for the usual public shock and outrage when a particular situation goes to hell.  The war is fucked?  Well, duh.  Nine-eleven? Slow train coming.  They hate our freedoms? Yo, they hate our actual guts!  Billy suspects his fellow Americans secretly know better, but something in the land is stuck on teenage drama, on extravagant theatrics of ravaged innocence and soothing mud wallows of self-justifying pity." -- Ben Fountain]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
