<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/28646-bryan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/28646-bryan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 13:00:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253648-stilletos-of-a-frozen-stillicide-in-the-lovely-line</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 13:00:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bryan add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253648-stilletos-of-a-frozen-stillicide-in-the-lovely-line]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stilletos of a frozen stillicide [...] In the lovely line heading this comment the reader should note the last word. My dictionary defines it as 'a succession of drops falling from the eaves, eavesdrop, cavesdrop.' I remember having encountered it for the first time in a poem by Thomas Hardy. The bright frost has eternalized the bright eavesdrop." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154795-there-was-a-time-in-my-demented-youth-when-somehow</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 13:02:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bryan add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154795-there-was-a-time-in-my-demented-youth-when-somehow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was a time in my demented youth
When somehow I suspected that the truth
About survival after death was known
To every human being: I alone
Knew nothing, and a great conspiracy
Of books and people hid the truth from me." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214696-i-was-the-shadow-of-the-waxwing-slain-by-the-false</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 13:02:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bryan add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214696-i-was-the-shadow-of-the-waxwing-slain-by-the-false]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was the shadow of the waxwing slain/By the false azure in the windowpane..." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256847-feeling-a-bit-nervous-as-most-people-do-at-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2010 04:42:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bryan add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256847-feeling-a-bit-nervous-as-most-people-do-at-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Feeling a bit nervous, as most people do at the prospect of seeing a doctor, I thought I would buy on my way to him something soothing to prevent an accelerated pulse from misleading credulous science." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392736-a-good-movie-can-take-you-out-of-your-dull</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2011 03:21:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bryan add a quote by Pauline Kael]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392736-a-good-movie-can-take-you-out-of-your-dull]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A good movie can take you out of your dull funk and the hopelessness that so often goes with slipping into a theatre; a good movie can make you feel alive again, in contact, not just lost in another city. Good movies make you care, make you believe in possibilities again. If somewhere in the Hollywood-entertainment world someone has managed to break through with something that speaks to you, then it isn’t all corruption. The movie doesn’t have to be great; it can be stupid and empty and you can still have the joy of a good performance, or the joy in just a good line. An actor’s scowl, a small subversive gesture, a dirty remark that someone tosses off with a mock-innocent face, and the world makes a little bit of sense. Sitting there alone or painfully alone because those with you do not react as you do, you know there must be others perhaps in this very theatre or in this city, surely in other theatres in other cities, now, in the past or future, who react as you do. And because movies are the most total and encompassing art form we have, these reactions can seem the most personal and, maybe the most important, imaginable. The romance of movies is not just in those stories and those people on the screen but in the adolescent dream of meeting others who feel as you do about what you’ve seen. You do meet them, of course, and you know each other at once because you talk less about good movies than about what you love in bad movies." -- Pauline Kael]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104495-he-gave-her-a-bright-fake-smile-so-much-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 02:23:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bryan add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104495-he-gave-her-a-bright-fake-smile-so-much-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He gave her a bright fake smile; so much of life was a putting off of unhappiness for another time. Nothing was ever lost by delay. He had a dim idea that perhaps if one delayed long enough, things were taken out of one's hands altogether by death." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104499-point-me-out-the-happy-man-and-i-will-point</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2012 09:30:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bryan add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104499-point-me-out-the-happy-man-and-i-will-point]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Point me out the happy man and I will point you out either extreme egotism, selfishness, evil -- or else an absolute ignorance." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/748471-so-he-was-always-in-the-town-at-one-place</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 02:27:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bryan add a quote by D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/748471-so-he-was-always-in-the-town-at-one-place]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So he was always in the town at one place or another, drinking, knocking about with the men he knew. It really wearied him. He talked to barmaids, to almost any woman, but there was that dark, strained look in his eyes, as if he were hunting something.

Everything seemed so different, so unreal. There seemed no reason why people should go along the street, and houses pile up in the daylight. There seemed no reason why these things should occupy the space, instead of leaving it empty. His friends talked to him: he heard the sounds, and he answered. But why there should be the noise of speech he could not understand." -- D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/489919-they-can-print-statistics-and-count-the-populations-in-hundreds</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 08:36:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bryan add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/489919-they-can-print-statistics-and-count-the-populations-in-hundreds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They can print statistics and count the populations in hundreds of thousands, but to each man a city consists of no more than a few streets, a few houses, a few people. Remove those few and a city exists no longer except as a pain in the memory, like a pain of an amputated leg no longer there." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/860209-we-most-of-us-hesitate-to-make-so-complete-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 07:29:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bryan add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/860209-we-most-of-us-hesitate-to-make-so-complete-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We most of us hesitate to make so complete a statement - we remember and we foresee and we doubt. She had no doubts. The moment only mattered. Eternity is said not to be an extension of time but an absence of time, and sometimes it seemed to me that her abandonment touched that strange mathematical point of endlessness, a point with no width, occupying no space. What did time matter - all the past and the other men she may from time to time (there is that word again) have known, or all the future in which she might be making the same statement with the same sense of truth? When I replied that I loved her too in that way, I was the liar, not she, for I never lose the consciousness of time: to me the present is never here: it is always last year or next week." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/574044-it-did-not-do-to-think-nor-for-the-matter</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2013 08:16:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bryan add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/574044-it-did-not-do-to-think-nor-for-the-matter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It did not do to think, nor, for the matter of that, to feel. She gave up trying to understand herself, and joined the vast armies of the benighted, who follow neither the heart nor the brain, and march to their destiny by catch-words. The armies are full of pleasant and pious folk. But they have yielded to the only enemy that matters--the enemy within. They have sinned against passion and truth, and vain will be their strife after virtue. As the years pass, they are censured. Their pleasantry and their piety show cracks, their wit becomes cynicism, their unselfishness hypocrisy; they feel and produce discomfort wherever they go. They have sinned against Eros and against Pallas Athene, and not by any heavenly intervention, but by the ordinary course of nature, those allied deities will be avenged." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
