<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/286825-shveta-thakrar]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/286825-shveta-thakrar" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 13:13:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236926-a-journey-is-a-never-ending-road--a-discovery-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 13:13:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shveta add a quote by Loreena McKennitt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236926-a-journey-is-a-never-ending-road--a-discovery-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A journey is a never ending road- a discovery that there is so much more to hold us together than to tear us apart. These are the dreams we hold in the palm of our hand." -- Loreena McKennitt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266030-obsessed-by-a-fairy-tale-we-spend-our-lives-searching</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 07:41:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shveta add a quote by Eugene O'Neill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266030-obsessed-by-a-fairy-tale-we-spend-our-lives-searching]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Obsessed by a fairy tale, we spend our lives searching for a magic door and a lost kingdom of peace." -- Eugene O'Neill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280757-you-must-never-behave-as-if-your-life-belongs-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2010 13:52:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shveta add a quote by Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280757-you-must-never-behave-as-if-your-life-belongs-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must never behave as if your life belongs to a man. Do you hear me?' Aunty Ifeka said. 'Your life belongs to you and you alone." -- Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18276-good-books-don-t-give-up-all-their-secrets-at-once</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 07:07:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shveta add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18276-good-books-don-t-give-up-all-their-secrets-at-once]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good books don't give up all their secrets at once." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6273-don-t-ask-what-the-world-needs-ask-what-makes-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 13:13:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shveta add a quote by Howard Thurman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6273-don-t-ask-what-the-world-needs-ask-what-makes-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don’t ask what the world needs. Ask what makes you come alive, and go do it. Because what the world needs is people who have come alive." -- Howard Thurman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62605-literature-is-a-textually-transmitted-disease-normally-contracted-in-childhood</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 11:33:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shveta add a quote by Jane Yolen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62605-literature-is-a-textually-transmitted-disease-normally-contracted-in-childhood]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Literature is a textually transmitted disease, normally contracted in childhood." -- Jane Yolen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321-if-there-s-a-book-that-you-want-to-read-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 14:18:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shveta add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321-if-there-s-a-book-that-you-want-to-read-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there's a book that you want to read, but it hasn't been written yet, then you must write it." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/438948-a-cupcake-temple-her-chest-still-tight-with-anxiety-bertie</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 12:58:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shveta add a quote by Lisa Mantchev]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/438948-a-cupcake-temple-her-chest-still-tight-with-anxiety-bertie]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A cupcake temple?' Her chest still tight with anxiety, Bertie forced herself to imagine it: bricks of pound cake mortared with buttercream and chocolate ganache, torches like striped birthday candles set into the walls, pilgrims upon the Path of Delectable Righteousness delivering daily tributes of almond paste and raspberry filling. . . ." -- Lisa Mantchev]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/527605-something-that-s-bothered-me-for-a-while-now-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 10:44:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shveta add a quote by Foz Meadows]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/527605-something-that-s-bothered-me-for-a-while-now-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Something that’s bothered me for a while now is the current profligacy in YA culture of Team Boy 1 vs Team Boy 2 fangirling. [...] Despite the fact that I have no objection to shipping, this particular species of team-choosing troubled me, though I had difficulty understanding why. Then I saw it applied to Suzanne Collins’s The Hunger Games trilogy – Team Peeta vs Team Gale – and all of a sudden it hit me that anyone who thought romance and love-triangles were the main event in that series had utterly missed the point. Sure, those elements are present in the story, but they aren’t anywhere near being the bones of it, because The Hunger Games, more than anything else, is about war, survival, politics, propaganda and power. Seeing such a strong, raw narrative reduced to a single vapid argument – which boy is cuter? – made me physically angry.

So, look. People read different books for different reasons. The thing I love about a story are not necessarily the things you love, and vice versa. But riddle me this: are the readers of these series really so excited, so thrilled by the prospect of choosing! between! two! different! boys! that they have to boil entire narratives down to a binary equation based on male physical perfection and, if we’re very lucky, chivalrous behaviour? While feminism most certainly champions the right of women to chose their own partners, it also supports them to choose things besides men, or to postpone the question of partnership in favour of other pursuits – knowledge, for instance. Adventure. Careers. Wild dancing. Fun. Friendship. Travel. Glorious mayhem. And while, as a woman now happily entering her fourth year of marriage, I’d be the last person on Earth to suggest that male companionship is inimical to any of those things, what’s starting to bother me is the comparative dearth of YA stories which aren’t, in some way, shape or form, focussed on Girls Getting Boyfriends, and particularly Hot Immortal Or Magical Boyfriends Whom They Will Love For All Eternity.

Blog post: Love Team Freezer" -- Foz Meadows]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/452034-i-want-to-talk-about-creating-your-life-there-s-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 12:40:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shveta add a quote by Laini Taylor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/452034-i-want-to-talk-about-creating-your-life-there-s-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to talk about creating your life. There’s a quote I love, from the poet Mary Oliver, that goes:

Tell me, what is it you plan to do with your one wild and precious life?

I so clearly remember what it was like, being young and always in the grip of some big fat daydream. I wanted to be a writer always, but more than that, I wanted to have an extraordinary life. I’m sure I dreamed it a million different ways, and that plenty of them were ridiculous, but I think the daydreams were training for writing, and I also think they spurred me to pursue my dreams for real.

Daydreaming, however awesome it is, is passive. It happens in your head. Learning to make dreams real is another matter, and I think it should be the work of your life. Everyone’s life, whatever their dream (unless their dream is to be an axe murderer or something.)

It took me a while to finish a book. Too long. And you know, it doesn’t matter how good a writer you are unless you finish what you start! I think this is the hardest part for most people who want to write. I was in my mid-30s before I figured it out. The brain plays tricks. You can be convinced you’re following your dream, or that you’re going to start tomorrow, and years can pass like that. Years.

The thing is, there will be pressure to adjust your expectations, always shrinking them, shrinking, shrinking, until they fit in your pocket like a folded slip of paper, and you know what happens to folded slips of paper in your pocket. They go through the wash and get ruined. Don’t ever put your dream in your pocket. If you have to put it somewhere, get one of those holsters for your belt, like my dad has for his phone, so you can whip it out at any moment. 

Hello there, dream.

Also, don’t be realistic. The word “realistic” is poison. Who decides? 

And “backup plan” is code for, “Give up on your dreams,” and everyone I know who put any energy into a backup plan is now living that backup plan instead of their dream. Put all your energy into your dream. That’s the only way it will ever become real.

The world at large has this attitude, “What makes you so special that you think you deserve an extraordinary life?” 

Personally, I think the passion for an extraordinary life, and the courage to pursue it, is what makes us special. And I don’t even think of it as an “extraordinary life” anymore so much as simple happiness. It’s rarer than it should be, and I believe it comes from creating a life that fits you perfectly, not taking what’s already there, but making your own from scratch. 

You can let life happen to you, or you can happen to life. It’s harder, but so much better." -- Laini Taylor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398408-i-want-to-think-again-of-dangerous-and-noble-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 15:58:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shveta add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398408-i-want-to-think-again-of-dangerous-and-noble-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to think again of dangerous and noble things.
 I want to be light and frolicsome.
 I want to be improbable beautiful and afraid of nothing,
 as though I had wings." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25-we-are-all-in-the-gutter-but-some-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 14:22:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shveta add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25-we-are-all-in-the-gutter-but-some-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all in the gutter, but some of us are looking at the stars." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70845-the-stars-began-to-burn-through-the-sheets-of-clouds</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 21:16:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shveta add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70845-the-stars-began-to-burn-through-the-sheets-of-clouds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the stars began to burn
through the sheets of clouds,
and there was a new voice
which you slowly
recognized as your own" -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1205926-people-would-walk-in-and-walk-out-of-your-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 09:40:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shveta add a quote by Michael Bassey Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1205926-people-would-walk-in-and-walk-out-of-your-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People would walk in and walk out of your life, but the one whose footstep made a long lasting impression is the one you should never allow to walk out." -- Michael Bassey Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
