<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/28733-carolee-wheeler]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/28733-carolee-wheeler" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2007 09:08:25 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6873-i-think-it-s-so-foolish-for-people-to-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2007 09:08:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Georgia O'Keefe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6873-i-think-it-s-so-foolish-for-people-to-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think it's so foolish for people to want to be happy.  Happy is so momentary--you're happy for an instant and then you start thinking again.  Interest is the most important thing in life; happiness is temporary, but interest is continuous." -- Georgia O'Keefe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18410-i-think-we-are-well-advised-to-keep-on-nodding</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 22:45:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18410-i-think-we-are-well-advised-to-keep-on-nodding]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think we are well advised to keep on nodding terms with the  people we used to be, whether we find them attractive company or not.  Otherwise they turn up unannounced and surprise us, come hammering on the mind's door at 4 a.m. of a bad night and demand to know who deserted them, who betrayed them, who is going to make amends." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103410-who-was-it-who-said-that-every-virtue-contains-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 22:45:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Kevin Brockmeier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103410-who-was-it-who-said-that-every-virtue-contains-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who was it who said that every virtue contains its corresponding vice? C.S. Lewis? Virginia Woolf? You forget. But it has always worried you that what the virtue of wit contained was the vice of scorn." -- Kevin Brockmeier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/262-i-lost-the-conviction-that-lights-would-always-turn-green</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 22:45:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/262-i-lost-the-conviction-that-lights-would-always-turn-green]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I lost the conviction that lights would always turn green for me, the pleasant certainty that those rather passive virtues which had won me approval as a child automatically guaranteed me not only Phi Beta Kappa keys but happiness, honor, and the love of a good man; lost a certain touching faith in the totem power of good manners, clean hair, and a proven competence on the Stanford-Binet scale. To such doubtful amulets had my self-respect been pinned, and I faced myself that day with the non-plused apprehension of someone who has come across a vampire and has no crucifix at hand." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103414-people-who-read-d-h-lawrence-suspect-that-the-forbidden-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 22:45:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Kevin Brockmeier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103414-people-who-read-d-h-lawrence-suspect-that-the-forbidden-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People who read D.H. Lawrence suspect that the forbidden is not necessarily without its virtue, and so are easily persuaded that the forbidden and the virtuous are one and the same." -- Kevin Brockmeier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 21:30:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102204-it-seems-to-me-that-almost-all-our-sadnesses-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 10:51:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102204-it-seems-to-me-that-almost-all-our-sadnesses-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seems to me that almost all our sadnesses are moments of tension, which we feel as paralysis because we no longer hear our astonished emotions living. Because we are alone with the unfamiliar presence that has entered us; because everything we trust and are used to is for a moment taken away from us; because we stand in the midst of a transition where we cannot remain standing. That is why the sadness passes: the new presence inside us, the presence that has been added, has entered our heart, has gone into its innermost chamber and is no longer even there, - is already in our bloodstream. And we don't know what it was. We could easily be made to believe that nothing happened, and yet we have changed, as a house that a guest has entered changes. We can't say who has come, perhaps we will never know, but many signs indicate that the future enters us in this way in order to be transformed in us, long before it happens. And that is why it is so important to be solitary and attentive when one is sad: because the seemingly uneventful and motionless moment when our future steps into us is so much closer to life than that other loud and accidental point of time when it happens to us as if from outside. The quieter we are, the more patient and open we are in our sadnesses, the more deeply and serenely the new presence can enter us, and the more we can make it our own, the more it becomes our fate." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147290-i-want-to-be-with-those-who-know-secret-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 10:54:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147290-i-want-to-be-with-those-who-know-secret-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to be with those who know secret things or else alone." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9371-the-purpose-of-life-is-to-be-defeated-by-greater</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 17:48:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9371-the-purpose-of-life-is-to-be-defeated-by-greater]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The purpose of life is to be defeated by greater and greater things." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141479-why-do-you-want-to-shut-out-of-your-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 17:48:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141479-why-do-you-want-to-shut-out-of-your-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why do you want to shut out of your life any uneasiness, any misery, any depression, since after all you don't know what work these conditions are doing inside you? Why do you want to persecute yourself with the question of where all this is coming from and where it is going? Since you know, after all, that you are in the midst of transitions and you wished for nothing so much as to change. If there is anything unhealthy in your reactions, just bear in mind that sickness is the means by which an organism frees itself from what is alien; so one must simply help it to be sick, to have its whole sickness and to break out with it, since that is the way it gets better." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145545-lonely-s-like-any-other-organism-competitive-and-resourceful-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 18:37:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Sebastian Faulks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145545-lonely-s-like-any-other-organism-competitive-and-resourceful-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lonely's like any other organism; competitive and resourceful in the struggle to perpetuate itself." -- Sebastian Faulks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/389178-we-are-often-told-we-are-materialistic-it-seems-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 20:15:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by George Monbiot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/389178-we-are-often-told-we-are-materialistic-it-seems-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are often told we are materialistic. It seems to me, we are not materialistic enough. We have a disrespect for materials. We use it quickly and carelessly. 

If were genuinely materialistic people, we would understand where materials come from and where they go to. 

But, at the moment, the entire global economy seems to be built on the model of digging things up from one hole in the ground on one side of the earth, transporting them around the world, using them for a few days, and sticking them in a hole in the ground on the other side of the world." -- George Monbiot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442429-it-was-interesting-how-much-of-adult-life-consisted-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 12:14:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Kevin Canty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442429-it-was-interesting-how-much-of-adult-life-consisted-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was interesting, how much of adult life consisted of pretending." -- Kevin Canty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442430-also-people-pretended-not-to-want-what-they-wanted-pretending</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 12:15:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Kevin Canty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442430-also-people-pretended-not-to-want-what-they-wanted-pretending]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Also: people pretended not to want what they wanted. Pretending tried to hide the will. That was the secret of adult life, the undisclosed motor of the whole thing. People wanted what they wanted. They did what they could to get it. It wasn't complicated. Kenny knew that was the last step he needed to take before he could be an adult: he had to learn what he wanted, then had to learn to &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; what he wanted." -- Kevin Canty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445376-i-m-turning-fifty-and-it-is-just-now-dawning-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 12:03:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Dana Spiotta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445376-i-m-turning-fifty-and-it-is-just-now-dawning-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm turning fifty, and it is just now dawning on me that I have limited time,&quot; Nash said. &quot;No kidding. I always felt my life was circumscribed by the finite terms, you know? There is a whole world of things I missed out on and will never experience. Whatever I have done, there is an endless amount I have not done. Do you know what that tells me?&quot;
...
&quot;It tells me it is not meant to be this all-encompassing journey. It is not meant to be catholic or encyclopedic. By now I have carved some grooves in this life. A few. What I need to do is hunker down and make those grooves deep and indelible." -- Dana Spiotta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445379-i-wondered-if-my-life-was-going-to-be-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 12:06:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Dana Spiotta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445379-i-wondered-if-my-life-was-going-to-be-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wondered if my life was going to be one immersion after another, a great march of shallow, unpopular popular culture infatuations that don't really last and don't really mean anything. Sometimes I even think maybe my deepest obsessions are just random manifestations of my loneliness or isolation. Maybe I infuse ordinary experience with a kind of sacred aura to mitigate the spiritual vapidity of my life....no, it is beautiful to be enraptured. To be enthralled by something, anything. And it isn't random. It speaks to you for a reason. If you wanted to, you could look at it that way, and you might find you aren't wasting your life. You are discovering things about yourself and the world, even if it is just what you find beautiful, right now, this second." -- Dana Spiotta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18719-the-truth-will-set-you-free-but-not-until-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 21:16:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18719-the-truth-will-set-you-free-but-not-until-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth will set you free. But not until it is finished with you." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 17:33:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184013-i-don-t-trust-people-who-don-t-love-themselves-and-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 17:35:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184013-i-don-t-trust-people-who-don-t-love-themselves-and-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't trust people who don't love themselves and tell me, 'I love you.' ... There is an African saying which is: Be careful when a naked person offers you a shirt." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/86640-no-need-to-hurry-no-need-to-sparkle-no-need</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 21:34:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/86640-no-need-to-hurry-no-need-to-sparkle-no-need]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No need to hurry. No need to sparkle. No need to be anybody but oneself." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/856195-some-periods-of-our-growth-are-so-confusing-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2014 15:40:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carolee add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/856195-some-periods-of-our-growth-are-so-confusing-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some periods of our growth are so confusing that we don’t even recognize that growth is happening. We may feel hostile or angry or weepy and hysterical, or we may feel depressed. It would never occur to us, unless we stumbled on a book or a person who explained to us, that we were in fact in the process of change, of actually becoming larger, spiritually, than we were before. Whenever we grow, we tend to feel it, as a young seed must feel the weight and inertia of the earth as it seeks to break out of its shell on its way to becoming a plant. Often the feeling is anything but pleasant. But what is most unpleasant is the not knowing what is happening. Those long periods when something inside ourselves seems to be waiting, holding its breath, unsure about what the next step should be, eventually become the periods we wait for, for it is in those periods that we realize that we are being prepared for the next phase of our life and that, in all probability, a new level of the personality is about to be revealed." -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
