<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/287473-cui]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/287473-cui" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 05:08:18 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70599-i-get-irritated-i-get-upset-especially-when-i-m-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 05:08:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70599-i-get-irritated-i-get-upset-especially-when-i-m-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I get irritated, I get upset. Especially when I'm in a hurry. But I see it all as part of our training. To get irritated is to lose our way in life." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131591-nothing-is-original-steal-from-anywhere-that-resonates-with-inspiration</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2011 17:30:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Jim Jarmusch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131591-nothing-is-original-steal-from-anywhere-that-resonates-with-inspiration]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing is original. Steal from anywhere that resonates with inspiration or fuels your imagination. Devour old films, new films, music, books, paintings, photographs, poems, dreams, random conversations, architecture, bridges, street signs, trees, clouds, bodies of water, light and shadows. Select only things to steal from that speak directly to your soul. If you do this, your work (and theft) will be authentic. Authenticity is invaluable; originality is non-existent. And don’t bother concealing your thievery - celebrate it if you feel like it. In any case, always remember what Jean-Luc Godard said: “It’s not where you take things from - it’s where you take them to.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;MovieMaker Magazine&lt;/i&gt; #53 - Winter, January 22, 2004 ]" -- Jim Jarmusch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 13:50:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425317-how-often-do-we-tell-our-own-life-story-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 13:58:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Julian Barnes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425317-how-often-do-we-tell-our-own-life-story-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How often do we tell our own life story? How often do we adjust, embellish, make sly cuts? And the longer life goes on, the fewer are those around to challenge our account, to remind us that our life is not our life, merely the story we have told about our life. Told to others, but&amp;mdash;mainly&amp;mdash;to ourselves." -- Julian Barnes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460624-history-is-that-certainty-produced-at-the-point-where-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 13:58:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Julian Barnes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460624-history-is-that-certainty-produced-at-the-point-where-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["History is that certainty produced at the point where the imperfections of memory meet the inadequacies of documentation." -- Julian Barnes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338604-memory-is-like-fiction-or-else-it-s-fiction-that-s-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 14:04:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338604-memory-is-like-fiction-or-else-it-s-fiction-that-s-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Memory is like fiction; or else it's fiction that's like memory. This really came home to me once I started writing fiction, that memory seemed a kind of fiction, or vice versa. Either way, no matter how hard you try to put everything neatly into shape, the context wanders this way and that, until finally the context isn't even there anymore. You're left with this pile of kittens lolling all over one another. Warm with life, hopelessly unstable. And then to put these things out as saleable items, you call them finished products - at times it's downright embarrassing just to think of it. Honestly, it can make me blush." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 18:07:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Groucho Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Outside of a dog, a book is man's best friend. Inside of a dog it's too dark to read." -- Groucho Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 18:12:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32862-you-are-a-little-soul-carrying-about-a-corpse-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 16:31:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32862-you-are-a-little-soul-carrying-about-a-corpse-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are a little soul carrying about a corpse, as Epictetus used to say." -- Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123384-the-art-of-living-is-more-like-wrestling-than-dancing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 19:11:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123384-the-art-of-living-is-more-like-wrestling-than-dancing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The art of living is more like wrestling than dancing, in so far as it stands ready against the accidental and the unforeseen, and is not apt to fall." -- Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167419-life-is-opinion</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 19:11:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167419-life-is-opinion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is opinion." -- Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/426719-there-comes-a-time-in-a-man-s-life-when-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 13:27:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Bernard Malamud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/426719-there-comes-a-time-in-a-man-s-life-when-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There comes a time in a man's life when to get where he has to go--if there are no doors or windows--he walks through a wall." -- Bernard Malamud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12428-i-want-to-stand-as-close-to-the-edge-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2012 16:02:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12428-i-want-to-stand-as-close-to-the-edge-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to stand as close to the edge as I can without going over. Out on the edge you see all kinds of things you can't see from the center." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131860-the-greatest-patriotism-is-to-tell-your-country-when-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 21:14:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Julian Barnes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131860-the-greatest-patriotism-is-to-tell-your-country-when-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greatest patriotism is to tell your country when it is behaving dishonorably, foolishly, viciously." -- Julian Barnes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/348156-if-you-don-t-become-the-ocean-you-ll-be-seasick-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 19:38:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Leonard Cohen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/348156-if-you-don-t-become-the-ocean-you-ll-be-seasick-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you don't become the ocean, you'll be seasick every day." -- Leonard Cohen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518950-it-is-best-as-one-grows-older-to-strip-oneself</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 15:31:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Sylvia Townsend Warner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518950-it-is-best-as-one-grows-older-to-strip-oneself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is best as one grows older to strip oneself of possessions, to shed oneself downward like a tree, to be almost wholly earth before one dies." -- Sylvia Townsend Warner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177343-you-get-them-wrong-before-you-meet-them-while-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 15:39:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177343-you-get-them-wrong-before-you-meet-them-while-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You get them wrong before you meet them, while you're anticipating meeting them; you get them wrong while you're with them; and then you go home to tell somebody else about the meeting and you get them all wrong again. Since the same generally goes for them with you, the whole thing is really a dazzling illusion. ... The fact remains that getting people right is not what living is all about anyway. It's getting them wrong that is living, getting them wrong and wrong and wrong and then, on careful reconsideration, getting them wrong again. That's how we know we're alive: we're wrong. Maybe the best thing would be to forget being right or wrong about people and just go along for the ride. But if you can do that -- well, lucky you." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151387-people-were-standing-up-everywhere-shouting-this-is-me-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 15:39:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151387-people-were-standing-up-everywhere-shouting-this-is-me-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People were standing up everywhere shouting, &quot;This is me! This is me!&quot; Every time you looked at them they stood up and told you who they were, and the truth of it was that they had no more idea who or what they were than he had. They believed their flashing signs, too. They ought to be standing up and shouting, &quot;This isn't me! This isn't me!&quot; They would if they had any decency. &quot;This isn't me!&quot; Then you might know how to proceed through the flashing bullshit of this world." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280481-you-fight-your-superficiality-your-shallowness-so-as-to-try</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 15:40:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280481-you-fight-your-superficiality-your-shallowness-so-as-to-try]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You fight your superficiality, your shallowness, so as to try to come at people without unreal expectations, without an overload of bias or hope or arrogance, as untanklike as you can be, sans cannon and machine guns and steel plating half a foot thick; you come at them unmenacingly on your own ten toes instead of tearing up the turf with your caterpillar treads, take them on with an open mind, as equals, man to man, as we used to say, and yet you never fail to get them wrong.  You might as well have the &quot;brain&quot; of a tank.  You get them wrong before you meet them, while you're anticipating meeting them; you get them wrong while you're with them; and then you go home to tell somebody else about the meeting and you get them all wrong again.  Since the same generally goes for them with you, the whole thing is really a dazzling illusion empty of all perception, an astonishing farce of misperception.  And yet what are we to do about this terribly significant business of &quot;other people,&quot; which gets bled of the significance we think it has and takes on instead a significance that is ludicrous, so ill-equipped are we all to envision one another's interior workings and invisible aims?  Is everyone to go off and lock the door and sit secluded like the lonely writers do, in a soundproof cell, summoning people out of words and then proposing that these word people are closer to the real thing than the real people that we mangle with our ignorance every day?  The fact remains that getting people right is not what living is all about anyway.  It's getting them wrong that is living, getting them wrong and wrong and wrong and then, on careful reconsideration, getting them wrong again.  That's how we know we're alive:  we're wrong.  Maybe the best thing would be to forget being right or wrong about people and just go along for the ride.  But if you can do that--well, lucky you." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/469224-life-shouldn-t-be-about-the-either-or-we-re-capable-of-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 15:44:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/469224-life-shouldn-t-be-about-the-either-or-we-re-capable-of-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life shouldn't be about the either/or. We're capable of more than that, you know?" -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35482-and-i-asked-myself-about-the-present-how-wide-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 17:00:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35482-and-i-asked-myself-about-the-present-how-wide-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I asked myself about the present: how wide it was, how deep it was, how much was mine to keep." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/944659-the-future-has-an-ancient-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 22:15:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Carlo Levi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/944659-the-future-has-an-ancient-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The future has an ancient heart." -- Carlo Levi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172617-the-stupidity-of-people-comes-from-having-an-answer-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 10:27:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172617-the-stupidity-of-people-comes-from-having-an-answer-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The stupidity of people comes from having an answer for everything. The wisdom of the novel comes from having a question for everything....The novelist teaches the reader to comprehend the world as a question. There is wisdom and tolerance in that attitude. In a world built on sacrosanct certainties the novel is dead. The totalitarian world, whether founded on Marx, Islam, or anything else, is a world of answers rather than questions. There, the novel has no place." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142715-it-takes-so-little-so-infinitely-little-for-a-person</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 10:27:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142715-it-takes-so-little-so-infinitely-little-for-a-person]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It takes so little, so infinitely little, for a person to cross the border beyond which everything loses meaning: love, convictions, faith, history. Human life -- and herein lies its secret -- takes place in the immediate proximity of that border, even in direct contact with it; it is not miles away, but a fraction of an inch." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395557-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 14:20:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395557-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hello, babies. Welcome to Earth. It's hot in the summer and cold in the winter. It's round and wet and crowded. At the outside, babies, you've got about a hundred years here. There's only one rule that I know of, babies--: God damn it, you've got to be kind." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13719-we-are-what-we-pretend-to-be-so-we-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2013 16:59:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13719-we-are-what-we-pretend-to-be-so-we-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are what we pretend to be, so we must be careful about what we pretend to be." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196431-sometimes-people-put-up-walls-not-to-keep-others-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2013 17:08:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Banana Yoshimoto]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196431-sometimes-people-put-up-walls-not-to-keep-others-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes people put up walls, not to keep others out, but to see who cares enough to break them down." -- Banana Yoshimoto]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98109-even-when-i-try-to-stir-myself-up-i-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2013 17:08:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Banana Yoshimoto]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98109-even-when-i-try-to-stir-myself-up-i-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even when I try to stir myself up, I just get irritated because I can't make anything come out. And in the middle of the night I lie here thinking about all this. If I don't get back on track somehow, I'm dead, that's the sense I get. There isn't a single strong emotion inside me." -- Banana Yoshimoto]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/810632-even-the-wolf-has-two-and-more-than-two-souls</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 09:32:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/810632-even-the-wolf-has-two-and-more-than-two-souls]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even the wolf has two, and more than two, souls in his wolf's breast, and he who desires to be a wolf falls into the same forgetfulness as the man who sings: &quot;If I could be a child once more!&quot; He who sentimentally sings of blessed childhood is thinking of the return to nature and innocence and the origin of things, and has quite forgotten that these blessed children are beset with conflict and complexities and capable of all suffering.
There is, in fact, no way back either to the wolf or to the child. From the very start there is no innocence and no singleness. Every created thing, even the simplest, is already guilty, already
multiple. It has been thrown into the muddy stream of being and may never more swim back again to its source. The way to innocence, to the uncreated and to God leads on, not back, not back to the wolf or to the child, but ever further into sin, ever deeper into human life. Nor will suicide really solve your problem, unhappy Steppenwolf. You will, instead, embark on the longer and wearier and harder road of life. You will have to multiply many times your two-fold being and complicate your complexities still further. Instead of narrowing your world and simplifying your soul, you will have to absorb more and more of the world and at last take all of it up in your painfully expanded soul, if you are ever to find peace." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6010-whatever-it-is-you-re-seeking-won-t-come-in-the-form</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 07:58:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cui add a quote by Haruki Marukami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6010-whatever-it-is-you-re-seeking-won-t-come-in-the-form]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever it is you're seeking won't come in the form you're expecting." -- Haruki Marukami]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
