<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/287800-andrea-avalon]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/287800-andrea-avalon" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 12:24:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132157-the-pessimist-resembles-a-man-who-observes-with-fear-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 12:24:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132157-the-pessimist-resembles-a-man-who-observes-with-fear-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The pessimist resembles a man who observes with fear and sadness that his wall calendar, from which he daily tears a sheet, grows thinner with each passing day.  On the other hand, the person who attacks the problems of life actively is like a man who removes each successive leaf from his calendar and files it neatly and carefully away with its predecessors, after first having jotted down a few diary notes on the back.  He can reflect with pride and joy on all the richness set down in these notes, on all the life he has already lived to the fullest.  What will it matter to him if he notices that he is growing old?  Has he any reason to envy the young people whom he sees, or wax nostalgic over his own lost youth?  What reasons has he to envy a young person?  For the possibilities that a young person has, the future which is in store for him?

No, thank you,' he will think.  'Instead of possibilities, I have realities in my past, not only the reality of work done and of love loved, but of sufferings bravely suffered.  These sufferings are even the things of which I am most proud, although these are things which cannot inspire envy.' &quot;

From &quot;Logotherapy in a Nutshell&quot;, an essay" -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/748876-leaving-is-not-enough-you-must-stay-gone-train-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 08:39:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Marty McConnell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/748876-leaving-is-not-enough-you-must-stay-gone-train-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Leaving is not enough. You must stay gone. Train your heart like a dog. Change the locks even on the house he's never visited. You lucky, lucky girl. You have an apartment just your size. A bathtub full of tea. A heart the size of Arizona, but not nearly so arid. Don't wish away your cracked past, your crooked toes, your problems are papier mache puppets you made or bought because the vendor at the market was so compelling you just had to have them. You had to have him. And you did. And now you pull down the bridge between your houses, you make him call before he visits, you take a lover for granted, you take a lover who looks at you like maybe you are magic. Make the first bottle you consume in this place a relic. Place it on whatever altar you fashion with a knife and five cranberries. Don't lose too much weight. Stupid girls are always trying to disappear as revenge. And you are not stupid. You loved a man with more hands than a parade of beggars, and here you stand. Heart like a four-poster bed. Heart like a canvas. Heart leaking something so strong they can smell it in the street." -- Marty McConnell]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
