<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/287889-michele]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/287889-michele" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 11:35:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24729-there-are-it-seems-two-muses-the-muse-of-inspiration</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 11:35:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michele add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24729-there-are-it-seems-two-muses-the-muse-of-inspiration]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are, it seems, two muses: the Muse of Inspiration, who gives us inarticulate visions and desires, and the Muse of Realization, who returns again and again to say &quot;It is yet more difficult than you thought.&quot; This is the muse of form. It may be then that form serves us best when it works as an obstruction, to baffle us and deflect our intended course. It may be that when we no longer know what to do, we have come to our real work and when we no longer know which way to go, we have begun our real journey. The mind that is not baffled is not employed. The impeded stream is the one that sings." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9432-so-friends-every-day-do-something-that-won-t-compute-give-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 11:37:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michele add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9432-so-friends-every-day-do-something-that-won-t-compute-give-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So, friends, every day do something that won't compute...Give your approval to all you cannot understand...Ask the questions that have no answers. Put your faith in two inches of humus that will build under the trees every thousand years...Laugh. Be joyful though you have considered all the facts....Practice resurrection." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51717-and-in-some-of-the-people-of-the-town-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 11:37:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michele add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51717-and-in-some-of-the-people-of-the-town-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["and in some of the people of the town and community surrounding it, one of the characteristic diseases of the twentieth century was making its way: the suspicion that they would be greatly improved if they were somewhere else." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11895-one-final-paragraph-of-advice-do-not-burn-yourselves-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 15:22:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michele add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11895-one-final-paragraph-of-advice-do-not-burn-yourselves-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One final paragraph of advice: do not burn yourselves out. Be as I am - a reluctant enthusiast....a part-time crusader, a half-hearted fanatic. Save the other half of yourselves and your lives for pleasure and adventure. It is not enough to fight for the land; it is even more important to enjoy it. While you can. While it’s still here. So get out there and hunt and fish and mess around with your friends, ramble out yonder and explore the forests, climb the mountains, bag the peaks, run the rivers, breathe deep of that yet sweet and lucid air, sit quietly for a while and contemplate the precious stillness, the lovely, mysterious, and awesome space. Enjoy yourselves, keep your brain in your head and your head firmly attached to the body, the body active and alive, and I promise you this much; I promise you this one sweet victory over our enemies, over those desk-bound men and women with their hearts in a safe deposit box, and their eyes hypnotized by desk calculators. I promise you this; You will outlive the bastards." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143182-love-is-what-carries-you-for-it-is-always-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 15:27:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michele add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143182-love-is-what-carries-you-for-it-is-always-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is what carries you, for it is always there, even in the dark, or most in the dark, but shining out at times like gold stitches in a piece of embroidery. " -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130070-you-have-been-given-questions-to-which-you-cannot-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 15:27:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michele add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130070-you-have-been-given-questions-to-which-you-cannot-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have been given questions to which you cannot be given answers. You will have to live them out - perhaps a little at a time.'
And how long is that going to take?'
I don't know. As long as you live, perhaps.'
That could be a long time.'
I will tell you a further mystery,' he said. 'It may take longer." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142986-you-can-plan-all-you-want-to-you-can-lie</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 15:28:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michele add a quote by Wallace Stegner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142986-you-can-plan-all-you-want-to-you-can-lie]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can plan all you want to. You can lie in your morning bed and fill whole notebooks with schemes and intentions. But within a single afternoon, within hours or minutes, everything you plan and everything you have fought to make yourself can be undone as a slug is undone when salt is poured on him. And right up to the moment when you find yourself dissolving into foam you can still believe you are doing fine." -- Wallace Stegner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199388-towns-are-like-people-old-ones-often-have-character-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 15:30:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michele add a quote by Wallace Stegner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199388-towns-are-like-people-old-ones-often-have-character-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Towns are like people. Old ones often have character, the new ones are interchangeable." -- Wallace Stegner]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
