<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/288380-elmira]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/288380-elmira" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 00:47:03 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190-were-these-boys-in-their-right-minds-here-were-two</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 00:47:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmira add a quote by Clarence Darrow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190-were-these-boys-in-their-right-minds-here-were-two]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Were these boys in their right minds? Here were two boys with good intellect, one eighteen and one nineteen. They had all the prospects that life could hold out for any of the young; one a graduate of Chicago and another of Ann Arbor; one who had passed his examination for the Harvard Law School and was about to take a trip in Europe,--another who had passed at Ann Arbor, the youngest in his class, with three thousand dollars in the bank. Boys who never knew what it was to want a dollar; boys who could reach any position that was to boys of that kind to reach; boys of distinguished and honorable families, families of wealth and position, with all the world before them. And they gave it all up for nothing, for nothing! They took a little companion of one of them, on a crowded street, and killed him, for nothing, and sacrificed everything that could be of value in human life upon the crazy scheme of a couple of immature lads.

Now, your Honor, you have been a boy; I have been a boy. And we have known other boys. The best way to understand somebody else is to put yourself in his place.

Is it within the realm of your imagination that a boy who was right, with all the prospects of life before him, who could choose what he wanted, without the slightest reason in the world would lure a young companion to his death, and take his place in the shadow of the gallows?

...No one who has the process of reasoning could doubt that a boy who would do that is not right.

How insane they are I care not, whether medically or legally. They did not reason; they could not reason; they committed the most foolish, most unprovoked, most purposeless, most causeless act that any two boys ever committed, and they put themselves where the rope is dangling above their heads....

Why did they kill little Bobby Franks?

Not for money, not for spite; not for hate. They killed him as they might kill a spider or a fly, for the experience. They killed him because they were made that way. Because somewhere in the infinite processes that go to the making up of the boy or the man something slipped, and those unfortunate lads sit here hated, despised, outcasts, with the community shouting for their blood.

. . . I know, Your Honor, that every atom of life in all this universe is bound up together. I know that a pebble cannot be thrown into the ocean without disturbing every drop of water in the sea. I know that every life is inextricably mixed and woven with every other life. I know that every influence, conscious and unconscious, acts and reacts on every living organism, and that no one can fix the blame. I know that all life is a series of infinite chances, which sometimes result one way and sometimes another. I have not the infinite wisdom that can fathom it, neither has any other human brain" -- Clarence Darrow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191-my-tongue-will-tell-the-anger-of-my-heart-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 00:47:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmira add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191-my-tongue-will-tell-the-anger-of-my-heart-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My tongue will tell the anger of my heart, or else my heart concealing it will break." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54-don-t-walk-behind-me-i-may-not-lead-don-t-walk</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 01:41:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmira add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54-don-t-walk-behind-me-i-may-not-lead-don-t-walk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't walk behind me; I may not lead. Don't walk in front of me; I may not follow. Just walk beside me and be my friend." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44190</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 02:18:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmira add a quote by دکتر علی شریعتی]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44190]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["در شگفتم که سلام آغاز هر دیداریست ، ولی در نماز پایان است . شاید این بدین معناست که پایان نماز ، آغاز دیدار است" -- دکتر علی شریعتی]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
