<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/289071-sara]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/289071-sara" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 May 2009 13:46:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321-if-there-s-a-book-that-you-want-to-read-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2009 13:46:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321-if-there-s-a-book-that-you-want-to-read-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there's a book that you want to read, but it hasn't been written yet, then you must write it." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8694-the-struggle-is-inner-chicano-indio-american-indian-mojado-mexicano</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2009 14:21:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Gloria Anzaldua]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8694-the-struggle-is-inner-chicano-indio-american-indian-mojado-mexicano]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The struggle is inner: Chicano, indio, American Indian, mojado, mexicano, immigrant Latino, Anglo in power, working class Anglo, Black,  Asian--our psyches resemble the bordertowns and are populated by the  same people. The struggle has always been inner, and is played out in outer terrains. Awareness of our situation must come before inner changes, which in turn come before changes in society. Nothing happens in the &quot;real&quot; world unless it first happens in the images in our heads." -- Gloria Anzaldua]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84850-by-creating-a-new-mythos---that-is-a-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2009 14:21:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Gloria Anzaldúa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84850-by-creating-a-new-mythos---that-is-a-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By creating a new mythos - that is, a change in the way we perceive reality, the way we see ourselves, and the ways we behave - la mestiza creates a new consciousness.  The work of mestiza consciousness is to break down the subject/object duality that keeps her prisoner and to show in the flesh and through the images in her work how duality is transcended.  The answer to the problem between the white race and the colored, between males and females, lies in healing the split that originates in the very foundation of our lives, our culture, our languages, our thoughts.  A massive uprooting of dualistic thinking in the individual and collective consciousness is the beginning of a long struggle, but one that could, in our best hopes, bring us to the end of rape, of violence, of war." -- Gloria Anzaldúa]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
