<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/290266-levi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/290266-levi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 14:04:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/661151-i-m-all-these-words-all-these-strangers-this-dust-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 14:04:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Levi add a quote by Samuel Beckett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/661151-i-m-all-these-words-all-these-strangers-this-dust-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm all these words, all these strangers, this dust of words, with no ground for their settling, no sky for their dispersing, coming together to say, fleeing one another to say, that I am they, all of them, those that merge, those that part, those that never meet, and nothing else, yes, something else, that I'm something quite different, a quite different thing, a wordless thing in an empty place, a hard shut dry cold black place, where nothing stirs, nothing speaks, and that I listen, and that I seek, like a caged beast born of caged beasts born of caged beasts born of caged beasts born in a cage and dead in a cage, born and then dead, born in a cage and then dead in a cage, in a word like a beast, in one of their words, like such a beast, and that I seek, like such a beast, with my little strength, such a beast, with nothing of its species left but fear and fury, no, the fury is past, nothing but fear, nothing of all its due but fear centupled, fear of its shadow, no, blind from birth, of sound then, if you like, we'll have that, one must have something, it's a pity, but there it is, fear of sound, fear of sounds, the sounds of beasts, the sounds of men, sounds in the daytime and sounds at night, that's enough, fear of sounds all sounds, more or less, more or less fear, all sounds, there's only one, continuous, day and night, what is it, it's steps coming and going, it's voices speaking for a moment, it's bodies groping their way, it's the air, it's things, it's the air among the things, that's enough, that I seek, like it, no, not like it, like me, in my own way, what am I saying, after my fashion, that I seek, what do I seek now, what it is, it must be that, it can only be that, what it is, what it can be, what what can be, what I seek, no, what I hear, I hear them, now it comes back to me, they say I seek what it is I hear, I hear them, now it comes back to me, what it can possibly be, and where it can possibly come from, since all is silent here, and the walls thick, and how I manage, without feeling an ear on me, or a head, or a body, or a soul, how I manage, to do what, how I manage, it's not clear, dear dear, you say it's not clear, something is wanting to make it clear, I'll seek, what is wanting, to make everything clear, I'm always seeking something, it's tiring in the end, and it's only the beginning." -- Samuel Beckett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296650-the-struggle-itself-towards-the-heights-is-enough-to-fill</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 08:16:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Levi add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296650-the-struggle-itself-towards-the-heights-is-enough-to-fill]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The struggle itself towards the heights is enough to fill a man's heart. One must imagine Sisyphus happy." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56136-hungry-man-reach-for-the-book-it-is-a-weapon</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 12:11:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Levi add a quote by Bertolt Brecht]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56136-hungry-man-reach-for-the-book-it-is-a-weapon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hungry man, reach for the book: it is a weapon." -- Bertolt Brecht]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71044-we-shouldn-t-be-looking-for-heroes-we-should-be-looking</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 09:07:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Levi add a quote by Noam Chomsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71044-we-shouldn-t-be-looking-for-heroes-we-should-be-looking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We shouldn't be looking for heroes, we should be looking for good ideas." -- Noam Chomsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5890-be-steady-and-well-ordered-in-your-life-so-that-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 11:57:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Levi add a quote by Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5890-be-steady-and-well-ordered-in-your-life-so-that-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be steady and well-ordered in your life so that you can be fierce and original in your work." -- Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22524-we-are-just-an-advanced-breed-of-monkeys-on-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 11:11:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Levi add a quote by Stephen Hawking]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22524-we-are-just-an-advanced-breed-of-monkeys-on-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are just an advanced breed of monkeys on a minor planet of a very average star. But we can understand the Universe. That makes us something very special." -- Stephen Hawking]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201369-the-first-duty-of-wine-is-to-be-red-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 09:44:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Levi add a quote by Henry Murger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201369-the-first-duty-of-wine-is-to-be-red-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first duty of wine is to be red. Don't talk to me of your white wines." -- Henry Murger]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
