<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/290432-madmadam]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/290432-madmadam" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 17:59:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75716-we-can-surely-no-longer-pretend-that-our-children-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 17:59:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75716-we-can-surely-no-longer-pretend-that-our-children-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can surely no longer pretend that our children are growing up into a peaceful, secure, and civilized world.  We've come to the point where it's irresponsible to try to protect them from the irrational world they will have to live in when they grow up. The children themselves haven't yet isolated themselves by selfishness and indifference; they do not fall easily into the error of despair; they are considerably braver than most grownups. Our responsibility to them is not to pretend that if we don't look, evil will go away, but to give them weapons against it." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/447060-poetry-is-a-life-cherishing-force-for-poems-are-not-words</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 17:04:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/447060-poetry-is-a-life-cherishing-force-for-poems-are-not-words]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Poetry is a life-cherishing force. For poems are not words, after all, but fires for the cold, ropes let down to the lost, something as necessary as bread in the pockets of the hungry. Yes indeed." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157573-being-good-felt-like-a-heavy-coat-so-i-took</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 21:28:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Naomi Shihab Nye]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157573-being-good-felt-like-a-heavy-coat-so-i-took]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being good felt like a heavy coat, so I took it off." -- Naomi Shihab Nye]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73146-one-cannot-divine-nor-forecast-the-conditions-that-will-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 15:08:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Willa Cather]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73146-one-cannot-divine-nor-forecast-the-conditions-that-will-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One cannot divine nor forecast the conditions that will make happiness; one only stumbles upon them by chance, in a lucky hour, at the world's end somewhere, and hold fast to the days..." -- Willa Cather]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/619-it-is-never-too-late-to-be-what-you-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 17:31:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/619-it-is-never-too-late-to-be-what-you-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is never too late to be what you might have been." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32967-the-moment-we-begin-to-fear-the-opinions-of-others</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 07:05:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Elizabeth Cady Stanton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32967-the-moment-we-begin-to-fear-the-opinions-of-others]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The moment we begin to fear the opinions of others and hesitate to tell the truth that is in us, and from motives of policy are silent when we should speak, the divine floods of light and life no longer flow into our souls." -- Elizabeth Cady Stanton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5775-give-sorrow-words-the-grief-that-does-not-speak-knits</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 13:05:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5775-give-sorrow-words-the-grief-that-does-not-speak-knits]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Give sorrow words; the grief that does not speak knits up the o-er wrought heart and bids it break." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278948-i-cannot-stand-people-who-disagree-with-me-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 18:00:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Stephen Colbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278948-i-cannot-stand-people-who-disagree-with-me-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot stand people who disagree with me on the issue of Roe v. Wade... which I believe is about the proper way to cross a lake." -- Stephen Colbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69375-and-in-the-act-of-making-things-just-by-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 13:08:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Anne Bartlett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69375-and-in-the-act-of-making-things-just-by-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And in the act of making things, just by living their daily lives, they also make history. 

Knitting is clothing made in spare moments, or round the fire, whenever women gathered together... It's something to celebrate-clothes made in love and service, something women have always done." -- Anne Bartlett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124490-given-good-yarn-good-workmanship-and-good-care-a-knitted</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 13:12:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Martha Waterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124490-given-good-yarn-good-workmanship-and-good-care-a-knitted]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Given good yarn, good workmanship, and good care, a knitted shawl and outlive its knitter, providing warmth and pleasure to several generations of family and friends." -- Martha Waterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417360-but-unvented---ahh-one-un-vents-something-one-unearths-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 13:13:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Elizabeth Zimmermann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417360-but-unvented---ahh-one-un-vents-something-one-unearths-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But unvented - ahh! One un-vents something; one unearths it; one digs it up, one runs it down in whatever recesses of the eternal consciousness it has gone to ground.  I very much doubt if anything is really new when one works in the prehistoric medium of wool with needles.  The products of science and technology may be new, and some of them are quite horrid, but knitting?  In knitting there are ancient possibilities; the earth is enriched with the dust of the millions of knitters who have held wool and needles since the beginning of sheep.  Seamless sweaters and one-row buttonholes; knitted hems and phoney seams - it is unthinkable that these have, in mankind's history, remained undiscovered and unknitted.  One likes to believe that there is memory in the fingers; memory undeveloped, but still alive." -- Elizabeth Zimmermann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36317-why-did-you-do-all-this-for-me-he-asked</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 05:07:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36317-why-did-you-do-all-this-for-me-he-asked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why did you do all this for me?' he asked. 'I don't deserve it. I've never done anything for you.' 'You have been my friend,' replied Charlotte. 'That in itself is a tremendous thing." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42485-there-are-moments-when-troubles-enter-our-lives-and-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 19:06:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42485-there-are-moments-when-troubles-enter-our-lives-and-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are moments when troubles enter our lives and we can do nothing to avoid them.
But they are there for a reason. Only when we have overcome them will we understand why they were there." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445898-you-can-do-something-extraordinary-and-something-that-a-lot</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 19:09:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Morgan Matson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445898-you-can-do-something-extraordinary-and-something-that-a-lot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...You can do something extraordinary, and something that a lot of people can't do. And if you have the opportunity to work on your gifts, it seems like a crime not to. I mean, it's just weakness to quit because something becomes too hard..." -- Morgan Matson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3278-i-may-not-have-gone-where-i-intended-to-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 05:58:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by douglas adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3278-i-may-not-have-gone-where-i-intended-to-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I may not have gone where I intended to go, but I think I have ended up where I needed to be." -- douglas adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150555-it-was-his-subconscious-which-told-him-this---that-infuriating-part</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 06:02:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150555-it-was-his-subconscious-which-told-him-this---that-infuriating-part]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was his subconscious which told him this---that infuriating part of a person's brain which never responds to interrogation, merely gives little meaningful nudges and then sits humming quietly to itself, saying nothing." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24091-it-is-a-curious-situation-that-the-sea-from-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 20:24:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Rachel Carson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24091-it-is-a-curious-situation-that-the-sea-from-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a curious situation that the sea, from which life first arose should now be threatened by the activities of one form of that life. But the sea, though changed in a sinister way, will continue to exist; the threat is rather to life itself." -- Rachel Carson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104724-i-think-you-travel-to-search-and-you-come-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2013 18:47:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104724-i-think-you-travel-to-search-and-you-come-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think you travel to search and you come back home to find yourself there." -- Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/345789-many-stories-matter-stories-have-been-used-to-dispossess-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2013 18:47:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Chimamanda Adichie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/345789-many-stories-matter-stories-have-been-used-to-dispossess-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many stories matter. Stories have been used to dispossess and to malign. But stories can also be used to empower, and to humanize. Stories can break the dignity of a people. But stories can also repair that broken dignity." -- Chimamanda Adichie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/791095-her-blog-was-doing-well-with-thousands-of-unique-visitors</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2013 18:49:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/791095-her-blog-was-doing-well-with-thousands-of-unique-visitors]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her blog was doing well, with thousands of unique visitors each month, and she was earning good speaking fees, and she had a fellowship at Princeton and a relationship with Blaine - &quot;You are the absolute love of my life,&quot; he'd written in her last birthday card - and yet there was cement in her soul. It had been there for a while, an early morning disease of fatigue, shapeless desires, brief imaginary glints of other lives she could be living, that over the months melded into a piercing homesickness." -- Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334409-whenever-you-go-on-a-trip-to-visit-foreign-lands</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 19:10:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Vera Nazarian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334409-whenever-you-go-on-a-trip-to-visit-foreign-lands]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever you go on a trip to visit foreign lands or distant places, remember that they are all someone's home and backyard." -- Vera Nazarian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407117-there-is-no-hospitality-like-understanding</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 19:09:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Vanna Bonta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407117-there-is-no-hospitality-like-understanding]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no hospitality like understanding." -- Vanna Bonta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/929-whatever-you-can-do-or-dream-you-can-begin-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2013 18:31:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Johann Wolfgang von Goethe ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/929-whatever-you-can-do-or-dream-you-can-begin-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever you can do or dream you can, begin it. Boldness has genius, power and magic in it!" -- Johann Wolfgang von Goethe ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74399-the-greatest-threat-to-freedom-is-the-absence-of-criticism</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2013 05:05:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Wole Soyinka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74399-the-greatest-threat-to-freedom-is-the-absence-of-criticism]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greatest threat to freedom is the absence of criticism." -- Wole Soyinka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/537548-i-wish-i-were-a-girl-again-half-savage-and-hardy</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 14:54:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/537548-i-wish-i-were-a-girl-again-half-savage-and-hardy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish I were a girl again, half-savage and hardy, and free." -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413794-if-i-should-have-a-daughter-instead-of-mom-she-s-gonna</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 13:30:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Sarah Kay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413794-if-i-should-have-a-daughter-instead-of-mom-she-s-gonna]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I should have a daughter…“Instead of “Mom”, she’s gonna call me “Point B.” Because that way, she knows that no matter what happens, at least she can always find her way to me. And I’m going to paint the solar system on the back of her hands so that she has to learn the entire universe before she can say “Oh, I know that like the back of my hand.”

She’s gonna learn that this life will hit you, hard, in the face, wait for you to get back up so it can kick you in the stomach. But getting the wind knocked out of you is the only way to remind your lungs how much they like the taste of air. There is hurt, here, that cannot be fixed by band-aids or poetry, so the first time she realizes that Wonder-woman isn’t coming, I’ll make sure she knows she doesn’t have to wear the cape all by herself. Because no matter how wide you stretch your fingers, your hands will always be too small to catch all the pain you want to heal. Believe me, I’ve tried.

And “Baby,” I’ll tell her “don’t keep your nose up in the air like that, I know that trick, you’re just smelling for smoke so you can follow the trail back to a burning house so you can find the boy who lost everything in the fire to see if you can save him. Or else, find the boy who lit the fire in the first place to see if you can change him.”

But I know that she will anyway, so instead I’ll always keep an extra supply of chocolate and rain boats nearby, ‘cause there is no heartbreak that chocolate can’t fix. Okay, there’s a few heartbreaks chocolate can’t fix. But that’s what the rain boots are for, because rain will wash away everything if you let it.

I want her to see the world through the underside of a glass bottom boat, to look through a magnifying glass at the galaxies that exist on the pin point of a human mind. Because that’s how my mom taught me. That there’ll be days like this, “There’ll be days like this my momma said” when you open your hands to catch and wind up with only blisters and bruises. When you step out of the phone booth and try to fly and the very people you wanna save are the ones standing on your cape. When your boots will fill with rain and you’ll be up to your knees in disappointment and those are the very days you have all the more reason to say “thank you,” ‘cause there is nothing more beautiful than the way the ocean refuses to stop kissing the shoreline no matter how many times it’s sent away.

You will put the “wind” in win some lose some, you will put the “star” in starting over and over, and no matter how many land mines erupt in a minute be sure your mind lands on the beauty of this funny place called life.

And yes, on a scale from one to over-trusting I am pretty damn naive but I want her to know that this world is made out of sugar. It can crumble so easily but don’t be afraid to stick your tongue out and taste it.

“Baby,” I’ll tell her “remember your mama is a worrier but your papa is a warrior and you are the girl with small hands and big eyes who never stops asking for more.”

Remember that good things come in threes and so do bad things and always apologize when you’ve done something wrong but don’t you ever apologize for the way your eyes refuse to stop shining.

Your voice is small but don’t ever stop singing and when they finally hand you heartbreak, slip hatred and war under your doorstep and hand you hand-outs on street corners of cynicism and defeat, you tell them that they really ought to meet your mother." -- Sarah Kay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33350-no-matter-what-he-does-every-person-on-earth-plays</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 18:54:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33350-no-matter-what-he-does-every-person-on-earth-plays]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No matter what he does, every person on earth plays a central role in the history of the world. And normally he doesn't know it." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13566-it-is-always-better-to-avenge-dear-ones-than-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 14:44:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Seamus Heaney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13566-it-is-always-better-to-avenge-dear-ones-than-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is always better
to avenge dear ones than to indulge in mourning.
For every one of us, living in this world
means waiting for our end. Let whoever can
win glory before death. When a warrior is gone,
that will be his best and only bulwark." -- Seamus Heaney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200431-if-you-have-the-words-there-s-always-a-chance-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 14:44:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Seamus Heaney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200431-if-you-have-the-words-there-s-always-a-chance-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you have the words, there's always a chance that you'll find the way." -- Seamus Heaney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7480-real-isn-t-how-you-are-made-said-the-skin-horse</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2013 17:16:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madmadam add a quote by Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7480-real-isn-t-how-you-are-made-said-the-skin-horse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Real isn't how you are made,' said the Skin Horse. 'It's a thing that happens to you. When a child loves you for a long, long time, not just to play with, but REALLY loves you, then you become Real.'

'Does it hurt?' asked the Rabbit. 

'Sometimes,' said the Skin Horse, for he was always truthful. 'When you are Real you don't mind being hurt.' 

'Does it happen all at once, like being wound up,' he asked, 'or bit by bit?' 

'It doesn't happen all at once,' said the Skin Horse. 'You become. It takes a long time. That's why it doesn't happen often to people who break easily, or have sharp edges, or who have to be carefully kept. Generally, by the time you are Real, most of your hair has been loved off, and your eyes drop out and you get loose in the joints and very shabby. But these things don't matter at all, because once you are Real you can't be ugly, except to people who don't understand." -- Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
