<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/290878-christine-durant]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/290878-christine-durant" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 19:24:23 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559998-the-chances-of-finding-out-what-s-really-going-on-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 19:24:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559998-the-chances-of-finding-out-what-s-really-going-on-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The chances of finding out what’s really going on in the universe are so remote, the only thing to do is hang the sense of it and keep yourself occupied." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11418-expose-yourself-to-your-deepest-fear-after-that-fear-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 19:40:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Jim Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11418-expose-yourself-to-your-deepest-fear-after-that-fear-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Expose yourself to your deepest fear; after that, fear has no power, and the fear of freedom shrinks and vanishes. You are free." -- Jim Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/570041-we-stood-there-looking-at-each-other-saying-nothing-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 19:59:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Jenny Han]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/570041-we-stood-there-looking-at-each-other-saying-nothing-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We stood there, looking at each other, saying nothing. But it was the kind of nothing that meant everything. In his eyes, there was no trace of what had happened between us earlier and I could feel something inside me break.
So that was that. We were finally, finally over.
I looked at him, and I felt so sad, because this thought occurred to me: 'I will never look at you the same way again. I'll never be that girl again. The girl who comes running back every time you push her away, the girl who loves you anyway.'
I couldn’t even be mad at him, because this was who he was. This was who he’d
always been. He’d never lied about that. He gave and then he took away. I felt it in the pit of my stomach, the familiar ache, that lost, regretful feeling only he could give me. I never wanted to feel it again. Never, ever.
Maybe this was why I came, so I could really know. So I could say good-bye.
I looked at him, and I thought, 'If I was very brave or very honest, I would tell him.'
I would say it, so he would know it and I would know it, and I could never take it back. But I wasn’t that brave or honest, so all I did was look at him. And I think he knew anyway.
'I release you. I evict you from my heart. Because if I don't do it now, I never will.'
I was the one to look away first." -- Jenny Han]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329628-to-cry-was-to-release-all-sorts-of-ugly-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 20:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Anne McCaffrey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329628-to-cry-was-to-release-all-sorts-of-ugly-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To cry was to release all sorts of ugly little pressures and tensions. Like waking out of a long, dark dream to a sun-filled day." -- Anne McCaffrey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/675893-the-tyranny-of-the-living-body-listen----those-cells</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 20:01:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Eve Alexandra]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/675893-the-tyranny-of-the-living-body-listen----those-cells]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The tyranny of the living body.
Listen -- those cells are at it again.
Gossiping.
Her veins are singing. 
Belting out gospel and disco. Amazing Grace.
And her tired mind
says hush. Enough is enough." -- Eve Alexandra]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268379-people-of-our-time-are-losing-the-power-of-celebration</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 20:03:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Abraham Joshua Heschel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268379-people-of-our-time-are-losing-the-power-of-celebration]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People of our time are losing the power of celebration. Instead of celebrating we seek to be amused or entertained. Celebration is an active state, an act of expressing reverence or appreciation. To be entertained is a passive state--it is to receive pleasure afforded by an amusing act or a spectacle.... Celebration is a confrontation, giving attention to the transcendent meaning of one's actions.
Source: The Wisdom of Heschel" -- Abraham Joshua Heschel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/400783-come-here-let-me-share-a-bit-of-wisdom-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 20:04:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Anne Carson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/400783-come-here-let-me-share-a-bit-of-wisdom-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Come here, let me share a bit of wisdom with you.
Have you given much thought to our mortal condition?
Probably not. Why would you? Well, listen.
&lt;i&gt;All mortals owe a debt to death.&lt;/i&gt;
There's no one alive
who can say if he will be tomorrow.
Our fate moves invisibly! A mystery.
No one can teach it, no one can grasp it.
Accept this! Cheer up! Have a drink!
But don't forget Aphrodite--that's &lt;i&gt;one sweet goddess.&lt;/i&gt;
You can let the rest go. Am I making sense?
I think so. How about a drink.
Put on a garland. I'm sure
the happy splash of wine will cure your mood.
We're all mortal you know. Think mortal.
Because my theory is, there's no such thing as life,
&lt;i&gt;it's just catastrophe.&lt;/i&gt;" -- Anne Carson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
