<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/290982-cassie-pendergraff]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/290982-cassie-pendergraff" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 05:55:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215417-there-is-a-common-misunderstanding-among-the-human-beings-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 05:55:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cassie add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215417-there-is-a-common-misunderstanding-among-the-human-beings-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a common misunderstanding among the human beings who have ever been born on earth that the best way to live is to try to avoid pain and just try to get comfortable.  You see this even in insects and animals and birds.  All of us are the some.  A much more interesting, kind and joyful approach to life is to begin to develop our curiosity, not caring whether the object of our curiosity is bitter or sweet.  To lead to a life that goes beyond pettiness and prejudice and always wanting to make sure that everything turns out on our own terms, to lead a more passionate, full, and delightful life than that, we must realize that we can endure a lot of pain and pleasure for the sake of finding out who we are and what this world is, how we tick and how our world ticks, how the whole thing just is.  If we are committed to comfort at any cost, as soon as we come up against the least edge of pain, we’re going to run; we’ll never know what’s beyond that particular barrier or wall or fearful thing." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259381-as-human-beings-not-only-do-we-seek-resolution-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 05:56:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cassie add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259381-as-human-beings-not-only-do-we-seek-resolution-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As human beings, not only do we seek resolution, but we also feel that we deserve resolution. However, not only do we not deserve resolution, we suffer from resolution. We don't deserve resolution; we deserve something better than that. We deserve our birthright, which is the middle way, an open state of mind that can relax with paradox and ambiguity." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19797-the-only-reason-we-don-t-open-our-hearts-and-minds</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 05:56:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cassie add a quote by Pema Chodron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19797-the-only-reason-we-don-t-open-our-hearts-and-minds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only reason we don't open our hearts and minds to other people is that they trigger confusion in us that we don't feel brave enough or sane enough to deal with. To the degree that we look clearly and compassionately at ourselves, we feel confident and fearless about looking into someone else's eyes. " -- Pema Chodron]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
