<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/291063-chris]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/291063-chris" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 07:41:46 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31171-el-amor-es-m-s-poderoso-que-todos-los-prejuicios-en</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 07:41:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Laureano Vallenilla Lanz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31171-el-amor-es-m-s-poderoso-que-todos-los-prejuicios-en]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["El amor es más poderoso que todos los prejuicios.  En las historias sangrientas, como en las comedias, todo termina en matrimonio." -- Laureano Vallenilla Lanz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31165-i-have-an-idea-that-some-men-are-born-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 07:43:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31165-i-have-an-idea-that-some-men-are-born-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have an idea that some men are born out of their due place.  Accident has cast them amid certain surroundings, but they have always a nostalgia for a home they know not.  They are strangers in their birthplace, and the leafy lanes they have known from childhood or the populous streets in which they have played, remain but a place of passage.  They may spend their whole lives aliens among their kindred and remain aloof among the only scenes they have ever known.  Perhaps it is this sense of strangeness that sends men far and wide in the search for something permanent, to which they may attach themselves.  Perhaps some deep-rooted atavism urges the wanderer back to lands which his ancestors left in the dim beginnings of history.  Sometimes a man hits upon a place to which he mysteriously feels that he belongs.  Here is the home he sought, and he will settle amid scenes that he has never seen before, among men he has never known, as though they were familiar to him from his birth.  Here at last he finds rest." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31166-en-las-noches-de-invierno-mientras-herv-a-la-sopa-en</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 07:44:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31166-en-las-noches-de-invierno-mientras-herv-a-la-sopa-en]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["En las noches de invierno, mientras hervía la sopa en la chimenea, añoraba el calor de su trastienda, el zumbido del sol en los almendros polvorientos, el pito del tren en el sopor de la siesta, lo mismo que añoraba en Macondo la sopa del invierno de la chimenea, los pregones del vendedor de café y las alondras fugaces de la primavera.  Aturdido por dos nostalgias enfrentadas como dos espejos, perdió su maravilloso sentido de la irrealidad, hasta que terminó por recomendarles a todos que se fueran de Macondo, que olvidaron cuanto él les había enseñado del mundo y del corazón humano, que se cagaran de Horacio y que en cualquier lugar en que estuvieran recordaran siempre que el pasado era mentira, que la memoria no tenía caminos de regreso, que toda primavera antigua era irrecuperable, y que el amor más desatinado y tenaz era de todos modos una verdad efímera." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
