<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/291226-leo-romero]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/291226-leo-romero" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 03:11:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1145964-those-who-think-money-can-t-buy-happiness-just-don-t-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 03:11:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leo add a quote by Jonathan Haidt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1145964-those-who-think-money-can-t-buy-happiness-just-don-t-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who think money can't buy happiness just don't know where to shop … People would be happier and healthier if they took more time off and spent it with their family and friends, yet America has long been heading in the opposite direction. People would be happier if they reduced their commuting time, even if it meant living in smaller houses, yet American trends are toward even larger houses and ever longer commutes. People would be happier and healthier if they took longer vacations even if that meant earning less, yet vacation times are shrinking in the United States, and in Europe as well. People would be happier, and in the long run and wealthier, if they bought basic functional appliances, automobiles, and wristwatches, and invested the money they saved for future consumption; yet, Americans and in particular spend almost everything they have – and sometimes more – on goods for present consumption, often paying a large premium for designer names and superfluous features." -- Jonathan Haidt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1146058-love-and-work-are-to-people-what-water-and-sunshine</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 05:43:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leo add a quote by Jonathan Haidt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1146058-love-and-work-are-to-people-what-water-and-sunshine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love and work are to people what water and sunshine are to plants." -- Jonathan Haidt]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
