<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/291419-virre]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/291419-virre" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 07:08:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/523094-being-vegetarian-here-also-means-that-we-do-not-consume</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 07:08:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/523094-being-vegetarian-here-also-means-that-we-do-not-consume]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being vegetarian here also means that we do not consume dairy and egg products, because they are products of the meat industry. If we stop consuming, they will stop producing. Only collective awakening can create enough determination for action." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5022-people-usually-consider-walking-on-water-or-in-thin-air</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 15:02:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5022-people-usually-consider-walking-on-water-or-in-thin-air]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People usually consider walking on water or in thin air a miracle. But I think the real miracle is not to walk either on water or in thin air, but to walk on earth. Every day we are engaged in a miracle which we don't even recognize: a blue sky, white clouds, green leaves, the black, curious eyes of a child -- our own two eyes. All is a miracle." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120409-by-eating-meat-we-share-the-responsibility-of-climate-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 15:04:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120409-by-eating-meat-we-share-the-responsibility-of-climate-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By eating meat we share the responsibility of climate change, the destruction of our forests, and the poisoning of our air and water. The simple act of becoming a vegetarian will make a difference in the health of our planet." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190372-compassion-is-a-verb</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 15:05:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190372-compassion-is-a-verb]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Compassion is a verb." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172764-there-is-a-story-i-would-like-to-tell-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 22:07:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172764-there-is-a-story-i-would-like-to-tell-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a story I would like to tell you about a woman who practices the invocation of the Buddha Amitabha's name. She is very tough, and she practices the invocation three times daily, using a wooden drum and a bell, reciting, &quot;Namo Amitabha Buddha&quot; for one hour each time. When she arrives at one thousand times, she invites the bell to sound. (In Vietnamese, we don't say &quot;strike&quot; or &quot;hit&quot; a bell.) Although she has been doing this for ten years, her personality has not changed. She is still quite mean, shouting at people all the time.

A friend wanted to teach her a lesson, so one afternoon when she had just lit the incense, invited the bell to sound three times, and was beginning to recite &quot;Namo Amitabha Buddha,&quot; he came to her door, and said, &quot;Mrs. Nguyen, Mrs. Nguyen!&quot; She found it very annoying because this was her time of practice, but he just stood at the front gate shouting her name. She said to herself, &quot;I have to struggle against my anger, so I will ignore that,&quot; and she went on, &quot;Namo Amitabha Buddha, Namo Amitabha Buddha.&quot;

The gentleman continued to shout her name, and her anger became more and more oppressive. She struggled against it, wondering, &quot;Should I stop my recitation and go and give him a piece of my mind?&quot; But she continued chanting, and she struggled very hard. Fire mounted in her, but she still tried to chant &quot;Namo Amitabha Buddha.&quot; The gentleman knew it, and he continued to shout, &quot;Mrs. Nguyen! Mrs. Nguyen!&quot; 

She could not bear it any longer. She threw away the bell and the drum. She slammed the door, went out to the gate and said, &quot;Why, why do you behave like that? Why do you call my name hundreds of times like that?&quot; The gentleman smiled at her and said, &quot;I just called your name for ten minutes, and you are so angry. You have been calling the Buddha's name for ten years. Think how angry he must be!" -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/586199-a-line-is-a-fuse-that-s-lit-the-line-smolders</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 02:11:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Vladimir Mayakovsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/586199-a-line-is-a-fuse-that-s-lit-the-line-smolders]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A line is a fuse
                                                    that's lit.
The line smolders,
                              the rhyme explodes—
and by a stanza
                        a city
                                  is blown to bits." -- Vladimir Mayakovsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1071-never-doubt-that-a-small-group-of-thoughtful-committed-citizens</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:12:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Margaret Mead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1071-never-doubt-that-a-small-group-of-thoughtful-committed-citizens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never doubt that a small group of thoughtful, committed, citizens can change the world. Indeed, it is the only thing that ever has." -- Margaret Mead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:14:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what you shall do; Love the earth and sun and the animals, despise riches, give alms to every one that asks, stand up for the stupid and crazy, devote your income and labor to others, hate tyrants, argue not concerning God, have patience and indulgence toward the people, take off your hat to nothing known or unknown or to any man or number of men, go freely with powerful uneducated persons and with the young and with the mothers of families, read these leaves in the open air every season of every year of your life, re-examine all you have been told at school or church or in any book, dismiss whatever insults your own soul, and your very flesh shall be a great poem and have the richest fluency not only in its words but in the silent lines of its lips and face and between the lashes of your eyes and in every motion and joint of your body." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3343-you-may-never-know-what-results-come-of-your-actions</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:16:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3343-you-may-never-know-what-results-come-of-your-actions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may never know what results come of your actions, but if you do nothing, there will be no results." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36299-one-has-a-moral-responsibility-to-disobey-unjust-laws</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:18:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36299-one-has-a-moral-responsibility-to-disobey-unjust-laws]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One has a moral responsibility to disobey unjust laws." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111119-every-day-i-get-better-at-knowing-that-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:23:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Staceyann Chin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111119-every-day-i-get-better-at-knowing-that-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every day I get better at knowing that it is not a choice to be an activist; rather, it is the only way to hold on to the better parts of my human self. It is the only way I can live and laugh without guilt." -- Staceyann Chin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130139-if-you-want-government-to-intervene-domestically-you-re-a-liberal</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:26:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Joseph Sobran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130139-if-you-want-government-to-intervene-domestically-you-re-a-liberal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want government to intervene domestically, you’re a liberal. If you want government to intervene overseas, you’re a conservative. If you want government to intervene everywhere, you’re a moderate. If you don’t want government to intervene anywhere, you’re an extremist." -- Joseph Sobran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66430-if-slaughterhouses-had-glass-walls-the-whole-world-would-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:32:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Linda McCartney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66430-if-slaughterhouses-had-glass-walls-the-whole-world-would-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If slaughterhouses had glass walls, the whole world would be vegetarian." -- Linda McCartney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521985-we-do-not-need-to-eat-animals-wear-animals-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:33:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Gary L. Francione]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521985-we-do-not-need-to-eat-animals-wear-animals-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We do not need to eat animals, wear animals, or use animals for entertainment purposes, and our only defense of these uses is our pleasure, amusement, and convenience." -- Gary L. Francione]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521927-being-vegan-is-easy-are-there-social-pressures-that-encourage</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:33:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by GaryLFrancione]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521927-being-vegan-is-easy-are-there-social-pressures-that-encourage]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being vegan is easy. Are there social pressures that encourage you to continue to eat, wear, and use animal products? Of course there are. But in a patriarchal, racist, homophobic, and ableist society, there are social pressures to participate and engage in sexism, racism, homophobia, and ableism. At some point, you have to decide who you are and what matters morally to you. And once you decide that you regard victimizing vulnerable nonhumans is not morally acceptable, it is easy to go and stay vegan" -- GaryLFrancione]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521917-veganism-is-not-about-giving-anything-up-or-losing-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:33:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by GaryLFrancione]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521917-veganism-is-not-about-giving-anything-up-or-losing-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Veganism is not about giving anything up or losing anything; it is about gaining the peace within yourself that comes from embracing nonviolence and refusing to participate in the exploitation of the vulnerable" -- GaryLFrancione]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521918-veganism-is-not-a-sacrifice-it-is-a-joy</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:33:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by GaryLFrancione]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521918-veganism-is-not-a-sacrifice-it-is-a-joy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Veganism is not a &quot;sacrifice.&quot; It is a joy." -- GaryLFrancione]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521990-if-you-are-not-vegan-please-consider-going-vegan-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:33:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Gary L. Francione]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521990-if-you-are-not-vegan-please-consider-going-vegan-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are not vegan, please consider going vegan. It’s a matter of nonviolence. Being vegan is your statement that you reject violence to other sentient beings, to yourself, and to the environment, on which all sentient beings depend." -- Gary L. Francione]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521997-we-can-no-more-justify-using-nonhumans-as-human-resources</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:34:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Gary L. Francione]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521997-we-can-no-more-justify-using-nonhumans-as-human-resources]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can no more justify using nonhumans as human resources than we can justify human slavery. Animal use and slavery have at least one important point in common: both institutions treat sentient beings exclusively as resources of others. That cannot be justified with respect to humans; it cannot be justified with respect to nonhumans—however “humanely” we treat them." -- Gary L. Francione]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521981-every-time-you-drink-a-glass-of-milk-or-eat</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:34:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by GaryLFrancione]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521981-every-time-you-drink-a-glass-of-milk-or-eat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every time you drink a glass of milk or eat a piece of cheese, you harm a mother. Please go vegan." -- GaryLFrancione]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521938-donald-watson-who-founded-the-vegan-society-in-1944-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:34:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by GaryLFrancione]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521938-donald-watson-who-founded-the-vegan-society-in-1944-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Donald Watson, who founded The Vegan Society in 1944 and who lived a healthy, active life until passing on in 2005, maintained that dairy products, such as milk, eggs, and cheese, were every bit as cruel and exploitive of sentient animal life as was slaughtering animals for their flesh: “The unquestionable cruelty associated with the production of dairy produce has made it clear that lactovegetarianism is but a half-way house between flesh-eating and a truly humane, civilised diet, and we think, therefore, that during our life on earth we should try to evolve sufficiently to make the ‘full journey.’” He also avoided wearing leather, wool or silk and used a fork, rather than a spade in his gardening to avoid killing worms.

Let us instil in others the reverence or life that Donald Watson had and that he passed on to us." -- GaryLFrancione]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522029-i-reject-animal-welfare-reform-and-single-issue-campaigns-because-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:34:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Gary L. Francione]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522029-i-reject-animal-welfare-reform-and-single-issue-campaigns-because-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I reject animal welfare reform and single-issue campaigns because they are not only inconsistent with the claims of justice that we should be making if we really believe that animal exploitation is wrong, but because these approaches cannot work as a practical matter. Animals are property and it costs money to protect their interests; therefore, the level of protection accorded to animal interests will always be low and animals will, under the best of circumstances, still be treated in ways that would constitute torture if applied to humans.

By endorsing welfare reforms that supposedly make exploitation more “compassionate” or single-issue campaigns that falsely suggest that there is a coherent moral distinction between meat and dairy or between fur and wool or between steak and foie gras, we betray the principle of justice that says that all sentient beings are equal for purposes of not being used exclusively as human resources. And, on a practical level, we do nothing more than make people feel better about animal exploitation." -- Gary L. Francione]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521968-we-should-always-be-clear-that-animal-exploitation-is-wrong</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:35:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by GaryLFrancione]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521968-we-should-always-be-clear-that-animal-exploitation-is-wrong]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We should always be clear that animal exploitation is wrong because it involves speciesism. And speciesism is wrong because, like racism, sexism, homophobia, anti-semitism, classism, and all other forms of human discrimination, speciesism involves violence inflicted on members of the moral community where that infliction of violence cannot be morally justified. But that means that those of us who oppose speciesism necessarily oppose discrimination against humans. It makes no sense to say that speciesism is wrong because it is like racism (or any other form of discrimination) but that we do not have a position about racism. We do. We should be opposed to it and we should always be clear about that." -- GaryLFrancione]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521984-veganism-is-an-act-of-nonviolent-defiance-it-is-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:35:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by GaryLFrancione]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521984-veganism-is-an-act-of-nonviolent-defiance-it-is-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Veganism is an act of nonviolent defiance. It is our statement that we reject the notion that animals are things and that we regard sentient nonhumans as moral persons with the fundamental moral right not to be treated as the property or resources of humans." -- GaryLFrancione]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521979-all-sentient-beings-should-have-at-least-one-right-the-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:35:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by GaryLFrancione]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521979-all-sentient-beings-should-have-at-least-one-right-the-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All sentient beings should have at least one right—the right not to be treated as property" -- GaryLFrancione]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381987-our-economic-order-is-tightly-woven-around-the-exploitation-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:43:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Virre add a quote by Bob Torres]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381987-our-economic-order-is-tightly-woven-around-the-exploitation-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our economic order is tightly woven around the exploitation of animals, and while it may seem easy to dismiss concern about animals as the soft-headed mental masturbation of people who really don't understand oppression and the depths of actual human misery, I hope to get you to think differently about suffering and pain, to convince you that animals matter, and to argue that anyone serious about ending domination and hierarchy needs to think critically about bringing animals into consideration." -- Bob Torres]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
