<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/29183-amanda]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/29183-amanda" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 08:29:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7480-real-isn-t-how-you-are-made-said-the-skin-horse</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 08:29:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7480-real-isn-t-how-you-are-made-said-the-skin-horse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Real isn't how you are made,' said the Skin Horse. 'It's a thing that happens to you. When a child loves you for a long, long time, not just to play with, but REALLY loves you, then you become Real.'

'Does it hurt?' asked the Rabbit. 

'Sometimes,' said the Skin Horse, for he was always truthful. 'When you are Real you don't mind being hurt.' 

'Does it happen all at once, like being wound up,' he asked, 'or bit by bit?' 

'It doesn't happen all at once,' said the Skin Horse. 'You become. It takes a long time. That's why it doesn't happen often to people who break easily, or have sharp edges, or who have to be carefully kept. Generally, by the time you are Real, most of your hair has been loved off, and your eyes drop out and you get loose in the joints and very shabby. But these things don't matter at all, because once you are Real you can't be ugly, except to people who don't understand." -- Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 17:14:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by William Nicholson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We read to know we're not alone." -- William Nicholson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 12:54:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the only people for me are the mad ones, the ones who are mad to live, mad to talk, mad to be saved, desirous of everything at the same time, the ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn like fabulous yellow roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 07:26:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8030-you-were-born-with-wings-why-prefer-to-crawl-through</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 07:27:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8030-you-were-born-with-wings-why-prefer-to-crawl-through]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You were born with wings, why prefer to crawl through life?" -- Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19483-on-ne-voit-bien-qu-avec-le-c-ur-l-essentiel-est-invisible</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 07:29:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19483-on-ne-voit-bien-qu-avec-le-c-ur-l-essentiel-est-invisible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On ne voit bien qu'avec le cœur. L'essentiel est invisible pour les yeux." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150105-mortal-beauty-often-makes-me-ache-and-mortal-grandeur-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 15:38:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Anne Rice]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150105-mortal-beauty-often-makes-me-ache-and-mortal-grandeur-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mortal beauty often makes me ache, and mortal grandeur can fill me with that longing...but Paris, Paris drew me close to her heart, so I forgot myself entirely. Forgot the damned and questing preternatural thing that doted on mortal skin and mortal clothing. Paris overwhelmed, and lightened and rewarded more richly than any promise. " -- Anne Rice]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/168252-what-if-a-demon-were-to-creep-after-you-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 15:40:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/168252-what-if-a-demon-were-to-creep-after-you-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What if a demon were to creep after you one night, in your loneliest loneliness, and say, 'This life which you live must be lived by you once again and innumerable times more; and every pain and joy and thought and sigh must come again to you, all in the same sequence. The eternal hourglass will again and again be turned and you with it, dust of the dust!' Would you throw yourself down and gnash your teeth and curse that demon? Or would you answer, 'Never have I heard anything more divine'? " -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275093-today-is-the-first-of-august-it-is-hot-steamy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 16:54:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275093-today-is-the-first-of-august-it-is-hot-steamy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today is the first of August.  It is hot, steamy and wet.  It is raining.  I am tempted to write a poem.  But I remember what it said on one rejection slip: 'After a heavy rainfall, poems titled 'Rain' pour in from across the nation." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
