<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/29191-catherine]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/29191-catherine" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2009 22:32:29 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/845-the-individual-has-always-had-to-struggle-to-keep-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2009 22:32:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/845-the-individual-has-always-had-to-struggle-to-keep-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The individual has always had to struggle to keep from being overwhelmed by the tribe. If you try it, you will be lonely often, and sometimes frightened. But no price is too high to pay for the privilege of owning yourself." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4213-still-there-are-times-i-am-bewildered-by-each-mile</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2009 22:37:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Jhumpa Lahiri]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4213-still-there-are-times-i-am-bewildered-by-each-mile]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Still, there are times I am bewildered by each mile I have traveled, each meal I have eaten, each person I have known, each room in which I have slept. As ordinary as it all appears, there are times when it is beyond my imagination." -- Jhumpa Lahiri]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3411-but-what-is-certain-is-that-in-five-ten-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2009 21:52:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Irene Nemirovsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3411-but-what-is-certain-is-that-in-five-ten-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But what is certain is that in five, ten or twenty years, this problem unique to our time, according to him, will no longer exist, it will be replaced by others...Yet this music, the sound of this rain on the windows, the great mournful creaking of the cedar tree in the garden outside, this moment, so tender, so strange in the middle of war, this will never change, not this, this is forever." -- Irene Nemirovsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2009 22:32:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes fate is like a small sandstorm that keeps changing directions. You change direction but the sandstorm chases you. You turn again, but the storm adjusts. Over and over you play this out, like some ominous dance with death just before dawn. Why? Because this storm isn't something that blew in from far away, something that has nothing to do with you. This storm is you. Something &lt;i&gt;inside&lt;/i&gt; of you. So all you can do is give in to it, step right inside the storm, closing your eyes and plugging up your ears so the sand doesn't get in, and walk through it, step by step. There's no sun there, no moon, no direction, no sense of time. Just fine white sand swirling up into the sky like pulverized bones. That's the kind of sandstorm you need to imagine.

An you really will have to make it through that violent, metaphysical, symbolic storm. No matter how metaphysical or symbolic it might be, make no mistake about it: it will cut through flesh like a thousand razor blades. People will bleed there, and &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; will bleed too. Hot, red blood. You'll catch that blood in your hands, your own blood and the blood of others.

And once the storm is over you won't remember how you made it through, how you managed to survive. You won't even be sure, in fact, whether the storm is really over. But one thing is certain. When you come out of the storm you won't be the same person who walked in. That's what this storm's all about." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58980-narrow-minds-devoid-of-imagination-intolerance-theories-cut-off-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2009 22:33:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58980-narrow-minds-devoid-of-imagination-intolerance-theories-cut-off-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Narrow minds devoid of imagination. Intolerance, theories cut off from reality, empty terminology, usurped ideals, inflexible systems. Those are the things that really frighten me. What I absolutely fear and loathe." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134645-lost-opportunities-lost-possibilities-feelings-we-can-never-get-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2009 22:35:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134645-lost-opportunities-lost-possibilities-feelings-we-can-never-get-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lost opportunities, lost possibilities, feelings we can never get back.  That's part of what it means to be alive.  But inside our heads - at least that's where I imagine it - there's a little room where we store those memories.  A room like the stacks in this library.  And to understand the workings of our own heart we have to keep on making new reference cards.  We have to dust things off every once in awhile, let in fresh air, change the water in the flower vases.  In other words, you'll live forever in your own private library." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48219-oshima-s-silent-for-a-time-as-he-gazes-at-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2009 22:35:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48219-oshima-s-silent-for-a-time-as-he-gazes-at-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oshima's silent for a time as he gazes at the forest, eyes narrowed. Birds are flitting from one branch to the next. His hands are clasped behind his head. &quot;I know how you feel,&quot; he finally says. &quot;But this is something you have to work out on your own. Nobody can help you. That's what love's all about, Kafka. You're the one having those wonderful feelings, but you have to go it alone as you wander through the dark. Your mind and body have to bear it all. All by yourself." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
