<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/292662-zona]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/292662-zona" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 11:29:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13454-i-turned-silences-and-nights-into-words-what-was-unutterable</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 11:29:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zona add a quote by Arthur Rimbaud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13454-i-turned-silences-and-nights-into-words-what-was-unutterable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I turned silences and nights into words. What was unutterable, I wrote down. I made the whirling world stand still." -- Arthur Rimbaud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/397391-my-turn-now-the-story-of-one-of-my-insanities</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 11:31:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zona add a quote by Arthur Rimbaud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/397391-my-turn-now-the-story-of-one-of-my-insanities]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My turn now. The story of one of my insanities.

For a long time I boasted that I was master of all possible landscapes-- and I thought the great figures of modern painting and poetry were laughable.

What I liked were: absurd paintings, pictures over doorways, stage sets, carnival backdrops, billboards, bright-colored prints, old-fashioned literature, church Latin, erotic books full of misspellings, the kind of novels our grandmothers read, fairy tales, little children's books, old operas, silly old songs, the naive rhythms of country rimes.

I dreamed of Crusades, voyages of discovery that nobody had heard of, republics without histories, religious wars stamped out, revolutions in morals, movements of races and continents; I used to believe in every kind of magic.

I invented colors for the vowels! A black, E white, I red, O blue, U green. I made rules for the form and movement of every consonant, and I boasted of inventing, with rhythms from within me, a kind of poetry that all the senses, sooner or later, would recognize. And I alone would be its translator.

I began it as an investigation. I turned silences and nights into words. What was unutterable, I wrote down. I made the whirling world stand still." -- Arthur Rimbaud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/869-benedicto-may-your-trails-be-crooked-winding-lonesome-dangerous-leading</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 05:26:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zona add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/869-benedicto-may-your-trails-be-crooked-winding-lonesome-dangerous-leading]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Benedicto: May your trails be crooked, winding, lonesome, dangerous, leading to the most amazing view. May your mountains rise into and above the clouds. May your rivers flow without end, meandering through pastoral valleys tinkling with bells, past temples and castles and poets towers into a dark primeval forest where tigers belch and monkeys howl, through miasmal and mysterious swamps and down into a desert of red rock, blue mesas, domes and pinnacles and grottos of endless stone, and down again into a deep vast ancient unknown chasm where bars of sunlight blaze on profiled cliffs, where deer walk across the white sand beaches, where storms come and go as lightning clangs upon the high crags, where something strange and more beautiful and more full of wonder than your deepest dreams waits  for you -- beyond that next turning of the canyon walls." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
