<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/293524-margaret]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/293524-margaret" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 09:38:05 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2807-as-a-woman-i-have-no-country-as-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 09:38:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by virginia woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2807-as-a-woman-i-have-no-country-as-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As a woman I have no country. As a woman I want no country. As a woman, my country is the whole world." -- virginia woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263493-i-am-no-bird-and-no-net-ensnares-me-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 09:37:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263493-i-am-no-bird-and-no-net-ensnares-me-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am no bird; and no net ensnares me: I am a free human being with an independent will." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15303-ah-how-good-it-is-to-be-among-people-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2008 08:31:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15303-ah-how-good-it-is-to-be-among-people-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ah, how good it is to be among people who are reading!" -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8305-he-that-hath-a-beard-is-more-than-a-youth</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2008 08:45:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8305-he-that-hath-a-beard-is-more-than-a-youth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He that hath a beard is more than a youth, and he that hath no beard is less than a man. He that is more than a youth is not for me, and he that is less than a man, I am not for him." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3419-and-there-is-a-chance-that-everything-we-did-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2008 09:39:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3419-and-there-is-a-chance-that-everything-we-did-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And there is a chance that everything we did was incorrect, but stasis is itself criminal for those with the means to move, and the means to weave communion between people." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16593-responsibility-to-yourself-means-refusing-to-let-others-do-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2008 11:23:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Adrienne Rich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16593-responsibility-to-yourself-means-refusing-to-let-others-do-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Responsibility to yourself means refusing to let others do your thinking, talking, and naming for you...it means that you do not treat your body as a commodity with which to purchase superficial intimacy or economic security; for our bodies to be treated as objects, our minds are in mortal danger. It means insisting that those to whom you give your friendship and love are able to respect your mind. It means being able to say, with Charlotte Bronte's Jane Eyre: &quot;I have an inward treasure born with me, which can keep me alive if all the extraneous delights should be withheld or offered only at a price I cannot afford to give.

Responsibility to yourself means that you don't fall for shallow and easy solutions--predigested books and ideas...marrying early as an escape from real decisions, getting pregnant as an evasion of already existing problems. It means that you refuse to sell your talents and aspirations short...and this, in turn, means resisting the forces in society which say that women should be nice, play safe, have low professional expectations, drown in love and forget about work, live through others, and stay in the places assigned to us. It means that we insist on a life of meaningful work, insist that work be as meaningful as love and friendship in our lives. It means, therefore, the courage to be &quot;different&quot;...The difference between a life lived actively, and a life of passive drifting and dispersal of energies, is an immense difference. Once we begin to feel committed to our lives, responsible to ourselves, we can never again be satisfied with the old, passive way." -- Adrienne Rich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2008 11:27:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We accept the love we think we deserve." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165998-i-am-always-incorrigibly-interested-in-the-behaviour-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2009 19:48:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Kingsley Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165998-i-am-always-incorrigibly-interested-in-the-behaviour-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am always incorrigibly interested in the behaviour of the 'human animal', and look forward to perusing divers effusions of your lively pen." -- Kingsley Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51957-human-nature-will-not-flourish-any-more-than-a-potato</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 13:09:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Nathaniel Hawthorne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51957-human-nature-will-not-flourish-any-more-than-a-potato]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human nature will not flourish, any more than a potato, if it be planted and replanted, for too long a series of generations, in the same worn-out soil. My children have had other birthplaces, and, so far as their fortunes may be within my control, shall strike their roots into unaccustomed earth." -- Nathaniel Hawthorne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44971-my-best-friend-is-a-person-who-will-give-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 09:18:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44971-my-best-friend-is-a-person-who-will-give-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My Best Friend is a person who will give me a book I have not read." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
