<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/29460-vicki]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/29460-vicki" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 17:31:23 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58751-i-wanted-to-tell-the-book-thief-many-things-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 17:31:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vicki add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58751-i-wanted-to-tell-the-book-thief-many-things-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted to tell the book thief many things, about beauty and brutality.  But what could I tell her about those things that she didn't already know?  I wanted to explain that I am constantly overestimating and underestimating the human race-that rarely do I ever simply estimate it.  I wanted to ask her how the same thing could be so ugly and so glorious, and its words and stories so damning and brilliant." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123754-when-gods-die-they-die-hard-it-s-not-like-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 17:34:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vicki add a quote by Gary Schmidt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123754-when-gods-die-they-die-hard-it-s-not-like-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When gods die, they die hard. It's not like they fade away, or grow old, or fall asleep. They die in fire and pain, and when they come out of you, they leave your guts burned. It hurts more than anything you can talk about. And maybe worst of all is, you're not sure if there will ever be another god to fill their place. Or if you'd ever want another god to fill their place. You don't want the fire to go out inside you twice." -- Gary Schmidt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136036-i-wanted-to-feel-hatred-and-love-despair-and-tedium---all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2009 14:19:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vicki add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136036-i-wanted-to-feel-hatred-and-love-despair-and-tedium---all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted to...feel hatred and love, despair and tedium-- all those simple, yet foolish things that make up everyday life but that give pleasure to your existence. If one day I could get out of here, I would allow myself to be crazy, Everyone is indeed crazy, but the craziest are the ones who don't know they are crazy; they just keep repeating what others tell them to." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10024-once-in-my-father-s-bookshop-i-heard-a-regular-customer</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2009 21:12:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vicki add a quote by Carlos Ruiz Zafon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10024-once-in-my-father-s-bookshop-i-heard-a-regular-customer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once, in my father's bookshop, I heard a regular customer say that few things leave a deeper mark on a reader than the first book that finds its way into his heart.  Those first images, the echo of words we think we have left behind, accompany us throughout our lives and sculpt a palace in our memory to which, sooner or later—no matter how many books we read, how many worlds we discover, or how much we learn or forget—we will return." -- Carlos Ruiz Zafon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316808-she-either-confused-me-with-a-much-older-child-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 10:13:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vicki add a quote by Kate Morton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316808-she-either-confused-me-with-a-much-older-child-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She either confused me with a much older child or else she glimpsed deep inside my soul and perceived a hole that needed filling. I've always chosen to believe the latter. After all, it's the librarian's sworn purpose to bring books together with their one true reader." -- Kate Morton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382974-she-knew-things-that-nobody-had-ever-told-her-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 18:11:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vicki add a quote by Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382974-she-knew-things-that-nobody-had-ever-told-her-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She knew things that nobody had ever told her... She knew the world was a stallion rolling in the blue pastor of ether. She knew that God tore down the old world every evening and built a new one every sun-up. It was wonderful to see it take form with the sun and emerge from the gray dust of its making." -- Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
