<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/295699-babble]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/295699-babble" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 02:20:36 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51107-children-show-scars-like-medals-lovers-use-them-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 02:20:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Leonard Cohen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51107-children-show-scars-like-medals-lovers-use-them-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Children show scars like medals. Lovers use them as a secrets to reveal. A scar is what happens when the word is made flesh." -- Leonard Cohen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36878-quality-has-to-do-with-intention</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 02:23:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by elliott erwitt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36878-quality-has-to-do-with-intention]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Quality … has to do with intention." -- elliott erwitt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36883-i-often-think-that-the-night-is-more-alive-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 04:22:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by vincent van gogh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36883-i-often-think-that-the-night-is-more-alive-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I often think that the night is more alive and more richly colored than the day." -- vincent van gogh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36884-anyone-who-says-here-s-my-address-write-me-a-poem</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 04:24:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Naomi Shihab Nye]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36884-anyone-who-says-here-s-my-address-write-me-a-poem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who says, “Here’s my address, write me a poem,” deserves something in reply. So I’ll tell you a secret instead: poems hide. In the bottoms of our shoes, they are sleeping. They are the shadows drifting across our ceilings the moment before we wake up. What we have to do is live in a way that lets us find them." -- Naomi Shihab Nye]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625-poetry-is-what-gets-lost-in-translation</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 04:25:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625-poetry-is-what-gets-lost-in-translation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Poetry is what gets lost in translation." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37116-write-without-pay-until-somebody-offers-to-pay</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 18:17:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Mark Twain ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37116-write-without-pay-until-somebody-offers-to-pay]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Write without pay until somebody offers to pay." -- Mark Twain ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127241-forgiveness-must-be-immediate-whether-or-not-a-person-asks</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 20:03:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Rick Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127241-forgiveness-must-be-immediate-whether-or-not-a-person-asks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Forgiveness must be immediate, whether or not a person asks for it. Trust must be rebuilt over time. Trust requires a track record." -- Rick Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228691-usually-when-we-think-of-power-we-think-of-external</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 20:04:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228691-usually-when-we-think-of-power-we-think-of-external]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Usually, when we think of power, we think of external power. And we think of powerful people as those who have made it in the world. A powerful woman isn’t necessarily someone who has money, but we think of her as someone with a boldness or a spark that makes her manifest in a dramatic way.  When we think of a powerful man, we think of his ability to manifest abundance, usually money, in the world.
Most people say that a powerful woman does best with a powerful man, that she needs someone who understands the bigness of her situation, a man who can meet her at the same or even greater level of power in the world. 
Now this is true, if power is defined as material abundance.  A woman often faces cultural prejudice when she makes more money than a man, as does he. A woman who defines power by worldly standards can rarely feel totally relaxed in the arms of a man who doesn’t have it.  
If power is seen as an internal matter, then the situation changes drastically. Internal power has less to do with money and worldly position, and more to do than with emotional expansiveness, spirituality and conscious living…
I used to think I needed a powerful man, someone who could protect me from the harshness and evils of the world.  What I have come to realize is that…the powerful man I was looking for would be foremost, someone who supported me in keeping myself on track spiritually, and in so maintaining clarity within myself, that life would present fewer problems. When it did get rough, he would help me forgive. 
I no longer wanted somebody who would say to me, “Don’t worry honey, if they’re mean to you I’ll beat them up or buy them out.”  Instead, I want someone who prays and meditates with me regularly so that fewer monsters from the outer world disturb me, and who when they do, helps me look within my own consciousness for answers, instead of looking to false power to combat false power.
There’s a big difference between a gentle man and a weak man. Weak men make us nervous. Gentle men make us calm." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206025-what-we-hunger-for-perhaps-more-than-anything-else-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 20:04:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206025-what-we-hunger-for-perhaps-more-than-anything-else-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What we hunger for perhaps more than anything else is to be known in our full humanness, and yet that is often just what we also fear more than anything else.  It is important to tell at least from time to time the secret of who we truly and fully are . . . because otherwise we run the risk of losing track of who we truly and fully are and little by little come to accept instead the highly edited version which we put forth in hope that the world will find it more acceptable than the real thing.  It is important to tell our secrets too because it makes it easier . . . for other people to tell us a secret or two of their own . . .     " -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64162-i-feel-quite-lost-inside-myself-like-i-m-looking-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 20:09:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Sabrina Ward Harrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64162-i-feel-quite-lost-inside-myself-like-i-m-looking-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I feel quite lost INSIDE myself, like I'm looking for my train tracks for my life, as if they would just appear and solve the growing questions I seem to face (my reflection in the morning)." -- Sabrina Ward Harrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65002-when-you-re-lost-in-those-woods-it-sometimes-takes-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 20:48:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65002-when-you-re-lost-in-those-woods-it-sometimes-takes-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you're lost in those woods, it sometimes takes you a while to realize that you are lost. For the longest time, you can convince yourself that you've just wandered off the path, that you'll find your way back to the trailhead any moment now. Then night falls again and again, and you still have no idea where you are, and it's time to admit that you have bewildered yourself so far off the path that you don't even know from which direction the sun rises anymore." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43062-we-must-take-care-of-our-families-wherever-we-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 20:50:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43062-we-must-take-care-of-our-families-wherever-we-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["we must take care of our families wherever we find them." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287971-so-now-i-have-started-living-my-own-life-imperfect</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 21:45:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287971-so-now-i-have-started-living-my-own-life-imperfect]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So now I have started living my own life. Imperfect and clumsy as it may look, it is resembling me now, thoroughly." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90598-there-is-plenty-of-misery-in-the-world-all-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 22:26:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90598-there-is-plenty-of-misery-in-the-world-all-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is plenty of misery in the world, all right, but there is ample pleasure, as well. If a person forswears pleasure in order to avoid misery, what has he gained?...how can you admire a human who consciously embraces the bland, the mediocre, and the safe rather than risk the suffering that disappointments can bring?...If desire causes suffering, it may be because we do not desire wisely, or that we are inexpert at obtaining what we desire...why not get better at fulfilling desire? I cannot believe that the most delicious things were placed here merely to test us, to tempt us, to make it the more difficult for us to achieve the grand prize - they safety of the void. To fashion of life such a petty game is unworthy of both men and gods." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90595-to-diminish-the-worth-of-women-men-had-to-diminish</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 22:27:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90595-to-diminish-the-worth-of-women-men-had-to-diminish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To diminish the worth of women, men had to diminish the worth of the moon. They had to drive a wedge between human beings and the trees and the beasts and the waters, because trees and beasts and waters are as loyal to the moon as to the sun. They had to drive a wedge between thought and feeling...At first they used Apollo as the wedge, and the abstract logic of Apollo made a mighty wedge, indeed, but Apollo the artist maintained a love for women, not the open, unrestrained lust that Pan has, but a controlled longing that undermined the patriarchal ambition. When Christ came along, Christ, who slept with no female...Christ, who played no musical instrument, recited no poetry, and never kicked up his heels by moonlight, this Christ was the perfect wedge. Christianity is merely a system for turning priestesses into handmaidens, queens into concubines, and goddesses into muses." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65031-if-you-lack-the-iron-and-the-fuzz-to-take</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 22:31:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65031-if-you-lack-the-iron-and-the-fuzz-to-take]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you lack the iron and the fuzz to take control of your own life, if you insist on leaving your fate to the gods, then the gods will repay your weakness by having a grin or two at your expense. Should you fail to pilot your own ship, don't be surprised at what inappropriate port you find yourself docked. The dull and prosaic will be granted adventures that will dice their central nervous systems like an onion, romantic dreamers will end up in the rope yard. You may protest that it is too much to ask of an uneducated fifteen-year-old girl that she defy her family, her society, her weighty cultural and religious heritage in order to pursue a dream that she doesn't really understand. Of course it is asking too much. The price of self-destiny is never cheap, and in certain situations it is unthinkable. But to achieve the marvelous, it is precisely the unthinkable that must be thought." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268788-what-bothers-me-today-is-the-lack-of-well-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 22:46:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268788-what-bothers-me-today-is-the-lack-of-well-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["what bothers me today is the lack of, well, i guess you'd call it authentic experience.  so much is a sham. so much is artificial, synthetic, watered-down, and standardized...we're standardizing people, their goals, their ideas.  the sham is everywhere." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189738-a-sense-of-humor-properly-developed-is-superior-to-any</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 22:46:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189738-a-sense-of-humor-properly-developed-is-superior-to-any]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A sense of humor, properly developed, is superior to any religion so far devised." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360137-if-desire-causes-suffering-it-may-be-because-we-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 22:47:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360137-if-desire-causes-suffering-it-may-be-because-we-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If desire causes suffering, it may be because we do not desire wisely, or that we are inexpert at obtaining what we desire.  Instead of hiding our heads in a prayer cloth and building walls against temptation, why not get better at fulfilling desire?  Salvation is for the feeble, that's what I think.  I don't want salvation, I want life, all of life, the miserable as well as the superb.  If the gods would tax ecstasy, then I shall pay; however, I shall protest their taxes at each opportunity, and if Woden or Shiva or Buddha or that Christian fellow--what's his name?--cannot respect that, then I'll accept their wrath.  At least I will have tasted the banquet that they have spread before me on this rich, round planet, rather than recoiling from it like a toothless bunny.  I cannot believe that the most delicious things were placed here merely to test us, to tempt us, to make it the more difficult for us to capture the grand prize:  the safety of the void.  To fashion of life such a petty game is unworthy of both men and gods." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43810-as-a-child-i-was-an-imaginary-playmate</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 21:35:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43810-as-a-child-i-was-an-imaginary-playmate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As a child, I was an imaginary playmate." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123570-scientists-do-not-join-hands-every-sunday-and-sing-yes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 17:07:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Dan Barker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123570-scientists-do-not-join-hands-every-sunday-and-sing-yes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Scientists do not join hands every Sunday and sing &quot;Yes gravity is real!  I know gravity is real!  I will have faith!  I believe in my heart that what goes up, up, up must come down, down, down.  Amen!&quot;  If they did, we would think they were pretty insecure about the concept." -- Dan Barker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219935-i-am-an-atheist-out-and-out-it-took-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 17:08:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Isaac Asimov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219935-i-am-an-atheist-out-and-out-it-took-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am an atheist, out and out. It took me a long time to say it. I've been an atheist for years and years, but somehow I felt it was intellectually unrespectable to say one was an atheist, because it assumed knowledge that one didn't have. Somehow, it was better to say one was a humanist or an agnostic. I finally decided that I'm a creature of emotion as well as of reason. Emotionally, I am an atheist. &lt;b&gt;I don't have the evidence to prove that God doesn't exist, but I so strongly suspect he doesn't that I don't want to waste my time&lt;/b&gt;." -- Isaac Asimov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202435-the-bible-may-indeed-does-contain-a-warrant-for-trafficking</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 17:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202435-the-bible-may-indeed-does-contain-a-warrant-for-trafficking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Bible may, indeed does, contain a warrant for trafficking in humans, for ethnic cleansing, for slavery, for bride-price, and for indiscriminate massacre, but we are not bound by any of it because it was put together by crude, uncultured human mammals." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200510-who-knew-that-the-devil-had-a-factory-where-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 17:17:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Lewis Black]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200510-who-knew-that-the-devil-had-a-factory-where-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who knew that the devil had a factory where he made millions of fossils, which his minions distributed throughout the earth, in order to confuse my tiny brain?" -- Lewis Black]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107578-i-noticed-that-all-the-prayers-i-used-to-offer</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 17:17:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107578-i-noticed-that-all-the-prayers-i-used-to-offer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I noticed that all the prayers I used to offer to God, and all the prayers I now offer to Joe Pesci, are being answered at about the same fifty percent rate. Half the time I get what I want, half the time I don't...Same as the four-leaf clover and the horseshoe...same as the voodoo lady who tells you your fortune by squeezing the goat's testicles. It's all the same...so just pick your superstition, sit back, make a wish, and enjoy yourself..." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52224-if-you-are-a-christian-you-do-not-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 17:19:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52224-if-you-are-a-christian-you-do-not-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are a Christian you do not have to believe that all the other religions are simply wrong all through. If you are an atheist you do have to believe that the main point in all the religions of the whole world is simply one huge mistake." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181804-existentialism-isn-t-so-atheistic-that-it-wears-itself-out-showing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 17:20:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181804-existentialism-isn-t-so-atheistic-that-it-wears-itself-out-showing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Existentialism isn't so atheistic that it wears itself out showing that God doesn't exist. Rather, it declares that even if God did exist, that would change nothing." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/447523-i-want-an-avowed-atheist-in-the-white-house-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 17:21:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Quentin R. Bufogle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/447523-i-want-an-avowed-atheist-in-the-white-house-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want an avowed atheist in the White House. When time comes to push that button, I want whoever's making the decision to understand that once it's pushed, it's over.  Finito.  They're not gonna have lunch with Jesus.  Won't be deflowering 72 virgins on the great shag carpet of eternity, or reincarnated as a cow.  I want someone making that decision who believes life on this Earth isn't just a dress rehearsal for something better -- but the only shot we get." -- Quentin R. Bufogle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74453-an-atheist-believes-that-a-hospital-should-be-built-instead</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 17:21:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by Madalyn Murray O'Hair]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74453-an-atheist-believes-that-a-hospital-should-be-built-instead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An atheist believes that a hospital 
should be built instead of a church. 
An atheist believes that deed must 
be done instead of prayer said.
An atheist strives for involvement in life 
and not escape into death. 
He wants disease conquered, 
poverty vanished, war eliminated." -- Madalyn Murray O'Hair]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34647-a-tattoo-is-a-true-poetic-creation-and-is-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 02:32:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Babble add a quote by V. Vale]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34647-a-tattoo-is-a-true-poetic-creation-and-is-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A tattoo is a true poetic creation, and is always more than meets the eye.  As a tattoo is grounded on living skin, so its essence emotes a poignancy unique to the mortal human condition." -- V. Vale]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
