<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/296204-ross]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/296204-ross" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 18:41:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189935-if-there-was-magic-in-this-world-it-happened-within</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 18:41:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Tee Morris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189935-if-there-was-magic-in-this-world-it-happened-within]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there was magic in this world, it happened within sight of the three bases and home plate.  All the gems in my world that decorated the walls and floors of dragons' lairs, the sword hilts of privileged princes, and crowns worn by emperors and kings, were nothing compared to the beauty and splendor of the diamond in Wrigley Stadium.  It wasn't just a yard with dirt, chalk lines, bases, and a small hill in its center.  Wrigley was a field of dreams.  Dreams of eternal glory for the men who ran to the outfield, who took their respective bases, and prepared for battle against those who would dare enter their hallowed realm.  Dreams for the kids in the stands, all wanting to don a uniform, kiss their moms goodbye, and wield their bats as enchanted weapons destined to knock the cover off the ball.  And for the adults who had already selected their lot in life, Wrigley made the dreams of past innocence, lost wonder, and the promise that there was something inherently good still left in the world, come true.

Yeah, corny as hell.  But all true." -- Tee Morris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42276-can-a-magician-kill-a-man-by-magic-lord-wellington</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 07:44:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Susanna Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42276-can-a-magician-kill-a-man-by-magic-lord-wellington]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Can a magician kill a man by magic?” Lord Wellington asked Strange. Strange frowned. He seemed to dislike the question. “I suppose a magician might,” he admitted, “but a gentleman never would." -- Susanna Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196975-black-as-night-sweet-as-sin</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 09:49:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196975-black-as-night-sweet-as-sin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Black as night, sweet as sin." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9467-alice-laughed-there-s-no-use-trying-she-said-one-can-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 05:34:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9467-alice-laughed-there-s-no-use-trying-she-said-one-can-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alice laughed. 'There's no use trying,' she said. 'One can't believe impossible things.'

I daresay you haven't had much practice,' said the Queen. 'When I was your age, I always did it for half-an-hour a day. Why, sometimes I've believed as many as six impossible things before breakfast. There goes the shawl again!" -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358502-only-boxers-can-understand-the-loneliness-of-tennis-players--</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2011 17:46:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Andre Agassi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358502-only-boxers-can-understand-the-loneliness-of-tennis-players--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only boxers can understand the loneliness of tennis players - and yet boxers have their corner men and managers.  Even a boxer's opponent provides a kind of companionship, someone he can grapple with and grunt at.  In tennis you stand face-to-face with the enemy, trade blows with him, but never touch him or talk to him, or anyone else.  The rules forbid a tennis player from even talking to his coach while on the court.  People sometimes mention the track-and-field runner as a comparably lonely figure, but I have to laugh.  At least the runner can feel and smell his opponents.  They're inches away.  In tennis you're on an island.  Of all the games men and women play, tennis is the closest to solitary confinement...." -- Andre Agassi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358505-it-s-no-accident-i-think-that-tennis-uses-the-language</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2011 17:53:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Andre Agassi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358505-it-s-no-accident-i-think-that-tennis-uses-the-language]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's no accident, I think, that tennis uses the language of life.  Advantage, service, fault, break, love, the basic elements of tennis are those of everyday existence, because every match is a life in miniature.  Even the structure of tennis, the way the pieces fit inside one another like Russian nesting dolls, mimics the structure of our days.  Points become games become sets become tournaments, and it's all so tightly connected that any point can become the turning point.  It reminds me of the way seconds become minutes become hours, and any hour can be our finest.  Or darkest.  It's our choice." -- Andre Agassi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395127-you-don-t-pay-back-your-parents-you-can-t-the-debt</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 09:25:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395127-you-don-t-pay-back-your-parents-you-can-t-the-debt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't pay back your parents.  You can't.  The debt you owe them gets collected by your children, who hand it down in turn.  It's a sort of entailment.  Or if you don't have children of the body, it's left as a debt to your common humanity.  Or to your God, if you possess or are possessed by one.

The family economy evades calculation in the gross planetary product.  It's the only deal I know where, when you give more than you get, you aren't bankrupted - but rather, vastly enriched." -- Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13907-reputation-is-what-other-people-know-about-you-honor-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 10:26:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13907-reputation-is-what-other-people-know-about-you-honor-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reputation is what other people know about you. Honor is what you know about yourself." -- Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/461561-there-are-people-who-try-to-look-as-if-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 11:37:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by John D. MacDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/461561-there-are-people-who-try-to-look-as-if-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...there are people who try to look as if they are doing a good and thorough job, and then there are the people who actually damn well do it, for its own sake." -- John D. MacDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730526-it-seems-to-me-that-any-law-that-is-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 09:29:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Robert A Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730526-it-seems-to-me-that-any-law-that-is-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seems to me that any law that is not enforced and can't be enforced weakens all other laws." -- Robert A Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730530-sick-cultures-show-a-complex-of-symptoms-such-as-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 09:31:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Robert A Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730530-sick-cultures-show-a-complex-of-symptoms-such-as-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sick cultures show a complex of symptoms such as you have named...but a dying culture invariably exhibits personal rudeness.  Bad manners.  Lack of consideration for others in minor matters.  A loss of politeness, of gentle manners, is more significant than is a riot." -- Robert A Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/684719-he-seemed-a-part-of-the-mute-melancholy-landscape-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 09:33:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/684719-he-seemed-a-part-of-the-mute-melancholy-landscape-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He seemed a part of the mute melancholy landscape, an incarnation of it's frozen woe, with all that was warm and sentient in him fast bound below the surface; but there was nothing nothing unfriendly in his silence.  I simply felt that he lived in a depth of moral isolation too remote for casual access, and I had the sense that his loneliness was not merely the result of his personal plight, tragic as I guessed that to be, but had in it, as Harmon Gow had hinted, the profound accumulated cold of many Starkfield winters." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730538-the-curt-maneuver-forced-hearty-laughter-from-all-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 09:36:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730538-the-curt-maneuver-forced-hearty-laughter-from-all-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The curt maneuver forced hearty laughter from all of the fathers in the ballroom, who were delighted by the illusion of danger and the impotence of Nature." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8510-to-argue-with-a-man-who-has-renounced-the-use</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 09:36:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Thomas Paine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8510-to-argue-with-a-man-who-has-renounced-the-use]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To argue with a man who has renounced the use and authority of reason, and whose philosophy consists in holding humanity in contempt, is like administering medicine to the dead, or endeavoring to convert an atheist by scripture." -- Thomas Paine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730544-you-know-emily-was-a-selfish-old-woman-in-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 09:40:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Agatha Christie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730544-you-know-emily-was-a-selfish-old-woman-in-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know, Emily was a selfish old woman in her way.  She was very generous, but she always wanted a return.  She never let people forget what she had done for them - and, that way she missed love." -- Agatha Christie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730548-i-had-a-lot-of-other-ideas-now-and-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 09:42:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by H. Beam Piper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730548-i-had-a-lot-of-other-ideas-now-and-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had a lot of other ideas, now and then, but every time I took a second look at one, it got sick and died." -- H. Beam Piper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730561-how-is-a-sincere-criminal-trying-hard-going-to-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 09:51:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730561-how-is-a-sincere-criminal-trying-hard-going-to-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How is a sincere criminal, trying hard, going to get ahead in his profession if his victim fails to cooperate?" -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416296-hit-it-you-have-to-hit-it-harder-than-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 09:52:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416296-hit-it-you-have-to-hit-it-harder-than-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hit it! You have to hit it harder than that. Electrons are timid little things but notional; you have to let them know who’s boss." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730569-the-way-to-find-justice-is-to-deal-fairly-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 09:53:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730569-the-way-to-find-justice-is-to-deal-fairly-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The way to find justice is to deal fairly with other people and not worry about how they deal with you." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11649-the-america-of-my-time-line-is-a-laboratory-example</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 07:50:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ross add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11649-the-america-of-my-time-line-is-a-laboratory-example]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The America of my time line is a laboratory example of what can happen to democracies, what has eventually happened to all perfect democracies throughout all histories.  A perfect democracy, a ‘warm body’ democracy in which every adult may vote and all votes count equally, has no internal feedback for self-correction.  It depends solely on the wisdom and self-restraint of citizens… which is opposed by the folly and lack of self-restraint of other citizens.  What is supposed to happen in a democracy is that each sovereign citizen will always vote in the public interest for the safety and welfare of all.  But what does happen is that he votes his own self-interest as he sees it… which for the majority translates as ‘Bread and Circuses.’

‘Bread and Circuses’ is the cancer of democracy, the fatal disease for which there is no cure.  Democracy often works beautifully at first.  But once a state extends the franchise to every warm body, be he producer or parasite, that day marks the beginning of the end of the state.  For when the plebs discover that they can vote themselves bread and circuses without limit and that the productive members of the body politic cannot stop them, they will do so, until the state bleeds to death, or in its weakened condition the state succumbs to an invader—the barbarians enter Rome." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
