<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/297812-japhet-els]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/297812-japhet-els" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 08:21:35 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/783-what-is-love-i-have-met-in-the-streets-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 08:21:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Japhet add a quote by Victor Hugo ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/783-what-is-love-i-have-met-in-the-streets-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What Is Love? I have met in the streets a very poor young man who was in love. His hat was old, his coat worn, the water passed through his shoes and the stars through his soul" -- Victor Hugo ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437-out-beyond-ideas-of-wrongdoing-and-rightdoing-there-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 08:22:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Japhet add a quote by Jalal Ad-Din Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437-out-beyond-ideas-of-wrongdoing-and-rightdoing-there-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Out beyond ideas of wrongdoing 
and rightdoing there is a field.
I'll meet you there.

When the soul lies down in that grass
the world is too full to talk about." -- Jalal Ad-Din Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7492-i-have-lots-of-things-to-teach-you-now-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 08:27:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Japhet add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7492-i-have-lots-of-things-to-teach-you-now-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have lots of things  to teach you now, in case we ever meet, concerning the message that was transmitted to me under a pine tree in North Carolina on a cold winter moonlit night. It said that Nothing Ever Happened, so don't worry. It's all like a dream. Everything is ecstasy, inside. We just don't know it because of our thinking-minds. But in our true blissful essence of mind is known that everything is alright forever and forever and forever. Close your eyes, let your hands and nerve-ends drop, stop breathing for 3 seconds, listen to the silence inside the illusion of the world, and you will remember the lesson you forgot, which was taught in immense milky way soft cloud innumerable worlds long ago and not even at all. It is all one vast awakened thing. I call it the golden eternity. It is perfect. We were never really born, we will never really die. It has nothing to do with the imaginary idea of a personal self, other selves, many selves everywhere: Self is only an idea, a mortal idea. That which passes into everything is one thing. It's a dream already ended. There's nothing to be afraid of and nothing to be glad about. I know this from staring at mountains months on end. They never show any expression, they are like empty space. Do you think the emptiness of space will ever crumble away? Mountains will crumble, but the emptiness of space, which is the one universal essence of mind, the vast awakenerhood, empty and awake, will never crumble away because it was never born." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104714-because-to-influence-a-person-is-to-give-him-one-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 08:30:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Japhet add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104714-because-to-influence-a-person-is-to-give-him-one-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because to influence a person is to give him one's own soul. He does not think his natural thoughts, or burn with his natural passions. His virtues are not real to him. His sins, if there are such things as sins, are borrowed. He becomes an echo of some one else's music, an actor of a part that has not been written for him. The aim of life is self-development. To realize one's nature perfectly -- that is what each of us is here for. People are afraid of themselves, nowadays. They have forgotten the highest of all duties, the duty that one owes to oneself. Of course they are charitable. They feed the hungry, and clothe the beggar. But their own souls starve, and are naked. Courage has gone out of our race. Perhaps we never really had it. The terror of society, which is the basis of morals, the terror of God, which is the secret of religion -- these are the two things that govern us." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
