<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/299378-sohrab-rahimi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/299378-sohrab-rahimi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 06:38:46 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/731291-azita-ghahreman-is-an-iranian-poet-1-she-was-born-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 06:38:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sohrab add a quote by آزیتا قهرمان]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/731291-azita-ghahreman-is-an-iranian-poet-1-she-was-born-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Azita Ghahreman, is an Iranian poet.[1] She was born in Iran in 1962. She has written four books in Persian and one book in Swedish. She has also translated American poetry. She is a member of the Iranian Writers Association and International PEN.
She has published four collections of poetry: Eve's Songs (1983), Sculptures of Autumn (1986), Forgetfulness is a Simple Ritual (1992) and The Suburb of Crows (2008), a collection reflecting on he exile in Sweden (she lives in an area called oxie on the outskirts of Malmö) that was published in both Swedish and Persian.
Her poems directly address questions of female desire and challenge the accepted position of women.
A collection of Azita's work was published in Swedish in 2009 alongside the work of Sohrab Rahimi and Christine Carlson. She has also translated a collection of poems by the American poet and cartoonist, Shel Silverstein, into Persian, The Place Where the Sidewalk Ends (2000). And she has edited three volumes of poems by poets from Khorasan, the eastern province of Iran that borders Afghanistan and which has a rich and distinctive history.
Azita's poems have been translated into German, Dutch, Arabic, Chinese, Swedish, Spanish, Macedonian, Turkish, Danish, French and English. A new book of poetry, Under Hypnosis in Dr Caligari's Cabinet was published in Sweden in April 2012.
[edit]Books

Eva's Songs, (persian)1990
Autumn Sculptures,(persian) 1995
Where the sidewalk ends, Shell Silverstein(Translated to Persian with Morteza Behravan) 2000
The Forgetfulness has a Simple Ceremony,(persian) 2002
Here is the Suburb of Crows,(persian) 2009
four Poetry books ( collected poems 1990-2009 in Swedish), 2009
under hypnosis in Dr kaligaris Cabinet, (Swedish) 2012
Poetry Translation Center London( collected poems in English) 2012" -- آزیتا قهرمان]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/731353-fron-wikipedia-http-sv-wikipedia-org-wiki-azita-ghahreman-azita-ghahreman-f-ddes-i-iran-efter-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 08:32:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sohrab add a quote by Azita Ghahreman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/731353-fron-wikipedia-http-sv-wikipedia-org-wiki-azita-ghahreman-azita-ghahreman-f-ddes-i-iran-efter-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["fron wikipedia:
http://sv.wikipedia.org/wiki/Azita_Ghahreman

Azita Ghahreman föddes i Iran. Efter att ha utbildat sig till lärare studerade hon språk, litteratur och mytologi. Hon har haft uppdrag i FN och arbetat för organisationen ”läkare utan gränser”.Sedan 2006 bor hon i Malmö. Hon är medlem i Författarcentrum syd.
Författarskap [redigera]

Azita Ghahreman debuterade som poet 1990. Hennes första bok Avazhaaye havva (Evas sånger) blev mycket uppmärksammad i iranska media. Tandishaaye paeezi (höstens skulpturer) kom ut 1996. Den tredje diktsamlingen Faramooshi aine sadei daarad (glömskan har en enkel ceremoni) 2002 blev nominerad till årets bästa diktsamling och fick bra kritik i iransk press.
Hennes dikter är översatta till franska, holländska, engelska, tyska, arabiska, makedonska, kinesiska,albanska, danska och svenska. Förutom i Iran har hon haft föredrag och poesiuppläsningar i Sverige, Holland, Tyskland, Makedonien, Albanien, England och Frankrike.
Analys av författarskapet [redigera]

Dikterna handlar om människans möte med det ofrånkomliga och det som uppstår i varje kontakt med tingen och skeenden runtomkring oss. I hennes tidigare dikter finns spår av sorg över en förlorad barndom i ett religiöst land, som sätter många förbud. I senare dikter ser man en mognare hållning till världen och språket. Här upptäcker poeten människans begränsningar och försöker komma underfund med ångestens drivande kraft. Genom skapandet försöker hon göra sig fri från förutbestämda, förutfattade meningar om rätt och fel. I de dikter som har skrivits efter 2000 märks en lekfull poet som behärskar orden, språket och historien. Filosofiska och mytologiska studier gör sig påminda som en sorts nyupptäckt av språket och ett nytt sätt att se på världen. Poeten möter en bitter verklighet med en känsla av ironi och filosofisk beundran över stora och små händelser. Det vore fel att betrakta Ghahreman som en politisk poet. Hennes dikter kan betecknas som universella, samtidigt som de karakteriserar en iransk kvinnas liv och öde. I de senare dikterna finns dikter av erotisk karaktär. Det är få iranska kvinnor som har vågat skriva erotiska dikter så öppet och starkt. Hennes dikter ingår i en tusenårig tradition av persisk litteratur.
Bibliografi" -- Azita Ghahreman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/721042</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 08:08:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sohrab add a quote by سهراب رحیمی]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/721042]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["سهراب رحیمی، متولد چهارم دیماه سال ۱۳۴۱ چهارمحال بختیاری، ساکن مالمو؛سوئد است. سهراب رحیمی، شاعر ,نویسنده,منتقد و مترجم؛ عضو کانون نویسندگان سوئد و عضو کانون مترجمان ادبی سوئد است. او همچنین عضو هیئت مدیره ی مرکز نویسندگان سوئد است و عضو و کارشناس انجمن قلم سوئد. از سال ۱۳۶۵ به سوئد مهاجرت کرده‌است. رحیمی همکاری با نشریات ایران و سوئد را از سال ۱۳۶۸ با چاپ شعر، نقد، مقاله و ترجمه آغاز کرد. او از ۱۳۷۵ تا ۱۳۷۷سردبیری گاهنامه‌ی شعری اثر را بر عهده داشت. از کتاب‌هایش می‌توان به مجموعه شعر &quot;خانه خواب‌ها&quot;، نشر آموزش ۱۳۷۵،مجموعه شعر &quot;هسته‌های فاسد زمان&quot;، نشر رویا ۱۳۷۶،مجموعه شعر &quot;مرهم سپید&quot; از کلاستروفوبی ۱۳۷۷ (با رباب محب و س.مازندرانی) نشر ولی،مجموعه شعر &quot;نامه ای برای تو&quot;، نشر آینهٔ جنوب۱۳۸۴و مجموعه شعر &quot;رسم هندسی ی مالیخولیا&quot; ١٣٩٠ اشاره کرد.سهراب رحیمی همچنین، مجموعه‌ی آثار آزیتا قهرمان را با همکاری کریستیان کارلسون به سوئدی ترجمه کرده و در سال ۱۳۸۸ توسط نشر اسموکادول به چاپ رسانده است.همچنین رمانی در باره ی خاطرات جنگ در سال١٣٩٠ در سوئد به زبان سوئدی منتشر کرد که مورد توجه مطبوعات سوئد قرار گرفت.سهراب رحیمی هم‌اکنون منتقد شعر نشریه‌ی کولتورن سوئد است.او به عنوان مسئول بخش سوئدی و مسئول بخش ترجمه؛ با سایت‌های ادبی تاسیان و پیاده‌رو همکاری می‌کند.اشعار رحیمی تا کنون به زبان‌های ترکی، عربی، انگلیسی، فارسی، اسپانیایی؛ فرانسوی، مقدونی؛دانمارکی؛ روسی؛اوکراینی ؛ چینی و آلمانی ترجمه شده‌است.سهراب رحیمی در سال ۱۳۸۹ داوری جایزه‌ی شعر خبرنگاران ایران را بر عهده داشت. سال ۱۳۹۰ به عنوان داور با جایزه‌ی شعر نیما و جایزه شعر لیراو همکاری داشت .و همچنین در سال ۱۳۹۱ داور جایزه ی شعر زنان ایران ( خورشید)بود.از جمله ی آثار او در یک سال گذشته می توان به منتخب اشعارتوماس ترانسترومر اشاره کرد که در سال جاری با همکاری آزیتا قهرمان ترجمه شد و با همیاری ی نشر آرست بچاپ رسید. همچنین انتشار مجموعه اشعارش به سوئدی در آذر امسال با نام سفرهای ناگزیر." -- سهراب رحیمی]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22872-words-are-flowing-out-like-endless-rain-into-a-paper</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 12:53:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sohrab add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22872-words-are-flowing-out-like-endless-rain-into-a-paper]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Words are flowing out like endless rain into a paper cup,
They slither wildly as they slip away across the universe
Pools of sorrow, waves of joy are drifting through my open mind,
Possessing and caressing me.
Images of broken light which dance before me like a million eyes,
They call me on and on across the universe,
Thoughts meander like a restless wind inside a letter box
They tumble blindly as they make their way
Across the universe
Sounds of laughter shades of love are
Ringing through my open ears inciting and inviting me
Limitless undying love which shines around me like a  
Million suns, and calls me on and on
Across the universe" -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73700</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 00:28:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sohrab add a quote by عرفان نظرآهاری]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73700]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["به شانه ام زدي 

كه تنهايي ام را تكانده باشي 


به چه دل خوش كرده اي ؟ 

تكاندن برف 

از شانه هاي آدم برفي ؟
" -- عرفان نظرآهاری]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/745121-love-is-a-rebellious-bird-that-nobody-can-tame-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 06:04:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sohrab add a quote by Ludovic Halévy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/745121-love-is-a-rebellious-bird-that-nobody-can-tame-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a rebellious bird, 
that nobody can tame, 
and you call him quite in vain, 
if it suits him not to come." -- Ludovic Halévy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78025</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 05:01:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sohrab add a quote by صادق هدایت]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78025]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["اگر زندگانی سپری نمی شد چقدر تلخ و ترسناک بود." -- صادق هدایت]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1858-for-most-of-history-anonymous-was-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 05:01:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sohrab add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1858-for-most-of-history-anonymous-was-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For most of history, Anonymous was a woman." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339676-the-one-who-doesnt-play-doesnt-win-anything-but-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 05:01:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sohrab add a quote by alber camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339676-the-one-who-doesnt-play-doesnt-win-anything-but-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the one who doesnt play, doesnt win anything, but he actually looses somehting, {playing}" -- alber camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2495-do-you-hate-people-i-don-t-hate-them-i-just-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 05:01:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sohrab add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2495-do-you-hate-people-i-don-t-hate-them-i-just-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you hate people?

I don't hate them...I just feel better when they're not around." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1222-you-cannot-find-peace-by-avoiding-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 05:01:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sohrab add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1222-you-cannot-find-peace-by-avoiding-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You cannot find peace by avoiding life." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
