<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/301858-brandi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/301858-brandi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 22:05:34 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54301-remember-remember-this-is-now-and-now-and-now-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 22:05:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandi add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54301-remember-remember-this-is-now-and-now-and-now-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember, remember, this is now, and now, and now. Live it, feel it, cling to it. I want to become acutely aware of all I’ve taken for granted." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23327-that-s-one-of-the-reasons-i-never-wanted-to-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 22:10:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandi add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23327-that-s-one-of-the-reasons-i-never-wanted-to-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That’s one of the reasons I never wanted to get married. The last thing I wanted was infinite security and to be the place an arrow shoots off from. I wanted change and excitement and to shoot off in all directions myself, like the colored arrows from a Fourth of July rocket." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211000-i-like-people-too-much-or-not-at-all-i-ve</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 22:12:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandi add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211000-i-like-people-too-much-or-not-at-all-i-ve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like people too much or not at all. I've got to go down deep, to fall into people, to really know them." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200854-the-only-way-to-make-sense-out-of-change-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 18:59:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandi add a quote by Alan Wilson Watts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200854-the-only-way-to-make-sense-out-of-change-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only way to make sense out of change is to plunge into it, move with it, and join the dance." -- Alan Wilson Watts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440833-basic-principles-1-creativity-is-the-natural-order-of-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 19:04:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandi add a quote by Julia Cameron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440833-basic-principles-1-creativity-is-the-natural-order-of-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Basic Principles:

1. Creativity is the natural order of life. Life is energy: pure creative energy.

2. There is an underlying, in-dwelling creative force infusing all of life -- including ourselves.

3. When we open ourselves to our creativity, we open ourselves to the creator's creativity within us and our lives.

4. We are, ourselves, creations. And we, in turn, are meant to continue creativity by being creative ourselves.

5. Creativity is God's gift to us. Using our creativity is our gift back to God.

6. The refusal to be creative is self-will and is counter to our true nature.

7. When we open ourselves to exploring our creativity, we open ourselves to God: good orderly direction.

8. As we open our creative channel to the creator, many gentle but powerful changes are to be expected.

9. It is safe to open ourselves up to greater and greater creativity.

10. Our creative dreams and yearnings come from a divine source. As we move toward our dreams, we move toward our divinity." -- Julia Cameron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/697770-contrary-to-what-we-usually-believe-moments-like-these-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 19:07:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandi add a quote by Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/697770-contrary-to-what-we-usually-believe-moments-like-these-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Contrary to what we usually believe, moments like these, the best moments in our lives, are not the passive, receptive, relaxing times—although such experiences can also be enjoyable, if we have worked hard to attain them. The best moments usually occur when a person’s body or mind is stretched to its limits in a voluntary effort to accomplish something difficult and worthwhile. Optimal experience is thus something that we
make happen. For a child, it could be placing with trembling fingers the last blockon a tower she has built, higher than any she has built so far; for a swimmer, it could be trying to beat his own record; for a violinist, mastering an intricate musical passage. For each person there are thousands of opportunities, challenges to expand ourselves." -- Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/348731-but-it-is-impossible-to-enjoy-a-tennis-game-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 19:07:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandi add a quote by Csikszentmihaly]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/348731-but-it-is-impossible-to-enjoy-a-tennis-game-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But it is impossible to enjoy a tennis game, a book, or a conversation unless attention is fully concentrated on the activity." -- Csikszentmihaly]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
