<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/302268-loi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/302268-loi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 10:42:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 10:42:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 10:43:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Groucho Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Outside of a dog, a book is man's best friend. Inside of a dog it's too dark to read." -- Groucho Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298-a-day-without-sunshine-is-like-you-know-night</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 10:44:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298-a-day-without-sunshine-is-like-you-know-night]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A day without sunshine is like, you know, night." -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66512-i-believe-in-pink-i-believe-that-laughing-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 09:10:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66512-i-believe-in-pink-i-believe-that-laughing-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in pink. I believe that laughing is the best calorie burner. I believe in kissing, kissing a lot. I believe in being strong when everything seems to be going wrong. I believe that happy girls are the prettiest girls. I believe that tomorrow is another day and I believe in miracles." -- Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5402-so-it-s-not-gonna-be-easy-it-s-going-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 10:36:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5402-so-it-s-not-gonna-be-easy-it-s-going-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So it's not gonna be easy. It's going to be really hard; we're gonna have to work at this everyday, but I want to do that because I want you. I want all of you, forever, everyday. You and me... everyday." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29652-a-girl-should-be-two-things-classy-and-fabulous</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2011 09:47:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Coco Chanel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29652-a-girl-should-be-two-things-classy-and-fabulous]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A girl should be two things: classy and fabulous." -- Coco Chanel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54377-i-m-tough-i-m-ambitious-and-i-know-exactly-what-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2011 09:49:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Madonna]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54377-i-m-tough-i-m-ambitious-and-i-know-exactly-what-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm tough, I'm ambitious, and I know exactly what I want. If that makes me a bitch, okay." -- Madonna]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50909-make-it-your-ambition-to-lead-a-quiet-life-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 19:01:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by 1 Thessalonians 4:11-12]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50909-make-it-your-ambition-to-lead-a-quiet-life-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Make it your ambition to lead a quiet life, to mind your own business and to work with your hands, just as we told you, so that your daily life may win the respect of outsiders and so that you will not be dependent on anyone." -- 1 Thessalonians 4:11-12]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6130-a-woman-should-have-enough-money-within-her-control</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 23:47:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Pamela Redmond Satran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6130-a-woman-should-have-enough-money-within-her-control]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  enough money within her control to move out
  and rent a place of her own even if she never wants
  to or needs to...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  something perfect to wear if the employer or date of her
  dreams wants to see her in an hour...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ...
  a youth she's content to leave behind....
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a past juicy enough that she's looking forward to
  retelling it in her old age....
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE .....
  a set of screwdrivers, a cordless drill, and a black
  lace bra...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  one friend who always makes her laugh... and one who
  lets her cry...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a good piece of furniture not previously owned by anyone
  else in her family...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  eight matching plates, wine glasses with stems, and a
  recipe for a meal that will make her guests feel honored...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a feeling of control over her destiny...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  how to fall in love without losing herself..
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  HOW TO QUIT A JOB,
  BREAK UP WITH A LOVER,
  AND CONFRONT A FRIEND WITHOUT RUINING THE FRIENDSHIP...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  when to try harder... and WHEN TO WALK AWAY...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  that she can't change the length of her calves,
  the width of her hips, or the nature of her parents..
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  that her childhood may not have been perfect...but it's over...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  what she would and wouldn't do for love or more...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  how to live alone... even if she doesn't like it...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  whom she can trust,
  whom she can't,
  and why she shouldn't
  take it personally...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  where to go...
  be it to her best friend's kitchen table...
  or a charming inn in the woods...
  when her soul needs soothing...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  what she can and can't accomplish in a day...
  a month...and a year..." -- Pamela Redmond Satran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145819-once-you-had-put-the-pieces-back-together-even-though</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 00:25:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145819-once-you-had-put-the-pieces-back-together-even-though]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once you had put the pieces back together, even though you may look intact, you were never quite the same as you'd been before the fall." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13163-but-there-are-times-in-this-harum-scarum-world-when-figuring</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 00:29:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13163-but-there-are-times-in-this-harum-scarum-world-when-figuring]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But there are times in this harum-scarum world when figuring out the right thing to do is quite simple, but doing the right thing is simply impossible...." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149964-change-is-a-funny-thing-we-never-are-quite-sure</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 00:32:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149964-change-is-a-funny-thing-we-never-are-quite-sure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Change is a funny thing. We never are quite sure what we are becoming or even why. Then one day we look at ourselves and wonder who we are and how we got that way. Only one thing about change remains constant...it is always painful" -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 00:38:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Bob Moorehead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The paradox of our time in history is that we have taller buildings but 
shorter tempers, wider Freeways, but narrower viewpoints.  We spend more, 
but have less, we buy more, but enjoy less. We have bigger houses and 
smaller families, more conveniences, but less time.  We have more degrees 
but less sense, more knowledge, but less judgment, more experts, yet more 
problems, more medicine, but less wellness.

We drink too much, smoke too much, spend too recklessly, laugh too little, 
drive too fast, get too angry, stay up too late, get up too tired, read too 
little, watch TV too much, and pray too seldom.  We have multiplied our 
possessions, but reduced our values.  We talk too much, love too seldom, and 
hate too often.

We've learned how to make a living, but not a life. We've added years to 
life not life to years.  We've been all the way to the moon and back, but 
have trouble crossing the street to meet a new neighbor.  We conquered outer 
space but not inner space.  We've done larger things, but not better things.

We've cleaned up the air, but polluted the soul. We've conquered the atom, 
but not our prejudice.  We write more, but learn less.  We plan more, but 
accomplish less.  We've learned to rush, but not to wait.  We build more 
computers to hold more information, to produce more copies than ever, but we 
communicate less and less.

These are the times of fast foods and slow digestion, big men and small 
character, steep profits and shallow relationships.

These are the days of two incomes but more divorce, fancier houses, but 
broken homes.  These are days of quick trips, disposable diapers, throwaway 
morality, one night stands, overweight bodies, and pills that do everything 
from cheer, to quiet, to kill.  It is a time when there is much in the 
showroom window and nothing in the stockroom.  A time when technology can 
bring this letter to you, and a time when you can choose either to share 
this insight, or to just hit delete...

Remember, to spend some time with your loved ones, because they are not 
going to be around forever.  Remember, say a kind word to someone who looks 
up to you in awe, because that little person soon will grow up and leave 
your side.

Remember, to give a warm hug to the one next to you, because that is the 
only treasure you can give with your heart and it doesn't cost a cent.

Remember, to say, &quot;I love you&quot; to your partner and your loved ones, but most 
of all mean it.  A kiss and an embrace will mend hurt when it comes from 
deep inside of you.

Remember to hold hands and cherish the moment for someday that person might 
not be there again.  Give time to love, give time to speak! And give time to 
share the precious thoughts in your mind." -- Bob Moorehead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54328-you-may-tire-of-reality-but-you-never-tire-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 00:47:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54328-you-may-tire-of-reality-but-you-never-tire-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may tire of reality but you never tire of dreams." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51592-man-was-made-at-the-end-of-the-week-s-work</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 07:09:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51592-man-was-made-at-the-end-of-the-week-s-work]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man was made at the end of the week's work when God was tired." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251836-we-re-so-self-important-everybody-s-going-to-save-something-now-save</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 07:12:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251836-we-re-so-self-important-everybody-s-going-to-save-something-now-save]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We’re so self-important. Everybody’s going to save something now. “Save the trees, save the bees, save the whales, save those snails.” And the greatest arrogance of all: save the planet. Save the planet, we don’t even know how to take care of ourselves yet. I’m tired of this shit.  I’m tired of f-ing Earth Day.  I’m tired of these self-righteous environmentalists, these white, bourgeois liberals who think the only thing wrong with this country is that there aren’t enough bicycle paths.  People trying to make the world safe for Volvos.  Besides, environmentalists don’t give a shit about the planet.  Not in the abstract they don’t.  You know what they’re interested in?  A clean place to live.  Their own habitat.  They’re worried that some day in the future they might be personally inconvenienced.  Narrow, unenlightened self-interest doesn’t impress me.

The planet has been through a lot worse than us. Been through earthquakes, volcanoes, plate tectonics, continental drift, solar flares, sun spots, magnetic storms, the magnetic reversal of the poles … hundreds of thousands of years of bombardment by comets and asteroids and meteors, worldwide floods, tidal waves, worldwide fires, erosion, cosmic rays, recurring ice ages … And we think some plastic bags and some aluminum cans are going to make a difference? The planet isn’t going anywhere. WE are!

We’re going away. Pack your shit, folks. We’re going away. And we won’t leave much of a trace, either. Maybe a little Styrofoam … The planet’ll be here and we’ll be long gone. Just another failed mutation. Just another closed-end biological mistake. An evolutionary cul-de-sac. The planet’ll shake us off like a bad case of fleas.

The planet will be here for a long, long, LONG time after we’re gone, and it will heal itself, it will cleanse itself, ’cause that’s what it does. It’s a self-correcting system. The air and the water will recover, the earth will be renewed.  And if it’s true that plastic is not degradable, well, the planet will simply incorporate plastic into a new paradigm: the earth plus plastic.  The earth doesn’t share our prejudice toward plastic.  Plastic came out of the earth.  The earth probably sees plastic as just another one of its children.  Could be the only reason the earth allowed us to be spawned from it in the first place.  It wanted plastic for itself.  Didn’t know how to make it.  Needed us.  Could be the answer to our age-old egocentric philosophical question, “Why are we here?” 

Plastic… asshole." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200357-if-i-die-suddenly-my-gravestone-might-appropriately-offer-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 07:16:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Beth Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200357-if-i-die-suddenly-my-gravestone-might-appropriately-offer-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...if I die suddenly, my gravestone might appropriately offer this insight into my departure: &quot;God got tired.&quot;  I require lots of work." -- Beth Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32896-if-you-are-irritated-by-every-rub-how-will-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 07:26:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32896-if-you-are-irritated-by-every-rub-how-will-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are irritated by every rub, how will your mirror be polished?" -- Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189796-promise-yourself-to-be-so-strong-that-nothing-can-disturb</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 19:00:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Christian D. Larson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189796-promise-yourself-to-be-so-strong-that-nothing-can-disturb]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Promise Yourself

To be so strong that nothing
can disturb your peace of mind.
To talk health, happiness, and prosperity
to every person you meet.

To make all your friends feel
that there is something in them
To look at the sunny side of everything
and make your optimism come true.

To think only the best, to work only for the best,
and to expect only the best.
To be just as enthusiastic about the success of others
as you are about your own.

To forget the mistakes of the past
and press on to the greater achievements of the future.
To wear a cheerful countenance at all times
and give every living creature you meet a smile.

To give so much time to the improvement of yourself
that you have no time to criticize others.
To be too large for worry, too noble for anger, too strong for fear,
and too happy to permit the presence of trouble.

To think well of yourself and to proclaim this fact to the world,
not in loud words but great deeds.
To live in faith that the whole world is on your side
so long as you are true to the best that is in you." -- Christian D. Larson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16354-this-is-very-important----to-take-leisure-time-pace</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 19:19:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16354-this-is-very-important----to-take-leisure-time-pace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is very important -- to take leisure time. Pace is the essence. Without stopping entirely and doing nothing at all for great periods, you're gonna lose everything...just to do nothing at all, very, very important. And how many people do this in modern society? Very few. That's why they're all totally mad, frustrated, angry and hateful." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181932-it-is-very-frustrating-not-to-be-understood-in-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 19:21:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181932-it-is-very-frustrating-not-to-be-understood-in-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is very frustrating not to be understood in this world. If you say one thing and keep being told that you mean something else, it can make you want to scream. But somewhere in the world there is a place for all of us, whether you are an electric form of decoration, peppermint-scented sweet, a source of timber, or a potato pancake." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18075-one-lives-in-the-hope-of-becoming-a-memory</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 06:48:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Antonio Porchia]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18075-one-lives-in-the-hope-of-becoming-a-memory]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One lives in the hope of becoming a memory." -- Antonio Porchia]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109487-love-is-how-you-stay-alive-even-after-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 06:49:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109487-love-is-how-you-stay-alive-even-after-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is how you stay alive, even after you are gone." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60289-no-one-really-knows-why-they-are-alive-until-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 06:51:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60289-no-one-really-knows-why-they-are-alive-until-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one really knows why they are alive until they know what they'd die for." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13928-at-the-temple-there-is-a-poem-called-loss-carved</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 06:52:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Arthur Golden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13928-at-the-temple-there-is-a-poem-called-loss-carved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the temple there is a poem called &quot;Loss&quot; carved into the stone.  It has three words, but the poet has scratched them out.  You cannot read loss, only feel it." -- Arthur Golden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127972-if-reality-is-hard-and-flat-and-unjust-then-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 19:50:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Brent Weeks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127972-if-reality-is-hard-and-flat-and-unjust-then-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...if reality is hard and flat and unjust, then it's better to adjust to what really is than to complain that it isn't what you wish.  That was what made me lose faith.....  But having lost it, soon I doubted my lack of faith.  There were niggling hints of meaning everywhere." -- Brent Weeks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 05:40:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't interest me what you do for a living. I want to know what you ache for, and if you dare to dream of meeting your heart's longing.
It doesn't interest me how old you are. I want to know if you will risk looking like a fool for love, for your dream, for the adventure of being alive. 
It doesn't interest me what planets are squaring your moon. I want to know if you have touched the center of your own sorrow, if you have been opened by life's betrayals or have become shriveled and closed from fear of further pain!I want to know if you can sit with pain, mine or your own, without moving to hide it or fade it, or fix it. 
I want to know if you can be with joy, mine or your own, if you can dance with wildness and let the ecstasy fill you to the tips of your fingers and toes without cautioning us to be careful, to be realistic, to remember the limitations of being human. 
It doesn't interest me if the story you are telling me is true. I want to know if you can disappoint another to be true to yourself; if you can bear the accusation of betrayal and not betray your own soul; if you can be faithlessand therefore trustworthy. 
I want to know if you can see beauty even when it's not pretty, every day,and if you can source your own life from its presence. 
I want to know if you can live with failure, yours and mine, and still stand on the edge of the lake and shout to the silver of the full moon, “Yes!”
It doesn't interest me to know where you live or how much money you have. I want to know if you can get up, after the night of grief and despair, weary and bruised to the bone, and do what needs to be done to feed the children. 
It doesn't interest me who you know or how you came to be here. I want to know if you will stand in the center of the fire with me and not shrink back. 
It doesn't interest me where or what or with whom you have studied. I want to know what sustains you, from the inside, when all else falls away. 
I want to know if you can be alone with yourself and if you truly like the company you keep in the empty moments." -- Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204193-i-live-in-my-own-little-world-but-its-ok</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2011 06:56:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Lauren Myracle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204193-i-live-in-my-own-little-world-but-its-ok]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I live in my own little world. But its ok, they know me here." -- Lauren Myracle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9131-if-you-tell-the-truth-you-don-t-have-to-remember</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 16:48:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9131-if-you-tell-the-truth-you-don-t-have-to-remember]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you tell the truth, you don't have to remember anything." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 16:29:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loi add a quote by Kent M. Keith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Paradoxical Commandments

People are illogical, unreasonable, and self-centered.
Love them anyway.

If you do good, people will accuse you of selfish ulterior motives.
Do good anyway.

If you are successful, you will win false friends and true enemies.
Succeed anyway.

The good you do today will be forgotten tomorrow.
Do good anyway.

Honesty and frankness make you vulnerable.
Be honest and frank anyway.

The biggest men and women with the biggest ideas can be shot down by the smallest men and women with the smallest minds.
Think big anyway.

People favor underdogs but follow only top dogs.
Fight for a few underdogs anyway.

What you spend years building may be destroyed overnight.
Build anyway.

People really need help but may attack you if you do help them.
Help people anyway.

Give the world the best you have and you'll get kicked in the teeth.
Give the world the best you have anyway." -- Kent M. Keith]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
