<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/302418-julia]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/302418-julia" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 18:11:15 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13878-whatever-i-do-however-i-find-a-way-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 18:11:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13878-whatever-i-do-however-i-find-a-way-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever I do, however I find a way to live, I will tell these stories.  I have spoken to every person I have encountered these last difficult days...I speak to these people, and I speak to you because I cannot help it.  It gives me strength, almost unbelievable strength, to know that you are there.  I covet your eyes, your ears, the collapsible space between us.  How blessed are we to have each other?  I am alive and you are alive and so we must fill the air with our words.  I will fill today, tomorrow, every day until I am taken back to God.  I will tell stories to people who will listen and to people who don't want to listen, to people who seek me out and to those who run.  All the while I will know that you are there.  How can I pretend that you do not exist?  It would be almost as impossible as you pretending that I do not exist." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21330-love-is-life-all-everything-that-i-understand-i-understand</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 18:12:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21330-love-is-life-all-everything-that-i-understand-i-understand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is life. All, everything that I understand, I understand only because I love. Everything is, everything exists, only because I love. Everything is united by it alone. Love is God, and to die means that I, a particle of love, shall return to the general and eternal source." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84371-morality-like-art-means-drawing-a-line-someplace</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 17:21:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by oscar wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84371-morality-like-art-means-drawing-a-line-someplace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Morality, like art, means drawing a line someplace." -- oscar wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127558-it-is-the-curse-of-humanity-that-it-learns-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 17:22:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Rudolf Virchow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127558-it-is-the-curse-of-humanity-that-it-learns-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is the curse of humanity that it learns to tolerate even the most horrible situations by habituation." -- Rudolf Virchow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 17:23:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13421-how-wrong-is-it-for-a-woman-to-expect-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 17:24:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13421-how-wrong-is-it-for-a-woman-to-expect-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How wrong is it for a woman to expect the man to build the world she wants, rather than to create it herself?" -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26108-if-you-do-not-breathe-through-writing-if-you-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 17:24:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26108-if-you-do-not-breathe-through-writing-if-you-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you do not breathe through writing, if you do not cry out in writing, or sing in writing, then don't write, because our culture has no use for it." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2846-and-the-day-came-when-the-risk-to-remain-tight</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 17:24:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2846-and-the-day-came-when-the-risk-to-remain-tight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the day came when the risk to remain tight in a bud was more painful than the risk it took to blossom." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50516-every-reader-as-he-reads-is-actually-the-reader-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 17:30:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50516-every-reader-as-he-reads-is-actually-the-reader-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every reader, as he reads, is actually the reader of himself.  The writer's work is only a kind of optical instrument he provides the reader so he can discern what he might never have seen in himself without this book.  The reader's recognition in himself of what the book says is the proof of the book's truth." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29455-thanks-to-art-instead-of-seeing-one-world-only-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 17:30:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29455-thanks-to-art-instead-of-seeing-one-world-only-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thanks to art, instead of seeing one world only, our own, we see that world multiply itself and we have at our disposal as many worlds as there are original artists, worlds more different one from the other than those which revolve in infinite space, worlds which, centuries after the extinction of the fire from which their light first emanated, whether it is called Rembrandt or Vermeer, send us still each one its special radiance." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18907-we-don-t-receive-wisdom-we-must-discover-it-for-ourselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 17:30:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18907-we-don-t-receive-wisdom-we-must-discover-it-for-ourselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't receive wisdom; we must discover it for ourselves after a journey that no one can take for us or spare us." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300662-it-is-not-easy-to-convey-unless-one-has-experienced</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 06:40:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Francis Crick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300662-it-is-not-easy-to-convey-unless-one-has-experienced]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not easy to convey, unless one has experienced it, the dramatic feeling of sudden enlightenment that floods the mind when the right idea finally clicks into place. One immediately sees how many previously puzzling facts are neatly explained by the new hypothesis. One could kick oneself for not having the idea earlier, it now seems so obvious. Yet before, everything was in a fog." -- Francis Crick]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
