<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/302462-arcyllin-arcilla]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/302462-arcyllin-arcilla" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 07:20:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110525-a-woman-s-question-do-you-know-you-have-asked-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 07:20:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arcyllin add a quote by Joshua Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110525-a-woman-s-question-do-you-know-you-have-asked-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A Woman's Question

Do you know you have asked for the costliest thing
Ever made by the Hand above?
A woman's heart, and a woman's life---
And a woman's wonderful love.

Do you know you have asked for this priceless thing
As a child might ask for a toy?
Demanding what others have died to win,
With a reckless dash of boy.

You have written my lesson of duty out,
Manlike, you have questioned me.
Now stand at the bars of my woman's soul
Until I shall question thee.

You require your mutton shall always be hot,
Your socks and your shirt be whole;
I require your heart be true as God's stars
And as pure as His heaven your soul.

You require a cook for your mutton and beef,
I require a far greater thing;
A seamstress you're wanting for socks and shirts---
I look for a man and a king.

A king for the beautiful realm called Home,
And a man that his Maker, God,
Shall look upon as He did on the first
And say: &quot;It is very good.&quot;

I am fair and young, but the rose may fade
From this soft young cheek one day;
Will you love me then 'mid the falling leaves,
As you did 'mong the blossoms of May?

Is your heart an ocean so strong and true,
I may launch my all on its tide?
A loving woman finds heaven or hell
On the day she is made a bride.

I require all things that are grand and true,
All things that a man should be;
If you give this all, I would stake my life
To be all you demand of me.

If you cannot be this, a laundress and cook
You can hire and little to pay;
But a woman's heart and a woman's life
Are not to be won that way." -- Joshua Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114912-less-is-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2008 02:31:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arcyllin add a quote by William Zinsser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114912-less-is-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Less is more." -- William Zinsser]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
