<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/302596-shamim-a]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/302596-shamim-a" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 18:26:37 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511366-the-problem-often-not-discovered-until-late-in-life-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 18:26:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shamim add a quote by Neil deGrasse Tyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511366-the-problem-often-not-discovered-until-late-in-life-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem, often not discovered until late in life, is that when you look for things in life like love, meaning, motivation, it implies they are sitting behind a tree or under a rock. The most successful people in life recognize, that in life they create their own love, they manufacture their own meaning, they generate their own motivation. For me, I am driven by two main philosophies, know more today about the world than I knew yesterday. And lessen the suffering of others. You'd be surprised how far that gets you. 

- Neil deGrasse Tyson's response on Reddit when asked &quot;What can you tell a young man looking for motivation in life itself?&quot;

http://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/qccer/i_am_neil_degrasse_tyson_ask_me_anything/" -- Neil deGrasse Tyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32978-recognize-that-the-very-molecules-that-make-up-your-body</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 18:26:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shamim add a quote by Neil deGrasse Tyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32978-recognize-that-the-very-molecules-that-make-up-your-body]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Recognize that the very molecules that make up your body, the atoms that construct the molecules, are traceable to the crucibles that were once the centers of high mass stars that exploded their chemically rich guts into the galaxy, enriching pristine gas clouds with the chemistry of life.  So that we are all connected to each other biologically, to the earth chemically and to the rest of the universe atomically.  That’s kinda cool!  That makes me smile and I actually feel quite large at the end of that.  It’s not that we are better than the universe, we are part of the universe.  We are in the universe and the universe is in us." -- Neil deGrasse Tyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
