<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/304869-andrea]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/304869-andrea" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 09:10:43 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 09:10:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 09:08:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Insanity is doing the same thing, over and over again, but expecting different results." -- Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 09:10:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Groucho Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Outside of a dog, a book is man's best friend. Inside of a dog it's too dark to read." -- Groucho Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1398-i-love-deadlines-i-love-the-whooshing-noise-they-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 09:11:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1398-i-love-deadlines-i-love-the-whooshing-noise-they-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love deadlines. I love the whooshing noise they make as they go by." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3312-women-and-cats-will-do-as-they-please-and-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 09:13:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3312-women-and-cats-will-do-as-they-please-and-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Women and cats will do as they please, and men and dogs should relax and get used to the idea." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240-reality-is-merely-an-illusion-albeit-a-very-persistent-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 09:20:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240-reality-is-merely-an-illusion-albeit-a-very-persistent-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reality is merely an illusion, albeit a very persistent one." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2400-some-humans-would-do-anything-to-see-if-it-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 09:22:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2400-some-humans-would-do-anything-to-see-if-it-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some humans would do anything to see if it was possible to do it. If you put a large switch in some cave somewhere, with a sign on it saying 'End-of-the-World Switch. PLEASE DO NOT TOUCH', the paint wouldn't even have time to dry." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9028-when-you-are-courting-a-nice-girl-an-hour-seems</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 09:23:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9028-when-you-are-courting-a-nice-girl-an-hour-seems]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you are courting a nice girl an hour seems like a second. When you sit on a red-hot cinder a second seems like an hour. That's relativity." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/747-if-we-knew-what-it-was-we-were-doing-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 09:27:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/747-if-we-knew-what-it-was-we-were-doing-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we knew what it was we were doing, it would not be called research, would it?" -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1896-when-i-have-a-little-money-i-buy-books-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 09:26:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Desiderius Erasmus Roterodamus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1896-when-i-have-a-little-money-i-buy-books-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I have a little money, I buy books; and if I have any left, I buy food and clothes." -- Desiderius Erasmus Roterodamus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4959-you-don-t-have-to-burn-books-to-destroy-a-culture</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 09:26:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4959-you-don-t-have-to-burn-books-to-destroy-a-culture]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't have to burn books to destroy a culture. Just get people to stop reading them." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1502-facts-do-not-cease-to-exist-because-they-are-ignored</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 09:27:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1502-facts-do-not-cease-to-exist-because-they-are-ignored]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Facts do not cease to exist because they are ignored." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5789-but-who-prays-for-satan-who-in-eighteen-centuries-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 09:28:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by mark twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5789-but-who-prays-for-satan-who-in-eighteen-centuries-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But who prays for Satan? Who, in eighteen centuries, has had the common humanity to pray for the one sinner that needed it most?" -- mark twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6130-a-woman-should-have-enough-money-within-her-control</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 09:30:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Pamela Redmond Satran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6130-a-woman-should-have-enough-money-within-her-control]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  enough money within her control to move out
  and rent a place of her own even if she never wants
  to or needs to...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  something perfect to wear if the employer or date of her
  dreams wants to see her in an hour...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ...
  a youth she's content to leave behind....
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a past juicy enough that she's looking forward to
  retelling it in her old age....
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE .....
  a set of screwdrivers, a cordless drill, and a black
  lace bra...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  one friend who always makes her laugh... and one who
  lets her cry...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a good piece of furniture not previously owned by anyone
  else in her family...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  eight matching plates, wine glasses with stems, and a
  recipe for a meal that will make her guests feel honored...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a feeling of control over her destiny...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  how to fall in love without losing herself..
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  HOW TO QUIT A JOB,
  BREAK UP WITH A LOVER,
  AND CONFRONT A FRIEND WITHOUT RUINING THE FRIENDSHIP...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  when to try harder... and WHEN TO WALK AWAY...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  that she can't change the length of her calves,
  the width of her hips, or the nature of her parents..
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  that her childhood may not have been perfect...but it's over...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  what she would and wouldn't do for love or more...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  how to live alone... even if she doesn't like it...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  whom she can trust,
  whom she can't,
  and why she shouldn't
  take it personally...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  where to go...
  be it to her best friend's kitchen table...
  or a charming inn in the woods...
  when her soul needs soothing...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  what she can and can't accomplish in a day...
  a month...and a year..." -- Pamela Redmond Satran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5115-loyalty-to-country-always-loyalty-to-government-when-it-deserves</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 10:54:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5115-loyalty-to-country-always-loyalty-to-government-when-it-deserves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Loyalty to country ALWAYS. Loyalty to government, when it deserves it." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16261-life-is-a-disease-sexually-transmitted-and-invariably-fatal</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 11:03:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16261-life-is-a-disease-sexually-transmitted-and-invariably-fatal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is a disease: sexually transmitted, and invariably fatal." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12841-everyone-thinks-of-changing-the-world-but-no-one-thinks</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 11:01:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12841-everyone-thinks-of-changing-the-world-but-no-one-thinks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone thinks of changing the world, but no one thinks of changing himself." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 11:08:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4061-the-most-exciting-phrase-to-hear-in-science-the-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 12:24:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Isaac Asimov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4061-the-most-exciting-phrase-to-hear-in-science-the-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most exciting phrase to hear in science, the one that heralds the most discoveries, is not &quot;Eureka!&quot; (I found it!) but 'That's funny..." -- Isaac Asimov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4104-even-if-there-is-only-one-possible-unified-theory-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 12:21:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Stephen Hawking]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4104-even-if-there-is-only-one-possible-unified-theory-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even if there is only one possible unified theory, it is just a set of rules and equations. What is it that breathes fire into the equations and makes a universe for them to describe? The usual approach of science of constructing a mathematical model cannot answer the questions of why there should be a universe for the model to describe. Why does the universe go to all the bother of existing?" -- Stephen Hawking]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363-it-is-better-to-remain-silent-at-the-risk-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 17:53:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea add a quote by Maurice Switzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363-it-is-better-to-remain-silent-at-the-risk-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to remain silent at the risk of being thought a fool, than to talk and remove all doubt of it." -- Maurice Switzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
