<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/30583-louann]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/30583-louann" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 15:31:56 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102694-what-shall-we-do-all-of-us-all-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 15:31:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Francesca Lia Block]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102694-what-shall-we-do-all-of-us-all-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What shall we do, all of us? All of us oassionate girls who fear crushing the boys we love with our mouths like caverns of teeth, our mushrooming brains, our watermelon hearts?" -- Francesca Lia Block]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2009 07:22:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99661-the-truly-faithless-one-is-the-one-who-makes-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 15:48:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99661-the-truly-faithless-one-is-the-one-who-makes-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truly faithless one is the one who makes love to only a fraction of you. And denies the rest." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194844-one-can-be-in-love-with-several-people-at-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 15:49:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194844-one-can-be-in-love-with-several-people-at-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One can be in love with several people at the same time, feel the sorrow with each, and not betray any of them." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 15:52:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 15:53:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't see things as they are, we see them as we are." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1231-be-kind-for-everyone-you-meet-is-fighting-a-harder</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 15:55:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Plato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1231-be-kind-for-everyone-you-meet-is-fighting-a-harder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be kind, for everyone you meet is fighting a harder battle." -- Plato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362747-she-trailed-after-him-admiring-the-line-of-his-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 15:57:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Meljean Brook]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362747-she-trailed-after-him-admiring-the-line-of-his-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She trailed after him, admiring the line of his back. He began climbing the stairs, and she sighed with pleasure. Every bit of him was gorgeous. “Do you mind if I objectify you?”
“Please do,” he said over his shoulder. “Particularly my knees, as they are oft-neglected.”
“Maybe if you ever got your pants off, they wouldn’t be.”
“It hardly matters, sweet; once they’ve come off, the attention isn’t likely to center on my absurdly handsome knees." -- Meljean Brook]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184695-i-like-my-body-when-it-is-with-your-body</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 16:06:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by e.e. cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184695-i-like-my-body-when-it-is-with-your-body]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["i like my body when it is with your
body. It is so quite new a thing.
Muscles better and nerves more.
i like your body. i like what it does,
i like its hows. i like to feel the spine
of your body and its bones, and the trembling
-firm-smooth ness and which i will
again and again and again
kiss, i like kissing this and that of you,
i like, slowly stroking the, shocking fuzz
of your electric fur, and what-is-it comes
over parting flesh ... And eyes big love-crumbs,

and possibly i like the thrill

of under me you so quite new." -- e.e. cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34437-i-had-not-intended-to-love-him-the-reader-knows</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 18:00:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34437-i-had-not-intended-to-love-him-the-reader-knows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had not intended to love him; the reader knows I had wrought hard to extirpate from my soul the germs of love there detected; and now, at the first renewed view of him, they spontaneously revived, great and strong! He made me love him without looking at me." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263493-i-am-no-bird-and-no-net-ensnares-me-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 18:00:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263493-i-am-no-bird-and-no-net-ensnares-me-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am no bird; and no net ensnares me: I am a free human being with an independent will." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37196-so-many-people-walk-around-with-a-meaningless-life-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 15:42:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37196-so-many-people-walk-around-with-a-meaningless-life-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many people walk around with a meaningless life. They seem half-asleep, even when they're busy doing things they think are important. This is because they're chasing the wrong things. The way you get meaning into your life is to devote yourself to loving others, devote yourself to your community around you, and devote yourself to creating something that gives you purpose and meaning." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32222-you-see-you-closed-your-eyes-that-was-the-difference</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 15:42:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32222-you-see-you-closed-your-eyes-that-was-the-difference]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You see, you closed your eyes. That was the difference. Sometimes you cannot believe what you see, you have to believe what you feel. And if you are ever going to have other people trust you, you must feel that you can trust them, too--even when you’re in the dark. Even when you’re falling." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238134-maybe-you-can-afford-to-wait-maybe-for-you-there-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 15:44:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Lauren Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238134-maybe-you-can-afford-to-wait-maybe-for-you-there-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe you can afford to wait. Maybe for you there's a tomorrow. Maybe for you there's one thousand tomorrows, or three thousand, or ten, so much time you can bathe in it, roll around it, let it slide like coins through you fingers. So much time you can waste it.
But for some of us there's only today. And the truth is, you never really know." -- Lauren Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277505-so-many-things-become-beautiful-when-you-really-look</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 15:44:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Lauren Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277505-so-many-things-become-beautiful-when-you-really-look]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many things become beautiful when you really look." -- Lauren Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140236-what-did-my-fingers-do-before-they-held-him-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 07:33:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140236-what-did-my-fingers-do-before-they-held-him-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What did my fingers do before they held him?
What did my heart do, with its love?

From &quot; Three Women: A Poem for Three Voices&quot;, 1962" -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72849-because-sometimes-that-is-the-only-way-to-remember-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 07:36:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Amy Tan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72849-because-sometimes-that-is-the-only-way-to-remember-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because sometimes that is the only way to remember what is in your bones.  You must peel off your skin, and that of your mother, and her mother.  Until there is nothing.  No scar, no skin, no flesh.
-An-mei" -- Amy Tan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 10:25:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70562-just-for-the-record-the-weather-today-is-calm-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 10:27:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70562-just-for-the-record-the-weather-today-is-calm-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just for the record, the weather today is calm and sunny, but the air is full of bullshit." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 13:56:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 13:56:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May your coming year be filled with magic and dreams and good madness. I hope you read some fine books and kiss someone who thinks you're wonderful, and don't forget to make some art -- write or draw or build or sing or live as only you can. And I hope, somewhere in the next year, you surprise yourself." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230886-you-may-not-be-her-first-her-last-or-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 13:56:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230886-you-may-not-be-her-first-her-last-or-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may not be her first, her last, or her only. She loved before she may love again. But if she loves you now, what else matters? She's not perfect—you aren't either, and the two of you may never be perfect together but if she can make you laugh, cause you to think twice, and admit to being human and making mistakes, hold onto her and give her the most you can. She may not be thinking about you every second of the day, but she will give you a part of her that she knows you can break—her heart. So don't hurt her, don't change her, don't analyze and don't expect more than she can give. Smile when she makes you happy, let her know when she makes you mad, and miss her when she's not there." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6303-i-am-not-sure-exactly-what-heaven-will-be-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2011 12:41:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6303-i-am-not-sure-exactly-what-heaven-will-be-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am not sure exactly what heaven will be like, but I know that when we die and it comes time for God to judge us, he will not ask, 'How many good things have you done in your life?' rather he will ask, 'How much love did you put into what you did?" -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15202-a-woman-s-heart-should-be-so-hidden-in-god-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2011 12:42:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Max Lucado]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15202-a-woman-s-heart-should-be-so-hidden-in-god-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A woman's heart should be so hidden in God that a man has to seek Him just to find her." -- Max Lucado]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68943-may-today-there-be-peace-within-may-you-trust-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2011 15:28:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Saint Terese of Liseaux]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68943-may-today-there-be-peace-within-may-you-trust-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May today there be peace within. May you trust that you are exactly where you are meant to be. May you not forget the infinite possibilities that are born of faith in yourself and others. May you use the gifts that you have received, and pass on the love that has been given to you. May you be content with yourself just the way you are. Let this knowledge settle into your bones, and allow your soul the freedom to sing, dance, praise and love. It is there for each and every one of us.&quot; ..." -- Saint Terese of Liseaux]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113579-i-close-my-eyes-thinking-that-there-is-nothing-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 06:00:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113579-i-close-my-eyes-thinking-that-there-is-nothing-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I close my eyes, thinking that there is nothing like an embrace after an absence, nothing like fitting my face into the curve of his shoulder and filling my lungs with the scent of him." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149624-what-can-the-love-in-my-soul-be-compared-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 18:14:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Sorin Cerin ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149624-what-can-the-love-in-my-soul-be-compared-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What can the love in my soul be compared to another wonderful soul which is so far and yet so close of my self? What can this symbiosis between two souls can be? What can love be when you feel you cannot sleep at night, that every drop of dew becomes a crystal in your heart, when every breeze of wind has magical meanings? What can love be when you feel that you want nothing more in this world that to be with the soul you love? But what can love be in other transcendental realities? What about our souls? Are our souls a waterfall, a true Niagara or a smile, a flirt of an angel? Are our souls a mere mood of a fairy or a lightening in a summer rain? Our souls could be all of this and much more. But what really happens in that transcendental reality when we feel we are truly in love, that we love so much that it hurts? That the air in the room is unbreathable, that the sentimental, spiritual or physical distances kill us? What happens when dawn find us sadder than ever, looking for an excuse or an argument for the person we love so much, our Great Love? What are all thses? What are the looks lost in the desert horizons of unfulfilment or those in the eyes that deeply loose each other in the others inside the souls?" -- Sorin Cerin ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72943-every-act-i-live-while-i-am-fully-awake-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 02:54:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72943-every-act-i-live-while-i-am-fully-awake-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every act I live while I am fully awake can not help but be both prayer and lovemaking." -- Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386067-do-not-touch-me-and-keep-your-soul-out-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 02:54:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386067-do-not-touch-me-and-keep-your-soul-out-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not touch me and keep your soul out of your fingerstips...Die into me or don't come to me at all" -- Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405314-and-i-found-that-i-can-do-it-if-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 02:54:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louann add a quote by Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405314-and-i-found-that-i-can-do-it-if-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I found that I can do it if I choose to - I can stay awake and let the sorrows of the world tear me apart and then allow the joys to put me back together different from before but whole once again." -- Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
