<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/305959-alexis]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/305959-alexis" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 21:28:14 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266376-today-i-want-to-puke-when-i-hear-the-word</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 21:28:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexis add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266376-today-i-want-to-puke-when-i-hear-the-word]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today I want to puke when I hear the word 'radical' applied so slothfully and stupidly to Islamist murderers; the most plainly reactionary people in the world." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/490976-the-conventional-word-that-is-employed-to-describe-tyranny-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 21:29:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexis add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/490976-the-conventional-word-that-is-employed-to-describe-tyranny-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The conventional word that is employed to describe tyranny is “systematic.” The true essence of a dictatorship is in fact not its regularity but its unpredictability and caprice; those who live under it must never be able to relax, must never be quite sure if they have followed the rules correctly or not. (The only rule of thumb was: whatever is not compulsory is forbidden.) Thus, the ruled can always be found to be in the wrong." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/608047-another-bottle-was-brought-out-and-poured-into-the-reservoir</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 18:59:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexis add a quote by Tom McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/608047-another-bottle-was-brought-out-and-poured-into-the-reservoir]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Another bottle was brought out and poured into the reservoir.  Once more I climbed inside the car and pressed the spurter button.  Once more nothing happened--and once more, when we looked inside the reservoir, we found it empty.
    &quot;Two litres!&quot; I said. &quot;Where has it all gone?&quot;
    They'd vaporized, evaporated.  And do you know what? It felt wonderful. Don't ask me why: it just did. It was as though I'd just witnessed a miracle: matter--these two litres of liquid--becoming un-matter--not surplus matter, mess or clutter, but pure, bodiless blueness. Transubstantiated. I looked up at the sky: it was blue and endless. I looked back at the boy. His overalls and face were covered in smears. He'd taken on these smears so that the miracle could happen, like a Christian martyr being flagellated, crucified, scrawled over with stigmata. I felt elated--elated and inspired.
    &quot;If only...&quot; I started, but paused.
    &quot;What?&quot; he asked.
    &quot;If only everything could...&quot;
    I trailed off. I knew what I meant. I stood there looking at his grubby face and told him:
    &quot;Thank you.&quot;
    Then I got into the car and turned the ignition key in its slot. The engine caught--and as it did, a torrent of blue liquid burst out of the dashboard and cascaded down. It gushed from the radio, the heating panel, the hazard-lights switch and the speedometer and mileage counter. It gushed all over me: my shirt, my legs, my groin." -- Tom McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/608051-to-be-real--to-become-fluent-natural-to-cut-out-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 19:12:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexis add a quote by Tom McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/608051-to-be-real--to-become-fluent-natural-to-cut-out-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[...]to be real--to become fluent, natural, to cut out the detour that sweeps us around what's fundamental to events, preventing us from touching their core: the detour that makes us all second-hand and second-rate." -- Tom McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/608052-he-was-still-undecided-it-depended-on-how-you-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 19:16:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexis add a quote by Pearl Abraham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/608052-he-was-still-undecided-it-depended-on-how-you-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was still undecided.  It depended on how you thought of God.  If God is nature, then God doesn't care, since nature doesn't care.  But if, as the mystics understood, God is the best of man and within man, then God cares, since man does." -- Pearl Abraham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/608053-and-again-the-news-offered-no-news-on-cnn-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 19:17:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexis add a quote by Pearl Abraham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/608053-and-again-the-news-offered-no-news-on-cnn-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And again the news offered no news: On CNN, a rerun of Larry King interviewing the widowed and the suffering. On CNN2, a rerun of Larry King interviewing a fatherless son. On CNN3, a rerun of Flight 11 flying toward the first tower, in slow motion. On CNN4, a rerun of the tower collapsing, in slow motion, and again the towers fell, again people jumped and died. On CNN5, a rerun of Larry King interviewing a motherless daughter, a daughterless father, interviewing the motherless, fatherless, wifeless, husbandless, childless, shameless--disgusted, Bill pressed POWER and beheaded King, exiled CNN, and the world went dark. They sat relieved in the silence and dark. Not much road traffic now, but somewhere in the distant overhead the honk and flap of southbound geese, instinct bound, in vees for victory. The turkey was still on the table; the sides were still out. Let all who are hungry come and eat. Let all who are tired come home." -- Pearl Abraham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/678584-when-he-picked-out-the-gravesite-plot-my-father-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 13:53:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexis add a quote by Marco Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/678584-when-he-picked-out-the-gravesite-plot-my-father-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When he picked out the [gravesite] plot, my father had joked that he was moving, at last, to the suburbs." -- Marco Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78983-you-know-what-charm-is-a-way-of-getting-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 17:44:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexis add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78983-you-know-what-charm-is-a-way-of-getting-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know what charm is: a way of getting the answer yes without having asked any clear question." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1123681-if-pimps-and-thieves-were-invariably-sentenced-all-decent-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 17:50:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexis add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1123681-if-pimps-and-thieves-were-invariably-sentenced-all-decent-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If pimps and thieves were invariably sentenced, all decent people would get to thinking they themselves were constantly innocent." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/563878-he-feared-in-his-secret-heart-that-one-day-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 19:35:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexis add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/563878-he-feared-in-his-secret-heart-that-one-day-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He feared, in his secret heart, that one day in company the baby would sit up and speak; that it would engage his eyes, appraise him, and say, 'You prick." -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/563888-92-93-94-liberty-equality-fraternity-or-death</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 19:35:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexis add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/563888-92-93-94-liberty-equality-fraternity-or-death]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["92, '93, '94. Liberty, Equality, Fraternity or Death." -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/781391-the-reader-may-ask-how-to-tell-fact-from-fiction</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 19:35:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexis add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/781391-the-reader-may-ask-how-to-tell-fact-from-fiction]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The reader may ask how to tell fact from fiction. A rough guide: anything that seems particularly unlikely is probably true." -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
