<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/306482-zoan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/306482-zoan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 18:34:19 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1977-it-s-like-tolstoy-said-happiness-is-an-allegory-unhappiness-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 18:34:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1977-it-s-like-tolstoy-said-happiness-is-an-allegory-unhappiness-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's like Tolstoy said. Happiness is an allegory, unhappiness a &lt;i&gt;story&lt;/i&gt;." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8527-time-weighs-down-on-you-like-an-old-ambiguous-dream</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 18:52:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8527-time-weighs-down-on-you-like-an-old-ambiguous-dream]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time weighs down on you like an old, ambiguous dream. You keep on moving, trying to sleep through it. But even if you go to the ends of the earth, you won't be able to escape it. Still, you have to go there- to the edge of the world. There's something you can't do unless you get there." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24774-that-s-why-i-like-listening-to-schubert-while-i-m-driving</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 18:52:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24774-that-s-why-i-like-listening-to-schubert-while-i-m-driving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's why I like listening to Schubert while I'm driving. Like I said, it's because all his performances are imperfect. A dense, artistic kind of imperfection stimulates your consciousness, keeps you alert. If I listen to some utterly perfect performance of an utterly perfect piece while I'm driving, I might want to close my eyes and die right then and there. But listening to the D major, I can feel the limits of what humans are capable of - that a certain type of perfection can only be realized through a limitless accumulation of the imperfect. And personally I find that encouraging." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 18:53:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes fate is like a small sandstorm that keeps changing directions. You change direction but the sandstorm chases you. You turn again, but the storm adjusts. Over and over you play this out, like some ominous dance with death just before dawn. Why? Because this storm isn't something that blew in from far away, something that has nothing to do with you. This storm is you. Something &lt;i&gt;inside&lt;/i&gt; of you. So all you can do is give in to it, step right inside the storm, closing your eyes and plugging up your ears so the sand doesn't get in, and walk through it, step by step. There's no sun there, no moon, no direction, no sense of time. Just fine white sand swirling up into the sky like pulverized bones. That's the kind of sandstorm you need to imagine.

An you really will have to make it through that violent, metaphysical, symbolic storm. No matter how metaphysical or symbolic it might be, make no mistake about it: it will cut through flesh like a thousand razor blades. People will bleed there, and &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; will bleed too. Hot, red blood. You'll catch that blood in your hands, your own blood and the blood of others.

And once the storm is over you won't remember how you made it through, how you managed to survive. You won't even be sure, in fact, whether the storm is really over. But one thing is certain. When you come out of the storm you won't be the same person who walked in. That's what this storm's all about." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48208-the-pure-present-is-an-ungraspable-advance-of-the-past</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 19:47:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48208-the-pure-present-is-an-ungraspable-advance-of-the-past]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The pure present is an ungraspable advance of the past devouring the future. In truth, all sensation is already memory." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48219-oshima-s-silent-for-a-time-as-he-gazes-at-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 20:01:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48219-oshima-s-silent-for-a-time-as-he-gazes-at-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oshima's silent for a time as he gazes at the forest, eyes narrowed. Birds are flitting from one branch to the next. His hands are clasped behind his head. &quot;I know how you feel,&quot; he finally says. &quot;But this is something you have to work out on your own. Nobody can help you. That's what love's all about, Kafka. You're the one having those wonderful feelings, but you have to go it alone as you wander through the dark. Your mind and body have to bear it all. All by yourself." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54897-the-sense-of-tragedy---according-to-aristotle---comes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 20:20:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54897-the-sense-of-tragedy---according-to-aristotle---comes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sense of tragedy - according to Aristotle - comes, ironically enough, not from the protagonist's weak points but from his good qualities. Do you know what I'm getting at? People are drawn deeper into tragedy not by their defects but by their virtues.
...
[But] we accept irony through a device called metaphor. And through that we grow and become deeper human beings." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 20:46:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32583-wisest-is-she-who-knows-she-does-not-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 20:51:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Jostein Gaarder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32583-wisest-is-she-who-knows-she-does-not-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wisest is she who knows she does not know." -- Jostein Gaarder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10521-if-pain-must-come-may-it-come-quickly-because-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 20:53:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10521-if-pain-must-come-may-it-come-quickly-because-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If pain must come, may it come quickly. Because I have a life to live, and I need to live it in the best way possible. If he has to make a choice, may he make it now. Then I will either wait for him or forget him." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49618-passion-is-passion-it-s-the-excitement-between-the-tedious-spaces</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 20:57:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49618-passion-is-passion-it-s-the-excitement-between-the-tedious-spaces]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Passion is passion. It's the excitement between the tedious spaces, and it doesn't matter where it's directed...It can be coins or sports or politics or horses or music or faith...the saddest people I've ever met in life are the ones who don't care deeply about anything at all." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45371-and-i-learned-what-is-obvious-to-a-child-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 20:57:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45371-and-i-learned-what-is-obvious-to-a-child-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I learned what is obvious to a child. That life is simply a collection of little lives, each lived one day at a time. That each day should be spent finding beauty in flowers and poetry and talking to animals. That a day spent with dreaming and sunsets and refreshing breezes cannot be bettered. But most of all, I learned that life is about sitting on benches next to ancient creeks with my hand on her knee and sometimes, on good days, for falling in love." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/463332-travel-is-never-a-matter-of-money-but-of-courage</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 18:29:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/463332-travel-is-never-a-matter-of-money-but-of-courage]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Travel is never a matter of money but of courage" -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93331-i-finally-understood-what-true-love-meant-love-meant-that-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 18:29:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93331-i-finally-understood-what-true-love-meant-love-meant-that-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I finally understood what true love meant...love meant that you care for another person's happiness more than your own, no matter how painful the choices you face might be." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488560-don-t-be-intimidated-by-other-people-s-opinions-only-mediocrity-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 20:03:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488560-don-t-be-intimidated-by-other-people-s-opinions-only-mediocrity-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don’t be intimidated by other people’s opinions.  Only mediocrity is sure of itself, so take risks and do what you really want to do." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511381-if-i-had-to-give-you-one-piece-of-advice</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 20:04:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511381-if-i-had-to-give-you-one-piece-of-advice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I had to give you one piece of advice it would be this: Don’t be intimidated by other people’s opinions. Only mediocrity is sure of itself, so take risks and do what you really want to do. Seek out people who aren’t afraid of making mistakes and who, therefore, do make mistakes. Because of that, their work often isn’t recognized, but they are precisely the kind of people who change the world and, after many mistakes, do something that will transform their own community completely." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/534783-mathematicians-call-them-twin-primes-pairs-of-prime-numbers-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 23:06:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Paolo Giordano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/534783-mathematicians-call-them-twin-primes-pairs-of-prime-numbers-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mathematicians call them twin primes: pairs of prime numbers that are close to each other, almost neighbors, but between them there is always an even number that prevents them from truly touching. Numbers like 11 and 13, like 17 and 19, 41 and 43. If you have the patience to go on counting, you discover that these pairs gradually become rarer. You encounter increasingly isolated primes, lost in that silent, measured space made only of ciphers, and you develop a distressing presentiment that the pairs encountered up until that point were accidental, that solitude is the true destiny. Then, just when you’re about to surrender, when you no longer have the desire to go on counting, you come across another pair of twins, clutching each other tightly. There is a common conviction among mathematicians that however far you go, there will always be another two, even if no one can say where exactly, until they are discovered.

Mattia thought that he and Alice were like that, twin primes, alone and lost, close but not close enough to really touch each other. He had never told her that. When he imagined confessing these things to her, the thin layer of sweat on his hands evaporated completely and for a good ten minutes he was no longer capable of touching anything." -- Paolo Giordano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410130-they-lived-the-slow-and-invisible-interpenetration-of-their-universes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 23:06:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Paolo Giordano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410130-they-lived-the-slow-and-invisible-interpenetration-of-their-universes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They lived the slow and invisible interpenetration of their universes, like two stars gravitating around a common axis, in ever tighter orbits, whose clear destiny is to coalesce at some point in space and time." -- Paolo Giordano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268489-people-took-what-they-wanted-they-clutched-at-coincidences-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 23:06:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Paolo Giordano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268489-people-took-what-they-wanted-they-clutched-at-coincidences-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People took what they wanted, they clutched at coincidences, the few there were, and made a life from them. . . . Choices are made in brief seconds and paid for in the time that remains." -- Paolo Giordano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/438145-choices-are-made-in-brief-seconds-and-paid-for-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 23:07:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Paolo Giordano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/438145-choices-are-made-in-brief-seconds-and-paid-for-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Choices are made in brief seconds and paid for in the time that remains." -- Paolo Giordano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34071-imagining-the-future-is-a-kind-of-nostalgia-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 04:10:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34071-imagining-the-future-is-a-kind-of-nostalgia-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagining the future is a kind of nostalgia. (...) You spend your whole life stuck in the labyrinth, thinking about how you'll escape it one day, and how awesome it will be, and imagining that future keeps you going, but you never do it. You just use the future to escape the present." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128065-i-go-to-seek-a-great-perhaps</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 04:57:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by François Rabelais]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128065-i-go-to-seek-a-great-perhaps]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I go to seek a Great Perhaps." -- François Rabelais]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420678-in-room-me-and-ma-had-time-for-everything-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 18:33:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Emma Donoghue]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420678-in-room-me-and-ma-had-time-for-everything-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In Room me and Ma had time for everything. I guess the time gets spread very thin like butter all over the world, the roads and houses and playgrounds and stores, so there's only a little smear of time on each place, then everyone has to hurry on to the next bit...." -- Emma Donoghue]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/448831-you-know-who-you-belong-to-jack---yeah-yourself</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 18:34:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Emma Donoghue]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/448831-you-know-who-you-belong-to-jack---yeah-yourself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know who you belong to Jack? - Yeah. Yourself. - He's wrong, actually, I belong to Ma. p. 261 Room by E Donoghue" -- Emma Donoghue]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541944-solving-a-problem-for-which-you-know-there-s-an-answer</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 17:14:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Yoko Ogawa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541944-solving-a-problem-for-which-you-know-there-s-an-answer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Solving a problem for which you know there’s an answer is like climbing a mountain with a guide, along a trail someone else has laid. In mathematics, the truth is somewhere out there in a place no one knows, beyond all the beaten paths. And it’s not always at the top of the mountain. It might be in a crack on the smoothest cliff or somewhere deep in the valley." -- Yoko Ogawa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1858-for-most-of-history-anonymous-was-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 02:26:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1858-for-most-of-history-anonymous-was-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For most of history, Anonymous was a woman." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2012 03:32:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We accept the love we think we deserve." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8716-and-in-that-moment-i-swear-we-were-infinite</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2012 03:32:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8716-and-in-that-moment-i-swear-we-were-infinite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And in that moment, I swear we were infinite." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110554-it-s-just-that-i-don-t-want-to-be-somebody-s-crush</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2012 03:33:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110554-it-s-just-that-i-don-t-want-to-be-somebody-s-crush]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's just that I don't want to be somebody's crush. If somebody likes me, I want them to like the real me, not what they think I am. And I don't want them to carry it around inside. I want them to show me, so I can feel it too." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111870-once-on-a-yellow-piece-of-paper-with-green-lines</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2012 03:34:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoan add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111870-once-on-a-yellow-piece-of-paper-with-green-lines]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once on a yellow piece of paper with green lines
	he wrote a poem
And he called it &quot;Chops&quot;
	because that was the name of his dog

And that's what it was all about
And his teacher gave him an A
	and a gold star
And his mother hung it on the kitchen door
	and read it to his aunts
That was the year Father Tracy
	took all the kids to the zoo

And he let them sing on the bus
And his little sister was born
	with tiny toenails and no hair
And his mother and father kissed a lot
And the girl around the corner sent him a
Valentine signed with a row of X's

	and he had to ask his father what the X's meant
And his father always tucked him in bed at night
And was always there to do it

Once on a piece of white paper with blue lines
	he wrote a poem
And he called it &quot;Autumn&quot;

	because that was the name of the season
And that's what it was all about
And his teacher gave him an A
	and asked him to write more clearly
And his mother never hung it on the kitchen door
	because of its new paint

And the kids told him
	that Father Tracy smoked cigars
And left butts on the pews
And sometimes they would burn holes
That was the year his sister got glasses
	with thick lenses and black frames
And the girl around the corner laughed

	when he asked her to go see Santa Claus
And the kids told him why
	his mother and father kissed a lot
And his father never tucked him in bed at night
And his father got mad
	when he cried for him to do it.


Once on a paper torn from his notebook
	he wrote a poem
And he called it &quot;Innocence: A Question&quot;
	because that was the question about his girl
And that's what it was all about
And his professor gave him an A

	and a strange steady look
And his mother never hung it on the kitchen door
	because he never showed her
That was the year that Father Tracy died
And he forgot how the end
	of the Apostle's Creed went

And he caught his sister
	making out on the back porch
And his mother and father never kissed
	or even talked
And the girl around the corner
	wore too much makeup
That made him cough when he kissed her

	but he kissed her anyway
	because that was the thing to do
And at three a.m. he tucked himself into bed
	his father snoring soundly

That's why on the back of a brown paper bag
	he tried another poem

And he called it &quot;Absolutely Nothing&quot;
Because that's what it was really all about
And he gave himself an A
	and a slash on each damned wrist
And he hung it on the bathroom door
	because this time he didn't think

	he could reach the kitchen." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
