<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/308713-michelle-slonim]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/308713-michelle-slonim" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 20:41:25 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353358-when-i-was-first-aware-that-i-had-been-laid</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 20:41:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by William Styron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353358-when-i-was-first-aware-that-i-had-been-laid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was first aware that I had been laid low by the disease, I felt a need, among other things, to register a strong protest against the word &quot;depression.&quot; Depression, most people know, used to be termed &quot;melancholia,&quot; a word which appears in English as the year 1303 and crops up more than once in Chaucer, who in his usade seemed to be aware of its pathological nuances. &quot;Melancholia&quot; would still appear to be a far more apt and evocative word for the blacker forms of the disorder, but it was usurped by a noun with a blank tonality and lacking any magisterial presence, used indifferentl to describe an economic decline or a rut in the ground, a true wimp of a word for such a major illness.

It may be that the scientist generally held responsible for its currency in modern times, a Johns Hopkins Medical School faculty member justly venerated --the Swiss-born psychiatrist Adolf Meyer -- had a tin ear for the finer rhthms of English and therefore was unaware of the semantic damage he had inflicted for such a dreadful and raging disease. Nonetheless, for over seventy-five years the word has slithered innocuously through the language like a slug, leaving little trace of its intrinsic malevolence and preventing, by its insipidity, a general awareness of the horrible intensity of the disease when out of control." -- William Styron]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
