<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/30900-adrianne-mathiowetz]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/30900-adrianne-mathiowetz" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 09:39:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65399-but-criticism-for-the-most-part-comes-from-the-opposite</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 09:39:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adrianne add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65399-but-criticism-for-the-most-part-comes-from-the-opposite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But criticism, for the most part, comes from the opposite place that book-enjoying should come from. To enjoy art one needs time, patience, and a generous heart, and criticism is done, by and large, by impatient people who have axes to grind. The worst sort of critics are (analogy coming) butterfly collectors - they chase something, ostensibly out of their search for beauty, then, once they get close, they catch that beautiful something, they kill it, they stick a pin through its abdomen, dissect it and label it. The whole process, I find, is not a happy or healthy one. Someone with his or her own shit figured out, without any emotional problems or bitterness or envy, instead of killing that which he loves, will simply let the goddamn butterfly fly, and instead of capturing and killing it and sticking it in a box, will simply point to it - &quot;Hey everyone, look at that beautiful thing&quot; - hoping everyone else will see the beautiful thing he has seen. Just as no one wants to grow up to be an IRS agent, no one should want to grow up to maliciously dissect books. " -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166840-the-moment-of-recognizing-your-own-lack-of-talent-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 16:50:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adrianne add a quote by Stanislaw Jerzy Lec]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166840-the-moment-of-recognizing-your-own-lack-of-talent-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The moment of recognizing your own lack of talent is a flash of genius. " -- Stanislaw Jerzy Lec]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1254254-want-the-change-be-inspired-by-the-flame-where-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 07:01:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adrianne add a quote by Rilke, Rainer Maria]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1254254-want-the-change-be-inspired-by-the-flame-where-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Want the change. Be inspired by the flame
where everything shines as it disappears.
The artist, when sketching, loves nothing so much
as the curve of a body as it turns away." -- Rilke, Rainer Maria]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
