<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/30920-laura]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/30920-laura" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 13:34:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110394-there-are-two-kinds-of-things-the-nature-of-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 13:34:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[laura add a quote by Plato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110394-there-are-two-kinds-of-things-the-nature-of-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[there are] two kinds of things the nature of which it would be quite wonderful to grasp by means of a systematic art...

the first consists in seeing together things that are scattered about everywhere and collecting them into one kind, so that by defining each thing we can make clear the subject of any instruction we wish to give...

[the second], in turn, is to be able to cut up each kind according to its species along its natural joints, and to try not to splinter any part, as a bad butcher might do...

phaedrus, i myself am a lover of these divisions and collections, so that i may be able to think and to speak." -- Plato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363475-in-learning-how-to-imagine-x-you-gain-abilities-later</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 13:38:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[laura add a quote by David Kellogg Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363475-in-learning-how-to-imagine-x-you-gain-abilities-later]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["in learning how to imagine x, you gain abilities; later you have all the relevant imaginative abilities you had before, and more besides. and you notice, a priori, relationships of coherence or incoherence between attitudes that might figure in the realisation of x; later you are aware of all that you had noticed before, and more besides. and you think of new questions to explore in your imagining...and later you have in mind all the questions you had thought of before, and more besides." -- David Kellogg Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 13:33:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[laura add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hello babies. Welcome to Earth. It's hot in the summer and cold in the winter. It's round and wet and crowded. On the outside, babies, you've got a hundred years here. There's only one rule that I know of, babies-&quot;God damn it, you've got to be kind." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9888-the-anguished-suspense-of-watching-the-lips-you-hunger-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2008 21:39:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[laura add a quote by Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9888-the-anguished-suspense-of-watching-the-lips-you-hunger-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The anguished suspense of watching the lips you hunger for, framing the words, the death sentence, of sheer triteness!" -- Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52993-in-addition-to-the-conditions-under-which-life-is-given</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2008 22:27:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[laura add a quote by Hannah Arendt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52993-in-addition-to-the-conditions-under-which-life-is-given]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["in addition to the conditions under which life is given to man on earth, and partly out of them, men constantly create their own, self-made conditions, which, their human origins notwithstanding, possess the same conditioning power as natural things.  whatever touches or enters into a sustained relationship with human life immediately assumes the character of a condition of human existence.  this is why men, no matter what they do, are always conditioned beings.  whatever enters the human world of its own accord or is drawn into it by human effort becomes part of the human condition. " -- Hannah Arendt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105648-if-you-are-willing-to-reflect-on-the-courage-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 09:52:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[laura add a quote by Plato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105648-if-you-are-willing-to-reflect-on-the-courage-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["if you are willing to reflect on the courage and moderation of other people, you will find them strange...they all consider death a great evil...and the brave among them face death, when they do, for fear of greater evils...therefore, it is fear and terror that make all men brave, except for philosophers.  yet it is illogical to be brave through fear and cowardice...what of the moderate among them?  is their experience not similar?...they master certain pleasures because they are mastered by others...i fear this is not the right exchange to attain virtue, to exchange pleasures for pleasures, pains for pains, and fears for fears, the greater for the less like coins, but that they only valid currency for which all these things should be exchanged is wisdom." -- Plato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3273-if-people-bring-so-much-courage-to-this-world-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 11:10:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[laura add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3273-if-people-bring-so-much-courage-to-this-world-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If people bring so much courage to this world the world has to kill them to break them, so of course it kills them. The world breaks every one and afterward many are strong at the broken places. But those that will not break it kills. It kills the very good and the very gentle and the very brave impartially. If you are none of these you can be sure it will kill you too but there will be no special hurry." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
