<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/309262-michele-campbell]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/309262-michele-campbell" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 04:29:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22783-i-wish-i-could-show-you-when-you-are-lonely</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 04:29:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michele add a quote by Hafiz of Shiraz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22783-i-wish-i-could-show-you-when-you-are-lonely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish I could show you when you are lonely or in darkness the astonishing light of your own being." -- Hafiz of Shiraz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89794-all-my-life-i-ve-wanted-to-be-the-kid-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 08:54:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michele add a quote by Charles de Lint]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89794-all-my-life-i-ve-wanted-to-be-the-kid-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All my life I've wanted to be the kid who gets to cross over into the magical kingdom. I devoured those books by C.S. Lewis and William Dunthorn, Ellen Wentworth, Susan Cooper, and Alan Garner. When I could get them from the library, I read them out of order as I found them, and then in order, and then reread them all again, many times over. Because even when I was a child I knew it wasn't simply escape that lay on the far side of the borders of fairyland. Instinctively I knew crossing over would mean more than fleeing the constant terror and shame that was mine at that time of my life. There was a knowledge – an understanding hidden in the marrow of my bones that only I can access ― telling me that by crossing over, I'd be coming home.
  That's the reason I’ve yearned so desperately to experience the wonder, the mystery, the beauty of that world beyond the World As It Is. It's because I know that somewhere across the border there's a place for me. A place of safety and strength and learning, where I can become who I'm supposed to be. I've tried forever to be that person here, but whatever I manage to accomplish in the World As It Is only seems to be an echo of what I could be in that other place that lies hidden somewhere beyond the borders." -- Charles de Lint]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
