<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/310149-liz-ahmed]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/310149-liz-ahmed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 10:33:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392516-on-the-girl-s-brown-legs-there-were-many-small-white</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 10:33:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liz add a quote by Chris Cleave]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392516-on-the-girl-s-brown-legs-there-were-many-small-white]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the girl’s brown legs there were many small white scars. I was thinking, Do those scars cover the whole of you, like the stars and moons on your dress? I thought that would be pretty too, and I ask you right here please to agree with me that a scar is never ugly. That is what the scar makers want us to think. But you and I, we must make an agreement to defy them. We must see all scars a s beauty. Okay? This will be our secret. Because take it from me, a scar does not form on the dying. A scar means, ‘I survived’.

In a few breaths’ time I will speak some sad words to you. But you must hear them as we have agreed to see scars now. Sad words are just another beauty. A sad story means the storyteller is alive. The next thing you know, something fine will happen to her, something marvellous, and then she will turn round and smile." -- Chris Cleave]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45921-what-you-are-is-a-complicated-girl-with-simple-needs</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 14:26:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liz add a quote by Brian Morton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45921-what-you-are-is-a-complicated-girl-with-simple-needs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What you are is a complicated girl with simple needs.  You need your books and time to read, and you need a few friends and you need someone-not to take care of you, but to care for you.  If you have all those things, you'll always be alright." -- Brian Morton]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
