<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/310629-esa-ruoho]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/310629-esa-ruoho" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 05:25:53 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155433-we-live-in-a-community-of-people-not-so-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 05:25:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155433-we-live-in-a-community-of-people-not-so-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We live in a community of people not so that we can suppress and dominate eachother or make each other miserable but so that we can better and more reliably satisfy all life's healthy needs." -- Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74461-full-sexual-consciousness-and-a-natural-regulation-of-sexual-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 05:29:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74461-full-sexual-consciousness-and-a-natural-regulation-of-sexual-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Full sexual consciousness and a natural 
regulation of sexual life mean the end of 
mystical feelings of any kind. In other words, 
natural sexuality is the deadly enemy of 
mystical religion. The church, by making 
the fight over sexuality the center of its 
dogmas and of its influence over the masses, 
confirms this concept." -- Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159742-the-question-of-how-and-why-the-encrustations-and-rigidifications</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2009 01:13:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159742-the-question-of-how-and-why-the-encrustations-and-rigidifications]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The question of how and why the encrustations and rigidifications of human emotional life are brought about led directly into the realm of vegetative life." -- Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159744-i-came-to-consider-the-instinct-as-nothing-more-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2009 01:14:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159744-i-came-to-consider-the-instinct-as-nothing-more-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I came to consider the instinct as nothing more than the &quot;motor aspect of pleasure.&quot;
" -- Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164603-and-the-truth-must-finally-lie-in-that-which-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2009 00:28:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164603-and-the-truth-must-finally-lie-in-that-which-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the truth must finally lie in that which every oppressed individual feels within himself but hasn't the courage to express" -- Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164604-saw-a-film-on-cancer-yesterday-shown-by-the-english</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2009 00:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164604-saw-a-film-on-cancer-yesterday-shown-by-the-english]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Saw a film on cancer yesterday, shown by the English delegation. No doubt about it. I'm right. &quot;Migratory cancer cells&quot; are amoebic formations. They are produced from disintegrating tissue and thus demonstrate the law of tension and charge in its purest form - as does the orgastic convulsion. 
Now money is a must - cancer the main issue - in every respect, even political.
It was a staggering experience. My intuition is good. I depend on it. Was absolutely driven to buy a microscope. The sight of the cancer cells was exactly as I had previously imagined it, had almost physically felt it would be. Cancer is an autoinfection of the body, of an organ. And researchers have no idea of what, hor, or where!!" -- Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170080-i-can-imagine-no-greater-catastrophe-than-if-i-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 13:36:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170080-i-can-imagine-no-greater-catastrophe-than-if-i-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can imagine no greater catastrophe than if I were mistaken, and the theory were correct that what I consider secondary instincts or drives are actually primary instincts! Because in that case the emotional plague would rest upon the support of a natural law while its archenemies, truth and sociality, would be relying upon unfounded ethics. Until now both lies and truth have taken recourse to ethics. But only lies have profited because they were able to appear under the guise of truth. Under these circumstances, egoism, theft, petty selfishness, slander, etc., would be the natural rule. (26.july.1943)" -- Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171452-the-stiff-dead-retracted-pelvis-is-one-of-man-s-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 02:46:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171452-the-stiff-dead-retracted-pelvis-is-one-of-man-s-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The &quot;stiff, dead, retracted pelvis&quot; is one of man's most frequent vegetative disturbances. It is responsible for lumbago as well as for hemorrhoidal disturbances. Elsewhere, we shall demonstrate an important connection between these disturbances and genital cancer in women, which is so common.
Thus, the &quot;deadning of the pelvis&quot; has the same function as the deadening of the abdomen, i.e., to avoid feelings, particularly those of pleasure and anxiety." -- Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220761-while-the-repression-of-a-memory-is-a-psychological-process</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 09:02:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Alexander Lowen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220761-while-the-repression-of-a-memory-is-a-psychological-process]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["While the repression of a memory is a psychological process, the suppression of feeling is accomplished by deadening a part of the body or reducing its motility so that feeling is diminished. The repression of the memory is dependent upon and related to the suppression of feeling, for as long as the feeling persists, the memory remains vivid. Suppression entails the development of chronic muscular tension in those areas of the body where the feeling would be experienced. In the case of sexual feeling, this tension is found in and about the abdomen and pelvis" -- Alexander Lowen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220769-since-the-experience-is-different-for-each-individual-the-tension</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 09:32:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Alexander Lowen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220769-since-the-experience-is-different-for-each-individual-the-tension]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Since the experience is different for each individual, the tension will reflect that experience. In some persons the whole lower half of the body is relatively immobilized and held in a passive state; in others the muscular tensions are localized in the pelvic floor and around the genital apparatus. If the latter sort of tension is severe, it constitutes a functional castration; for, although the genitals operate normally, they are dissociated in feeling from the rest of the body. Any reduction of sexual feeling amounts to a psychological castration. Generally the person is unaware of these muscular tensions, but putting pressure upon the muscles in the attempt to release the tension is often experienced as very painful and frightening." -- Alexander Lowen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229300-the-cases-described-in-this-section-the-fear-of-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2010 12:08:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Alexander Lowen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229300-the-cases-described-in-this-section-the-fear-of-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The cases described in this section (The Fear of Being) may seem extreme, but I have become convinced that they are not as uncommon as one would think. Beneath the seemingly rational exterior of our lives is a fear of insanity. We dare not question the values by which we live or rebel against the roles we play for fear of putting our sanity into doubt. We are like the inmates of a mental institution who must accept its inhumanity and insensitivity as caring and knowledgeableness if they hope to be regarded as sane enough to leave. The question who is sane and who is crazy was the theme of the novel [book:One Flew Over The Cuckoo's Nest|332613]. The question, what is sanity? was clearly asked in the play [book:Equus|51216].
The idea that much of what we do is insane and that if we want to be sane, we must let ourselves go crazy has been strongly advanced by [author:R.D. Laing|4436873]. In the preface to the Pelican edition of his book [book:The Divided Self|9012074], Laing writes: &quot;In the context of our present pervasive madness that we call normality, sanity, freedom, all of our frames of reference are ambiguous and equivocal.&quot; And in the same preface: &quot;Thus I would wish to emphasize that our 'normal' 'adjusted' state is too often the abdication of ecstasy, the betrayal of our true potentialities; that many of us are only too successful in acquiring a false self to adapt to false realities.&quot;
[author:Wilhelm Reich|118694] had a somewhat similar view of present-day human behavior. Thus Reich says, &quot;Homo normalis blocks off entirely the perception of basic orgonotic functioning by means of rigid armoring; in the schizophrenic, on the other hand, the armoring practically breaks down and thus the biosystem is flooded with deep experiences from the biophysical core with which it cannot cope.&quot; The &quot;deep experiences&quot; to which Reich refers are the pleasurable streaming sensations associated with intense excitation that is mainly sexual in nature. The schizophrenic cannot cope with these sensations because his body is too contracted to tolerate the charge. Unable to &quot;block&quot; the excitation or reduce it as a neurotic can, and unable to &quot;stand&quot; the charge, the schizophrenic is literally &quot;driven crazy.&quot;
But the neurotic does not escape so easily either. He avoids insanity by blocking the excitation, that is, by reducing it to a point where there is no danger of explosion, or bursting. In effect the neurotic undergoes a psychological castration. However, the potential for explosive release is still present in his body, although it is rigidly guarded as if it were a bomb. The neurotic is on guard against himself, terrified to let go of his defenses and allow his feelings free expression. Having become, as Reich calls him, &quot;homo normalis,&quot; having bartered his freedom and ecstasy for the security of being &quot;well adjusted,&quot; he sees the alternative as &quot;crazy.&quot; And in a sense he is right. Without going &quot;crazy,&quot; without becoming &quot;mad,&quot; so mad that he could kill, it is impossible to give up the defenses that protect him in the same way that a mental institution protects its inmates from self-destruction and the destruction of others." -- Alexander Lowen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229306-the-most-effective-weapon-a-parent-has-to-control-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2010 12:16:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Alexander Lowen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229306-the-most-effective-weapon-a-parent-has-to-control-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most effective weapon a parent has to control a child is the withdrawal of love or its threat. A young child between the ages of three and six is too dependent on parental love and approval to resist this pressure. Robert's mother, as we saw earlier, controlled him by &quot;cutting him out.&quot; Margaret's mother beat her into submission, but it was the loss of her father's love that devastated her. Whatever the means parents use, the result is that the child is forced to give up his instinctual longing, to suppress his sexual desires for one parent and his hostility toward the other. In their place he will develop feelings of guilt about his sexuality and fear of authority figures. This surrender constitutes an acceptance of parental power and authority and a submission to the parents' values and demands. The child becomes &quot;good&quot;, which means that he gives up his sexual orientation in favor of one directed toward achievement. Parental authority is introjected in the form of a superego, ensuring that the child will follow his parents' wishes in the acculturation process. In effect, the child now identifies with the threatening parent. Freud says, &quot;The whole process, on the one hand, preserves the genital organ wards off the danger of losing it; on the other hand, it paralyzes it, takes its function away from it." -- Alexander Lowen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229310-there-are-many-roles-that-people-play-and-many-images</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2010 12:20:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Alexander Lowen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229310-there-are-many-roles-that-people-play-and-many-images]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are many roles that people play and many images that they project. There is, for example, the &quot;nice&quot; man who is always smiling and agreeable. &quot;Such a nice man,&quot; people say. &quot;He never gets angry.&quot; The facade always covers its opposite expression. Inside, such a person is full of rage that he dares not acknowledge or show. Some men put up a tough exterior to hide a very sensitive, childlike quality. Even failure can be a role. Many masochistic characters engage in the game of failure to cover an inner feeling of superiority. An outward show of superiority could bring down on them the jealous wrath of the father and the threat of castration. As long as they act like failures they can retain some sexuality, since they are not a threat to her father." -- Alexander Lowen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2010 08:55:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256895-many-conscientious-environmentalists-are-repelled-by-the-word-abundance-automatically</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2010 10:05:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Jeane Manning and Joel Garbon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256895-many-conscientious-environmentalists-are-repelled-by-the-word-abundance-automatically]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many conscientious environmentalists are repelled by the word &quot;abundance,&quot; automatically associating it with irresponsible consumerism and plundering of Earth's resources. In the context of grassroots frustration, insensitive enthusing about the potential for energy abundance usually elicits an annoyed retort. &quot;We have to conserve.&quot; The authors believe the human family also has to _choose_. The people we speak with at the recycling depot or organic juice bar are for the most part not looking at the _difference_ between harmony-with-nature technologies and exploitative practices such as mountaintop coal mining. &quot;Destructive&quot; was yesterday's technology of choice. As a result, the words &quot;science and technology&quot; are repugnant to many of the people who passionately care about health, peace, justice and the biosphere. Usually these acquaintances haven't heard about the variety of constructive yet powerful clean energy technologies that have the potential to gradually replace oil and nuclear industries if allowed. Wastewater-into-energy technologies could clean up waterways and other variations solve the problem of polluting feedlots and landfills." -- Jeane Manning and Joel Garbon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233258-the-greatest-weariness-comes-from-work-not-done</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2010 11:23:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Eric Hoffer ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233258-the-greatest-weariness-comes-from-work-not-done]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greatest weariness comes from work not done.
" -- Eric Hoffer ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13119-you-never-change-things-by-fighting-the-existing-reality-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 15:33:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Buckminster Fuller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13119-you-never-change-things-by-fighting-the-existing-reality-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You never change things by fighting the existing reality.
To change something, build a new model that makes the existing model obsolete." -- Buckminster Fuller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57585-i-m-not-a-genius-i-m-just-a-tremendous-bundle-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 15:33:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by R. Buckminster Fuller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57585-i-m-not-a-genius-i-m-just-a-tremendous-bundle-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not a genius. I'm just a tremendous bundle of experience." -- R. Buckminster Fuller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35623-in-order-to-change-an-existing-paradigm-you-do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 15:33:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Buckminster R. Fuller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35623-in-order-to-change-an-existing-paradigm-you-do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In order to change an existing paradigm you do not struggle to try and change the problematic model.  You create a new model and make the old one obsolete." -- Buckminster R. Fuller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60782-i-just-invent-then-i-wait-until-man-comes-around</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 15:34:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Buckminster Fuller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60782-i-just-invent-then-i-wait-until-man-comes-around]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I just invent. Then I wait until man comes around to needing what I've invented." -- Buckminster Fuller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187054-defeat-i-shall-not-know-it-shall-not-touch-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 15:34:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Walter Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187054-defeat-i-shall-not-know-it-shall-not-touch-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Defeat I shall not know. It shall not touch me. I will meet it with true thinking. Resisting it will be my strengthening. But if, perchance, the day shall give to me the bitter cup, it shall sweeten in the drinking." -- Walter Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20089-the-pleasure-of-living-and-the-pleasure-of-the-orgasm</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 15:34:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20089-the-pleasure-of-living-and-the-pleasure-of-the-orgasm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The pleasure of living and the pleasure of the orgasm are identical. Extreme orgasm anxiety forms the basis of the general fear of life." -- Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63787-love-is-the-absence-of-anxiety</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 15:34:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63787-love-is-the-absence-of-anxiety]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is the absence of Anxiety." -- Wilhelm Reich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282226-we-must-realize-that-we-are-all-like-dr-faust</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 01:19:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Alexander Lowen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282226-we-must-realize-that-we-are-all-like-dr-faust]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must realize that we are all, like Dr. Faust, ready to accept the devil's inducements. The devil is in each one of us in the form of an ego that promises the fulfillment of desire on condition that we become subservient to its striving to dominate. The domination of the personality by the ego is a diabolical perversion of the nature of man. The ego was never intended to be the master of the body, but its loyal and obedient servant. The body, as opposed to the ego, desires pleasure, not power. Bodily pleasure is the source from which all our good feelings and good thinking stems. If the bodily pleasure of an individual is destroyed, he becomes an angry, frustrated, and hateful person. His thinking becomes distorted, and his creative potential is lost. He develops self-destructive attitudes." -- Alexander Lowen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283150-conversation-to-take-another-example-is-one-of-the-common</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2010 23:33:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Alexander Lowen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283150-conversation-to-take-another-example-is-one-of-the-common]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Conversation, to take another example, is one of the common pleasures of life, but not all conversation is pleasurable. The stutterer finds talking painful, and the listener is equally pained. Persons who are inhibited in expressing feeling are not good conversationalists. Nothing is more boring than to listen to a person talk in a monotone without feeling. We enjoy a conversation when there is a communication of feeling. We have pleasure in expressing our feelings, and we respond pleasurably to another person's expression of feeling. The voice, like the body, is a medium through which feeling flows, and when this flow occurs in an easy and rhythmic manner, it is a pleasure both to the speaker and listener." -- Alexander Lowen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298721-prototypes-of-inventions-that-use-novel-combinations-of-resonance-magnetism</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 22:52:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Jeane Manning and Joel Garbon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298721-prototypes-of-inventions-that-use-novel-combinations-of-resonance-magnetism]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Prototypes of inventions that use novel combinations of resonance, magnetism, states of matter, certain geometries or inward swirling motion to unlock the secrets of universal energy have already been built. They provide proof of new or rediscovered principles. In many variations of these inventions, a small input triggers a disproportionately large output of useable power.&quot;
&quot;These energy converters don't violate any laws of physics if they simply tap into a previously unrecognized source of power - background space. A flow of energy from that source can continue day and night, whether or not the sun shines or the wind blows." -- Jeane Manning and Joel Garbon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298722-bill-muller-was-a-tall-grey-haired-man-with-an-apparently</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 23:09:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Jeane Manning and Joel Garbon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298722-bill-muller-was-a-tall-grey-haired-man-with-an-apparently]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bill Muller was a tall grey-haired man with an apparently high level of vitality despite incessant cigarette smoking. Holding everyone's attention by his forceful personality, he described his invention as a way to make a heavy wheel carry strong magnets past electricity-inducing copper coils without needing to fight the electrical drag force which usually opposes rotation and limits how efficient a generator can be. His wheel didn't have any &quot;stuck&quot; position; it moved freely.
&quot;We have a magnetically balanced flywheel.&quot;
In his basement workshop, Bill showed us the beginnings of a permanent-magnet generator." -- Jeane Manning and Joel Garbon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298983-he-comings-has-in-the-past-performed-succesful-energy-converting-experiments</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 02:03:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Jeane Manning and Joel Garbon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298983-he-comings-has-in-the-past-performed-succesful-energy-converting-experiments]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He (Comings) has in the past performed succesful energy-converting experiments, creating a ringing resonance by injecting certain frequencies into piezo-electric crystals. When the crystal was in resonance with the plenum of space, the power output rose significantly higher than the input. He concluded that, if allowed politically, such discoveries could guide humankind in building a completely clean energy infrastructure -- resonant technologies that allow us to live in harmony with the universal energy field and the Earth." -- Jeane Manning and Joel Garbon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298984-resonance-is-a-real-here-today-phenomena-that-just-hasn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 02:06:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Jeane Manning and Joel Garbon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298984-resonance-is-a-real-here-today-phenomena-that-just-hasn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Resonance is a real 'here today' phenomena that just hasn't been looked at very carefully, and that is because of the (nonsense) that physicists have been putting out about 'energy' for decades. Electronic resonance has been used in radio tuners since their inception, while in the field of electric power resonance is avoided like the plague.&quot; &quot;My system is not 'of the future' but here on this earth with all of the world's present problems.&quot; McKie said his real-world solid-state electronic system could be understood today, if physicists were not teaching that it cannot be achieved.
&quot;...When physicists decide to 'come clean' and say that they don't know it all, we'll all be a lot closer to the gleaming world that you are describing." -- Jeane Manning and Joel Garbon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300736-for-decades-new-energy-researchers-talked-about-the-possibility-of-treating</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 08:22:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esa add a quote by Jeane Manning and Joel Garbon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300736-for-decades-new-energy-researchers-talked-about-the-possibility-of-treating]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For decades, new-energy researchers talked about the possibility of treating a magnet so that its magnetic field would continuously shake or vibrate. On rare occasions, Sweet saw this effect, called self-oscillation, occur in electric transformers. He felt it could be coaxed into doing something useful, such as producing energy. Sweet thought that if he could find the precise way to shake or disturb a magnet's force field, the field would continue to shake by itself. It would be similar to striking a bell and having the bell keep on ringing. Sweet - who said his ideas came to him in dreams - turned for inspiration to his expertise in magnets. He knew magnets could be used to produce electricity, and wanted to see if he could get power out of a magnet by something other than the standard induction process. What Sweet wanted to do was to keep the magnet still and just shake its magnetic field. This shaking, in turn, would create an electric current. One new-energy researcher compares self-oscillation to a leaf on a tree waving in a gentle breeze. While the breeze itself isn't moving back and forth, it sets the leaf into that kind of motion. Sweet thought that if cosmic energy could be captured to serve as the breeze, then the magnetic field would serve as the leaf. Sweet would just have to supply a small amount of energy to set the magnetic field in motion, and space energy would keep it moving." -- Jeane Manning and Joel Garbon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
