<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/310857-allie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/310857-allie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 14:18:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84775-it-s-perfectly-simple-said-wednesday-in-other-countries-over-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 14:18:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84775-it-s-perfectly-simple-said-wednesday-in-other-countries-over-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's perfectly simple,&quot; said Wednesday.  &quot;In other countries, over the years, people recognized the places of power.  Sometimes it would be a natural formation, sometimes it would just be a place that was, somehow, special.  They knew that something important was happening there, that there was some focusing point, some channel, some window to the Immanent.  And so they would build temples or cathedrals, or erect stone circles, or...well, you get the idea.&quot;

   &quot;There are churches all across the States, though,&quot; said Shadow.

   &quot;In every town.  Sometimes on every block.  And about as significant, in this context, as dentists' offices.  No, in the USA, people still get the call, or some of them, and they feel themselves being called to from the transcendent void, and they respond to it by building a model out of beer bottles of somewhere they've never visited, or by erecting a gigantic bat house in some part of the country that bats have traditionally declined to visit.  Roadside attractions: people feel themselves pulled to places where, in other parts of the world, they would recognize that part of themselves that is truly transcendent, and buy a hot dog, and walk around, feeling satisfied on a level they cannot truly describe, and profoundly dissatisfied on a level beneath that." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37596-we-need-enormous-pockets-pockets-big-enough-for-our-families</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 13:46:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allie add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37596-we-need-enormous-pockets-pockets-big-enough-for-our-families]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We need enormous pockets, pockets big enough for our families and our friends, and even the people who aren't on our lists, people we've never met but still want to protect.  We need pockets for boroughs and for cities, a pocket that could hold the universe." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470370-by-now-you-know-i-come-from-another-planet-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 20:12:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allie add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470370-by-now-you-know-i-come-from-another-planet-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By now you know: I come from another planet.  But I will never say to you, &quot;Take me to your leaders.&quot;  Even I--unused to your ways though I am--would never make that mistake.  We ourselves have such beings among us, made of cogs, pieces of paper, small disks of shiny metal, scraps of coloured cloth.  I do not need to encounter more of them.

Instead I will say, &quot;Take me to your trees.  Take me to your breakfasts, your sunsets, your bad dreams, your shoes, your nouns.  Take me to your fingers; take me to your deaths.&quot;

These are worth it.  These are what I have come for." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6061-love-takes-off-the-masks-we-fear-we-cannot-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2012 20:09:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allie add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6061-love-takes-off-the-masks-we-fear-we-cannot-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love takes off the masks we fear we cannot live without and know we cannot live within." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131591-nothing-is-original-steal-from-anywhere-that-resonates-with-inspiration</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 18:56:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allie add a quote by Jim Jarmusch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131591-nothing-is-original-steal-from-anywhere-that-resonates-with-inspiration]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing is original. Steal from anywhere that resonates with inspiration or fuels your imagination. Devour old films, new films, music, books, paintings, photographs, poems, dreams, random conversations, architecture, bridges, street signs, trees, clouds, bodies of water, light and shadows. Select only things to steal from that speak directly to your soul. If you do this, your work (and theft) will be authentic. Authenticity is invaluable; originality is non-existent. And don’t bother concealing your thievery - celebrate it if you feel like it. In any case, always remember what Jean-Luc Godard said: “It’s not where you take things from - it’s where you take them to.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;MovieMaker Magazine&lt;/i&gt; #53 - Winter, January 22, 2004 ]" -- Jim Jarmusch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/905867-the-question-about-the-page-is-what-is-beneath-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 15:10:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allie add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/905867-the-question-about-the-page-is-what-is-beneath-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The question about the page is: what is beneath it? It seems to have only two dimensions, you can pick it up and turn it over and the back is the same as the front. Nothing, you say, disappointed.

But you were looking in the wrong place, you were looking &lt;i&gt;on the back&lt;/i&gt; instead of &lt;i&gt;beneath&lt;/i&gt;. &lt;i&gt;Beneath the page&lt;/i&gt; is another story. Beneath the page is a story. Beneath the page is everything that has ever happened, most of which you would rather not hear about.

The page is not a pool but a skin, a skin is there to hold in and it can feel you touching it. Did you really think it would just lie there and do nothing?

Touch the page at your peril: it is you who are blank and innocent, not the page. Nevertheless you want to know, nothing will stop you. You touch the page, it's as if you've drawn a knife across it, the page has been hurt now, a sinuous wound opens, a thin incision. Darkness wells through." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/905868-if-the-stock-market-exists-so-must-previous-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 15:12:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allie add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/905868-if-the-stock-market-exists-so-must-previous-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the stock market exists, so must previous lives." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/905871-today-i-speak-to-my-bones-as-i-would-speak</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 15:16:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allie add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/905871-today-i-speak-to-my-bones-as-i-would-speak]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today I speak to my bones as I would speak to a dog. I want to go up the stairs, I tell them. Up, up, up, with one leg dragging. Is the ache deep in the bones, this elusive pain? Does that mean it will rain? Good bones, &lt;i&gt;good&lt;/i&gt; bones, I coax, wondering how to reward them; if they will sit up for me, beg, roll over, do one more trick, once more.

There. We're at the top. &lt;i&gt;Good&lt;/i&gt; bones! Good &lt;i&gt;bones&lt;/i&gt;! Keep on going." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/874772-october-baptize-me-with-leaves-swaddle-me-in-corduroy-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 09:06:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allie add a quote by Rainbow Rowell ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/874772-october-baptize-me-with-leaves-swaddle-me-in-corduroy-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["October, baptize me with leaves! Swaddle me in corduroy and nurse me with split pea soup. October, tuck tiny candy bars in my pockets and carve my smile into a thousand pumpkins. O autumn! O teakettle! O grace!" -- Rainbow Rowell ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/955249-one-day-the-english-language-is-going-to-perish-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 13:36:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allie add a quote by Nicholson Baker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/955249-one-day-the-english-language-is-going-to-perish-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One day the English language is going to perish. The easy spokenness of it will perish and go black and crumbly — maybe — and it will become a language like Latin that learned people learn. And scholars will write studies of &lt;i&gt;Larry Sanders&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Friends&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Will &amp; Grace&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Ellen&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Designing Women&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Mary Tyler Moore&lt;/i&gt;, and everyone will see that the sitcom is the great American art form. American poetry will perish with the language; the sitcoms, on the other hand, are new to human evolution and therefore will be less perishable." -- Nicholson Baker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/707150-anyone-who-isn-t-embarrassed-of-who-they-were-last-year</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 14:50:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allie add a quote by Alain de Botton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/707150-anyone-who-isn-t-embarrassed-of-who-they-were-last-year]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who isn't embarrassed of who they were last year probably isn't learning enough." -- Alain de Botton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1248735-i-m-not-good-with-the-low-level-unexplained-i-worry-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 07:28:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allie add a quote by David        Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1248735-i-m-not-good-with-the-low-level-unexplained-i-worry-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not good with the low-level unexplained. I worry at such things. I'm quite relaxed about the great mysteries of the universe; when it comes to the existence of God, for example, I figure that, as with a good episode of &lt;i&gt;Inspector Morse&lt;/i&gt;, I'll find out what's going on eventually." -- David        Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
