<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/31111-billy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/31111-billy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 17:42:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102031-few-beings-have-ever-been-so-impregnated-pierced-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 17:42:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billy add a quote by Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102031-few-beings-have-ever-been-so-impregnated-pierced-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Few beings have ever been so impregnated, pierced to the core, by the conviction of the absolute futility of human aspiration. The universe is nothing but a furtive arrangement of elementary particles. A figure in transition toward chaos. That is what will finally prevail. The human race will disappear. Other races in turn will appear and disappear.  The skies will be glacial and empty, traversed by the feeble light of half-dead stars. These too will disappear. Everything will disappear. And human actions are as free and as stripped of meaning as the unfettered movements of the elementary particles. Good, evil, morality, sentiments? Pure ‘Victorian fictions.’ All that exists is egotism. Cold, intact, and radiant." -- Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234236-does-britannia-when-she-sleeps-dream-is-america-her-dream---</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 00:10:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billy add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234236-does-britannia-when-she-sleeps-dream-is-america-her-dream---]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Does Britannia, when she sleeps, dream? Is America her dream?-- in which all that cannot pass in the metropolitan Wakefulness is allow'd Expression away in the restless Slumber of these Provinces, and on West-ward, wherever 'tis not yet mapp'd, nor written down, nor ever, by the majority of Mankind, seen,-- serving as a very Rubbish-Tip for subjunctive Hopes, for all that may yet be true,-- Earthly Paradise, Fountain of Youth, Realms of Prester John, Christ's Kingdom, ever behind the sunset, safe til the next Territory to the West be seen and recorded, measur'd and tied in, back into the Net-Work of Points already known, that slowly triangulates its Way into the Continent, changing all from subjunctive to declarative, reducing Possibilities to Simplicities that serve the ends of Governments,-- winning away from the realm of the Sacred, its Borderlands one by one, and assuming them unto the bare mortal World that is our home, and our Despair." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109059-back-in-paris-they-had-happy-moments-together-like-stills</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2008 12:04:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billy add a quote by Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109059-back-in-paris-they-had-happy-moments-together-like-stills]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Back in Paris they had happy moments together, like stills from a perfume ad (dashing hand in hand down the steps of Montmartre; or suddenly revealed in motionless embrace on the Pont des Arts by the lights of a bateau-mouche as it turned). There were the Sunday afternoon half-arguments, too, the moments of silence when bodies curl up beneath the sheets on the long shores of silence and apathy where life founders. Annabelle's studio was so dark they had to turn on the lights at four in the afternoon. They sometimes were sad, but mostly they were serious. Both of them knew that this would be their last human relationship, and this feeling lacerated every moment they spent together. They had a great respect and a profound sympathy for each other, and there were days when, caught up in some sudden magic, they knew moments of fresh air and glorious, bracing sunshine. For the most part, however, they could feel a gray shadow moving over them, on the earth that supported them, and in everything they could glimpse the end." -- Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219858-that-s-what-art-is-he-said-the-story-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 09:32:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billy add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219858-that-s-what-art-is-he-said-the-story-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's what art is, he said, the story of a life in all its particularity. It's the only thing that really is particular and personal. It's the expression and, at the same time, the fabric of the particular. And what do you mean by the fabric of the particular? I asked, supposing he would answer: Art. I was also thinking, indulgently, that we were pretty drunk already and that it was time to go home. But my friend said: What I mean is the secret story.... The secret story is the one we'll never know, although we're living it from day to day, thinking we're alive, thinking we've got it all under control and the stuff we overlook doesn't matter. But every damn thing matters! It's just that we don't realize. We tell ourselves that art runs on one track and life, our lives, on another, we don't even realize that's a lie." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224831-sometimes-after-they-d-done-the-shopping-they-would-stop-each</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 00:10:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billy add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224831-sometimes-after-they-d-done-the-shopping-they-would-stop-each]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, after they'd done the shopping, they would stop, each with his or her cart, in front of a bookstore that carried the paperback edition of his book. His wife would point to it and say: you're still there. Invariably, he would nod and then they would continue browsing the mall stores. Did he know her or didn't he? He knew her, of course he did, it was just that sometimes reality, the same little reality that served to anchor reality, seemed to fade around the edges, as if the passage of time had a porous effect on things, and blurred and made more insubstantial what was itself already, by its very nature, insubstantial and satisfactory and real." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305096-it-is-incomprehensible-that-he-should-want-to-have-these</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 20:35:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billy add a quote by Pär Lagerkvist]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305096-it-is-incomprehensible-that-he-should-want-to-have-these]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is incomprehensible that he should want to have these futile people here, and still more incomprehensible that he should be able to sit and listen to them and their stupid chatter. I can understand that he may occasionally listen to poets reciting their verses; they can be regarded as buffoons such as are always kept at court. They laud the lofty purity of the human soul, great events and heroic feats, and there is nothing to be said against all that, particularly if their songs flatter him. Human beings need flattery; otherwise they do not fulfill their purpose, not even in their own eyes. And both the present and the past contain much that is beautiful and noble which, without due praise, would have been neither noble nor beautiful. Above all, they sing the praises of love, which is quite as it should be, for nothing else is in such need of transformation into something different. The ladies are filled with melancholy and their breasts heave with sighs; the men gaze vaguely and dreamily into space, for they all know what it is really like and realize that this must be an especially beautiful poem." -- Pär Lagerkvist]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130692-people-often-say-that-the-english-are-very-cold-fish</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 21:37:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billy add a quote by Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130692-people-often-say-that-the-english-are-very-cold-fish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People often say that the English are very cold fish, very reserved, that they have a way of looking at things – even tragedy – with a sense of irony. There’s some truth in it; it’s pretty stupid of them, though. Humor won’t save you; it doesn’t really do anything at all. You can look at life ironically for years, maybe decades; there are people who seem to go through most of their lives seeing the funny side, but in the end, life always breaks your heart. Doesn’t matter how brave you are, how reserved, or how much you’ve developed a sense of humor, you still end up with your heart broken. That’s when you stop laughing. In the end there’s just the cold, the silence and the loneliness. In the end, there’s only death." -- Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17892-the-absence-of-the-will-to-live-is-alas-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 21:37:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billy add a quote by Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17892-the-absence-of-the-will-to-live-is-alas-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The absence of the will to live is, alas, not sufficient to make one want to die." -- Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/380022-the-trap-of-reputation-for-example-in-this-scenario-having</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2011 08:46:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billy add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/380022-the-trap-of-reputation-for-example-in-this-scenario-having]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trap of reputation, for example. In this scenario, having garnered a considerable reputation or level of acclaim, one becomes paralyzed by the dreadful thought of losing it all by doing something... undignified. Uncool. This is a trap. Reputation is a trap that will turn you into a lifeless marble bust of yourself before you're even dead. And then of courses there is reputation's immortal big brother, Posterity, worrying about which has driven better women and men than you into the asylum. All these things... reputation, posterity, cool... should be tested to destruction by a course of deliberate sabotage. As the often-illuminating Escape and New Musical Express cartoonist Shaky Kane once remarked, &quot;Don't be cool. Like everything.&quot; If you find yourself in danger of being taken seriously, then try to do something which undermines or sabotages that perception in some way. If your talent is of any genuine worth, it should be able to weather squalls of unpopularity and audience incomprehensio. The only thing that might seriously endanger either your talent or your relationship with your talent is if you suddenly found yourself fashionable." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420126-don-t-be-cool-like-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 22:26:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billy add a quote by Shaky Kane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420126-don-t-be-cool-like-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't be cool. Like everything." -- Shaky Kane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5759-academia-is-the-death-of-cinema-it-is-the-very</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 08:35:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billy add a quote by Werner Herzog]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5759-academia-is-the-death-of-cinema-it-is-the-very]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Academia is the death of cinema.  It is the very opposite of passion.  Film is not the art of scholars, but of illiterates." -- Werner Herzog]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
