<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/311259-meg]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/311259-meg" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 11:05:33 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198-i-am-so-clever-that-sometimes-i-don-t-understand-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 11:05:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198-i-am-so-clever-that-sometimes-i-don-t-understand-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am so clever that sometimes I don't understand a single word of what I am saying." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 11:05:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that is gold does not glitter,
Not all those who wander are lost;
The old that is strong does not wither,
Deep roots are not reached by the frost.

From the ashes a fire shall be woken,
A light from the shadows shall spring;
Renewed shall be blade that was broken,
The crownless again shall be king." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1776-remember-if-the-time-should-come-when-you-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 11:06:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1776-remember-if-the-time-should-come-when-you-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember, if the time should come when you have to make a choice between what is right and what is easy, remember what happened to a boy who was good, and kind, and brave, because he strayed across the path of Lord Voldemort.  Remember Cedric Diggory." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 11:06:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1398-i-love-deadlines-i-love-the-whooshing-noise-they-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 11:06:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1398-i-love-deadlines-i-love-the-whooshing-noise-they-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love deadlines. I love the whooshing noise they make as they go by." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298-a-day-without-sunshine-is-like-you-know-night</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 11:06:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298-a-day-without-sunshine-is-like-you-know-night]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A day without sunshine is like, you know, night." -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2621-love-all-trust-a-few-do-wrong-to-none</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 11:07:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2621-love-all-trust-a-few-do-wrong-to-none]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love all, trust a few, do wrong to none." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 11:07:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to write the book that wants to be written. And if the book will be too difficult for grown-ups, then you write it for children." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1427-i-have-never-let-my-schooling-interfere-with-my-education</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 11:07:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1427-i-have-never-let-my-schooling-interfere-with-my-education]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have never let my schooling interfere with my education." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 11:07:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is our choices, Harry, that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5399-if-you-want-to-know-what-a-man-s-like-take</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 11:08:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5399-if-you-want-to-know-what-a-man-s-like-take]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to know what a man's like, take a good look at how he treats his inferiors, not his equals." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240-reality-is-merely-an-illusion-albeit-a-very-persistent-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 11:08:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240-reality-is-merely-an-illusion-albeit-a-very-persistent-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reality is merely an illusion, albeit a very persistent one." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907-when-i-was-a-child-adults-would-tell-me-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 14:03:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907-when-i-was-a-child-adults-would-tell-me-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was a child, adults would tell me not to make things up, warning me of what would happen if I did. As far as I can tell so far, it seems to involve lots of foreign travel and not having to get up too early in the morning." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13155-it-is-a-curious-thing-the-death-of-a-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2009 19:26:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13155-it-is-a-curious-thing-the-death-of-a-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a curious thing, the death of a loved one. We all know that our time in this world is limited, and that eventually all of us will end up underneath some sheet, never to wake up. And yet it is always a surprise when it happens to someone we know. It is like walking up the stairs to your bedroom in the dark, and thinking there is one more stair than there is. Your foot falls down, through the air, and there is a sickly moment of dark surprise as you try and readjust the way you thought of things." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32566-my-favourite-piece-of-information-is-that-branwell-bront-brother</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2009 19:29:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by Douglas Adams (The Salmon of Doubt)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32566-my-favourite-piece-of-information-is-that-branwell-bront-brother]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My favourite piece of information is that Branwell Brontë, brother of Emily and Charlotte, died standing up leaning against a mantle piece, in order to prove it could be done.

This is not quite true, in fact. My absolute favourite piece of information is the fact that young sloths are so inept that they frequently grab their own arms and legs instead of tree limbs, and fall out of trees. 

However, this is not relevant to what is currently on my mind because it concerns sloths, whereas the Branwell Brontë piece of information concerns writers and feeling like death and doing things to prove they can be done, all of which are pertinent to my current situation to a degree that is, frankly, spooky." -- Douglas Adams (The Salmon of Doubt)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29024-because-children-grow-up-we-think-a-child-s-purpose-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2009 19:31:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29024-because-children-grow-up-we-think-a-child-s-purpose-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because children grow up, we think a child's purpose is to grow up. But a child's purpose is to be a child. Nature doesn't disdain what lives only for a day. It pours the whole of itself into the each moment. We don't value the lily less for not being made of flint and built to last. Life's bounty is in its flow, later is too late. Where is the song when it's been sung? The dance when it's been danced? It's only we humans who want to own the future, too. We persuade ourselves that the universe is modestly employed in unfolding our destination. We note the haphazard chaos of history by the day, by the hour, but there is something wrong with the picture. Where is the unity, the meaning, of nature's highest creation? Surely those millions of little streams of accident and wilfulness have their correction in the vast underground river which, without a doubt, is carrying us to the place where we're expected! But there is no such place, that's why it's called utopia. The death of a child has no more meaning than the death of armies, of nations. Was the child happy while he lived? That is a proper question, the only question. If we can't arrange our own happiness, it's a conceit beyond vulgarity to arrange the happiness of those who come after us." -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20304-you-are-so-young-lyra-too-young-to-understand-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2009 19:32:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20304-you-are-so-young-lyra-too-young-to-understand-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are so young, Lyra, too young to understand this, but I shall tell you anyway and you'll understand it later: men pass in front of our eyes like butterflies, creatures of a brief season. We love them; they are brave, proud, beautiful, clever; and they die almost at once. They die so soon that our hearts are continually racked with pain. We bear their children, who are witches if they are female, human if not; and then in the blink of an eye they are gone, felled, slain, lost. Our sons, too. When a little boy is growing, he thinks he is immortal. His mother knows he isn't. Each time becomes more painful, until finally your heart is broken. Perhaps that is when Yambe-Akka comes for you. She is older than the tundra. Perhaps, for her, witches' lives are as brief as men's are to us." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116834-when-i-heard-your-organization-was-recording-testimonies-i-knew</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2009 19:44:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116834-when-i-heard-your-organization-was-recording-testimonies-i-knew]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I heard your organization was recording testimonies, I knew I had to come. She died in my arms, saying 'I don't want to die.' That is what death is like. It doesn't matter what uniforms the soldiers are wearing. It doesn't matter how good the weapons are. I thought if everyone could see what I saw, we would never have war anymore." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36317-why-did-you-do-all-this-for-me-he-asked</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 12:40:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36317-why-did-you-do-all-this-for-me-he-asked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why did you do all this for me?' he asked. 'I don't deserve it. I've never done anything for you.' 'You have been my friend,' replied Charlotte. 'That in itself is a tremendous thing." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1132-deserves-it-i-daresay-he-does-many-that-live-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 13:26:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1132-deserves-it-i-daresay-he-does-many-that-live-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Deserves it! I daresay he does. Many that live deserve death. And some that die deserve life. Can you give it to them? Then do not be too eager to deal out death in judgement. For even the very wise cannot see all ends." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100888-because-here-s-something-else-that-s-weird-but-true-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 16:49:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by David Foster Wallace  ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100888-because-here-s-something-else-that-s-weird-but-true-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because here's something else that's weird but true: in the day-to day trenches of adult life, there is actually no such thing as atheism. There is no such thing as not worshipping. Everybody worships. The only choice we get is what to worship. And the compelling reason for maybe choosing some sort of god or spiritual-type thing to worship -- be it JC or Allah, be it YHWH or the Wiccan Mother Goddess, or the Four Noble Truths, or some inviolable set of ethical principles -- is that pretty much anything else you worship will eat you alive. If you worship money and things, if they are where you tap real meaning in life, then you will never have enough, never feel you have enough. It's the truth. Worship your body and beauty and sexual allure and you will always feel ugly. And when time and age start showing, you will die a million deaths before they finally grieve you. On one level, we all know this stuff already. It's been codified as myths, proverbs, clichés, epigrams, parables; the skeleton of every great story. The whole trick is keeping the truth up front in daily consciousness." -- David Foster Wallace  ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 16:49:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The really important kind of freedom involves attention, and awareness, and discipline, and effort, and being able truly to care about other people and to sacrifice for them, over and over, in myriad petty little unsexy ways, every day." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97082-there-are-these-two-young-fish-swimming-along-and-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 16:49:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97082-there-are-these-two-young-fish-swimming-along-and-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are these two young fish swimming along and they happen to meet an older fish swimming the other way, who nods at them and says &quot;Morning, boys. How's the water?&quot; And the two young fish swim on for a bit, and then eventually one of them looks over at the other and goes &quot;What the hell is water?" -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118882-in-real-life-i-always-seem-to-have-a-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 16:51:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118882-in-real-life-i-always-seem-to-have-a-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...in real life I always seem to have a hard time winding up a conversation or asking somebody to leave, and sometimes the moment becomes so delicate and fraught with social complexity that I'll get overwhelmed trying to sort out all the different possible ways of saying it and all the different implications of each option and will just sort of blank out and do it totally straight -- 'I want to terminate the conversation and not have you be in my apartment anymore' -- which evidently makes me look either as if I'm very rude and abrupt or as if I'm semi-autistic and have no sense of how to wind up a conversation gracefully...I've actually lost friends this way." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62349-in-dark-times-the-definition-of-good-art-would-seem</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 16:52:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62349-in-dark-times-the-definition-of-good-art-would-seem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In dark times, the definition of good art would seem to be art that locates and applies CPR to those elements of what's human and magical that still live and glow despite the times' darkness. Really good fiction could have as dark a worldview as it wished, but it'd find a way both to depict this world and to illuminate the possibilities for being alive and human in it." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194291-really-good-fiction-could-have-as-dark-a-worldview-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 17:01:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194291-really-good-fiction-could-have-as-dark-a-worldview-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Really good fiction could have as dark a worldview as it wished, but it'd find a way both to depict this world and to illuminate the possibilities for being alive and human in it.&quot;

[Q&amp;A with Larry McCaffery, &lt;i&gt;Review of Contemporary Fiction&lt;/i&gt;, Summer 1993, Vol. 13.2]" -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494064-i-remember-a-period-in-late-adolescence-when-my-mind</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 12:14:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by Julian Barnes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494064-i-remember-a-period-in-late-adolescence-when-my-mind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I remember a period in late adolescence when my mind would make itself drunk with images of adventurousness. This is how it will be when I grow up. I shall go there, do this, discover that, love her, and then her and her and her. I shall live as people in novels live and have lived. Which ones I was not sure, only that passion and danger, ecstasy and despair (but then more ecstasy) would be in attendance. However...who said that thing about &quot;the littleness of life that art exaggerates&quot;? There was a moment in my late twenties when I admitted that my adventurousness had long since petered out. I would never do those things adolescence had dreamt about. Instead, I mowed my lawn, I took holidays, I had my life.

But time...how time first grounds us and then confounds us. We thought we were being mature when we were only being safe. We imagined we were being responsible but we were only being cowardly. What we called realism turned out to be a way of avoiding things rather than facing them. Time...give us enough time and our best-supported decisions will seem wobbly, our certainties whimsical." -- Julian Barnes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3420-even-now-all-possible-feelings-do-not-yet-exist-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 08:25:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3420-even-now-all-possible-feelings-do-not-yet-exist-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even now, all possible feelings do not yet exist, there are still those that lie beyond our capacity and our imagination.  From time to time, when a piece of music no one has ever written or a painting no one has ever painted, or something else impossible to predict, fathom or yet describe takes place, a new feeling enters the world.  And then, for the millionth time in the history of feeling, the heart surges and absorbs the impact." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71213-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-who-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 08:26:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71213-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-who-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time there was a boy who loved a girl, and her laughter was a question he wanted to spend his whole life answering." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299694-she-s-kept-her-love-for-him-as-alive-as-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 08:27:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meg add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299694-she-s-kept-her-love-for-him-as-alive-as-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She’s kept her love for him as alive as the summer they first met. In order to do this, she’s turned life away. Sometimes she subsists for days on water and air. Being the only known complex life-form to do this, she should have a species named after her. Once Uncle Julian told me how the sculptor and painter Alberto Giacometti said that sometimes just to paint a head you have to give up the whole figure. To paint a leaf, you have to sacrifice the whole landscape. It might seem like you’re limiting yourself at first, but after a while you realize that having a quarter-of-an-inch of something you have a better chance of holding on to a certain feeling of the universe than if you pretended to be doing the whole sky.

My mother did not choose a leaf or a head. She chose my father. And to hold on to a certain feeling, she sacrificed the world." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
