<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/311431-daniel-casey]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/311431-daniel-casey" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2007 08:18:42 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7282-there-is-still-that-singular-perfection-and-it-s-perfect-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2007 08:18:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Michael Cunningham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7282-there-is-still-that-singular-perfection-and-it-s-perfect-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is still that singular perfection, and it's perfect in part because it seemed, at the time, so clearly to promise more." -- Michael Cunningham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12698-the-house-had-a-name-and-a-history-the-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 09:38:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12698-the-house-had-a-name-and-a-history-the-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The house had a name and a history; the old gentleman taking his tea would have been delighted to tell you these things: how it had been built under Edward the Sixth, had offered a night's hospitality to the great Elizabeth (whose august person had extended itself upon a huge, magnificent and terribly angular bed which still formed the principal honour of the sleeping apartments), had been a good deal bruised and defaced in Cromwell's wars, and then, under the Restoration, repaired and much enlarged; and how, finally, after having been remodeled and disfigured in the eighteenth century, it had passed into the careful keeping of a shrewd American banker, who had bought it originally because (owing to circumstances too complicated to set forth) it was offered at a great bargain: bought it with much grumbling at its ugliness, its antiquity, its incommodity, and who now, at the end of twenty years, had become conscious of a real aesthetic passion for it, so that he know all its points and would tell you just where to stand to see them in combination and just the hour when the shadows of its various protuberances--which fell so softly upon the warm, weary brickwork--were of the right measure." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20795-the-poor-go-to-war-to-fight-and-die-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2008 19:03:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Plutarch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20795-the-poor-go-to-war-to-fight-and-die-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The poor go to war, to fight and die for the delights, riches, and superfluities of others." -- Plutarch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20797-any-humane-and-reasonable-person-must-conclude-that-if-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2008 19:06:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20797-any-humane-and-reasonable-person-must-conclude-that-if-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any humane and reasonable person must conclude that if the ends, however desireable, are uncertain and the means are horrible and certain, these means must not be employed." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20799-deterence-is-only-a-stay-of-execution-not-a-reprieve</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2008 19:07:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Jonathan Schell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20799-deterence-is-only-a-stay-of-execution-not-a-reprieve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Deterence is only a stay of execution, not a reprieve." -- Jonathan Schell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20801-or-have-i-passed-my-time-in-pouring-words-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2008 19:11:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by William Hazlitt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20801-or-have-i-passed-my-time-in-pouring-words-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Or have I passed my time in pouring words like water into empty sieves, rolling a stone up a hill and then down again, trying to prove an argument in the teeth of facts, and looking for causes in the dark, and not finding them?" -- William Hazlitt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20803-but-it-is-not-the-job-of-truth-to-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2008 19:13:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by William Deresiewicz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20803-but-it-is-not-the-job-of-truth-to-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But it is not the job of truth to make us feel good. It is the job of truth to be true, and it is our job to deal with it." -- William Deresiewicz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20804-for-politics-is-not-just-about-things-necessary-and-eternal</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2008 19:15:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Daniel Gross]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20804-for-politics-is-not-just-about-things-necessary-and-eternal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For politics is not just about things necessary and eternal, nor is it just a matter of good judgment in a given situation. It is also about seeing in concrete terms how things might be otherwise and doing something about it." -- Daniel Gross]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20805-all-this-is-a-preface-to-the-fear-and-uncertainties</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2008 19:16:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20805-all-this-is-a-preface-to-the-fear-and-uncertainties]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All this is a preface to the fear and uncertainties which clamber over a man so that in his silly work he thinks he must be crazy because he is so alone." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1084701-religious-freedom-doesn-t-include-the-freedom-to-disregard-the-law</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 17:13:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Quentin R. Bufogle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1084701-religious-freedom-doesn-t-include-the-freedom-to-disregard-the-law]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Religious freedom doesn't include the freedom to disregard the law and restrict another's freedom to believe and act differently.  No one's forcing Catholic nuns to practice birth control, or priests to wear condoms (good idea tho).  If you really feel your religious beliefs conflict with the mandates of running a business, the solution is simple: Get your ass out of the boardroom and back to the pulpit (where it belongs)." -- Quentin R. Bufogle]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
