<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/313991-jp]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/313991-jp" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 21:52:03 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18375-she-had-lived-in-that-house-fourteen-years-and-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 21:52:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jp add a quote by Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18375-she-had-lived-in-that-house-fourteen-years-and-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had lived in that house fourteen years, and every year she had demanded of John that she be given a pet of some strange exotic breed. Not that she did not have enough animals. She had collected several wild and broken animals that, in a way, had become exotic by their breaking. Their roof would have collapsed from the number of birds who might have lived there if the desert hadn't killed three- quarters of those that tried to cross it. Still every animal that came within a certain radius of that house was given a welcome--the tame, the half born, the wild, the wounded." -- Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70633-the-functional-disenchantment-the-sweet-habit-of-each-other-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 22:29:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jp add a quote by Lorrie Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70633-the-functional-disenchantment-the-sweet-habit-of-each-other-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The functional disenchantment, the sweet habit of each other, had begun to put lines around her mouth, lines that looked like quotation marks--as if everything she said had already been said before...[the cat] was accustomed to much nestling and appreciation and drips from the faucet, though sometimes she would vanish outside, and they would not see her for days, only to spy her later, in the yard, dirty and matted, chomping a vole or eating old snow." -- Lorrie Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82933-later-at-the-sink-in-our-van-mama-rinsed-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 18:20:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jp add a quote by Katherine Dunn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82933-later-at-the-sink-in-our-van-mama-rinsed-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Later, at the sink in our van, Mama rinsed the blue stain and the odd spiders, caterpillars, and stems from the bucket.
 &quot;Not what we usually start with, but we can go again tomorrow. And this will set up nicely in about six, eight jars.&quot;
 The berries were beginning to simmer in the big pot on the back burner. Mama pushed her dark wooden spoon into the foaming berries and cicrcled the wall of the pot slowly.
 I leaned my hot arms on the table and said, &quot;Iphy better not go tomorrow. She got tired today.&quot; I was smelling the berries and Mamaa's sweat, and watching the flex of the blue veins behind her knees.
 &quot;Does them good. The twins always loved picking berries, even more than eating them. Though Elly likes her jam.&quot;
 &quot;Elly doesn't like anything anymore.&quot;
 The knees stiffened and I looked up. The spoon was motionless. Mama stared at the pot.
 &quot;Mama, Elly isn't there anymore. Iphy's changed. Everything's changed. This whole berry business, cooking big meals that nobody comes for, birthday cakes for Arty. It's dumb, Mama. Stop pretending. There isn't any family anymore, Mama.&quot;
 Then she cracked me with the big spoon. It smacked wet and hard across my ear, and the purple-black juice spayed across the table. She started at me, terrified, her mouth and eyes gaping with fear. I stared gaping at her. I broke and ran.
 I went to the generator truck and climbed up to sit by Grandpa. That's the only time Mama ever hit me and I knew I deserved it. I also knew that Mama was too far gone to understand why I deserved it. She'd swung that spoon in a tigerish reflex at blasphemy. But I believed that Arty had turned his back on us, that the twins were broken, that the Chick was lost, that Papa was weak and scared, that Mama was spinning fog, and that I was an adolescent crone sitting in the ruins, watching the beams crumble, and warming myself in the smoke from the funeral pyre. That was how I felt, and I wanted company. I hated Mama for refusing to see enough to be miserable with me. Maybe, too, enough of my child heart was still with me to think that if she would only open her eyes she could fix it all back up like a busted toy." -- Katherine Dunn]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
