<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/31599-bibbikinz-gomez]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/31599-bibbikinz-gomez" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 12:46:53 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57148-if-a-society-permits-one-portion-of-its-citizenry-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 12:46:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[bibbikinz add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57148-if-a-society-permits-one-portion-of-its-citizenry-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a society permits one portion of its citizenry to be menaced or destroyed, then, very soon, no one in that society is safe. The forces thus released in the people can never be held in check, but run their devouring course, destroying the very foundations which it was imagined they would save.

But we are unbelievably ignorant concerning what goes on in our country--to say nothing of what goes on in the rest of the world--and appear to have become too timid to question what we are told. Our failure to trust one another deeply enough to be able to talk to one another has become so great that people with these questions in their hearts do not speak them; our opulence is so pervasive that people who are afraid to lose whatever they think they have persuade themselves of the truth of a lie, and help disseminate it; and God help the innocent here, that man or womn who simply wants to love, and be loved. Unless this would-be lover is able to replace his or her backbone with a steel rod, he or she is doomed. This is no place for love. I know that I am now expected to make a bow in the direction of those millions of unremarked, happy marriages all over America, but I am unable honestly to do so because I find nothing whatever in our moral and social climate--and I am now thinking particularly of the state of our children--to bear witness to their existence. I suspect that when we refer to these happy and so marvelously invisible people, we are simply being nostalgic concerning the happy, simple, God-fearing life which we imagine ourselves once to have lived. In any case, wherever love is found, it unfailingly makes itself felt in the individual, the personal authority of the individual. Judged by this standard, we are a loveless nation. The best that can be said is that some of us are struggling. And what we are struggling against is that death in the heart which leads not only to the shedding of blood, but which reduces human beings to corpses while they live." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263577-to-summarize-the-summary-of-the-summary-people-are-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 05:59:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[bibbikinz add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263577-to-summarize-the-summary-of-the-summary-people-are-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To summarize the summary of the summary: people are a problem." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268048-love-poem-it-s-so-nice-to-wake-up-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2012 05:54:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[bibbikinz add a quote by Richard Brautigan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268048-love-poem-it-s-so-nice-to-wake-up-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love Poem
ـــــــــ
It's so nice
to wake up in the morning
all alone
and not have to tell somebody
you love them
when you don't love them
any more." -- Richard Brautigan]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
