<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/316640-lisa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/316640-lisa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 18:19:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7091-it-has-become-appallingly-obvious-that-our-technology-has-exceeded</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 18:19:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7091-it-has-become-appallingly-obvious-that-our-technology-has-exceeded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It has become appallingly obvious that our technology has exceeded our humanity." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4102-technology-is-the-knack-of-so-arranging-the-world-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 18:21:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Rollo May]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4102-technology-is-the-knack-of-so-arranging-the-world-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Technology is the knack of so arranging the world that we do not experience it." -- Rollo May]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17396-i-long-ago-became-convinced-that-the-most-reliable-source</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 18:23:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by James Lee Burke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17396-i-long-ago-became-convinced-that-the-most-reliable-source]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I long ago became convinced that the most reliable source for arcane and obscure and seemingly unobtainable information does not lie with the government or law enforcement agencies. Apparently neither the CIA nor the military intelligence apparatus inside the Pentagon had even a slight inkling of the Soviet Union's impending collapse, right up to the moment the Kremlin's leaders were trying to cut deals for their memoirs with New York publishers. Or, if a person really wishes a lesson in the subjective nature of official information, he can always call the IRS and ask for help with his tax forms, then call back a half hour later and ask the same questions to a different representative. So where do you go to find a researcher who is intelligent, imaginative, skilled in the use of computers, devoted to discovering the truth, and knowledgeable about science, technology, history, and literature, and who usually works for dirt and gets credit for nothing? After lunch I drove to the city library on Main and asked the reference librarian to find what she could on Junior Crudup." -- James Lee Burke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 18:25:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.

So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3172-and-i-urge-you-to-please-notice-when-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 18:27:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3172-and-i-urge-you-to-please-notice-when-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I urge you to please notice when you are happy, and exclaim or murmur or think at some point, 'If this isn't nice, I don't know what is." -- Kurt Vonnegut Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1035-when-i-look-back-i-am-so-impressed-again-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 18:20:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1035-when-i-look-back-i-am-so-impressed-again-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I look back, I am so impressed again with the life-giving power of literature. If I were a young person today, trying to gain a sense of myself in the world, I would do that again by reading, just as I did when I was young." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
