<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/316771-jeff-teuton]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/316771-jeff-teuton" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 10:46:26 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12305-the-people-cannot-be-all-and-always-well-informed-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 10:46:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12305-the-people-cannot-be-all-and-always-well-informed-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The people cannot be all, and always, well informed. The part which is wrong will be discontented, in proportion to the importance of the facts they misconceive. If they remain quiet under such misconceptions, it is lethargy, the forerunner of death to the public liberty. ... What country before ever existed a century and half without a rebellion? And what country can preserve its liberties if their rulers are not warned from time to time that their people preserve the spirit of resistance? Let them take arms. The remedy is to set them right as to facts, pardon and pacify them. What signify a few lives lost in a century or two? The tree of liberty must be refreshed from time to time with the blood of patriots and tyrants. It is its natural manure." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38371-the-tyrant-dies-and-his-rule-is-over-the-martyr</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 10:46:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Soren Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38371-the-tyrant-dies-and-his-rule-is-over-the-martyr]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The tyrant dies and his rule is over, the martyr dies and his rule begins." -- Soren Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174514-when-the-people-fear-the-government-there-is-tyranny-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 10:54:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by John Basil Barnhill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174514-when-the-people-fear-the-government-there-is-tyranny-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the people fear the government there is tyranny, when the government fears the people there is liberty." -- John Basil Barnhill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17188-bad-men-need-nothing-more-to-compass-their-ends-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 10:54:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by John Stuart Mill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17188-bad-men-need-nothing-more-to-compass-their-ends-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bad men need nothing more to compass their ends, than that good men should look on and do nothing." -- John Stuart Mill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19741-the-means-of-defence-agst-foreign-danger-have-been-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 10:54:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by James Madison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19741-the-means-of-defence-agst-foreign-danger-have-been-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The means of defence agst. foreign danger, have been always the instruments of tyranny at home." -- James Madison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128538-altho-i-rarely-waste-time-in-reading-on-theological-subjects</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 10:55:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128538-altho-i-rarely-waste-time-in-reading-on-theological-subjects]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Altho' I rarely waste time in reading on theological subjects, as mangled by our Pseudo-Christians, yet I can readily suppose Basanistos may be amusing. Ridicule is the only weapon which can be used against unintelligible propositions. Ideas must be distinct before reason can act upon them; and no man ever had a distinct idea of the trinity. It is mere Abracadabra of the mountebanks calling themselves the priests of Jesus. If it could be understood it would not answer their purpose. Their security is in their faculty of shedding darkness, like the scuttlefish, thro' the element in which they move, and making it impenetrable to the eye of a pursuing enemy, and there they will skulk.

[&lt;i&gt;Letter to Francis Adrian Van der Kemp on 30 July 1810 denouncing the Christian doctrine of the Trinity&lt;/i&gt;]" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36602-whereas-it-appeareth-that-however-certain-forms-of-government-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 10:55:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36602-whereas-it-appeareth-that-however-certain-forms-of-government-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whereas it appeareth that however certain forms of government are better calculated than others to protect individuals in the free exercise of their natural rights, and are at the same time themselves better guarded against degeneracy, yet experience hath shewn, that even under the best forms, those entrusted with power have, in time, and by slow operations, perverted it into tyranny; and it is believed that the most effectual means of preventing this would be, to illuminate, as far as practicable, the minds of the people at large, ....whence it becomes expedient for promoting the publick happiness that those persons, whom nature hath endowed with genius and virtue, should be rendered by liberal education worthy to receive, and able to guard the sacred deposit of the rights and liberties of their fellow citizens, and that they should be called to that charge without regard to wealth, birth or accidental condition of circumstance." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94621-some-are-whigs-liberals-democrats-call-them-what-you-please</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 10:55:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94621-some-are-whigs-liberals-democrats-call-them-what-you-please]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some are whigs, liberals, democrats, call them what you please. Others are tories, serviles, aristocrats, &amp;c. The latter fear the people, and wish to transfer all power to the higher classes of society; the former consider the people as the safest depository of power in the last resort; they cherish them therefore, and wish to leave in them all the powers to the exercise of which they are competent." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
