<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/318159-samira]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/318159-samira" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 09:10:07 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410281-i-will-never-buy-a-fish-tank-because-i-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 09:10:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samira add a quote by Jarod Kintz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410281-i-will-never-buy-a-fish-tank-because-i-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will never buy a fish tank, because I don't believe in supporting the funding of aquatic war machines." -- Jarod Kintz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/454548-fat-is-usually-the-first-insult-a-girl-throws-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 06:25:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samira add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/454548-fat-is-usually-the-first-insult-a-girl-throws-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fat’ is usually the first insult a girl throws at another girl when she wants to hurt her.

I mean, is ‘fat’ really the worst thing a human being can be? Is ‘fat’ worse than ‘vindictive’, ‘jealous’, ‘shallow’, ‘vain’, ‘boring’ or ‘cruel’? Not to me; but then, you might retort, what do I know about the pressure to be skinny? I’m not in the business of being judged on my looks, what with being a writer and earning my living by using my brain…

I went to the British Book Awards that evening. After the award ceremony I bumped into a woman I hadn’t seen for nearly three years. The first thing she said to me? ‘You’ve lost a lot of weight since the last time I saw you!’

‘Well,’ I said, slightly nonplussed, ‘the last time you saw me I’d just had a baby.’

What I felt like saying was, ‘I’ve produced my third child and my sixth novel since I last saw you. Aren’t either of those things more important, more interesting, than my size?’ But no – my waist looked smaller! Forget the kid and the book: finally, something to celebrate!

I’ve got two daughters who will have to make their way in this skinny-obsessed world, and it worries me, because I don’t want them to be empty-headed, self-obsessed, emaciated clones; I’d rather they were independent, interesting, idealistic, kind, opinionated, original, funny – a thousand things, before ‘thin’. And frankly, I’d rather they didn’t give a gust of stinking chihuahua flatulence whether the woman standing next to them has fleshier knees than they do. Let my girls be Hermiones, rather than Pansy Parkinsons." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
