<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/318513-rachel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/318513-rachel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 12:05:34 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4959-you-don-t-have-to-burn-books-to-destroy-a-culture</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 12:05:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4959-you-don-t-have-to-burn-books-to-destroy-a-culture]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't have to burn books to destroy a culture. Just get people to stop reading them." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1222-you-cannot-find-peace-by-avoiding-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 12:07:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1222-you-cannot-find-peace-by-avoiding-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You cannot find peace by avoiding life." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53417-a-man-can-know-his-father-or-his-son-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 18:27:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53417-a-man-can-know-his-father-or-his-son-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man can know his father, or his son, and there might still be nothing between them but loyalty and love and mutual incomprehension." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25238-all-morning-i-struggled-with-the-sensation-of-stray-wisps</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2008 09:00:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Diane Setterfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25238-all-morning-i-struggled-with-the-sensation-of-stray-wisps]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All morning I struggled with the sensation of stray wisps of one world seeping through the cracks of another. Do you know the feeling when you start reading a new book before the membrane of the last one has had time to close behind you?  You leave the previous book with ideas and themes -- characters even -- caught in the fibers of your clothes, and when you open the new book, they are still with you." -- Diane Setterfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17254-all-children-mythologise-their-birth-it-is-a-universal-trait</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2008 09:01:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Diane Setterfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17254-all-children-mythologise-their-birth-it-is-a-universal-trait]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All children mythologise their birth. It is a universal trait. You want to know someone? Heart, mind and soul? Ask him to tell you about when he was born. What you get won’t be the truth: it will be a story. And nothing is more telling than a story. " -- Diane Setterfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38225-if-you-are-careful-garp-wrote-if-you-use-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2009 14:35:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38225-if-you-are-careful-garp-wrote-if-you-use-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are careful,' Garp wrote, 'if you use good ingredients, and you don't take any shortcuts, then you can usually cook something very good. Sometimes it is the only worthwhile product you can salvage from a day; what you make to eat. With writing, I find, you can have all the right ingredients, give plenty of time and care, and still get nothing. Also true of love. Cooking, therefore, can keep a person who tries hard sane." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488091-also-when-you-are-young-you-think-you-can-predict</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 15:41:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Julian Barnes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488091-also-when-you-are-young-you-think-you-can-predict]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Also, when you are young, you think you can predict the likely pains and bleaknesses that age might bring. You imagine yourself being lonely, divorced, widowed; children growing away from you, friends dying. You imagine the loss of status, the loss of desire – and desirability. You may go further and consider your own approaching death, which, despite what company you may muster, can only be faced alone. But all this is looking ahead. What you fail to do is look ahead, and then imagine yourself looking back from the future point. Learning the new emotions that time brings. Discovering, for example, that as the witnesses to your life diminish, there is less corroboration, and therefore less certainty, as to what you are or have been. Even if you have assiduously kept records – in words, sound, pictures – you may find that you have attended to the wrong kind of record-keeping. What was the line Adrian used to quote? 'History is that certainty produced at the point where the imperfections of memory meet the inadequacies of documentation." -- Julian Barnes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425317-how-often-do-we-tell-our-own-life-story-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 15:43:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Julian Barnes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425317-how-often-do-we-tell-our-own-life-story-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How often do we tell our own life story? How often do we adjust, embellish, make sly cuts? And the longer life goes on, the fewer are those around to challenge our account, to remind us that our life is not our life, merely the story we have told about our life. Told to others, but&amp;mdash;mainly&amp;mdash;to ourselves." -- Julian Barnes]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
