<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/319593-banshi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/319593-banshi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:05:01 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102850-we-d-start-slow-the-way-we-always-did-because-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:05:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102850-we-d-start-slow-the-way-we-always-did-because-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We'd start slow, the way we always did, because the run, and the game, could go on for awhile. Maybe even forever.
That was the thing. You just never knew. Forever was so many different things. It was always changing, it was what everything was really all about. It was twenty minutes, or a hundred years, or just this instant, or any instant I wished would last and last. But there was only one truth about forever that really mattered, and that was this: it was happening. Right then, as I ran with Wes into that bright sun, and every moment afterwards. Look, there. Now. Now. Now." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147249-life-can-be-long-or-short-it-all-depends-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:05:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147249-life-can-be-long-or-short-it-all-depends-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life can be long or short, it all depends on how you choose to live it. it's like forever, always changing. for any of us our forever could end in an hour, or a hundred years from now. you can never know for sure, so you'd better make every second count. what you have to decide is how you want your life to be. if your forever was ending tomorrow, is this how you'd want to have spent it?" -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102848-okay-he-said-he-took-a-breath-what-would-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:05:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102848-okay-he-said-he-took-a-breath-what-would-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Okay,' he said. He took a breath. 'What would you do, if you could do anything?'
I took a step toward him, closing the space between us. 'This,' I said. And then I kissed him.
Kissed him. There, in the middle of the street, as the world went on around us. Behind me, I knew Jason was still waiting for an explanation, my sister was still lecturing, and that angel still had her eyes skyward, waiting to fly. As for me, I was just trying to get it right, whatever that meant. But now I finally felt I was on my way. Everyone had a forever, but given a choice, this would be mine. The one that began in this moment, with Wes, in a kiss that took my breath away, then gave it back- leaving me astounded, amazed, and most of all, alive." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:15:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that's what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that is holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life.  

A true soul mate is probably the most important person you'll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake.  But to live with a soul mate forever?  Nah. Too painful.  Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then leave.  

A soul mates purpose is to shake you up, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light can get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you have to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185753-i-watched-my-mother-do-what-she-did-best-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:19:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185753-i-watched-my-mother-do-what-she-did-best-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I watched my mother do what she did best, and realized there would never be a way to cut myself from her entirely. No matter how strong or weak I was, she was a part of me, as crucial as my own heart. I would never be strong enough, in all my life, to do without her." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:27:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37490-no-relationship-is-perfect-ever-there-are-always-some-ways</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:30:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37490-no-relationship-is-perfect-ever-there-are-always-some-ways]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No relationship is perfect, ever. There are always some ways you have to bend, to compromise, to give something up in order to gain something greater...The love we have for each other is bigger than these small differences. And that's the key. It's like a big pie chart, and the love in a relationship has to be the biggest piece. Love can make up for a lot." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67484-we-fell-in-love-despite-our-differences-and-once-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:30:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67484-we-fell-in-love-despite-our-differences-and-once-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We fell in love, despite our differences, and once we did, something rare and beautiful was created. For me, love like that has only happened once, and that's why every minute we spent together has been seared in my memory. I'll never forget a single moment of it." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204561-we-re-all-a-little-weird-and-life-is-a-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:35:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204561-we-re-all-a-little-weird-and-life-is-a-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We’re all a little weird. And life is a little weird. And when we find someone whose weirdness is compatible with ours, we join up with them and fall into mutually satisfying weirdness—and call it love—true love." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5402-so-it-s-not-gonna-be-easy-it-s-going-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:37:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5402-so-it-s-not-gonna-be-easy-it-s-going-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So it's not gonna be easy. It's going to be really hard; we're gonna have to work at this everyday, but I want to do that because I want you. I want all of you, forever, everyday. You and me... everyday." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109615-i-love-you-i-am-who-i-am-because-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:37:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109615-i-love-you-i-am-who-i-am-because-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you. I am who I am because of you. You are every reason, every hope, and every dream I've ever had, and no matter what happens to us in the future, everyday we are together is the greatest day of my life. I will always be yours. " -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119270-you-are-my-best-friend-as-well-as-my-lover</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:37:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119270-you-are-my-best-friend-as-well-as-my-lover]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are my best friend as well as my lover, and I do not know which side of you I enjoy the most. I treasure each side, just as I have treasured our life together." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122572-in-a-universe-of-ambiguity-this-kind-of-certainty-comes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:41:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Robert James Waller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122572-in-a-universe-of-ambiguity-this-kind-of-certainty-comes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a universe of ambiguity, this kind of certainty comes only once, and never again, no matter how many lifetimes you live." -- Robert James Waller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12874-analysis-destroys-wholes-some-things-magic-things-are-meant-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:41:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Robert James Waller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12874-analysis-destroys-wholes-some-things-magic-things-are-meant-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Analysis destroys wholes. Some things, magic things, are meant to stay whole. If you look at their pieces, they go away." -- Robert James Waller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119240-it-s-clear-to-me-now-that-i-have-been-moving</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:42:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Robert James Waller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119240-it-s-clear-to-me-now-that-i-have-been-moving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's clear to me now that I have been moving toward you and you toward me for a long time. Though neither of us was aware of the other before we met, there was a kind of mindless certainty bumming blithely along beneath our ignorance that ensured we would come together. Like two solitary birds flying the great prairies by celestial reckoning, all of these years and lifetimes we have been moving toward one another." -- Robert James Waller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:45:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't interest me what you do for a living. I want to know what you ache for, and if you dare to dream of meeting your heart's longing.
It doesn't interest me how old you are. I want to know if you will risk looking like a fool for love, for your dream, for the adventure of being alive. 
It doesn't interest me what planets are squaring your moon. I want to know if you have touched the center of your own sorrow, if you have been opened by life's betrayals or have become shriveled and closed from fear of further pain!I want to know if you can sit with pain, mine or your own, without moving to hide it or fade it, or fix it. 
I want to know if you can be with joy, mine or your own, if you can dance with wildness and let the ecstasy fill you to the tips of your fingers and toes without cautioning us to be careful, to be realistic, to remember the limitations of being human. 
It doesn't interest me if the story you are telling me is true. I want to know if you can disappoint another to be true to yourself; if you can bear the accusation of betrayal and not betray your own soul; if you can be faithlessand therefore trustworthy. 
I want to know if you can see beauty even when it's not pretty, every day,and if you can source your own life from its presence. 
I want to know if you can live with failure, yours and mine, and still stand on the edge of the lake and shout to the silver of the full moon, “Yes!”
It doesn't interest me to know where you live or how much money you have. I want to know if you can get up, after the night of grief and despair, weary and bruised to the bone, and do what needs to be done to feed the children. 
It doesn't interest me who you know or how you came to be here. I want to know if you will stand in the center of the fire with me and not shrink back. 
It doesn't interest me where or what or with whom you have studied. I want to know what sustains you, from the inside, when all else falls away. 
I want to know if you can be alone with yourself and if you truly like the company you keep in the empty moments." -- Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56088-we-all-have-the-potential-to-fall-in-love-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:46:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56088-we-all-have-the-potential-to-fall-in-love-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all have the potential to fall in love a thousand times in our lifetime. It's easy. The first girl I ever loved was someone I knew in sixth grade. Her name was Missy; we talked about horses. The last girl I love will be someone I haven't even met yet, probably. They all count. But there are certain people you love who do something else; they define how you classify what love is supposed to feel like. These are the most important people in your life, and you’ll meet maybe four or five of these people over the span of 80 years. But there’s still one more tier to all this; there is always one person you love who becomes that definition. It usually happens retrospectively, but it happens eventually. This is the person who unknowingly sets the template for what you will always love about other people, even if some of these loveable qualities are self-destructive and unreasonable. The person who defines your understanding of love is not inherently different than anyone else, and they’re often just the person you happen to meet the first time you really, really, want to love someone. But that person still wins. They win, and you lose. Because for the rest of your life, they will control how you feel about everyone else." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131148-i-read-once-that-the-ancient-egyptians-had-fifty-words</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:46:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Brian Andreas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131148-i-read-once-that-the-ancient-egyptians-had-fifty-words]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read once that the ancient Egyptians had fifty words for sand &amp; the Eskimos had a hundred words for snow. I wish I had a thousand words for love, but all that comes to mind is the way you move against me while you sleep &amp; there are no words for that." -- Brian Andreas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198937-i-wish-i-could-freeze-this-moment-right-here-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:51:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198937-i-wish-i-could-freeze-this-moment-right-here-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish I could freeze this moment, right here, right now and live in it forever." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17406-there-comes-a-point-when-you-just-love-someone-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:52:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Laurell K. Hamilton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17406-there-comes-a-point-when-you-just-love-someone-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There comes a point when you just love someone. Not because they're good, or bad, or anything really. You just love them. It doesn't mean you'll be together forever. It doesn't mean you won't hurt each other. It just mean you love them. Sometimes in spite of who they are, and sometimes because of who they are. And you know that they love you, sometimes because of who you are, and sometimes in spite of it." -- Laurell K. Hamilton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105025-have-you-ever-lost-someone-you-love-and-wanted-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:53:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105025-have-you-ever-lost-someone-you-love-and-wanted-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever lost someone you love and wanted one more conversation, one more chance to make up for the time when you thought they would be here forever? If so, then you know you can go your whole life collecting days, and none will outweigh the one you wish you had back." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120624-there-are-two-kinds-of-love-in-the-safe-kind-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:54:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120624-there-are-two-kinds-of-love-in-the-safe-kind-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two kinds of love...in the safe kind you look for someone who's exactly like you. It's what most folks settle for. But then there's the other kind of love. Everyone's born with a ragged edge, and some folks crave that piece that's a perfect fit. You'll search for it forever, if you have to. And if you're lucky enough to find it, it looks so &lt;I&gt;right&lt;/I&gt;, you start to tear at your own seams, thinking, &lt;I&gt;maybe I could look just as perfect&lt;/I&gt;. But then, of course, when you try to get close to their other half, you don't fit anymore. That kind of love...you come out of it a different person than you were when you started." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120767-finding-someone-you-love-and-who-loves-you-back-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:55:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Cecilia Ahern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120767-finding-someone-you-love-and-who-loves-you-back-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finding someone you love and who loves you back is a wonderful, wonderful feeling. But finding a true soul mate is an even better feeling. A soul mate is someone who understands you like no other, loves you like no other, will be there for you forever, no matter what. They say that nothing lasts forever, but I am a firm believer in the fact that for some, love lives on even after we're gone." -- Cecilia Ahern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219819-i-want-all-of-you-forever-you-and-me-everyday</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 09:55:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219819-i-want-all-of-you-forever-you-and-me-everyday]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want all of you, forever, you and me, everyday" -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76393-i-have-a-history-of-making-decisions-very-quickly-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 07:02:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76393-i-have-a-history-of-making-decisions-very-quickly-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have a history of making decisions very quickly about men.  I have always fallen in love fast and without measuring risks.  I have a tendency not only to see the best in everyone, but to assume that everyone is emotionally capable of reaching his highest potential.  I have fallen in love more times than I care to count with the highest potential of a man, rather than with the man himself, and I have hung on to the relationship for a long time (sometimes far too long) waiting for the man to ascend to his own greatness.  Many times in romance I have been a victim of my own optimism." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74646-when-you-re-in-love-you-never-really-know-whether</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 07:03:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Natalie Clifford Barney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74646-when-you-re-in-love-you-never-really-know-whether]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["	When you're in love you never really know whether your elation comes from the qualities of the one you love, or if it attributes them to her; whether the light which surrounds her like a halo comes from you, from her, or from the meeting of your sparks." -- Natalie Clifford Barney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97759-i-knew-in-the-silence-that-followed-that-anything-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 07:04:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97759-i-knew-in-the-silence-that-followed-that-anything-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I knew, in the silence that followed, that anything could happen here. It might be too late: again, I might have missed my chance. But I would at least know I tried, that I took my heart and extended my hand, whatever the outcome.
&quot;Okay,&quot; he said. He took a breath. &quot;What would you do, if you could do anything?&quot;
I took a step toward him, closing the space between us. &quot;This,&quot; I said. And then I kissed him." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104489-he-did-not-care-if-she-was-heartless-vicious-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 07:04:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104489-he-did-not-care-if-she-was-heartless-vicious-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He did not care if she was heartless, vicious and vulgar, stupid and grasping, he loved her. He would rather have misery with one than happiness with the other." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104791-statistically-speaking-there-is-a-65-percent-chance-that-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 07:05:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Scott Dikkers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104791-statistically-speaking-there-is-a-65-percent-chance-that-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Statistically speaking, there is a 65  percent chance that the love of your life is having an affair. Be very suspicious." -- Scott Dikkers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110861-the-very-first-moment-i-beheld-him-my-heart-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 07:06:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Banshi add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110861-the-very-first-moment-i-beheld-him-my-heart-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Very first moment I beheld him, my heart was irrevocably gone." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
