<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/319837-kate]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/319837-kate" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 08:10:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22330-to-live-in-this-world-you-must-be-able-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 08:10:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22330-to-live-in-this-world-you-must-be-able-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["to live in this world

you must be able
to do three things
to love what is mortal;
to hold it

against your bones knowing
your own life depends on it;
and, when the time comes to let it go,
to let it go" -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41428-any-father-must-finally-give-his-child-up-to-the-wilderness</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2013 11:41:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41428-any-father-must-finally-give-his-child-up-to-the-wilderness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any father…must finally give his child up to the wilderness and trust to the providence of God.  It seems almost a cruelty for one generation to beget another when parents can secure so little for their children, so little safety, even in the best circumstances.  Great faith is required to give the child up, trusting God to honor the parents’ love for him by assuring that there will indeed be angels in that wilderness." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184704-every-spirit-passing-through-the-world-fingers-the-tangible-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2013 11:45:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184704-every-spirit-passing-through-the-world-fingers-the-tangible-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every spirit passing through the world fingers the tangible and mars the mutable and finally has come to look and not to buy.  So shoes are worn and hassocks are sat upon and finally everything is left where it was and the spirit passes on, just as the wind in the orchard picks up the leaves from the ground as if there were no other pleasure in the world but brown leaves, as if it would deck, clothe, flesh itself in flourishes of dusty brown apple leaves and then drops them all in a heap at the side of the house and goes on." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186721-you-stand-there-braced-cloud-shadows-race-over-the-buff</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 10:09:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Annie Proulx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186721-you-stand-there-braced-cloud-shadows-race-over-the-buff]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You stand there, braced.  Cloud shadows race over the buff rock stacks as a projected film, casting a queasy, mottled ground rash.  The air hisses and it is no local breeze but the great harsh sweep of wind from the turning of the earth.  The wild country--indigo jags of mountain, grassy plain everlasting, tumbled stones like fallen cities, the flaring roll of sky--provokes a spiritual shudder.  It is like a deep note that cannot be heard but is felt, it is like a claw in the gut...
...Other cultures have camped here a while and disappeared.  Only earth and sky matter.  Only the endlessly repeated flood of morning light.  You begin to see that God does not owe us much beyond that." -- Annie Proulx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/652792-vulnerability-sounds-like-truth-and-feels-like-courage-truth-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 14:21:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Brené Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/652792-vulnerability-sounds-like-truth-and-feels-like-courage-truth-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Vulnerability sounds like truth and feels like courage. Truth and courage aren't always comfortable, but they're never weakness." -- Brené Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27786-life-is-short-and-often-stingy-feast-the-heart-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 14:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Reynolds Price]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27786-life-is-short-and-often-stingy-feast-the-heart-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is short and often stingy; feast the heart with what it craves, short of cruelty, and let the world wonder." -- Reynolds Price]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/805387-why-are-we-so-afraid-of-the-body-is-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 16:34:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Emily Rapp]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/805387-why-are-we-so-afraid-of-the-body-is-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why are we so afraid of the body? Is it because it's a mess, unpredictable, mortal, unreliable? We take pains to perfect it, to keep it healthy, but we probably wouldn't go to such extremes if we weren't scared to death to lose it. A paradox: we pretend we don't need it, that it's our minds that matter, and yet the body is the thing we can't ignore and that knocks our thinking minds flat to the floor." -- Emily Rapp]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179969-compassion-is-not-a-relationship-between-the-healer-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 16:44:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179969-compassion-is-not-a-relationship-between-the-healer-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Compassion is not a relationship between the healer and the wounded. It's a relationship between equals. Only when we know our own darkness well can we be present with the darkness of others. Compassion becomes real when we recognize our shared humanity." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/763073-parenthood-abruptly-catapults-us-into-a-permanent-relationship-with-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 09:50:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Andrew Solomon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/763073-parenthood-abruptly-catapults-us-into-a-permanent-relationship-with-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Parenthood abruptly catapults us into a permanent relationship with a stranger, and the more alien the stranger, the stronger the whiff of negativity. We depend on the guarantee in our children's faces that we will not die. Children whose defining quality annihilates that fantasy of immortality are a particular insult; we must love them for themselves, and not for the best of ourselves in them, and that is a great deal harder to do. Loving our own children is an exercise for the imagination." -- Andrew Solomon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/763076-defective-is-an-adjective-that-has-long-been-deemed-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 09:58:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Andrew Solomon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/763076-defective-is-an-adjective-that-has-long-been-deemed-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Defective is an adjective that has long been deemed too freighted for liberal discourse, but the medical terms that have supplanted it—illness, syndrome, condition—can be almost equally pejorative in their discreet way. We often use illness to disparage a way of being, and identity to validate that same way of being. This is a false dichotomy. In physics, the Copenhagen interpretation defines energy/matter as behaving sometimes like a wave and sometimes like a particle, which suggests that it is both, and posits that it is our human limitation to be unable to see both at the same time. The Nobel Prize–winning physicist Paul Dirac identified how light appears to be a particle if we ask a particle-like question, and a wave if we ask a wavelike question. A similar duality obtains in this matter of self. Many conditions are both illness and identity, but we can see one only when we obscure the other. Identity politics refutes the idea of illness, while medicine shortchanges identity. Both are diminished by this narrowness.

Physicists gain certain insights from understanding energy as a wave, and other insights from understanding it as a particle, and use quantum mechanics to reconcile the information they have gleaned. Similarly, we have to examine illness and identity, understand that observation will usually happen in one domain or the other, and come up with a syncretic mechanics. We need a vocabulary in which the two concepts are not opposites, but compatible aspects of a condition. The problem is to change how we assess the value of individuals and of lives, to reach for a more ecumenical take on healthy. Ludwig Wittgenstein said, ―All I know is what I have words for.‖ The absence of words is the absence of intimacy; these experiences are starved for language." -- Andrew Solomon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/822086-there-is-something-ironic-in-prejudice-against-the-disabled-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 10:05:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Andrew Solomon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/822086-there-is-something-ironic-in-prejudice-against-the-disabled-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is something ironic in prejudice against the disabled and their families, because their plight might befall anybody. Straight men are unlikely to wake up gay one morning, and white children don't become black; but any of us could be disabled in an instant. People with disabilities make up the largest minority in America; they constitute 15 percent of the population, though only 15 percent of those were born with their disability and about a third are over sixty-five. Worldwide, some 550 million people are disabled. The disability-rights scholar Tobin Siebers has written, &quot;The cycle of life runs in actuality from disability to temporary ability back to disablity, and that only if you are among the most fortunate." -- Andrew Solomon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/822348-did-i-think-then-or-do-i-believe-later-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 18:44:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Reynolds Price]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/822348-did-i-think-then-or-do-i-believe-later-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did I think then, or do I believe later, that the vision was in any sense a direct call to me from God or some other intelligent force in nature? Was it a gesture uniquely intended to draw me near? Near to whom and for what? Am I ready to say, at this late point in my life, that I was singled out in childhood for special attention from God?
    No, I'm not. I think it's possible that such revelations await a good many people who are lucky enough, or careful enough, to spend solitary time in feasible places and to be prepared-consciously or accidentally-to listen to a widely available transmission." -- Reynolds Price]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11316-i-had-been-my-whole-life-a-bell-and-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 12:20:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11316-i-had-been-my-whole-life-a-bell-and-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had been my whole life a bell, and never knew it until at that moment I was lifted and struck." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/344844-the-universe-that-suckled-us-is-a-monster-that-does</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 12:21:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/344844-the-universe-that-suckled-us-is-a-monster-that-does]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The universe that suckled us is a monster that does not care if we live or die--it does not care if it itself grinds to a halt. It is a beast running on chance and death, careening from nowhere to nowhere. It is fixed and blind, a robot programmed to kill. We are free and seeing; we can only try to outwit it at every turn to save our lives." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/827770-what-geomancy-reads-what-the-windblown-sand-writes-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 12:27:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/827770-what-geomancy-reads-what-the-windblown-sand-writes-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What geomancy reads what the windblown sand writes on the desert rock? I read there that all things live by a generous power and dance to a mighty tune; or I read there all things are scattered and hurled, that our every arabesque and grand jete is a frantic variation on our one free fall." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/827790-i-don-t-know-what-it-is-about-fecundity-that-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 12:58:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/827790-i-don-t-know-what-it-is-about-fecundity-that-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know what it is about fecundity that so appalls. I suppose it is the teeming evidence that birth and growth, which we value, are ubiquitous and blind, that life itself is so astonshingly cheap, that nature is as careless as it is bountiful, and that with extravagence goes a crushing waste that will one day include our own cheap lives, Henle's loops and all. Every glistening egg is a memento mori." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/828950-that-something-is-everywhere-and-always-amiss-is-part-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 08:38:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/828950-that-something-is-everywhere-and-always-amiss-is-part-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That something is everywhere and always amiss is part of the very stuff of creation. It is as though each clay form had baked into it, a blue streak of nonbeing, a shaded emptiness like a bubble that not only shapes its very structure but that also causes it to list and ultimately explode. We could have planned things more mercifully, perhaps, but our plan would never get off the drawing board until we agreed to the very comprising terms that are the only ones that being offers." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/837870-the-death-of-self-of-which-the-great-writers-speak</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 14:19:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/837870-the-death-of-self-of-which-the-great-writers-speak]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The death of self of which the great writers speak is no violent act. It is merely the joining of the great rock heart of the earth in its roll. It is merely the slow cessation of the will's spirits and the intellect's chatter: it is waiting like a hollow bell with a stilled tongue. Fuge, tace, quiesce. The waiting itself is the thing." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160967-we-have-not-yet-encountered-any-god-who-is-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 14:21:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160967-we-have-not-yet-encountered-any-god-who-is-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have not yet encountered any god who is as merciful as a man who flicks a beetle over on its feet." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/821707-the-mockingbird-took-a-single-step-into-the-air-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 14:25:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/821707-the-mockingbird-took-a-single-step-into-the-air-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...The mockingbird took a single step into the air and dropped. His wings were still folded against his sides as though he were singing from a limb and not falling, accelerating thirty-two feet per second, through empty air. Just a breath before he would have been dashed to the ground, he unfurled his wings with exact, deliberate care, revealing the broad bars of white, spread his elegant white-banded tail, and so floated onto the grass. I had just rounded a corner when his insouciant step caught my eye; there was no one else in sight. The fact of his free fall was like the old philosophical conundrum about the tree that falls in the forest. The answer must be, I think, that beauty and grace are performed whether or not we will or sense them. The least we can do is try to be there." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706704-i-center-down---i-retreat-not-inside-myself-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 14:28:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706704-i-center-down---i-retreat-not-inside-myself-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I center down - I retreat, not inside myself, but outside myself. ... Self-forgetfulness is tremendously invigorating.  I wonder if we don't waste most of our energy just by spending every waking minute saying hello to ourselves." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/743490-the-groove-is-so-mysterious-we-re-born-with-it-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2013 04:56:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Lynda Barry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/743490-the-groove-is-so-mysterious-we-re-born-with-it-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The groove is so mysterious. We're born with it and we lose it and the world seems to split apart before our eyes into stupid and cool. When we get it back, the world unifies around us, and both stupid and cool fall away.
I am grateful to those who are keepers of the groove. The babies and the grandmas who hang on to it and help us remember when we forget that any kind of dancing is better than no dancing at all." -- Lynda Barry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/899485-what-is-it-the-ordinary-is-extraordinary-the-ordinary-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2013 05:06:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Lynda Barry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/899485-what-is-it-the-ordinary-is-extraordinary-the-ordinary-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is it? The ordinary is EXTRAORDINARY. The ordinary is extraordinary. The ordinary is the thing we want back when someone we love dies. When someone dies or leaves or falls out of love with us. We call it &quot;little things&quot;. We say, &quot;it's the little things I miss most.&quot; The ordinary things. It's the little thing that brings them back to us unexpectedly. We say &quot;reminds us&quot; but it is more than reminding-it's a conflagration-it's an inundation-Both fire and flood is memory. It's spark and breach so ordinary we do not question it. The atom split. The little thing." -- Lynda Barry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/802793-glenn-used-to-say-the-reason-you-can-t-really-imagine</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 11:50:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/802793-glenn-used-to-say-the-reason-you-can-t-really-imagine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Glenn used to say the reason you can't really imagine yourself being dead was that as soon as you say, &quot;I'll be dead,&quot; you've said the word I, and so you're still alive inside the sentence. And that's how people got the idea of immortality of the soul - it was a consequence of grammar. And so was God, because as soon as there's a past tense, there has to be a past before the past, and you keep going back in time until you get to I don't know, and that's what God is. It's what you don't know - the dark, the hidden, the underside of the visible, and all because we have grammar, and grammar would be impossible without the FoxP2 gene; so God is a brain mutation, and that gene is the same one birds need for singing. So music is built in, Glenn said: It's knitted into us. It would be very hard to amputate it because it's an essential part of us, like water." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916939-thus-on-predator-day-we-meditate-on-the-alpha-predator</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 11:54:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916939-thus-on-predator-day-we-meditate-on-the-alpha-predator]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thus on Predator Day we meditate on the Alpha Predator aspects of God. The suddenness and ferocity with which an apprehension of the Divine may appear to us; our smallness and fearfulness-may I say, our Mouselikeness-in the face of such Power; our feelings of individual annihilation in the brightness of that splendid Light. God walks in the tender dawn Gardens of the mind, but He also prowls in its night Forests. He is not a tame Being, my Friends: he is a wild Being, and cannot be summoned and controlled like a Dog.&quot;-Adam One" -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916945-dear-diplodicus-dear-pterosaur-dear-trilobite-dear-mastodon-dear-dodo</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 11:58:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916945-dear-diplodicus-dear-pterosaur-dear-trilobite-dear-mastodon-dear-dodo]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dear Diplodicus; dear Pterosaur; dear Trilobite; dear Mastodon, dear Dodo, dear Great Auk, dear Passenger Pigeon, dear Panda, dear Whooping Crane; and all you countless others who have played in this our shared Garden in your day: be with us at this time of trial, and strengthen our resolve. Like you, we have enjoyed the air and the sunlight and the moonlight on the water; like you, we have heard the call of the seasons and have answered them. Like you, we have replenished the Earth. And like you, we must now witness the end of our Species, and pass from Earthly view.&quot; -Adam One" -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/958748-god-s-grace-is-not-defined-as-god-being-forgiving-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 08:07:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Nadia Bolz-Weber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/958748-god-s-grace-is-not-defined-as-god-being-forgiving-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God's grace is not defined as God being forgiving to us even though we sin.  Grace is when God is a source of wholeness, which makes up for my failings.  My failings hurt me and others and even the planet, and God's grace to me is that my brokenness is not the final word ... it's that God makes beautiful things out of even my own shit.  Grace isn't about God creating humans and flawed beings and then acting all hurt when we inevitably fail and then stepping in like the hero to grant us grace - like saying, &quot;Oh, it's OK, I'll be the good guy and forgive you.&quot;  It's God saying, &quot;I love the world too much to let your sin define you and be the final word.  I am a God who makes all things new." -- Nadia Bolz-Weber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/964170-the-movement-in-our-relationship-to-god-is-always-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 08:08:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Nadia Bolz-Weber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/964170-the-movement-in-our-relationship-to-god-is-always-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The movement in our relationship to God is always from God to us. Always. We can't, through our piety or goodness, move closer to God. God is always coming near to us. Most especially in the Eucharist and in the stranger." -- Nadia Bolz-Weber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1008676-the-life-changing-seems-always-bracketed-by-the-mundane-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 08:23:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Nadia Bolz-Weber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1008676-the-life-changing-seems-always-bracketed-by-the-mundane-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The life changing seems always bracketed by the mundane. The quotidian wrapped around the profound, like plain brown paper concealing the emotional version of an improvised explosive device. Then, in a single interminable moment, when we discover the bomb, absolutely everything changes. But when we recall it from our now forever-changed lives, when we start  with the plain brown wrapping, it looks like every other package, every other morning, every other walk." -- Nadia Bolz-Weber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1008687-singing-in-the-midst-of-evil-is-what-it-means</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 08:31:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Nadia Bolz-Weber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1008687-singing-in-the-midst-of-evil-is-what-it-means]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Singing in the midst of evil is what it means to be disciples. Like Mary Magdalene, the reason we stand and weep and listen for Jesus is because we, like Mary, are bearers of resurrection, we are made new. On the third day, Jesus rose again, and we do not need to be afraid. To sing to God amidst sorrow is to defiantly proclaim, like Mary Magdalene did to the apostles, and like my friend Don did at Dylan Klebold's funeral,t hat death is not the final word. To defiantly say, once again, that a light shines in the darkness and the darkness cannot, will not, shall not overcome it. And so, evil be damned, because even as we go to the grave, we still make our song alleluia. Alleluia. Alleluia." -- Nadia Bolz-Weber]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
