<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/321220-jessica]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/321220-jessica" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 07:20:19 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47882-to-crave-and-to-have-are-as-like-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 07:20:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47882-to-crave-and-to-have-are-as-like-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To crave and to have are as like as a thing and its shadow. For when does a berry break upon the tongue as sweetly as when one longs to taste it, and when is the taste refracted into so many hues and savors of ripeness and earth, and when do our senses know any thing so utterly as when we lack it? And here again is a foreshadowing -- the world will be made whole. For to wish for a hand on one's hair is all but to feel it. So whatever we may lose, very craving gives it back to us again." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/441532-so-thoroughly-and-sincerely-are-we-compelled-to-live-reverencing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2011 12:36:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/441532-so-thoroughly-and-sincerely-are-we-compelled-to-live-reverencing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So thoroughly and sincerely are we compelled to live, reverencing our life, and denying the possibility of change. This is the only way, we say; but there are as many ways as there can be drawn radii from one centre." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456945-wasn-t-it-better-if-they-kept-this-desire-to-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 12:33:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456945-wasn-t-it-better-if-they-kept-this-desire-to-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wasn't it better if they kept this desire to see each other hidden within them, and never actually got together?  That way, there would always be hope in their hearts.  That hope would be a small, yet vital flame that warmed them to their core-- a tiny flame to cup one's hands around and protect from the wind, a flame that the violent winds of reality might easily extinguish." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470575-most-people-are-not-looking-for-provable-truths-as-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 12:34:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470575-most-people-are-not-looking-for-provable-truths-as-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most people are not looking for provable truths. As you said, truth is often accompanied by intense pain, and almost no one is looking for painful truths. What people need is beautiful, comforting stories that make them feel as if their lives have some meaning. Which is where religion comes from." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464973-what-we-call-the-present-is-given-shape-by-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 12:34:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464973-what-we-call-the-present-is-given-shape-by-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What we call the present is given shape by an accumulation of the past." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464293-our-memory-is-made-up-of-our-individual-memories-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 12:34:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464293-our-memory-is-made-up-of-our-individual-memories-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our memory is made up of our individual memories and our collective memories.  The two are intimately linked. And history is our collective memory.  If our collective memory is taken from us - is rewritten - we lose the ability to sustain our true selves." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484086-there-was-just-one-moon-that-familiar-yellow-solitary-moon</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 12:39:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484086-there-was-just-one-moon-that-familiar-yellow-solitary-moon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was just one moon. That familiar, yellow, solitary moon. The same moon that silently floated over fields of pampas grass, the moon that rose--a gleaming, round saucer--over the calm surface of lakes, that tranquilly beamed down on the rooftops of fast-asleep houses. The same moon that brought the high tide to shore, that softly shone on the fur of animals and enveloped and protected travelers at night. The moon that, as a crescent, shaved slivers from the soul--or, as a new moon, silently bathed the earth in its own loneliness. THAT moon." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/336235-there-is-nothing-in-the-world-so-difficult-as-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 04:48:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Anthony Trollope]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/336235-there-is-nothing-in-the-world-so-difficult-as-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing in the world so difficult as that task of making up one's mind. Who is there that has not longed that the power and privilege of selection among alternatives should be taken away from him in some important crisis of his life, and that his conduct should be arranged for him, either this way or that, by some divine power if it were possible, - by some patriarchal power in the absence of divinity, - or by chance, even, if nothing better than chance could be found to do it? But no one dares to cast the die, and to go honestly by the hazard. There must be the actual necessity of obeying the die, before even the die can be of any use." -- Anthony Trollope]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560464-what-if-good-institutions-were-in-fact-the-product-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 14:05:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560464-what-if-good-institutions-were-in-fact-the-product-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What if good institutions were in fact the product of good intentions? What if the cynicism that is supposed to be rigor and the acquisitiveness that is supposed to be realism are making us forget the origins of the greatness we lay claim to - power and wealth as secondary consequences of the progress of freedom, or, as Whitman would prefer, Democracy?" -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560465-the-locus-of-the-human-mystery-is-perception-of-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 14:07:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560465-the-locus-of-the-human-mystery-is-perception-of-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The locus of the human mystery is perception of this world. From it proceeds every thought, every art." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560468-to-recognize-our-bias-toward-error-should-teach-us-modesty</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 14:10:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560468-to-recognize-our-bias-toward-error-should-teach-us-modesty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To recognize our bias toward error should teach us modesty and reflection, and to forgive it should help us avoid the inhumanity of thinking we ourselves are not as fallible as those who, in any instance, seem most at fault. Science can give us knowledge, but it cannot give us wisdom. Nor can religion, until it puts aside nonsense and distraction and becomes itself again." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560469-when-we-condescend-when-we-act-consistently-with-a-sense</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 14:13:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560469-when-we-condescend-when-we-act-consistently-with-a-sense]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...when we condescend, when we act consistently with a sense of the character of people in general which demeans them, we impoverish them AND ourselves, and preclude our having a part in the creation of the highest wealth, the testimony to the mysterious beauty of life we all value in psalms and tragedies and epics and meditations, in short stories and novels." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560470-but-there-is-something-about-human-beings-that-too-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 14:14:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560470-but-there-is-something-about-human-beings-that-too-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But there is something about human beings that too often makes our love for the world look very much like hatred for it." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560472-our-humanity-consists-in-the-fact-that-we-do-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 14:15:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560472-our-humanity-consists-in-the-fact-that-we-do-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our humanity consists in the fact that we do more than survive, that a great part of what we do confers no survival benefit in terms presumably salient from the Pleistocene point of view." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560474-we-are-in-the-process-of-disabling-our-most-distinctive</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 14:16:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560474-we-are-in-the-process-of-disabling-our-most-distinctive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are in the process of disabling our most distinctive achievement - our educational system - in the name of making the country more like itself." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560475-earthly-nature-may-be-parsimonious-but-the-human-mind-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 14:17:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560475-earthly-nature-may-be-parsimonious-but-the-human-mind-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Earthly nature may be parsimonious, but the human mind is prodigal, itself an anomaly that in its wealth of error as well as of insight is exceptional, utterly unique as far as we know, properly an object of wonder." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560476-if-we-do-not-know-the-character-of-being-itself</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 14:19:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560476-if-we-do-not-know-the-character-of-being-itself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we do not know the character of being itself - I have never seen anyone suggest that we do know it - then there is an inevitable superficiality in any claim to an exhaustive description of anything that participates in being. And the assertion of the existence, or the nonexistence, of God is the ultimate exhaustive description." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560477-so-perhaps-the-very-idea-of-explanation-is-an-error</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 14:19:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560477-so-perhaps-the-very-idea-of-explanation-is-an-error]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So perhaps the very idea of explanation is an error of anthropomorphism when it is applied to things that do not involve human intention." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/583788-delphine-witnessed-awful-things-occurring-to-other-humans-worse-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 08:26:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/583788-delphine-witnessed-awful-things-occurring-to-other-humans-worse-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Delphine witnessed awful things occurring to other humans. Worse than that, she was powerless to alter their fate. It would be that way all her life--disasters, falling like chairs all around her, falling so close they disarranged her hair, but not touching her." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/583792-upon-walking-into-eva-s-kitchen-something-profound-happened-to-delphine</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 08:29:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/583792-upon-walking-into-eva-s-kitchen-something-profound-happened-to-delphine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Upon walking into Eva's kitchen, something profound happened to Delphine. She experienced a fabulous expansion of being. Light-headed, she felt a swooping sensation and then a quiet, as though she'd settled like a bird." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/583793-as-delphine-watched-into-her-head-there-popped-a-strange</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 08:31:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/583793-as-delphine-watched-into-her-head-there-popped-a-strange]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As Delphine watched, into her head there popped a strange notion: the idea that perhaps strongly experienced moments, as when Eva turned and the sun met her hair and for that one instant the symbol blazed out, those particular moments were eternal. Those moments actually went somewhere. Into a file of moments that existed out of time's range and could not be pilfered by God." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/583795-when-small-towns-find-they-cannot-harm-the-strangest-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 08:33:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/583795-when-small-towns-find-they-cannot-harm-the-strangest-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When small towns find they cannot harm the strangest of their members, when eccentrics show resilience, they are eventually embraced and even cherished." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/583801-when-she-shut-her-eyes-her-mind-grew-alert-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 08:37:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/583801-when-she-shut-her-eyes-her-mind-grew-alert-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When she shut her eyes, her mind grew alert. Her senses opened. All around her, she felt how quickly things formed and were consumed. How there was so much blind feeling. It was going on beyond the wall of her sight, out of her control. Unheard, unnoticed, the blood dropped into her hands and feet, so that she was anchored. Which she was glad for, because the light was so feeble and the blackness so strong that she felt as though she could drift away like a boat of skin, never to return, leaving only her crumpled dress." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259369-she-had-always-been-a-reader-but-now-she-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 08:38:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259369-she-had-always-been-a-reader-but-now-she-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had always been a reader… but now she was obsessed. Since her discovery of the book hoard downstairs from her job, she’d been caught up in one such collection of people and their doings after the next…The pleasure of this sort of life – bookish, she supposed it might be called, a reading life – had made her isolation into a rich and even subversive thing. She inhabited one consoling or horrifying persona after another…That she was childless and husbandless and poor meant less once she picked up a book. Her mistakes disappeared into it. She lived with an invented force." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/583803-our-songs-travel-the-earth-we-sing-to-one-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 08:39:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/583803-our-songs-travel-the-earth-we-sing-to-one-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our songs travel the earth. We sing to one another. Not a single note is ever lost and no song is original. They all come from the same place and go back to a time when only the stones howled." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/631535-so-i-went-on-on-my-own-deeper-and-deeper-into-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 18:37:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by A.S. Byatt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/631535-so-i-went-on-on-my-own-deeper-and-deeper-into-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So—I went on, on my own—deeper and deeper into the silent Tunnel of the Ride—not so sure of where I was and yet not anxious either, not concerned about my companions nor even about the nearness of—certain friends. The trees were beech, and the buds, just breaking, fiercely brilliant, and the new, the renewed light on them—intermittent diamond—but the depths were dark, a silent Nave. And no birds sang, or I heard none, no woodpecker tapped, no thrush whistled or hopped. And I listened to the increasing Quiet—and my horse went softly on the beech-mast—which was wet after rain—not crackling, a little sodden, not wet enough to plash. And I had the sensation, common enough, at least to me, that I was moving out of time, that the way, narrow and dark-dappled, stretched away indifferently before and behind, and that I was who I had been and what I would become—all at once, all wound in one—and I moved onward indifferently, since it was all one, whether I came or went, or remained still. Now to me such moments are poetry. [Randolph Henry Ash]" -- A.S. Byatt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134198-what-is-it-my-dear-ah-how-can-we-bear</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 18:38:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by A.S. Byatt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134198-what-is-it-my-dear-ah-how-can-we-bear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is it my dear?&quot;

Ah, how can we bear it?&quot;

Bear what?&quot;

This. For so short a time. How can we sleep this time away?&quot;

We can be quiet together, and pretend - since it is only the beginning - that we have all the time in the world.&quot;

And every day we shall have less. And then none.&quot;

Would you rather, therefore, have had nothing at all?&quot;

No. This is where I have always been coming to. Since my time began. And when I go away from here, this will be the mid-point, to which everything ran, before, and from which everything will run. But now, my love, we are here, we are now, and those other times are running elsewhere." -- A.S. Byatt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175779-coherence-and-closure-are-deep-human-desires-that-are-presently</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 18:39:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by A.S. Byatt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175779-coherence-and-closure-are-deep-human-desires-that-are-presently]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Coherence and closure are deep human desires that are presently unfashionable. But they are always both frightening and enchantingly desirable. &quot;Falling in love,&quot; characteristically, combs the appearances of the word, and of the particular lover's history, out of a random tangle and into a coherent plot." -- A.S. Byatt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123837-vocabularies-are-crossing-circles-and-loops-we-are-defined-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 18:40:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by A.S. Byatt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123837-vocabularies-are-crossing-circles-and-loops-we-are-defined-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Vocabularies are crossing circles and loops. We are defined by the lines we choose to cross or to be confined by." -- A.S. Byatt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/631543-it-is-possible-for-a-writer-to-make-or-remake</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 18:46:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by A.S. Byatt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/631543-it-is-possible-for-a-writer-to-make-or-remake]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is possible for a writer to make, or remake at least, for a reader, the primary pleasures of eating, or drinking, or looking on, or sex. Novels have their obligatory tour-de-force, the green-flecked gold omelette &lt;i&gt;aux fines herbes&lt;/i&gt;, melting into buttery formlessness and tasting of summer, or the creamy human haunch, firm and warm, curved back to reveal a hot hollow, a crisping hair or two, the glimpsed sex. They do not habitually elaborate on the equally intense pleasure of reading. There are obvious reasons for this, the most obvious being the regressive nature of the pleasure, a &lt;i&gt;mise-en-abîme&lt;/i&gt; even, where words draw attention to the power and delight of words, and so &lt;i&gt;ad infinitum&lt;/i&gt;, thus making the imagination experience something papery and dry, narcissistic and yet disagreeably distanced, without the immediacy of sexual moisture or the scented garnet glow of a good burgundy. And yet, natures such as Roland's are at their most alert and heady when reading is violently yet steadily alive. (What an amazing word &quot;heady&quot; is, &lt;i&gt;en passant&lt;/i&gt;, suggesting both acute sensuous alertness and its opposite, the pleasure of the brain as opposed to the viscera—though each is implicated in the other, as we know very well, with both, when they are working.)" -- A.S. Byatt]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
