<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/321314-jeff-scott]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/321314-jeff-scott" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 15:57:09 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 15:57:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be the change that you wish to see in the world." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 15:57:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opposite of love is not hate, it's indifference. The opposite of art is not ugliness, it's indifference. The opposite of faith is not heresy, it's indifference. And the opposite of life is not death, it's indifference." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1776-remember-if-the-time-should-come-when-you-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 15:58:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1776-remember-if-the-time-should-come-when-you-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember, if the time should come when you have to make a choice between what is right and what is easy, remember what happened to a boy who was good, and kind, and brave, because he strayed across the path of Lord Voldemort.  Remember Cedric Diggory." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 15:59:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finish each day and be done with it. You have done what you could.  Some blunders and absurdities no doubt crept in; forget them as soon as you can. Tomorrow is a new day.  You shall begin it serenely and with too high a spirit to be encumbered with your old nonsense." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5253-try-to-understand-men-if-you-understand-each-other-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 16:42:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5253-try-to-understand-men-if-you-understand-each-other-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Try to understand men. If you understand each other you will be kind to each other. Knowing a man well never leads to hate and almost always leads to love." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 16:02:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always imagined that Paradise will be a kind of library." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146496-what-does-reading-do-you-can-learn-almost-everything-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 16:42:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Jose Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146496-what-does-reading-do-you-can-learn-almost-everything-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What does reading do, You can learn almost everything from reading, But I read too, So you must know something, Now I'm not so sure, You'll have to read differently then, How, The same method doesn't work for everyone, each person has to invent his or her own, whichever suits them best, some people spend their entire lives reading but never get beyond reading the words on the page, they don't understand that the words are merely stepping stones placed across a fast-flowing river, and the reason they're there is so that we can reach the farther shore, it's the other side that matters, Unless, Unless what, Unless those rivers don't have just two shores but many, unless each reader is his or her own shore, and that shore is the only shore worth reaching." -- Jose Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215253-chaos-is-merely-order-waiting-to-be-deciphered</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 16:42:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by José Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215253-chaos-is-merely-order-waiting-to-be-deciphered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chaos is merely order waiting to be deciphered" -- José Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111976-reading-a-novel-war-and-peace-for-example-is-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2008 10:55:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111976-reading-a-novel-war-and-peace-for-example-is-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reading a novel, War and Peace for example, is no Catnap. Because a novel is so long, reading one is like being married forever to somebody nobody knows or cares about." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13719-we-are-what-we-pretend-to-be-so-we-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2008 10:55:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13719-we-are-what-we-pretend-to-be-so-we-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are what we pretend to be, so we must be careful about what we pretend to be." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26979-as-for-literary-criticism-in-general-i-have-long-felt</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2008 10:57:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26979-as-for-literary-criticism-in-general-i-have-long-felt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As for literary criticism in general: I have long felt that any reviewer who expresses rage and loathing for a novel or a play or a poem is preposterous. He or she is like a person who has put on full armor and attacked a hot fudge sundae or a banana split." -- kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 15:45:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hello babies. Welcome to Earth. It's hot in the summer and cold in the winter. It's round and wet and crowded. On the outside, babies, you've got a hundred years here. There's only one rule that I know of, babies-&quot;God damn it, you've got to be kind." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55596-we-are-healthy-only-to-the-extent-that-our-ideas</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2008 11:01:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55596-we-are-healthy-only-to-the-extent-that-our-ideas]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are healthy only to the extent that our ideas are humane." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23053-the-only-way-you-can-write-the-truth-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2008 18:43:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23053-the-only-way-you-can-write-the-truth-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only way you can write the truth is to assume that what you set down will never be read. Not by any other person, and not even by yourself at some later date. Otherwise you begin excusing yourself. You must see the writing as emerging like a long scroll of ink from the index finger of your right hand; you must see your left hand erasing it." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115962-there-s-nothing-like-a-shovel-full-of-dirt-to-encourage</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2008 18:44:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115962-there-s-nothing-like-a-shovel-full-of-dirt-to-encourage]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's nothing like a shovel full of dirt to encourage literacy." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2009 10:20:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.

So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55064-i-guess-there-are-never-enough-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2009 16:43:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55064-i-guess-there-are-never-enough-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I guess there are never enough books." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33327-it-s-so-much-darker-when-a-light-goes-out-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2009 16:43:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33327-it-s-so-much-darker-when-a-light-goes-out-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's so much darker when a light goes out than it would have been if it had never shone." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18481-and-it-never-failed-that-during-the-dry-years-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2009 16:43:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18481-and-it-never-failed-that-during-the-dry-years-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And it never failed that during the dry years the people forgot about the rich years, and during the wet years they lost all memory of the dry years. It was always that way." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 07:53:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I say is, a town isn't a town without a bookstore. It may call itself a town, but unless it's got a bookstore it knows it's not fooling a soul." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65885-that-which-we-manifest-is-before-us-we-are-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2010 11:23:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Garth Stein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65885-that-which-we-manifest-is-before-us-we-are-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That which we manifest is before us; we are the creators of our own destiny. Be it through intention or ignorance, our successes and our failures have been brought on by none other than ourselves." -- Garth Stein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203231-hatred-is-like-a-long-dark-shadow-not-even-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 12:13:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203231-hatred-is-like-a-long-dark-shadow-not-even-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hatred is like a long, dark shadow.  Not even the person it falls upon knows where it comes from, in most cases.  It is like a two-edged sword.  When you cut the other person, you cut yourself.  The more violently you hack at the other person, the more violently you hack at yourself.  It can often be fatal.  But it is not easy to dispose of.  Please be careful, Mr.Okada.  It is very dangerous.  Once it has taken root in your heart, hatred is the most difficult think in the world to shake off." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191856-the-point-is-not-to-resist-the-flow-you-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 16:12:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191856-the-point-is-not-to-resist-the-flow-you-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The point is, not to resist the flow. You go up when you're supposed to go up and down when you're supposed to go down. When you're supposed to go up, find the highest tower and climb to the top. When you're supposed to go down, find the deepest well and go down to the bottom. When there's no flow, stay still. If you resist the flow, everything dries up. If everything dries up, the world is darkness." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239009-don-t-ever-become-a-pessimist-ira-a-pessimist-is-correct</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 08:36:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239009-don-t-ever-become-a-pessimist-ira-a-pessimist-is-correct]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't ever become a pessimist, Ira; a pessimist is correct oftener than an optimist, but an optimist has more fun--and neither can stop the march of events." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120131-of-course-i-m-being-rude-i-m-spoiling-the-ending-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 14:52:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120131-of-course-i-m-being-rude-i-m-spoiling-the-ending-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of course, I'm being rude. I'm spoiling the ending, not only of the entire book, but of this particular piece of it. I have given you two events in advance, because I don't have much interest in building mystery. Mystery bores me. It chores me. I know what happens and so do you. It's the machinations that wheel us there that aggravate, perplex, interest, and astound me. There are many things to think of. There is much story." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51337-writing-long-books-is-a-laborious-and-impoverishing-act-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2011 16:49:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51337-writing-long-books-is-a-laborious-and-impoverishing-act-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing long books is a laborious and impoverishing act of foolishness: expanding in five hundred pages an idea that could be perfectly explained in a few minutes. A better procedure is to pretend that those books already exist and to offer a summary, a commentary." -- Jorge Luis Borges ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48901-on-the-back-part-of-the-step-toward-the-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2011 16:51:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48901-on-the-back-part-of-the-step-toward-the-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the back part of the step, toward the right, I saw a small iridescent sphere of almost unbearable brilliance. At first I thought it was revolving; then I realised that this movement was an illusion created by the dizzying world it bounded. The Aleph's diameter was probably little more than an inch, but all space was there, actual and undiminished. Each thing (a mirror's face, let us say) was infinite things, since I distinctly saw it from every angle of the universe. I saw the teeming sea; I saw daybreak and nightfall; I saw the multitudes of America; I saw a silvery cobweb in the center of a black pyramid; I saw a splintered labyrinth (it was London); I saw, close up, unending eyes watching themselves in me as in a mirror; I saw all the mirrors on earth and none of them reflected me; I saw in a backyard of Soler Street the same tiles that thirty years before I'd seen in the entrance of a house in Fray Bentos; I saw bunches of grapes, snow, tobacco, lodes of metal, steam; I saw convex equatorial deserts and each one of their grains of sand; I saw a woman in Inverness whom I shall never forget; I saw her tangled hair, her tall figure, I saw the cancer in her breast; I saw a ring of baked mud in a sidewalk, where before there had been a tree; I saw a summer house in Adrogué and a copy of the first English translation of Pliny -- Philemon Holland's -- and all at the same time saw each letter on each page (as a boy, I used to marvel that the letters in a closed book did not get scrambled and lost overnight); I saw a sunset in Querétaro that seemed to reflect the colour of a rose in Bengal; I saw my empty bedroom; I saw in a closet in Alkmaar a terrestrial globe between two mirrors that multiplied it endlessly; I saw horses with flowing manes on a shore of the Caspian Sea at dawn; I saw the delicate bone structure of a hand; I saw the survivors of a battle sending out picture postcards; I saw in a showcase in Mirzapur a pack of Spanish playing cards; I saw the slanting shadows of ferns on a greenhouse floor; I saw tigers, pistons, bison, tides, and armies; I saw all the ants on the planet; I saw a Persian astrolabe; I saw in the drawer of a writing table (and the handwriting made me tremble) unbelievable, obscene, detailed letters, which Beatriz had written to Carlos Argentino; I saw a monument I worshipped in the Chacarita cemetery; I saw the rotted dust and bones that had once deliciously been Beatriz Viterbo; I saw the circulation of my own dark blood; I saw the coupling of love and the modification of death; I saw the Aleph from every point and angle, and in the Aleph I saw the earth and in the earth the Aleph and in the Aleph the earth; I saw my own face and my own bowels; I saw your face; and I felt dizzy and wept, for my eyes had seen that secret and conjectured object whose name is common to all men but which no man has looked upon -- the unimaginable universe.

I felt infinite wonder, infinite pity." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158499-without-turning-the-pharmacist-answered-that-he-liked-books-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 14:42:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Roberto Bolano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158499-without-turning-the-pharmacist-answered-that-he-liked-books-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without turning, the pharmacist answered that he liked books like The Metamorphosis, Bartleby, A Simple Heart, A Christmas Carol.  And then he said that he was reading Capote's Breakfast at Tiffany's. Leaving aside the fact that A Simple Heart and A Christmas Carol were stories, not books, there was something revelatory about the taste of this bookish young pharmacist, who ... clearly and inarguably preferred minor works to major ones.  He chose The Metamorphosis over The Trial, he chose Bartleby over Moby Dick, he chose A Simple Heart over Bouvard and Pecouchet, and A Christmas Carol over A Tale of Two Cities or The Pickwick Papers. What a sad paradox, thought Amalfitano.  Now even bookish pharmacists are afraid to take on the great, imperfect, torrential works, books that blaze a path into the unknown.  They choose the perfect exercises of the great masters.  Or what amounts to the same thing: they want to watch the great masters spar, but they have no interest in real combat, when the great masters struggle against that something, that something that terrifies us all, that something that cows us and spurs us on, amid blood and mortal wounds and stench." -- Roberto Bolano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136183-for-a-while-criticism-travels-side-by-side-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 14:44:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136183-for-a-while-criticism-travels-side-by-side-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For a while, Criticism travels side by side with the Work, then Criticism vanishes and it's the Readers who keep pace. The journey may be long or short. Then the Readers die one by one and the Work continues on alone, although a new Criticism and new Readers gradually fall into step with it along its path. Then Criticism dies again and the Readers die again and the Work passes over a trail of bones on its journey toward solitude. To come near the work, to sail in her wake, is a sign of certain death, but new Criticism and new Readers approach her tirelessly and relentlessly and are devoured by time and speed. Finally the Work journeys irremediably alone in the Great Vastness. And one day the Work dies, as all things must die and come to an end: the Sun and the Earth and the Solar System and the Galaxy and the farthest reaches of man's memory. Everything that begins as comedy ends in tragedy." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484673-i-try-to-find-the-books-that-i-lost-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 14:48:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484673-i-try-to-find-the-books-that-i-lost-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I try to find the books that I lost or forgot more than 30 years ago on another continent, with the hope and dedication and bitterness of those who search for their first lost books, books that if found I wouldn't read anyway, because I've already read them over and over, but that I would look at and touch just as the miser strokes the coins under which he's buried...Books are like ghosts" -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
