<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/32142-katrina]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/32142-katrina" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 21:08:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181241-in-ways-that-certain-of-us-are-uncomfortable-about-snoots</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 21:08:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katrina add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181241-in-ways-that-certain-of-us-are-uncomfortable-about-snoots]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In ways that certain of us are uncomfortable about, SNOOTs’ attitudes about contemporary usage resemble religious/political conservatives’ attitudes about contemporary culture. We combine a missionary zeal and a near-neural faith in our beliefs’ importance with a curmudgeonly hell-in-a-handbasket despair at the way English is routinely manhandled and corrupted by supposedly educated people. The Evil is all around us: boners and clunkers and solecistic howlers and bursts of voguish linguistic methane that make any SNOOT’s cheek twitch and forehead darken. A fellow SNOOT I know likes to say that listening to most people’s English feels like watching somebody use a Stradivarius to pound nails: We are the Few, the Proud, the Appalled at Everyone Else." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153555-language-is-a-skin-i-rub-my-language-against-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 20:12:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katrina add a quote by Roland Barthes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153555-language-is-a-skin-i-rub-my-language-against-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Language is a skin: I rub my language against the other. It is as if I had words instead of fingers, or fingers at the tip of my words. My language trembles with desire. The emotion derives from a double contact: on the one hand, a whole activity of discourse discreetly, indirectly focuses upon a single signified, which is &quot;I desire you,&quot; and releases, nourishes, ramifies it to the point of explosion (language experiences orgasm upon touching itself); on the other hand, I enwrap the other in my words, I caress, brush against, talk up this contact, I extend myself to make the commentary to which I submit the relation endure. " -- Roland Barthes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153558-if-i-acknowledge-my-dependency-i-do-so-because-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 20:12:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[katrina add a quote by Roland Barthes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153558-if-i-acknowledge-my-dependency-i-do-so-because-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I acknowledge my dependency, I do so because for me it is a means of signifying my demand: in the realm of love, futility is not a &quot;weakness&quot; or an &quot;absurdity&quot;: it is a strong sign: the more futile, the more it signifies and the more it asserts itself as strength.)" -- Roland Barthes]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
