<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/321871-madalena]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/321871-madalena" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 06:35:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171722-his-defences-were-all-in-his-wits-and-cunning-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 06:35:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madalena add a quote by D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171722-his-defences-were-all-in-his-wits-and-cunning-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His defences were all in his wits and cunning, his very instincts of cunning, and when these were abeyance he seemed doubly naked and like a child, of unfinished, tender flesh, and somehow struggling helplessly" -- D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171723-and-all-the-time-she-felt-the-reflection-of-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 06:38:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madalena add a quote by D. H. Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171723-and-all-the-time-she-felt-the-reflection-of-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And all the time she felt the reflection of his hopelessness in her. She couldn't quite, quite love in hoplessness. And he, being hopeless, couldn't ever love at all." -- D. H. Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39106-there-is-an-idea-of-a-patrick-bateman-some-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2010 07:47:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madalena add a quote by Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39106-there-is-an-idea-of-a-patrick-bateman-some-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…there is an idea of a Patrick Bateman, some kind of abstraction, but there is no real me, only an entity, something illusory, and though I can hide my cold gaze and you can shake my hand and feel flesh gripping yours and maybe you can even sense our lifestyles are probably comparable: I simply am not there.  It is hard for me to make sense on any given level.  Myself is fabricated, an aberration.  I am a noncontingent human being.  My personality is sketchy and unformed, my heartlessness goes deep and is persistent.  My conscience, my pity, my hopes disappeared a long time ago (probably at Harvard) if they ever did exist.  There are no more barriers to cross.  All I have in common with the uncontrollable and the insane, the vicious and the evil, all the mayhem I have caused and my utter indifference toward it, I have now surpassed.  I still, though, hold on to one single bleak truth: no one is safe, nothing is redeemed.  Yet I am blameless.  Each model of human behavior must be assumed to have some validity.  Is evil something you are?  Or is it something you do?  My pain is constant and sharp and I do not hope for a better world for anyone.  In fact, I want my pain to be inflicted on others.  I want no one to escape.  But even after admitting this—and I have countless times, in just about every act I’ve committed—and coming face-to-face with these truths, there is no catharsis.  I gain no deeper knowledge about myself, no new understanding can be extracted from my telling.  There has been no reason for me to tell you any of this.  This confession has meant nothing…." -- Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221645-this-is-not-an-exit</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2010 07:49:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madalena add a quote by Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221645-this-is-not-an-exit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is not an exit." -- Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147605-everything-failed-to-subdue-me-soon-everything-seemed-dull-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2010 07:49:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madalena add a quote by Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147605-everything-failed-to-subdue-me-soon-everything-seemed-dull-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything failed to subdue me. Soon everything seemed dull: another sunrise, the lives of heroes, falling in love, war, the discoveries people made about each other. The only thing that didn't bore me, obviously enough, was how much money Tim Price made, and yet in its obviousness it did. There wasn't a clear, identifiable emotion within me, except for greed and, possibly, total disgust. I had all the characteristics of a human being - flesh, blood, skin, hair - but my depersonalization was so intense, had gone so deep, that the normal ability to feel compassion had been eradicated, the victim of a slow, purposeful erasure. I was simply imitating reality, a rough resemblance of a human being, with only a dim corner of my mind functioning. Something horrible was happening and yet I couldn't figure out why - I couldn't put my finger on it." -- Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26491-fear-is-unnatural-lightning-and-thunder-are-unnatural-pain-death</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2010 07:58:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madalena add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26491-fear-is-unnatural-lightning-and-thunder-are-unnatural-pain-death]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fear is unnatural.  Lightning and thunder are unnatural.  Pain, death, reality, these are all unnatural.  We can't bear these things as they are.  We know too much.  So we resort to repression, compromise and disguise.  This is how we survive the universe.  This is the natural language of the species." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9364-the-nonbelievers-need-the-believers-they-are-desperate-to-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2010 07:58:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madalena add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9364-the-nonbelievers-need-the-believers-they-are-desperate-to-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The nonbelievers need the believers. They are desperate to have someone believe.&quot; &quot;As belief shrinks from the world, people find it more necessary than ever that someone believe...Those who have abandoned belief must still believe in us. They are sure that they are right not to believe but they know belief must not fade completely. Hell is when no one believes." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84678-the-family-is-the-cradle-of-the-world-s-misinformation-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2010 07:58:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madalena add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84678-the-family-is-the-cradle-of-the-world-s-misinformation-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The family is the cradle of the world’s misinformation. There must be something in family life that generates factual error. Over-closeness, the noise and heat of being. Perhaps even something deeper like the need to survive. Murray says we are fragile creatures surrounded by a world of hostile facts. Facts threaten our happiness and security. The deeper we delve into things, the looser our structure may seem to become. The family process works towards sealing off the world. Small errors grow heads, fictions proliferate. I tell Murray that ignorance and confusion can’t possibly be the driving forces behind family solidarity. What an idea, what a subversion. He asks me why the strongest family units exist in the least developed societies. Not to know is a weapon of survival, he says. Magic and superstition become entrenched as the powerful orthodoxy of the clan. The family is strongest where objective reality is most likely to be misinterpreted. What a heartless theory, I say. But Murray insists it’s true." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39358-this-is-the-whole-point-of-technology-it-creates-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2010 07:59:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madalena add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39358-this-is-the-whole-point-of-technology-it-creates-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is the whole point of technology. It creates an appetite for immortality on the one hand. It threatens universal extinction on the other. Technology is lust removed from nature. - Murray (WN 285)" -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
