<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/322421-boyd]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/322421-boyd" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 10:01:34 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56073-wherever-they-s-a-fight-so-hungry-people-can-eat-i-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 10:01:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Boyd add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56073-wherever-they-s-a-fight-so-hungry-people-can-eat-i-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wherever they’s a fight so hungry people can eat, I’ll be there. Wherever they’s a cop beatin’ up a guy, I’ll be there. If Casy knowed, why, I’ll be in the way guys yell when they’re mad an’—I’ll be in the way kids laugh when they’re hungry n’ they know supper’s ready. An’ when our folks eat the stuff they raise an’ live in the houses they build—why, I’ll be there." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 10:02:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Boyd add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are bored and disgusted by politics and don't bother to vote, you are in effect voting for the entrenched Establishments of the two major parties, who please rest assured are not dumb, and who are keenly aware that it is in their interests to keep you disgusted and bored and cynical and to give you every possible reason to stay at home doing one-hitters and watching MTV on primary day.  By all means stay home if you want, but don't bullshit yourself that you're not voting.  In reality, there is &lt;i&gt;no such thing as not voting:&lt;/i&gt; you either vote by voting, or you vote by staying home and tacitly doubling the value of some Diehard's vote." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2289-the-mind-is-its-own-place-and-in-itself-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 03:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Boyd add a quote by John Milton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2289-the-mind-is-its-own-place-and-in-itself-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The mind is its own place, and in itself can make a heaven of hell, a hell of heaven.." -- John Milton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2008 05:34:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Boyd add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what you shall do; Love the earth and sun and the animals, despise riches, give alms to every one that asks, stand up for the stupid and crazy, devote your income and labor to others, hate tyrants, argue not concerning God, have patience and indulgence toward the people, take off your hat to nothing known or unknown or to any man or number of men, go freely with powerful uneducated persons and with the young and with the mothers of families, read these leaves in the open air every season of every year of your life, re-examine all you have been told at school or church or in any book, dismiss whatever insults your own soul, and your very flesh shall be a great poem and have the richest fluency not only in its words but in the silent lines of its lips and face and between the lashes of your eyes and in every motion and joint of your body." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39297-i-saw-the-best-minds-of-my-generation-destroyed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 07:48:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Boyd add a quote by Allen Ginsberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39297-i-saw-the-best-minds-of-my-generation-destroyed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I saw the best minds of my generation destroyed by madness, starving hysterical naked, dragging themselves through the negro streets at dawn looking for an angry fix angelheaded hipsters burning for the ancient heavenly connection to the starry dynamo in the machinery of the night." -- Allen Ginsberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
