<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/322696-fira]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/322696-fira" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 09:59:10 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296278-peeta-how-come-i-never-know-when-you-re-having-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 09:59:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fira add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296278-peeta-how-come-i-never-know-when-you-re-having-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Peeta, how come I never know when you're having a nightmare?” I say.

“I don't know. I don't think I cry out or thrash around or anything. I just come to, paralyzed with terror,” he says.

“You should wake me,” I say, thinking about how I can interrupt his sleep two or three times on a bad night. About how long it can take to calm me down.

“It's not necessary. My nightmares are usually about losing you,” he says. “I'm okay once I realize you're here." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318573-at-a-few-minutes-before-four-peeta-turns-to-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 09:59:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fira add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318573-at-a-few-minutes-before-four-peeta-turns-to-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At a few minutes before four, Peeta turns to me again. &quot;Your favorite colour . . . it's green?&quot;
   &quot;That's right.&quot; Then I think of something to add. &quot;And yours is orange.&quot;
   &quot;Orange?&quot; He seems unconvinced.
   &quot;Not bright orange. But soft. Like the sunset,&quot; I say. &quot;At least, that's what you told me once.&quot;
   &quot;Oh.&quot; He closes his eyes briefly, maybe trying to conjure up that sunset, then nods his head. &quot;Thank you.&quot;
   But more words tumble out. &quot;You're a painter. You're a baker. You like to sleep with the windows open. You never take sugar in your tea. And you always double-knot your shoelaces.&quot;
   Then I dive into my tent before I do something stupid like cry." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/418977-we-ll-earn-it-all-back-today-i-say-and-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 10:02:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fira add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/418977-we-ll-earn-it-all-back-today-i-say-and-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We'll earn it all back today,&quot; I say, and we both plow into our plates. Even cold, it's one of the things I've ever tasted. I abandon my fork and scrape up the last dabs of gravy with my fingers. &quot;I can feel Effie trinket shuddering at my manners.&quot;
&quot;Hey, Effie, watch this!&quot; says Peeta. He tosses his fork over his shoulder and literally licks his plate his plate clean with his tongue making loud, satisfied sounds. Then he blows a kiss to her in general, and calls, &quot;We miss you, Effie!&quot; 
I cover his hand with my mouth. But I am laughing. 
&quot;Stop! Cato could be right outside our cave.&quot; 
 He grabs my hand away.&quot;What do I care. I've got you to protect me now,&quot; says Peeta, pulling me to him.
&quot;Come on,&quot; I say in exasperation, extricating myself from his grasp but not before he gets another kiss." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
