<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/323506-jack-bootjesus]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/323506-jack-bootjesus" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2012 12:00:06 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407412-the-bottom-line-is-this-peace-will-come-to-israel</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2012 12:00:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Jimmy Carter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407412-the-bottom-line-is-this-peace-will-come-to-israel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The bottom line is this: Peace will come to Israel and the Middle East only when the Israeli government is willing to comply with international law, with the Roadmap for Peace, with official American policy, with the wishes of a majority of its own citizens--and honor its own previous commitments--by accepting its legal borders.  All Arab neighbors must pledge to honor Israel's right to live in peace under these conditions.  The United States is squandering international prestige and goodwill and intensifying global anti-American terrorism by unofficially condoning or abetting the Israeli confiscation and colonization of Palestinian territories." -- Jimmy Carter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128765-the-human-louse-somewhat-resembles-a-tiny-lobster-and-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2013 11:42:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128765-the-human-louse-somewhat-resembles-a-tiny-lobster-and-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The human louse somewhat resembles a tiny lobster, and he lives chiefly in your trousers. Short of burning all your clothes there is no known way of getting rid of him. Down the seams of your trousers he lays his glittering white eggs, like tiny grains of rice, which hatch out and breed families of thier own at horrible speed. I think pacifists might find it helpful to illustrate thier pamphlets with enlarged photographs of lice. Glory of war indeed! In war all solderies are lousy, at the least when it is warm enough. The men that fought at Verdun, at Waterloo, at Flodden, at Senlac, at Thermopylae - every one of them had lice crawling over his testicles." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
