<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/324581-ioianthe]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/324581-ioianthe" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 16:51:46 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488980-true-generosity-consists-precisely-in-fighting-to-destroy-the-causes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 16:51:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ioianthe add a quote by Paulo Freire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488980-true-generosity-consists-precisely-in-fighting-to-destroy-the-causes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["True generosity consists precisely in fighting to destroy the causes which nourish false charity. False charity constrains the fearful and subdued, the &quot;rejects of life,&quot; to extend their trembling hands. True generosity lies in striving so that these hands--whether of individuals or entire peoples--need be extended less and less in supplication, so that more and more they become human hands which work and, working, transform the world." -- Paulo Freire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76359-the-radical-committed-to-human-liberation-does-not-become-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 16:54:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ioianthe add a quote by Paulo Freire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76359-the-radical-committed-to-human-liberation-does-not-become-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The radical, committed to human liberation, does not become the prisoner of a 'circle of certainty' within which reality is also imprisoned. On the contrary, the more radical the person is, the more fully he or she enters into reality so that, knowing it better, he or she can better transform it. This individual is not afraid to confront, to listen, to see the world unveiled. This person is not afraid to meet the people or to enter into dialogue with them. This person does not consider himself or herself the proprietor of history or of all people, or the liberator of the oppressed; but he or she does commit himself or herself, within history, to fight at their side." -- Paulo Freire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59583-education-either-functions-as-an-instrument-which-is-used-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 06:04:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ioianthe add a quote by Paulo Freire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59583-education-either-functions-as-an-instrument-which-is-used-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Education either functions as an instrument which is used to facilitate integration of the younger generation into the logic of the present system and bring about conformity or it becomes the practice of freedom, the means by which men and women deal critically and creatively with reality and discover how to participate in the transformation of their world." -- Paulo Freire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15683-t-he-more-radical-the-person-is-the-more-fully-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 06:04:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ioianthe add a quote by Paulo Freire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15683-t-he-more-radical-the-person-is-the-more-fully-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[T]he more radical the person is, the more fully he or she enters into reality so that, knowing it better, he or she can transform it. This individual is not afraid to confront, to listen, to see the world unveiled. This person is not afraid to meet the people or to enter into a dialogue with them. This person does not consider himself or herself the proprietor of history or of all people, or the liberator of the oppressed; but he or she does commit himself or herself, within history, to fight at their side." -- Paulo Freire]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
