<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/325280-hans-gerwitz]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/325280-hans-gerwitz" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2009 22:56:26 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209008-i-am-not-a-part-of-this-home-any-longer</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2009 22:56:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by James Tate]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209008-i-am-not-a-part-of-this-home-any-longer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am not a part of this home any longer. I am a tiny thing created by indifferent scientists. I am an experiment, a mechanical bee placed near the hive. The real bees were happy being bees until I came along and gave them all the false information that destroyed their little lives." -- James Tate]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/210935-you-re-safe-because-you-re-so-trapped-inside-your-culture-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2009 14:50:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/210935-you-re-safe-because-you-re-so-trapped-inside-your-culture-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're safe because you're so trapped inside your culture.  Anything you can conceive of is fine because you can conceive of it." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75043-if-i-can-t-be-beautiful-i-want-to-be-invisible</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2009 14:51:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75043-if-i-can-t-be-beautiful-i-want-to-be-invisible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I can't be beautiful, I want to be invisible." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159432-first-your-parents-they-give-you-your-life-but-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2009 14:52:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159432-first-your-parents-they-give-you-your-life-but-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First your parents, they give you your life, but then they try to give you their life." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215813-why-would-a-farmer-lock-the-doors-of-his-turkey</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 21:52:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215813-why-would-a-farmer-lock-the-doors-of-his-turkey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why would a farmer lock the doors of his turkey farm?" -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215820-since-the-world-has-changed-so-much-the-same-values</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 22:04:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215820-since-the-world-has-changed-so-much-the-same-values]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Since the world has changed so much, the same values don't lead to the same choices anymore." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275485-as-long-as-the-centuries-continue-to-unfold-the-number</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 02:40:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Denis Diderot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275485-as-long-as-the-centuries-continue-to-unfold-the-number]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As long as the centuries continue to unfold, the number of books will grow continually, and one can predict that a time will come when it will be almost as difficult to learn anything from books as from the direct study of the whole universe. It will be almost as convenient to search for some bit of truth concealed in nature as it will be to find it hidden away in an immense multitude of bound volumes." -- Denis Diderot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15758-no-nation-was-ever-so-virtuous-as-each-believes-itself</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 20:19:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15758-no-nation-was-ever-so-virtuous-as-each-believes-itself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No nation was ever so virtuous as each believes itself, and none was ever so wicked as each believes the other." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393512-he-didn-t-know-all-that-much-about-how-the-machinery</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 17:56:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Kurt Vonegat]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393512-he-didn-t-know-all-that-much-about-how-the-machinery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He didn't know all that much about how the machinery worked anyway. Such knowledge was for specialists. In war, as in love, he was a fearless, happy-go-lucky adventurer." -- Kurt Vonegat]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394165-more-and-more-people-back-then-and-not-just-andrew</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 12:14:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394165-more-and-more-people-back-then-and-not-just-andrew]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["More and more people back then, and not just Andrew MacIntosh, had found ensuring the survival of the human race a total bore." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26445-it-is-more-important-that-innocence-be-protected-than-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 19:32:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by John Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26445-it-is-more-important-that-innocence-be-protected-than-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is more important that innocence be protected than it is that guilt be punished, for guilt and crimes are so frequent in this world that they cannot all be punished.

But if innocence itself is brought to the bar and condemned, perhaps to die, then the citizen will say, 'whether I do good or whether I do evil is immaterial, for innocence itself is no protection,' and if such an idea as that were to take hold in the mind of the citizen that would be the end of security whatsoever." -- John Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49810-i-do-not-say-that-democracy-has-been-more-pernicious</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 19:33:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by John Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49810-i-do-not-say-that-democracy-has-been-more-pernicious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not say that democracy has been more pernicious on the whole, and in the long run, than monarchy or aristocracy. Democracy has never been and never can be so durable as aristocracy or monarchy; but while it lasts, it is more bloody than either. … Remember, democracy never lasts long. It soon wastes, exhausts, and murders itself. There never was a democracy yet that did not commit suicide. It is in vain to say that democracy is less vain, less proud, less selfish, less ambitious, or less avaricious than aristocracy or monarchy. It is not true, in fact, and nowhere appears in history. Those passions are the same in all men, under all forms of simple government, and when unchecked, produce the same effects of fraud, violence, and cruelty. When clear prospects are opened before vanity, pride, avarice, or ambition, for their easy gratification, it is hard for the most considerate philosophers and the most conscientious moralists to resist the temptation. Individuals have conquered themselves. Nations and large bodies of men, never." -- John Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47839-the-whole-drama-of-the-world-is-such-tragedy-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 19:36:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by John Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47839-the-whole-drama-of-the-world-is-such-tragedy-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The whole drama of the world is such tragedy that I am weary of the spectacle." -- John Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200573-we-think-ourselves-possessed-or-at-least-we-boast-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 19:37:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by John Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200573-we-think-ourselves-possessed-or-at-least-we-boast-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We think ourselves possessed, or at least we boast that we are so, of liberty of conscience on all subjects and of the right of free inquiry and private judgment in all cases, and yet how far are we from these exalted privileges in fact. There exists, I believe, throughout the whole Christian world, a law which makes it blasphemy to deny, or to doubt the divine inspiration of all the books of the Old and New Testaments, from Genesis to Revelations. In most countries of Europe it is punished by fire at the stake, or the rack, or the wheel. In England itself, it is punished by boring through the tongue with a red-hot poker. In America it is not much better; even in our Massachusetts, which, I believe, upon the whole, is as temperate and moderate in religious zeal as most of the States, a law was made in the latter end of the last century, repealing the cruel punishments of the former laws, but substituting fine and imprisonment upon all those blasphemies upon any book of the Old Testament or New. Now, what free inquiry, when a writer must surely encounter the risk of fine or imprisonment for adducing any arguments for investigation into the divine authority of those books? Who would run the risk of translating [author:Volney|2739197]'s &lt;i&gt;Recherches Nouvelles&lt;/i&gt;? Who would run the risk of translating [author:Dupuis|3081160]? But I cannot enlarge upon this subject, though I have it much at heart. I think such laws a great embarrassment, great obstructions to the improvement of the human mind. Books that cannot bear examination, certainly ought not to be established as divine inspiration by penal laws... but as long as they continue in force as laws, the human mind must make an awkward and clumsy progress in its investigations. I wish they were repealed.

{&lt;i&gt;Letter to [author:Thomas Jefferson|1673], January 23, 1825&lt;/i&gt;}" -- John Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456687-there-is-a-cult-of-ignorance-in-the-united-states</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 19:44:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Issac Asimov ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456687-there-is-a-cult-of-ignorance-in-the-united-states]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a cult of ignorance in the United States, and there has always been. The strain of anti-intellectualism has been a constant thread winding its way through our political and cultural life, nurtured by the false notion that  democracy means that 'my ignorance is just as good as your knowledge." -- Issac Asimov ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497943-in-a-thousand-years-alessandro-said-this-incident-will-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2012 22:09:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Mark Helprin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497943-in-a-thousand-years-alessandro-said-this-incident-will-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a thousand years,&quot; Alessandro said, &quot;this incident will be remembered.  By then, of course, we will have become angels, devils, or a dragon that breathes fire...but we have given this rock a story that will be passed on.&quot;
&quot;What good is that?&quot;
&quot;It isn't to our advantage, if that's what you mean.  However, it's pleasurable to cast a line into the future, no matter how tenuously.  You never know, the line may be unbroken all the way to the last judgment." -- Mark Helprin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22727-when-you-can-t-bear-something-but-it-goes-on-anyway</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 09:15:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Austin Grossman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22727-when-you-can-t-bear-something-but-it-goes-on-anyway]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you can't bear something but it goes on anyway, the person who survives isn't you anymore; you've changed and become someone else, a new person, the one who did bear it after all." -- Austin Grossman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166354-truth-of-course-must-of-necessity-be-stranger-than-fiction</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 19:01:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166354-truth-of-course-must-of-necessity-be-stranger-than-fiction]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Truth, of course, must of necessity be stranger than fiction, for we have made fiction to suit ourselves." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/634505-what-makes-an-object-beautiful-has-nothing-to-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 19:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Andrew Bowie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/634505-what-makes-an-object-beautiful-has-nothing-to-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["… what makes an object beautiful has nothing to do with its usefulness or its exchange value." -- Andrew Bowie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142015-when-you-are-a-bear-of-very-little-brain-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 06:29:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142015-when-you-are-a-bear-of-very-little-brain-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you are a Bear of Very Little Brain, and you Think of Things, you find sometimes that a Thing which seemed very Thingish inside you is quite different when it gets out into the open and has other people looking at it." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260114-i-believe-empathy-is-the-most-essential-quality-of-civilization</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2013 08:51:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Roger Ebert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260114-i-believe-empathy-is-the-most-essential-quality-of-civilization]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe empathy is the most essential quality of civilization." -- Roger Ebert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/370107-every-creature-is-better-alive-than-dead-men-and-moose</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 06:16:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/370107-every-creature-is-better-alive-than-dead-men-and-moose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every creature is better alive than dead, men and moose and pine trees, and he who understands it aright will rather preserve its life than destroy it. " -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/593784-but-what-force-in-the-galaxy-is-stronger-than-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 06:54:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Joan D. Vinge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/593784-but-what-force-in-the-galaxy-is-stronger-than-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But what force in the galaxy is stronger than she is?&quot;

&quot;Indifference.&quot; Jerusha surprised herself with the answer. &quot;Indifference, Gundhalinu, is the strongest force in the universe. It makes everything it touches meaningless. Love and hate don't stand a chance against it. It lets neglect and decay and monstrous injustice go unchecked. It doesn't act, it allows. And that's what gives it so much power." -- Joan D. Vinge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101168-among-my-most-prized-possessions-are-words-that-i-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 02:30:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Orson Scott Card]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101168-among-my-most-prized-possessions-are-words-that-i-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Among my most prized possessions are words that I have never spoken." -- Orson Scott Card]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196015-we-are-masters-of-the-unsaid-words-but-slaves-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 02:30:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hans add a quote by Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196015-we-are-masters-of-the-unsaid-words-but-slaves-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are masters of the unsaid words, but slaves of those we let slip out.." -- Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
