<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/326553-lauren]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/326553-lauren" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 18:30:46 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/529202-a-library-in-the-middle-of-a-community-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 18:30:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Caitlin Moran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/529202-a-library-in-the-middle-of-a-community-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A library in the middle of a community is a cross between an emergency exit, a life-raft and a festival. They are cathedrals of the mind; hospitals of the soul; theme parks of the imagination. On a cold rainy island, they are the only sheltered public spaces where you are not a consumer, but a citizen instead" -- Caitlin Moran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2010 23:03:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is our choices, Harry, that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2530-then-you-must-tell-em-dat-love-ain-t-somethin-lak</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 10:33:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2530-then-you-must-tell-em-dat-love-ain-t-somethin-lak]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then you must tell 'em dat love ain't somethin' lak uh grindstone dat's de same thing everywhere and do de same thing tuh everything it touch. Love is lak de sea. It's uh movin' thing, but still and all, it takes its shape from de shore it meets, and it's different with every shore." -- Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 11:57:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that is gold does not glitter,
Not all those who wander are lost;
The old that is strong does not wither,
Deep roots are not reached by the frost.

From the ashes a fire shall be woken,
A light from the shadows shall spring;
Renewed shall be blade that was broken,
The crownless again shall be king." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34933-but-for-my-own-part-if-a-book-is-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 11:57:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34933-but-for-my-own-part-if-a-book-is-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["but for my own part, if a book is well written, I always find it too short." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6702-i-declare-after-all-there-is-no-enjoyment-like-reading</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 11:57:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6702-i-declare-after-all-there-is-no-enjoyment-like-reading]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I declare after all there is no enjoyment like reading! How much sooner one tires of any thing than of a book! -- When I have a house of my own, I shall be miserable if I have not an excellent library." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222-courage-is-what-it-takes-to-stand-up-and-speak</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 09:09:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222-courage-is-what-it-takes-to-stand-up-and-speak]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Courage is what it takes to stand up and speak; courage is also what it takes to sit down and listen." -- Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2312-i-have-observed-indeed-generally-that-while-in-protestant-countries</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 09:10:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2312-i-have-observed-indeed-generally-that-while-in-protestant-countries]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have observed, indeed, generally, that while in protestant countries the defections from the Platonic Christianity of the priests is to Deism, in catholic countries they are to Atheism. [author:Diderot|11004], [author:D'Alembert|3295333], [author:D’Holbach|1228712], [author:Condorcet|6420223], are known to have been among the most virtuous of men. Their virtue, then, must have had some other foundation than the love of God.

[&lt;i&gt;Letter to Thomas Law, 13 June 1814&lt;/i&gt;]" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6373-we-took-the-liberty-to-make-some-enquiries-concerning-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 09:11:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6373-we-took-the-liberty-to-make-some-enquiries-concerning-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We took the liberty to make some enquiries concerning the ground of their pretensions to make war upon nations who had done them no injury, and observed that we considered all mankind as our friends who had done us no wrong, nor had given us any provocation.

The Ambassador [of Tripoli] answered us that it was founded on the Laws of their Prophet, that it was written in their Koran, that all nations who should not have acknowledged their authority were sinners, that it was their right and duty to make war upon them wherever they could be found, and to make slaves of all they could take as Prisoners, and that every Musselman who should be slain in battle was sure to go to Paradise.

{&lt;i&gt;Letter from the commissioners, [author:John Adams|1480] &amp; Thomas Jefferson, to [author:John Jay|63860], 28 March 1786&lt;/i&gt;}" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11291-when-the-clergy-addressed-author-general-washington-4356-on-his-departure-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 09:12:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11291-when-the-clergy-addressed-author-general-washington-4356-on-his-departure-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the clergy addressed [author:General Washington|4356] on his departure from the government, it was observed in their consultation that he had never on any occasion said a word to the public which showed a belief in the Christian religion and they thought they should so pen their address as to force him at length to declare publicly whether he was a Christian or not. They did so. However [Dr. Rush] observed the old fox was too cunning for them. He answered every article of their address particularly except that, which he passed over without notice... I know that [author:Gouverneur Morris|945122], who pretended to be in his secrets &amp; believed himself to be so, has often told me that &lt;b&gt;[author:General Washington|4356] believed no more of that system than he himself did&lt;/b&gt;.

{&lt;i&gt;The Anas, February 1, 1800, written shortly after the death of first US president [author:George Washington|4356]&lt;/i&gt;}" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10730-4-religion-your-reason-is-now-mature-enough-to-examine</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 09:12:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10730-4-religion-your-reason-is-now-mature-enough-to-examine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["4. Religion. Your reason is now mature enough to examine this object. In the first place, divest yourself of all bias in favor of novelty &amp; singularity of opinion... shake off all the fears &amp; servile prejudices, under which weak minds are servilely crouched. &lt;b&gt;Fix reason firmly in her seat, and call to her tribunal every fact, every opinion. Question with boldness even the existence of a God; because, if there be one, he must more approve of the homage of reason, than that of blindfolded fear&lt;/b&gt;. You will naturally examine first, the religion of your own country. Read the Bible, then as you would read [author:Livy|2840091] or [author:Tacitus|2936846]. The facts which are within the ordinary course of nature, you will believe on the authority of the writer, as you do those of the same kind in [author:Livy|2840091] and [author:Tacitus|2936846]. The testimony of the writer weighs in their favor, in one scale, and their not being against the laws of nature, does not weigh against them. But those facts in the Bible which contradict the laws of nature, must be examined with more care, and under a variety of faces. Here you must recur to the pretensions of the writer to inspiration from God. Examine upon what evidence his pretensions are founded, and whether that evidence is so strong, as that its falsehood would be more improbable than a change in the laws of nature, in the case he relates. For example in the book of Joshua we are told the sun stood still several hours. Were we to read that fact in [author:Livy|2840091] or [author:Tacitus|2936846] we should class it with their showers of blood, speaking of statues, beasts, &amp;c. But it is said that the writer of that book was inspired. Examine therefore candidly what evidence there is of his having been inspired. The pretension is entitled to your inquiry, because millions believe it. On the other hand you are astronomer enough to know how contrary it is to the law of nature that a body revolving on its axis as the earth does, should have stopped, should not by that sudden stoppage have prostrated animals, trees, buildings, and should after a certain time have resumed its revolution, &amp; that without a second general prostration. Is this arrest of the earth's motion, or the evidence which affirms it, most within the law of probabilities? You will next read the New Testament. It is the history of a personage called Jesus. Keep in your eye the opposite pretensions: 1, of those who say he was begotten by God, born of a virgin, suspended &amp; reversed the laws of nature at will, &amp; ascended bodily into heaven; and 2, of those who say he was a man of illegitimate birth, of a benevolent heart, enthusiastic mind, who set out without pretensions to divinity, ended in believing them, and was punished capitally for sedition, by being gibbeted, according to the Roman law, which punished the first commission of that offence by whipping, &amp; the second by exile, or death &lt;i&gt;in fureâ&lt;/i&gt;.

...Do not be frightened from this inquiry by any fear of its consequences. If it ends in a belief that there is no God, you will find incitements to virtue in the comfort and pleasantness you feel in its exercise, and the love of others which it will procure you... In fine, I repeat, you must lay aside all prejudice on both sides, and neither believe nor reject anything, because any other persons, or description of persons, have rejected or believed it... I forgot to observe, when speaking of the New Testament, that you should read all the histories of Christ, as well of those whom a council of ecclesiastics have decided for us, to be Pseudo-evangelists, as those they named Evangelists. Because these Pseudo-evangelists pretended to inspiration, as much as the others, and you are to judge their pretensions by your own reason, and not by the reason of those ecclesiastics. Most of these are lost...

[&lt;i&gt;Letter to his nephew, Peter Carr, advising him in matters of religion, 1787&lt;/i&gt;]" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17703-i-would-not-know-how-i-am-supposed-to-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 11:57:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Dave Barry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17703-i-would-not-know-how-i-am-supposed-to-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would not know how I am supposed to feel about many stories if not for the fact that the TV news personalities make sad faces for sad stories and happy faces for happy stories. " -- Dave Barry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43554-surely-everyone-is-aware-of-the-divine-pleasures-which-attend</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 11:57:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Thomas De Quincey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43554-surely-everyone-is-aware-of-the-divine-pleasures-which-attend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Surely everyone is aware of the divine pleasures which attend a wintry fireside; candles at four o'clock, warm hearthrugs, tea, a fair tea-maker, shutters closed, curtains flowing in ample draperies to the floor, whilst the wind and rain are raging audibly without." -- Thomas De Quincey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76821-art-enables-us-to-find-ourselves-and-lose-ourselves-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 15:37:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Thomas Merton ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76821-art-enables-us-to-find-ourselves-and-lose-ourselves-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Art enables us to find ourselves and lose ourselves at the same time." -- Thomas Merton ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27338-never-say-love-is-like-anything-it-isn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 19:26:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27338-never-say-love-is-like-anything-it-isn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never say love is &quot;like&quot; anything... It isn't." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7807-sometimes-i-feel-discriminated-against-but-it-does-not-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 14:52:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by ZORA NEALE HURSTON]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7807-sometimes-i-feel-discriminated-against-but-it-does-not-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, I feel discriminated against, but it does not make me angry. It merely astonishes me. How &lt;i&gt;can&lt;/i&gt; any deny themselves the pleasure of my company? It’s beyond me." -- ZORA NEALE HURSTON]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27411-happiness-is-not-a-possession-to-be-prized-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:37:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Daphne Du Maurier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27411-happiness-is-not-a-possession-to-be-prized-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is not a possession to be prized, it is a quality of thought, a state of mind." -- Daphne Du Maurier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174134-instead-of-hating-the-people-you-think-are-war-makers-hate</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 15:59:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Thomas Merton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174134-instead-of-hating-the-people-you-think-are-war-makers-hate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Instead of hating the people you think are war-makers, hate the appetites and disorder in your own soul, which are the causes of war. If you love peace, then hate injustice, hate tyranny, hate greed - but hate these things in yourself, not in another." -- Thomas Merton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 16:02:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 16:13:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 16:13:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one can make you feel inferior without your consent." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 16:14:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Darkness cannot drive out darkness: only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate: only love can do that." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19884-be-yourself-everyone-else-is-already-taken</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 16:14:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19884-be-yourself-everyone-else-is-already-taken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be yourself; everyone else is already taken." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 16:18:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that everything happens for a reason. People change so that you can learn to let go, things go wrong so that you appreciate them when they're right, you believe lies so you eventually learn to trust no one but yourself, and sometimes good things fall apart so better things can fall together." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1858-for-most-of-history-anonymous-was-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 16:18:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1858-for-most-of-history-anonymous-was-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For most of history, Anonymous was a woman." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30262-all-you-need-is-love-but-a-little-chocolate-now</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 16:18:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30262-all-you-need-is-love-but-a-little-chocolate-now]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All you need is love. But a little chocolate now and then doesn't hurt." -- Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21705-i-know-god-won-t-give-me-anything-i-can-t-handle</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 16:23:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Mother Theresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21705-i-know-god-won-t-give-me-anything-i-can-t-handle]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know God won't give me anything I can't handle. I just wish he didn't trust me so much." -- Mother Theresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5445-whereas-story-is-processed-in-the-mind-in-a-straightforward</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 15:16:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Jasper Fforde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5445-whereas-story-is-processed-in-the-mind-in-a-straightforward]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whereas story is processed in the mind in a straightforward manner, poetry bypasses rational thought and goes straight to the limbic system and lights it up like a brushfire.  It's the crack cocaine of the literary world." -- Jasper Fforde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47109-stay-gold-ponyboy-stay-gold</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 15:48:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by S.E. Hinton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47109-stay-gold-ponyboy-stay-gold]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stay gold, Ponyboy, stay gold." -- S.E. Hinton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197771-i-used-to-be-sure-of-things-me-once-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 15:49:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by S.E. Hinton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197771-i-used-to-be-sure-of-things-me-once-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I used to be sure of things. Me, once i had all the answers. I wish i was a kid again, when i had all the answers" -- S.E. Hinton]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
