<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/329729-teddee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/329729-teddee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 21:58:35 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/483549-it-is-quite-true-what-philosophy-says-that-life-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 21:58:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/483549-it-is-quite-true-what-philosophy-says-that-life-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is quite true what Philosophy says: that Life must be understood backwards. But that makes one forget the other saying: that it must be lived—forwards. The more one ponders this, the more it comes to mean that life in the temporal existence never becomes quite intelligible, precisely because at no moment can I find complete quiet to take the backward- looking position." -- Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484266-socrates-this-man-on-one-hand-believes-that-he-knows</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 21:58:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Plato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484266-socrates-this-man-on-one-hand-believes-that-he-knows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Socrates: This man, on one hand, believes that he knows something, while not knowing [anything]. On the other hand, I – equally ignorant – do not believe [that I know anything]." -- Plato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/376719-perhaps-we-re-intruding-this-seems-to-be-a-private-beach</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 07:43:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Heard on Gold Beach by Donald Gardner 47th Royal Marine Commandos June 6 1944 in The Longest Day]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/376719-perhaps-we-re-intruding-this-seems-to-be-a-private-beach]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps we're intruding, this seems to be a private beach." -- Heard on Gold Beach by Donald Gardner 47th Royal Marine Commandos June 6 1944 in The Longest Day]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/454948-we-all-know-what-to-do-but-we-don-t-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 14:47:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Jean-Claude Juncker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/454948-we-all-know-what-to-do-but-we-don-t-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all know what to do, but we don’t know how to get re-elected once we have done it." -- Jean-Claude Juncker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256048-truth-always-rests-with-the-minority-and-the-minority-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2012 14:54:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Soren Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256048-truth-always-rests-with-the-minority-and-the-minority-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Truth always rests with the minority, and the minority is always stronger than the majority, because the minority is generally formed by those who really have an opinion, while the strength of a majority is illusory, formed by the gangs who have no opinion — and who, therefore, in the next instant (when it is evident that the minority is the stronger) assume its opinion… while truth again reverts to a new minority." -- Soren Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 21:58:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be the change that you wish to see in the world." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501617-creativity-becomes-more-visible-when-adults-try-to-be-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 21:29:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Loris Malaguzzi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501617-creativity-becomes-more-visible-when-adults-try-to-be-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Creativity becomes more visible when adults try to be more attentive to the cognitive processes of children than to the results they achieve in various fields of doing and understanding." -- Loris Malaguzzi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501623-stand-aside-for-a-while-and-leave-room-for-learning</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 21:40:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Loris Malaguzzi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501623-stand-aside-for-a-while-and-leave-room-for-learning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stand aside for a while and leave room for learning, observe carefully what children do, and then, if you have understood well, perhaps teaching will be different from before." -- Loris Malaguzzi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/509475-your-job-as-a-parent-is-not-to-make-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2012 13:58:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Ellyn Satter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/509475-your-job-as-a-parent-is-not-to-make-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your job as a parent is not to make your child's way smooth, but rather to help her develop inner resources so she can cope." -- Ellyn Satter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/513037-religion-is-so-frequently-a-source-of-confusion-in-political</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 18:41:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Reinhold Niebuhr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/513037-religion-is-so-frequently-a-source-of-confusion-in-political]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Religion is so frequently a source of confusion in political life, and so frequently dangerous to democracy, precisely because it introduces absolutes into the realm of relative values." -- Reinhold Niebuhr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/514913-for-while-this-year-it-may-be-a-catholic-against</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 06:53:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by John F. Kennedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/514913-for-while-this-year-it-may-be-a-catholic-against]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For while this year it may be a Catholic against whom the finger of suspicion is pointed, in other years it has been, and may someday be again, a Jew--or a Quaker--or a Unitarian--or a Baptist. It was Virginia's harassment of Baptist preachers, for example, that helped lead to Jefferson's statute of religious freedom. Today I may be the victim- -but tomorrow it may be you--until the whole fabric of our harmonious society is ripped at a time of great national peril. 

Finally, I believe in an America where religious intolerance will someday end--where all men and all churches are treated as equal--where every man has the same right to attend or not attend the church of his choice--where there is no Catholic vote, no anti-Catholic vote, no bloc voting of any kind--and where Catholics, Protestants and Jews, at both the lay and pastoral level, will refrain from those attitudes of disdain and division which have so often marred their works in the past, and promote instead the American ideal of brotherhood. 

That is the kind of America in which I believe. And it represents the kind of Presidency in which I believe--a great office that must neither be humbled by making it the instrument of any one religious group nor tarnished by arbitrarily withholding its occupancy from the members of any one religious group. I believe in a President whose religious views are his own private affair, neither imposed by him upon the nation or imposed by the nation upon him as a condition to holding that office.
...
This is the kind of America I believe in--and this is the kind I fought for in the South Pacific, and the kind my brother died for in Europe. No one suggested then that we may have a &quot;divided loyalty,&quot; that we did &quot;not believe in liberty,&quot; or that we belonged to a disloyal group that threatened the &quot;freedoms for which our forefathers died." -- John F. Kennedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/561484-so-your-best-defense-is-knowledge-it-really-is-power</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 14:16:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Elizabeth Pantley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/561484-so-your-best-defense-is-knowledge-it-really-is-power]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So, your best defense is knowledge. It really is power, as they say...The more you know, the more easily you will develop your own philosophies about child rearing. When you have your facts straight, and when you have a parenting plan, you will be able to respond with confidence to those who are well-meaning  but offering contrary or incorrect advice." -- Elizabeth Pantley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292440-we-have-not-come-this-far-without-a-struggle-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 08:50:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Franklin Delano Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292440-we-have-not-come-this-far-without-a-struggle-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have not come this far without a struggle and I assure you we cannot go further without a struggle.

    For twelve years this Nation was afflicted with hear-nothing, see-nothing, do-nothing Government. The Nation looked to Government but the Government looked away . . . Powerful influences strive today to restore that kind of government with its doctrine that that Government is best which is most indifferent . . .

    We had to struggle with the old enemies of peace — business and financial monopoly, speculation, reckless banking, class antagonism, sectionalism, war profiteering.

    They had begun to consider the Government of the United States as a mere appendage to their own affairs. We know now that Government by organized money is just as dangerous as Government by organized mob.

    Never before in all our history have these forces been so united against one candidate as they stand today. They are unanimous in their hate for me — and I welcome their hatred." -- Franklin Delano Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/650072-research-experts-want-to-know-what-can-be-done-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 07:18:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Jonathan Kozol]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/650072-research-experts-want-to-know-what-can-be-done-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Research experts want to know what can be done about the values of poor segregated children; and this is a question that needs asking. But they do not ask what can be done about the values of the people who have segregated these communities. There is no academic study of the pathological detachment of the very rich..." -- Jonathan Kozol]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/654726-in-my-world-you-don-t-get-to-call-yourself-pro-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 12:03:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Thomas L. Friedman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/654726-in-my-world-you-don-t-get-to-call-yourself-pro-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In my world, you don’t get to call yourself “pro-life” and be against common-sense gun control — like banning public access to the kind of semiautomatic assault rifle, designed for warfare, that was used recently in a Colorado theater. You don’t get to call yourself “pro-life” and want to shut down the Environmental Protection Agency, which ensures clean air and clean water, prevents childhood asthma, preserves biodiversity and combats climate change that could disrupt every life on the planet. You don’t get to call yourself “pro-life” and oppose programs like Head Start that provide basic education, health and nutrition for the most disadvantaged children...The term “pro-life” should be a shorthand for respect for the sanctity of life. But I will not let that label apply to people for whom sanctity for life begins at conception and ends at birth. What about the rest of life? Respect for the sanctity of life, if you believe that it begins at conception, cannot end at birth." -- Thomas L. Friedman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/655542-the-principal-reason-that-districts-within-states-often-differ-markedly</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 09:35:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Robert E. Slavin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/655542-the-principal-reason-that-districts-within-states-often-differ-markedly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The principal reason that districts within states often differ markedly in per-pupil expenditures is that school funding is almost always tied to property taxes, which are in turn a direct function of local wealth. Having school funding depend on local wealth creates a situation in which poor districts must tax themselves far more heavily than wealthy ones, yet still may not be able to generate adequate income. For example, Baltimore City is one of the poorest jurisdictions in Maryland, and the Baltimore City Public Schools have the lowest per-pupil instructional expenses of any of Maryland's 24 districts. Yet Baltimore's property tax rate is twice that of the next highest jurisdiction.(FN2) Before the funding equity decision in New Jersey, the impoverished East Orange district had one of the highest tax rates in the state, but spent only $3,000 per pupil, one of the lowest per-pupil expenditures in the state.(FN3) A similar story could be told in almost any state in the U.S.(FN4) Funding formulas work systematically against children who happen to be located in high-poverty districts, but also reflect idiosyncratic local circumstances. For example, a factory closing can bankrupt a small school district. What sense does it make for children's education to suffer based on local accidents of geography or economics?
    To my knowledge, the U.S. is the only nation to fund elementary and secondary education based on local wealth. Other developed countries either equalize funding or provide extra funding for individuals or groups felt to need it. In the Netherlands, for example, national funding is provided to all schools based on the number of pupils enrolled, but for every guilder allocated to a middle-class Dutch child, 1.25 guilders are allocated for a lower-class child and 1.9 guilders for a minority child, exactly the opposite of the situation in the U.S. where lower-class and minority children typically receive less than middle-class white children.(FN5) Regional differences in per-pupil costs may exist in other countries, but the situation in which underfunded urban or rural districts exist in close proximity to wealthy suburban districts is probably uniquely American.
    Of course, even equality in per-pupil costs in no way ensures equality in educational services. Not only do poor districts typically have fewer funds, they also have greater needs." -- Robert E. Slavin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/658131-whenever-judges-of-the-highest-state-courts-have-actually-examined</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 19:30:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Michael A. Rebell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/658131-whenever-judges-of-the-highest-state-courts-have-actually-examined]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever judges of the highest state courts have actually examined the details of the &quot;savage inequalities&quot; that continue to be imposed on most low-income and minority students in the United States, they have virtually unanimously held that these conditions deny students the opportunity to be educated at the basic levels that are needed to function well in contemporary society." -- Michael A. Rebell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/439207-there-is-nobody-in-this-country-who-got-rich-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 18:59:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Elizabeth Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/439207-there-is-nobody-in-this-country-who-got-rich-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nobody in this country who got rich on their own. Nobody. You built a factory out there - good for you. But I want to be clear. You moved your goods to market on roads the rest of us paid for. You hired workers the rest of us paid to educate. You were safe in your factory because of police forces and fire forces that the rest of us paid for. You didn't have to worry that marauding bands would come and seize everything at your factory... Now look. You built a factory and it turned into something terrific or a great idea - God bless! Keep a hunk of it. But part of the underlying social contract is you take a hunk of that and pay forward for the next kid who comes along." -- Elizabeth Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28899-it-is-easier-to-build-strong-children-than-to-repair</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 06:18:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Frederick Douglass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28899-it-is-easier-to-build-strong-children-than-to-repair]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is easier to build strong children than to repair broken men." -- Frederick Douglass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/795887-there-s-simply-no-polite-way-to-tell-people-they-ve-dedicated</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 13:59:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Daniel Dennett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/795887-there-s-simply-no-polite-way-to-tell-people-they-ve-dedicated]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There’s simply no polite way to tell people they’ve dedicated their lives to an illusion." -- Daniel Dennett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/824301-however-this-court-is-constrained-by-law-and-under-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:02:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Colleen McMahon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/824301-however-this-court-is-constrained-by-law-and-under-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["However, this court is constrained by law, and under the law, I can only conclude that the Government has not violated FOIA by refusing to turn over the documents sought in the FOIA requests, and so cannot be compelled by this court of law to explain in detail the reasons why its actions do not violate the Constitution and the laws of the United States. The Alice-in-Wonderland nature of this pronouncement is not lost on me; but after careful and extensive consideration, I find myself stuck in a paradoxical situation in which I cannot solve a problem because of contradictory constraints and rules—a veritable Catch-22. I can find no way around the thicket of laws and precedents that effectively allow the Executive Branch of our Government to proclaim as perfectly lawful certain actions that seem on their face incompatible with our Constitution and laws, while keeping the reasons for their conclusion a secret." -- Colleen McMahon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/824624-often-the-best-source-of-information-about-waste-fraud-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 18:05:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Obama-Biden Transition Project: Office of the President-elect and Office of the Vice President-elect]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/824624-often-the-best-source-of-information-about-waste-fraud-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Often the best source of information about waste, fraud, and abuse in government is an existing government employee committed to public integrity and willing to speak out. Such acts of courage and patriotism, which can sometimes save lives and often save taxpayer dollars, should be encouraged rather than stifled. We need to empower federal employees as watchdogs of wrongdoing and partners in performance." -- Obama-Biden Transition Project: Office of the President-elect and Office of the Vice President-elect]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/825760-it-s-very-very-difficult-i-think-for-us-to-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 06:46:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Tom Udall]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/825760-it-s-very-very-difficult-i-think-for-us-to-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's very, very difficult I think for us to have a transparent debate about secret programs approved by a secret court issuing secret court orders based on secret interpretations of the law." -- Tom Udall]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70829-wherever-the-real-power-in-a-government-lies-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 14:20:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by James Madison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70829-wherever-the-real-power-in-a-government-lies-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wherever the real power in a Government lies, there is the danger of oppression. In our Governments, the real power lies in the majority of the Community, and the invasion of private rights is chiefly to be apprehended, not from the acts of Government contrary to the sense of its constituents, but from acts in which the Government is the mere instrument of the major number of the constituents." -- James Madison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/855846-it-is-a-fundamental-principle-of-american-democracy-that-laws</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 05:51:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Ron Wyden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/855846-it-is-a-fundamental-principle-of-american-democracy-that-laws]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a fundamental principle of American democracy that laws should not be public only when it is convenient for government officials to make them public. They should be public all the time, open to review by adversarial courts, and subject to change by an accountable legislature guided by an informed public. If Americans are not able to learn how their government is interpreting and executing the law then we have effectively eliminated the most important bulwark of our democracy. That’s why, even at the height of the Cold War, when the argument for absolute secrecy was at its zenith, Congress chose to make US surveillance laws public. Without public laws, and public court rulings interpreting those laws, it is impossible to have informed public debate. And when the American people are in the dark, they can’t make fully informed decisions about who should represent them, or protest policies that they disagree with. These are fundamentals. It’s Civics 101. And secret law violates those basic principles. It has no place in America." -- Ron Wyden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/855858-authorities-this-broad-give-the-national-security-bureaucracy-the-power</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 06:02:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Ron Wyden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/855858-authorities-this-broad-give-the-national-security-bureaucracy-the-power]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Authorities this broad give the national security bureaucracy the power to scrutinize the personal lives of every law-abiding American. Allowing that to continue is a grave error that demonstrates a willful ignorance of human nature. Moreover, it demonstrates a complete disregard for the responsibilities entrusted to us by the Founding Fathers to maintain robust checks and balances on the power of any arm of the government. That obviously raises some very serious questions. What happens to our government, our civil liberties and our basic democracy if the surveillance state is allowed to grow unchecked? As we have seen in recent days, the intelligence leadership is determined to hold on to this authority. Merging the ability to conduct surveillance that reveals every aspect of a person’s life with the ability to conjure up the legal authority to execute that surveillance, and finally, removing any accountable judicial oversight, creates the opportunity for unprecedented influence over our system of government." -- Ron Wyden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/855871-for-those-who-believe-executive-branch-officials-will-voluntarily-interpret</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 06:22:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Ron Wyden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/855871-for-those-who-believe-executive-branch-officials-will-voluntarily-interpret]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For those who believe executive branch officials will voluntarily interpret their surveillance authorities with restraint, I believe it is more likely that I will achieve my life-long dream of playing in the NBA." -- Ron Wyden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/859051-we-have-seen-segments-of-our-government-in-their-attitudes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 12:11:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Church Committee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/859051-we-have-seen-segments-of-our-government-in-their-attitudes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have seen segments of our Government, in their attitudes and action, adopt tactics unworthy of a democracy, and occasionally reminiscent of totalitarian regimes. We have seen a consistent pattern in which programs initiated with limited goals, such as preventing criminal violence or identifying foreign spies, were expanded to what witnesses characterized as &quot;vacuum cleaners&quot;, sweeping in information about lawful activities of American citizens. The tendency of intelligence activities to expand beyond their initial scope is a theme which runs through every aspect of our investigative findings. Intelligence collection programs naturally generate ever-increasing demands for new data. And once intelligence has been collected, there are strong pressures to use it against the target." -- Church Committee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8381-naturally-the-common-people-don-t-want-war-neither-in-russia</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 18:13:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Hermann Göring]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8381-naturally-the-common-people-don-t-want-war-neither-in-russia]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Naturally, the common people don't want war; neither in Russia nor in England nor in America nor, for that matter, in Germany. That is understood. But, after all, it is the leaders of the country who determine the policy and it is always a simple matter to drag the people along, whether it is a democracy or a fascist dictatorship or a Parliament or a Communist dictatorship. ... [V]oice or no voice, the people can always be brought to the bidding of the leaders. That is easy. All you have to do is tell them they are being attacked and denounce the pacifists for lack of patriotism and exposing the country to danger. It works the same way in any country." -- Hermann Göring]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/874289-the-national-security-agency-s-capability-at-any-time-could-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 04:32:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teddee add a quote by Frank Church]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/874289-the-national-security-agency-s-capability-at-any-time-could-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The National Security Agency’s capability at any time could be turned around on the American people, and no American would have any privacy left, such is the capability to monitor everything: telephone conversations, telegrams, it doesn’t matter. There would be no place to hide. If a dictator ever took over, the N.S.A. could enable it to impose total tyranny, and there would be no way to fight back." -- Frank Church]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
