<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/32974-tracy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/32974-tracy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 12:40:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35928-you-can-best-serve-civilization-by-being-against-what-usually</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 12:40:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35928-you-can-best-serve-civilization-by-being-against-what-usually]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can best serve civilization by being against what usually passes for it." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6759-man-is-the-only-creature-who-refuses-to-be-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 07:33:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6759-man-is-the-only-creature-who-refuses-to-be-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man is the only creature who refuses to be what he is." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8178-nobody-realizes-that-some-people-expend-tremendous-energy-merely-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 07:33:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8178-nobody-realizes-that-some-people-expend-tremendous-energy-merely-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody realizes that some people expend tremendous energy merely to be normal." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11144-an-intellectual-yes-and-never-deny-it-an-intellectual-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 07:34:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11144-an-intellectual-yes-and-never-deny-it-an-intellectual-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An intellectual? Yes. And never deny it. An intellectual is someone whose mind watches itself. I like this, because I am happy to be both halves, the watcher and the watched. &quot;Can they be brought together?&quot; This is a practical question. We must get down to it. &quot;I despise intelligence&quot; really means: &quot;I cannot bear my doubts." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919-the-man-who-does-not-read-has-no-advantage-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 06:12:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919-the-man-who-does-not-read-has-no-advantage-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who does not read has no advantage over the man who cannot read." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1288-i-don-t-know-about-you-but-i-m-kind-of-fed</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2008 06:07:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Audrey Niffenger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1288-i-don-t-know-about-you-but-i-m-kind-of-fed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know about you, but I'm kind of fed up with realism. After all, there's enough reality already; why make more of it? Why not leave realism for the memoirs of drug addicts, the histories of salt, the biographies of porn stars? Why must we continue to read about the travails of divorced people or mildly depressed Canadians when we could be contemplating the shopping habits of zombies, or the difficulties that ensue when living and dead people marry each other? We should be demanding more stories about faery handbags and pyjamas inscribed with the diaries of strange women. We should not rest until someone writes about a television show that features the Free People's World-Tree Library, with its elaborate waterfalls and Forbidden Books and Pirate-Magicians. We should be pining for a house haunted by rabbits." -- Audrey Niffenger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5606-ideally-what-should-be-said-to-every-child-repeatedly-throughout</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 06:05:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5606-ideally-what-should-be-said-to-every-child-repeatedly-throughout]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ideally, what should be said to every child, repeatedly, throughout his or her school life is something like this: 'You are in the process of being indoctrinated. We have not yet evolved a system of education that is not a system of indoctrination. We are sorry, but it is the best we can do. What you are being taught here is an amalgam of current prejudice and the choices of this particular culture. The slightest look at history will show how impermanent these must be. You are being taught by people who have been able to accommodate themselves to a regime of thought laid down by their predecessors. It is a self-perpetuating system. Those of you who are more robust and individual than others will be encouraged to leave and find ways of educating yourself — educating your own judgements. Those that stay must remember, always, and all the time, that they are being moulded and patterned to fit into the narrow and particular needs of this particular society." -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51055-i-am-sure-everyone-has-had-the-experience-of-reading</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 06:06:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51055-i-am-sure-everyone-has-had-the-experience-of-reading]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am sure everyone has had the experience of reading a book and finding it vibrating with aliveness, with colour and immediacy.  And then, perhaps some weeks later, reading it again and finding it flat and empty.  Well, the book hasn't changed: you have." -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22263-there-is-only-one-way-to-read-which-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 06:07:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22263-there-is-only-one-way-to-read-which-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is only one way to read, which is to browse in libraries and bookshops, picking up books that attract you, reading only those, dropping them when they bore you, skipping the parts that drag-and never, never reading anything because you feel you ought, or because it is part of a trend or a movement.  Remember that the book which bores you when you are twenty or thirty will open doors for you when you are forty or fifty-and vise versa.  Don’t read a book out of its right time for you.  " -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130121-with-school-turning-out-more-runners-jumpers-racers-tinkerers-grabbers</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 17:25:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130121-with-school-turning-out-more-runners-jumpers-racers-tinkerers-grabbers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With school turning out more runners, jumpers, racers, tinkerers, grabbers, snatchers, fliers, and swimmers instead of examiners, critics, knowers, and imaginative creators, the word 'intellectual,' of course, became the swear word it deserved to be." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10795-don-t-own-so-much-clutter-that-you-will-be-relieved</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 17:34:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10795-don-t-own-so-much-clutter-that-you-will-be-relieved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't own so much clutter that you will be relieved to see your house catch fire." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2071-one-of-the-most-important-resources-that-a-garden-makes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 17:36:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tracy add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2071-one-of-the-most-important-resources-that-a-garden-makes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the most important resources that a garden makes available for use, is the gardener's own body. A garden gives the body the dignity of working in its own support. It is a way of rejoining the human race." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
