<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/329875-liza]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/329875-liza" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 20:36:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71810-i-am-now-going-to-make-an-admission-i-confess</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 20:36:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liza add a quote by Paul Valery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71810-i-am-now-going-to-make-an-admission-i-confess]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am now going to make an admission. I confess, I agree, that all these good people who protested, who laughed, who did not perceive what we perceived, were in a quite legitimate position. Their opinion was quite in order. One must not be afraid to say that the kingdom of letters is only a province of the vast empire of entertainment. One picks up a book, one puts it aside; and even when one cannot put it down one very well understands that this interest is related to the facility of pleasure. That is to say that every effort of a creator of beauty or of fantasy should be bent, by the very essence of his work, on contriving &lt;i&gt;for the public&lt;/i&gt; pleasure which demands no effort, or almost none. It is through the public that he should deduce what touches, moves, soothes, animates or enchants the public.

There are however several publics; amongst whom it is not impossible to find some people who do not conceive of pleasure without pain, who do not like to enjoy themselves without paying, and who are not happy if their happiness is not in some part their own contrivance through which they wish to realize what it costs them. 
" -- Paul Valery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71811-i-believed-rather-more-accurately-that-a-work-resolutely-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 20:37:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liza add a quote by Paul Valery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71811-i-believed-rather-more-accurately-that-a-work-resolutely-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believed, rather more accurately, that a work resolutely thought out and sought for in the hazards of the mind, systematically, and through a determined analysis of definite and previously prescribed conditions, whatever its value might be once it had been produced, did not leave the mind of its creator without having modified him, and forced him to recognize and in some way reorganize himself. I said to myself &lt;i&gt;that it was not the accomplished work, and its appearance and effect in the world, that can fulfill and edify us; but only the way in which we have done it.&lt;/i&gt;" -- Paul Valery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20242-let-us-again-pretend-that-life-is-a-solid-substance</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2009 11:53:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liza add a quote by Virginia Woolf ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20242-let-us-again-pretend-that-life-is-a-solid-substance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let us again pretend that life is a solid substance, shaped like a globe, which we turn about in our fingers. Let us pretend that we can make out a plain and logical story, so that when one matter is despatched—love for instance—we go on, in an orderly manner, to the next. " -- Virginia Woolf ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/885089-history-produces-not-only-the-forces-of-domination-but-also</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2013 08:38:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liza add a quote by Elizabeth Grosz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/885089-history-produces-not-only-the-forces-of-domination-but-also]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["History produces not only the forces of domination but also the forces of resistance that press up against and are often the objects of such domination. Which is another way of saying that history, the past, is larger than the present, and is the ever-growing and ongoing possibility of resistance to the present’s imposed values, the possibility of futures not unlike the present, futures that resist and transform what dominates the present." -- Elizabeth Grosz]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
