<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/329996-david-ward]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/329996-david-ward" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 13:38:58 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39223-we-can-t-stop-here-this-is-bat-country</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 13:38:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39223-we-can-t-stop-here-this-is-bat-country]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can't stop here, this is bat country!" -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300669-i-loved-when-bush-came-out-and-said-we-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 11:22:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Bill Hicks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300669-i-loved-when-bush-came-out-and-said-we-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I loved when Bush  came out and said, 'We are losing the war against drugs.' 

You know what that implies? There's a war being fought, and the people on drugs are winning it." -- Bill Hicks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/733089-one-question-that-especially-intrigues-me-is-exactly-when-humpbacks</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 20:27:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Charles &quot;Flip&quot; Nicklin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/733089-one-question-that-especially-intrigues-me-is-exactly-when-humpbacks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One question that especially intrigues me is exactly when humpbacks started coming to Hawaii and why.  In artwork and oral histories of ancient Hawaiians there is no record of humpback whales being there, and there is no evidence that humpbacks were there in large numbers in the mid-1800's during the heyday of whaling.  The whalers who provisioned in Hawaii in the winter couldn't have overlooked the numbers of whales that are in Hawaii now.  We really don't know what happened, but everything points to a recent colonization of humpbacks. (p.162)." -- Charles &quot;Flip&quot; Nicklin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/854576-as-far-as-i-m-concerned-there-won-t-be-a-beatles</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 10:06:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by George Harrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/854576-as-far-as-i-m-concerned-there-won-t-be-a-beatles]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As far as I'm concerned, there won't be a Beatles reunion as long as John Lennon remains dead." -- George Harrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876977-was-the-government-to-prescribe-us-our-medicine-and-diet</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 11:45:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876977-was-the-government-to-prescribe-us-our-medicine-and-diet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Was the government to prescribe us our medicine and diet, our bodies would be in such keeping as our souls are now.&quot; - Thomas Jefferson" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/802641-when-i-was-a-kid-i-inhaled-frequently-that-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 11:46:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Barack Obama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/802641-when-i-was-a-kid-i-inhaled-frequently-that-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was a kid I inhaled frequently. That was the point." -- Barack Obama]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876980-lay-off-the-needle-drugs-the-only-dope-worth-shooting</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 11:47:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Abbie Hoffman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876980-lay-off-the-needle-drugs-the-only-dope-worth-shooting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lay off the needle drugs. The only dope worth shooting is Richard Nixon." -- Abbie Hoffman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/880168-it-s-all-chemicals-says-the-biochemistry-text-chlorophylls-keep</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 10:17:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by John Jerome]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/880168-it-s-all-chemicals-says-the-biochemistry-text-chlorophylls-keep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[":  “It’s all chemicals, says the biochemistry text.  Chlorophylls keep the leaves green while thy are green, carotenoids – as in butter, corn, canary feathers – turn them yellow when the chlorophyll goes.  Tannin adds the browns, the bronzes; something called anthocyanin turns leaves red if the sap of the plant is acidic, blue or purple if it is alkaline.  Color is a substance, says the chemist.” – John Jerome, Stone Work:  Reflections on Serious Play &amp; Other Aspects of Country Life, p. 140." -- John Jerome]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/880170-on-the-solstice-the-tilting-of-the-earth-may-very</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 10:18:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by John Jerome]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/880170-on-the-solstice-the-tilting-of-the-earth-may-very]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the solstice:  “The tilting of the earth may very well have stopped at the winter solstice, creaking to a halt and starting back the other way, but I was down in the basement at the time, running a power saw, and didn’t hear a thing." -- John Jerome]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/880172-snow-falling-in-the-woods-when-there-s-no-wind-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 10:19:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by John Jerome]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/880172-snow-falling-in-the-woods-when-there-s-no-wind-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Snow falling in the woods when there’s no wind is the most peaceful thing I’ve ever seen." -- John Jerome]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/880173-a-s-my-breath-begins-to-quiet-in-the-silent-woods</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 10:20:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by John Jerome]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/880173-a-s-my-breath-begins-to-quiet-in-the-silent-woods]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[A]s my breath begins to quiet in the silent woods, I pick up a squeaking, creaking sound, growing steadily louder, that makes the hair stand up on the back of my neck.  I snap my head up and overhead, oh my God, here comes three hundred, five hundred, a thousand Canada geese, maybe fifteen hundred, stretching across the sky in a succession of vees.  Largest flight I’ve ever seen.  Underlit from reflection off the snow, a skyful of silver arrowheads, bound due north for the summer to come.  A skyful of physiology, riding the physics of the air toward the pole.  Riches, riches, everywhere, just for the paying of attention." -- John Jerome]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/898910-survival-spanish-your-uncle-s-hotel-sounds-very-nice-but-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2013 06:39:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Randy Wayne White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/898910-survival-spanish-your-uncle-s-hotel-sounds-very-nice-but-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Survival Spanish:

Your uncle's hotel sounds very nice, but I have reservations at the Holiday Inn.
&lt;i&gt;El hotel de su tio debe de ser muy lindo, pero tengo reservacions en el Holiday Inn.&lt;/i&gt;
I would like your least expensive room.
&lt;i&gt;Quisiera su habitacion menos cara.&lt;/i&gt;
I would like a better room.
&lt;i&gt;Quisiera una habitacion mejor.&lt;/i&gt;
I would like any room not damaged by the recent earthquake.
&lt;i&gt;Quisiera cualquier habitacion que no sufrio danos en el temblor reciente.&lt;/i&gt;

The local women do WHAT to cause fermentation?
&lt;i&gt;Las mujures aqui hacen QUE para causar la fermentacion?
I don't question your abilities, but I am already married.
&lt;i&gt;No dudo sus habilidades, pero estoy botin.&lt;/i&gt;
My friend is drunk and I am lost.
&lt;i&gt;Mi amigo esta borracho y estoy perdido.&lt;/i&gt;
My friend is lost and I am drunk.
&lt;i&gt;Mi amigo esta perdido y estoy borracho.&lt;/i&gt;
My apologies.  I thought you asked me to dance.
&lt;i&gt;Disculpeme.  Pense que me invito a bailar.&lt;/i&gt;

Have I broken a law?
&lt;i&gt;He violado un ley?&lt;/i&gt;
May I offer you the gift of money?
&lt;i&gt;Puedo ofrecerle un regalito de dinero?&lt;/i&gt;
Did I say twenty dollars?  I meant &lt;i&gt;fifty&lt;/i&gt;.
&lt;i&gt;Dije veinte dolares?  Queria decir CINCUENTA!&lt;/i&gt;
You can have our women, but leave the plane tickets.
&lt;i&gt;Pueden llevarse a nuestras majeres, pero dejen nuestros boletos de avion.&lt;/i&gt;" -- Randy Wayne White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/897561-i-d-make-stuff-up-like-i-heard-that-when-jesus</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 11:15:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Scott Carrier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/897561-i-d-make-stuff-up-like-i-heard-that-when-jesus]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd make stuff up, like, 'I heard that when Jesus built furniture he never used glue in the joints, that he'd touch them and they'd hold forever." -- Scott Carrier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/901252-when-we-said-we-were-going-to-do-something-directly</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 14:43:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Timothy B. Tyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/901252-when-we-said-we-were-going-to-do-something-directly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we said we were going to do something &quot;directly,&quot; which is pronounced &quot;dreckly,&quot; we meant that we were going to get to it sooner or later, one of these days, maybe never, and please don't ask again." -- Timothy B. Tyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360783-tobacco-put-food-on-our-tables-steeples-on-our-churches</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 14:45:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Timothy B. Tyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360783-tobacco-put-food-on-our-tables-steeples-on-our-churches]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tobacco put food on our tables, steeples on our churches, stains on our fingers, spots on our lungs, and contradictions in our hearts." -- Timothy B. Tyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10601-i-used-to-have-a-drug-problem-now-i-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 15:38:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Lee Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10601-i-used-to-have-a-drug-problem-now-i-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I used to have a drug problem, now I make enough money." -- David Lee Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497886-i-think-that-everything-should-be-made-available-to-everybody</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 15:42:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497886-i-think-that-everything-should-be-made-available-to-everybody]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think that everything should be made available to everybody, and I mean LSD, cocaine, codeine, grass, opium, the works. Nothing on earth available to any man should be confiscated and made unlawful by other men in more seemingly powerful and advantageous positions." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/901448-it-s-an-odd-term-girlfriend-particularly-for-grown-persons-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 21:44:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Jeff Lindsay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/901448-it-s-an-odd-term-girlfriend-particularly-for-grown-persons-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s an odd term, 'girlfriend,' particularly for grown persons.  And in practice it provides an even odder concept.  Generally speaking, in adults it described a woman, not a girl, who was willing to provide sex, not friendship.  In fact, from what I had observed it was quite possible for one to actively dislike one’s girlfriend, although of course true hatred is reserved for marriage." -- Jeff Lindsay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63067-it-s-what-you-learn-after-you-know-it-all-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 14:45:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by John Wooden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63067-it-s-what-you-learn-after-you-know-it-all-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's what you learn after you know it all that counts." -- John Wooden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/912707-when-the-longhorns-could-be-gathered-up-and-driven-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 13:30:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Rick Bass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/912707-when-the-longhorns-could-be-gathered-up-and-driven-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the longhorns could be gathered up and driven, it was theorized that the heat from the herd's mass attracted lightning.  (Such was the radiant heat from a large herd that a cowboy's face would be blistered on whichever side of the herd he'd ridden by the day's end.)  Their great horns also seemed to attract electricity, so that lightning and ground-electricity would  bounce around from horn to horn throughout the herd - a phantasmagoric burning blue circuitry.  The cracking of the cowboy's whips and the twitching of the cattle's tails also emitted sparkling &quot;snakes of fire." -- Rick Bass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920408-the-average-man-seeks-certainty-in-the-eyes-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 15:42:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Carlos Castenada]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920408-the-average-man-seeks-certainty-in-the-eyes-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The average man seeks certainty in the eyes of the onlooker and calls that self-confidence.  The warrior seeks impeccability in his own eyes and calls that humbleness." -- Carlos Castenada]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/991274-my-mother-s-family-is-passionate-about-visiting-and-cleaning-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 12:13:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/991274-my-mother-s-family-is-passionate-about-visiting-and-cleaning-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My mother’s family is passionate about visiting and cleaning the graves of their deceased.  Once a year, the Peeks and the Nolens would gather to clean the tombstones and plant flowers at the grave sites of their people.  Once, in Piedmont, when I was a little boy, I was helping to clean a grave of an ancestor of my grandfather named Jerry Mire Peek.  When I asked my cousin Clyde whom this unknown relation was named after, he said, “He was named after the prophet Jerry Mire." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/997607-grateful-dead-performances-were-by-design-not-consciously-planned-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 16:39:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Steven Gimbel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/997607-grateful-dead-performances-were-by-design-not-consciously-planned-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Grateful Dead performances were by design not consciously planned, often reaching their artistic peak when the collective stumbled upon something stunning, when &quot;the music played the band,&quot; as it were. Instead of using set lists, the Grateful Dead chose songs by experimenting together until a pulse, rhythm, phrase, or riff emerged from the group, suggesting a song. Their collective, improvisatory musical works communicate felling like any other artwork." -- Steven Gimbel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1005518-g-randma-was-always-afraid-of-something-she-set-aside-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 14:10:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by J.R. Moehringer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1005518-g-randma-was-always-afraid-of-something-she-set-aside-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[G]randma was always afraid of something.  She set aside time each day for dread.  And not nameless dread.  She was quite specific about the various tragedies stalking her.  She feared pneumonia, muggers, riptides, meteors, drunk drivers, drug addicts, serial killers, tornadoes, doctors, unscrupulous grocery clerks, and the Russians.  The depth of Grandma’s dread came home to me when she bought a lottery ticket and sat before the tv as the numbers were called.  After her first three numbers were a match, she began praying feverishly that she wouldn’t have the next three.  She dreaded winning, for fear that her heart would give out." -- J.R. Moehringer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1005536-it-was-one-of-those-rare-moments-where-one-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 14:25:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Paul Greenberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1005536-it-was-one-of-those-rare-moments-where-one-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was one of those rare moments where one has a vision of the scope of the wild ocean.  Not just small cylinders firing to keep a tiny engine running, but rather the giant, massive gears of nature, each one with its own reasoning, its own meta-logic, spinning in its particular circle in competition or in confluence with the gear below it.  We zeroed in on the school, but our progress was painfully slow, It would have been foolish to speed into the tumult-we would have ruined our baits in the process and doomed our chances of hooking a tuna. 
But luckily, the commotion did not subside.  If anything it only grew more frantic and exhuberant on our approach.  Beneath the birds, beneath the dolphins, beneath the menhaden, there should have been an equally vast school of giant bluefin tuna, collaborating with vertebrates of the so-called higher orders of life to form the floor of the prey trap, sealing the baitfish in from below, while the dolphins and birds made up the trap's walls and ceiling.  A strike from a giant tuna seemed inevitable.....as the boat moved forward, I saw seabirds gathering up ahead into a cloud, the size and violence of which I had never seen before.  Gannets - big, albatross-like pelagic birds - flew hundreds of feet above the churning surface of the water.  In a flock of many thousands, they whirled in unison and then, as if on command from some brigadier general of bird life, dropped in an arc, bird after bird, into the water beneath.  The gyre of gannets turned in a clockwise direction, and down below, spinning counterclockwise, was the largest school of dolphins I'd ever seen.  There in the angry blue-green sea, the dolphins had corralled a vast school of menhaden-small herringlike creatures that, when bitten, release globules of oil that float on the surface.  Oil slicks flattened the water everywhere as the dolphins swirled around, using their exceptional intelligence and wolf-pack cooperation to befuddle and surround the fish, which in turn whirled in a clockwise direction." -- Paul Greenberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1005546-people-can-talk-all-they-want-about-the-big-ten</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 14:45:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Joe Menzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1005546-people-can-talk-all-they-want-about-the-big-ten]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People can talk all they want about the Big Ten.  About Michigan and Ohio State and Indiana and Kentucky or whatever, but there's no way that compares.  They're in different states.  Here, we share the same dry cleaners.&quot; - Mike Kryzewski" -- Joe Menzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559166-my-father-gave-me-the-greatest-gift-anyone-could-give</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 10:13:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Jim Valvano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559166-my-father-gave-me-the-greatest-gift-anyone-could-give]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My father gave me the greatest gift anyone could give another person, he believed in me." -- Jim Valvano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17073-to-me-there-are-three-things-everyone-should-do-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 10:13:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Jim Valvano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17073-to-me-there-are-three-things-everyone-should-do-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To me there are three things everyone should do every day. Number one is laugh. Number two is think -- spend some time time in thought. Number three, you should have your emotions move you to tears. If you laugh, think and cry, that's a heck of a day." -- Jim Valvano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17075-don-t-give-up-don-t-ever-give-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 10:13:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Jim Valvano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17075-don-t-give-up-don-t-ever-give-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't give up, don't ever give up." -- Jim Valvano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1025721-it-won-t-snow-on-us-i-told-my-hiking-companions</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 17:41:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Tim Cahill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1025721-it-won-t-snow-on-us-i-told-my-hiking-companions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It won't snow on us,&quot; I told my hiking companions, &quot;because I lead a good and virtuous life.&quot;
  
&quot;We're dead,&quot; Dave Long said." -- Tim Cahill]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
