<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/330374-cleverusername2]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/330374-cleverusername2" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 05:28:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97314-he-understood-it-to-be-another-deep-nudge-from-forces</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 05:28:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cleverusername2 add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97314-he-understood-it-to-be-another-deep-nudge-from-forces]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He understood it to be another deep nudge from forces unseen, almost surely connected with the letter that had come along with his latest mental-disability check, reminding him that unless he did something publicly crazy before a date now less than a week away, he would no longer qualify for benefits." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97315-atrocity-is-recognized-as-such-by-victim-and-predator-alike</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 05:29:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cleverusername2 add a quote by Frank Herbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97315-atrocity-is-recognized-as-such-by-victim-and-predator-alike]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Atrocity is recognized as such by victim and predator alike, by all who learn about it at whatever remove. Atrocity has no excuses, no mitigating argument. Atrocity never balances or rectifies the past. Atrocity merely arms the future for more atrocity. It is self-perpetuating upon itself — a barbarous form of incest. Whoever commits atrocity also commits those future atrocities thus bred. " -- Frank Herbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97317-the-usual-example-given-to-illustrate-an-outside-context-problem</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 05:37:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cleverusername2 add a quote by Iain Banks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97317-the-usual-example-given-to-illustrate-an-outside-context-problem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The usual example given to illustrate an Outside Context Problem was imagining you were a tribe on a largish, fertile island; you'd tamed the land, invented the wheel or writing or whatever, the neighbours were cooperative or enslaved but at any rate peaceful and you were busy raising temples to yourself with all the excess productive capacity you had, you were in a position of near-absolute power and control which your hallowed ancestors could hardly have dreamed of and the whole situation was just running along nicely like a canoe on wet grass... when suddenly this bristling lump of iron appears sailless and trailing steam in the bay and these guys carrying long funny-looking sticks come ashore and announce you've just been discovered, you're all subjects of the Emperor now, he's keen on presents called tax and these bright-eyed holy men would like a word with your priests." -- Iain Banks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2009 05:41:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cleverusername2 add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129367-the-fact-is-that-five-years-ago-i-was-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2009 05:50:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cleverusername2 add a quote by Siegfried Sassoon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129367-the-fact-is-that-five-years-ago-i-was-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fact is that five years ago I was, as near as possible, a different person to what I am tonight.  I, as I am now, didn't exist at all.  Will the same thing happen in the next five years?  I hope so." -- Siegfried Sassoon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12166-like-a-wind-crying-endlessly-through-the-universe-time-carries</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2009 05:51:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cleverusername2 add a quote by Harlan Ellison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12166-like-a-wind-crying-endlessly-through-the-universe-time-carries]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like a wind crying endlessly through the universe, Time carries away the names and the deeds of conquerors and commoners alike. And all that we were, all that remains, is in the memories of those who cared we came this way for a brief moment." -- Harlan Ellison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163539-did-you-have-one-of-those-days-today-like-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2009 05:55:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cleverusername2 add a quote by Harlan Ellison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163539-did-you-have-one-of-those-days-today-like-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did you have one of those days today, like a nail in the foot? Did the pterodactyl corpse dropped by the ghost of your mother from the spectral Hindenburg forever circling the Earth come smashing through the lid of your glass coffin? Did the New York strip steak you attacked at dinner suddenly show a mouth filled with needle-sharp teeth, and did it snap off the end of your fork, the last solid-gold fork from the set Anastasia pressed into your hands as they took her away to be shot? Is the slab under your apartment building moaning that it cannot stand the weight on its back a moment longer, and is the building stretching and creaking? Did a good friend betray you today, or did that good friend merely keep silent and fail to come to your aid? Are you holding the razor at your throat this very instant? Take heart, comfort is at hand. This is the hour that stretches. Djan karet. We are the cavalry. We're here. Put away the pills. We'll get you through this bloody night. Next time, it'll be your turn to help us.
&quot;Eidolons&quot; (1988)" -- Harlan Ellison]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
