<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/332561-louis-pz]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/332561-louis-pz" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 17:58:40 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25712-some-years-ago---never-mind-how-long-precisely--</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 17:58:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louis add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25712-some-years-ago---never-mind-how-long-precisely--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some years ago - never mind how long precisely - having little or no money in my purse, and nothing particular to interest me on shore, I thought I would sail about a little and see the watery part of the world. It is a way I have of driving off the spleen, and regulating the circulation. Whenever I find myself growing grim about the mouth; whenever it is a damp, drizzly November in my soul; whenever I find myself involuntarily pausing before coffin warehouses, and bringing up the rear of every funeral I meet; and especially whenever my hypos get such an upper hand of me, that it requires a strong moral principle to prevent me from deliberately stepping into the street, and methodically knocking people's hats off - then, I account it high time to get to sea as soon as I can. This is my substitute for pistol and ball. With a philosophical flourish Cato throws himself upon his sword; I quietly take to the ship. There is nothing surprising in this. If they but knew it, almost all men in their degree, some time or other, cherish very nearly the same feelings towards the ocean with me." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3172-and-i-urge-you-to-please-notice-when-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2008 11:32:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louis add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3172-and-i-urge-you-to-please-notice-when-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I urge you to please notice when you are happy, and exclaim or murmur or think at some point, 'If this isn't nice, I don't know what is." -- Kurt Vonnegut Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93352-te-occidere-possunt-sed-te-edere-non-possunt-nefas-est</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2009 21:54:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louis add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93352-te-occidere-possunt-sed-te-edere-non-possunt-nefas-est]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Te Occidere Possunt Sed Te Edere Non Possunt Nefas Est&quot; (&quot;They can kill you, but the legalities of eating you are quite a bit dicier&quot;)." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10467-an-economic-system-which-can-only-expand-or-expire-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 00:27:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louis add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10467-an-economic-system-which-can-only-expand-or-expire-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An economic system which can only expand or expire must be false to all that is human." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
