<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/335550-katya]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/335550-katya" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 23:43:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124402-and-she-would-say-today-you-believe-in-god-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 23:43:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124402-and-she-would-say-today-you-believe-in-god-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And she would say, &quot;Today you believe in God?&quot; And he would say, &quot;Today I believe in love&quot;." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 23:46:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1344-only-the-phoenix-rises-and-does-not-descend-and-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 23:46:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1344-only-the-phoenix-rises-and-does-not-descend-and-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only the phoenix rises and does not descend. And everything changes. And nothing is truly lost." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221968-you-re-in-a-car-with-a-beautiful-boy-and-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 11:53:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by richard siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221968-you-re-in-a-car-with-a-beautiful-boy-and-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You’re in a car with a beautiful boy, and he won’t tell you that he loves you, but he loves you. And you feel like you’ve done something terrible, like robbed a liquor store, or swallowed pills, or shoveled yourself a grave in the dirt, and you’re tired. You’re in a car with a beautiful boy, and you’re trying not to tell him that you love him, and you’re trying to choke down the feeling, and you’re trembling, but he reaches over and he touches you, like a prayer for which no words exist, and you feel your heart taking root in your body, like you’ve discovered something you didn’t even have a name for." -- richard siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261503-i-m-battling-monsters-i-m-pulling-you-out-of-the-burning</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 10:51:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Richard Siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261503-i-m-battling-monsters-i-m-pulling-you-out-of-the-burning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm battling monsters, I'm pulling you out of the burning buildings/ and you say &lt;i&gt;I'll give you anything&lt;/i&gt; but you never come through." -- Richard Siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9081-to-absent-friends-lost-loves-old-gods-and-the-season</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 05:41:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9081-to-absent-friends-lost-loves-old-gods-and-the-season]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To absent friends, lost loves, old gods, and the season of mists; and may each and every one of us always give the devil his due." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/531882-girls-like-her-my-grandfather-once-warned-me-girls-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 17:32:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Holly Black]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/531882-girls-like-her-my-grandfather-once-warned-me-girls-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Girls like her, my grandfather once warned me, girls like her turn into women with eyes like bullet holes and mouths made of knives. They are always restless. They are always hungry. They are bad news. They will drink you down like a shot of whisky. Falling in love with them is like falling down a flight of stairs. What no one told me, with all those warnings, is that even after you’ve fallen, even after you know how painful it is, you’d still get in line to do it again." -- Holly Black]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/531878-she-wears-trouble-like-a-crown-if-she-ever-falls</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 17:32:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Holly Black]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/531878-she-wears-trouble-like-a-crown-if-she-ever-falls]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She wears trouble like a crown. If she ever falls in love, she’ll fall like a comet, burning the sky as she goes." -- Holly Black]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/477707-and-it-s-the-wonders-i-m-after-even-if-i-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 17:35:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/477707-and-it-s-the-wonders-i-m-after-even-if-i-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And it's the wonders I'm after, even if I have to bleed for them." -- Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116119-sleep-is-good-he-said-and-books-are-better</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 11:26:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by George R. R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116119-sleep-is-good-he-said-and-books-are-better]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sleep is good, he said, And books are better." -- George R. R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/452875-we-are-only-human-and-the-gods-have-fashioned-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 11:29:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/452875-we-are-only-human-and-the-gods-have-fashioned-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are only human, and the gods have fashioned us for love. That is our great glory, and our great tragedy." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/593843-how-much-sweeter-life-would-be-if-it-all-happened</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 16:01:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Karen Thompson Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/593843-how-much-sweeter-life-would-be-if-it-all-happened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How much sweeter life would be if it all happened in reverse, if, after decades of disappointments, you finally arrived at an age when you had conceded nothing, when everything was possible." -- Karen Thompson Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/845353-only-a-man-who-hates-his-privilege-can-be-trusted</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2013 08:34:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Rebecca Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/845353-only-a-man-who-hates-his-privilege-can-be-trusted]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only a man who hates his privilege can be trusted with it." -- Rebecca Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 09:14:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always imagined that Paradise will be a kind of library." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/304617-i-am-not-sure-that-i-exist-actually-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 09:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/304617-i-am-not-sure-that-i-exist-actually-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am not sure that I exist, actually. I am all the writers that I have read, all the people that I have met, all the women that I have loved; all the cities I have visited." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80788-to-fall-in-love-is-to-create-a-religion-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 09:14:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80788-to-fall-in-love-is-to-create-a-religion-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To fall in love is to create a religion that has a fallible god." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437769-when-writers-die-they-become-books-which-is-after-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 09:14:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437769-when-writers-die-they-become-books-which-is-after-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When writers die they become books, which is, after all, not too bad an incarnation.&quot;

[As attributed by Alastair Reid in &lt;i&gt;Neruda and Borges&lt;/i&gt;, The New Yorker, June 24, 1996; as well as in &lt;i&gt;The Talk of the Town&lt;/i&gt;, The New Yorker, July 7, 1986]" -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136491-heaven-and-hell-seem-out-of-proportion-to-me-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 09:14:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136491-heaven-and-hell-seem-out-of-proportion-to-me-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Heaven and hell seem out of proportion to me: the actions of men do not deserve so much." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9305-if-one-wanted-to-depict-the-whole-thing-graphically-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 09:15:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9305-if-one-wanted-to-depict-the-whole-thing-graphically-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If one wanted to depict the whole thing graphically, every episode, with its climax, would require a three-dimensional, or, rather, no model: every experience is unrepeatable. What makes lovemaking and reading resemble each other most is that within both of them times and spaces open, different from measurable time and space." -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247469-cities-like-dreams-are-made-of-desires-and-fears-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 09:15:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247469-cities-like-dreams-are-made-of-desires-and-fears-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cities, like dreams, are made of desires and fears, even if the thread of their discourse is secret, their rules are absurd, their perspectives deceitful, and everything conceals something else." -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111707-melancholy-is-sadness-that-has-taken-on-lightness</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 09:15:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111707-melancholy-is-sadness-that-has-taken-on-lightness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Melancholy is sadness that has taken on lightness." -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/724712-throw-roses-into-the-abyss-and-say-here-is-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 19:00:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/724712-throw-roses-into-the-abyss-and-say-here-is-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...throw roses into the abyss and say: 'here is my thanks to the monster who didn't succeed in swallowing me alive." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/844769-it-was-late-on-a-friday-afternoon-when-the-air</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 18:06:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Rebecca Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/844769-it-was-late-on-a-friday-afternoon-when-the-air]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was late on a Friday afternoon, when the air is fertile, about to split and reveal its warm fruit—that gold nucleus of time, the weekend." -- Rebecca Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/845337-earlier-that-day-i-had-found-a-sheet-of-paper</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 18:06:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Rebecca Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/845337-earlier-that-day-i-had-found-a-sheet-of-paper]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Earlier that day I had found a sheet of paper on which Min’s grandmother had written her definition of the “superior woman.” At the top of the page is said, “Formula for Woman, According to Dignity.” The formula was “Has excellent posture, which is two-thirds contentment and one-third desire.&quot;
At first I thought this a bit arbitrary. But all day the idea had been passing through my mind like a mantra. I began to think, in this strange place—half kingdom, half city—that the grandmother’s formula caught the entire world in its tiny palm. Two-thirds contentment, one-third desire. Of course, I thought, as I spiraled my way through the trees to Asia Foodstore, that is the composition of the world." -- Rebecca Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28721-genius-is-an-infinite-capacity-for-causing-pain</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 16:02:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28721-genius-is-an-infinite-capacity-for-causing-pain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Genius is an infinite capacity for causing pain." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320453-extreme-good-extreme-evil-the-abilities-required-are-similar</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 16:02:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320453-extreme-good-extreme-evil-the-abilities-required-are-similar]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Extreme good, extreme evil: the abilities required are similar." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275881-when-i-saw-him-look-at-me-with-lust-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 17:50:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Angela Carter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275881-when-i-saw-him-look-at-me-with-lust-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I saw him look at me with lust, I dropped my eyes but, in glancing away from him, I caught sight of myself in the mirror. And I saw myself, suddenly, as he saw me, my pale face, the way the muscles in my neck stuck out like thin wire. I saw how much that cruel necklace became me. And, for the first time in my innocent and confined life, I sensed in myself a potentiality for corruption that took my breath away." -- Angela Carter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335167-anticipation-is-the-greater-part-of-pleasure</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 17:50:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Angela Carter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335167-anticipation-is-the-greater-part-of-pleasure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anticipation is the greater part of pleasure." -- Angela Carter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335168-there-is-a-striking-resemblance-between-the-act-of-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2014 11:56:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katya add a quote by Angela Carter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335168-there-is-a-striking-resemblance-between-the-act-of-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a striking resemblance between the act of love and the ministrations of a torturer." -- Angela Carter]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
