<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/335643-sandra]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/335643-sandra" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 03:57:20 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48084-so-in-america-when-the-sun-goes-down-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 03:57:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48084-so-in-america-when-the-sun-goes-down-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So in America when the sun goes down and I sit on the old broken-down river pier watching the long, long skies over New Jersey and sense all that raw land that rolls in one unbelievable huge bulge over to the West Coast, and all that road going, and all the people dreaming in the immensity of it, and in Iowa I know by now the children must be crying in the land where they let the children cry, and tonight the stars'll be out, and don't you know that God is Pooh Bear? the evening star must be drooping and shedding her sparkler dims on the prairie, which is just before the coming of complete night that blesses the earth, darkens all the rivers, cups the peaks and folds the final shore in, and nobody, nobody knows what's going to happen to anybody besides the forlorn rags of growing old, I think of Dean Moriarty, I even think of Old Dean Moriarty the father we never found, I think of Dean Moriarty." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43917-my-witness-is-the-empty-sky</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 03:57:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43917-my-witness-is-the-empty-sky]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My witness is the empty sky." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 03:57:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the only people for me are the mad ones, the ones who are mad to live, mad to talk, mad to be saved, desirous of everything at the same time, the ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn like fabulous yellow roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2798-i-like-too-many-things-and-get-all-confused-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 03:57:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2798-i-like-too-many-things-and-get-all-confused-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like too many things and get all confused and hung-up running from one falling star to another till i drop. This is the night, what it does to you. I had nothing to offer anybody except my own confusion." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21577-happiness-consists-in-realizing-it-is-all-a-great-strange</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 03:58:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21577-happiness-consists-in-realizing-it-is-all-a-great-strange]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness consists in realizing it is all a great strange dream" -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8525-what-is-that-feeling-when-you-re-driving-away-from-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 03:58:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8525-what-is-that-feeling-when-you-re-driving-away-from-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is that feeling when you're driving away from people and they recede on the plain till you see their specks dispersing? - it's the too-huge world vaulting us, and it's good-bye. But we lean forward to the next crazy venture beneath the skies." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12860-every-heart-sings-a-song-incomplete-until-another-heart-whispers</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:09:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Plato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12860-every-heart-sings-a-song-incomplete-until-another-heart-whispers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every heart sings a song, incomplete, until another heart whispers back. Those who wish to sing always find a song. At the touch of a lover, everyone becomes a poet." -- Plato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54454-she-says-nothing-at-all-but-simply-stares-upward-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:09:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54454-she-says-nothing-at-all-but-simply-stares-upward-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She says nothing at all, but simply stares upward into the dark sky and watches, with sad eyes, the slow dance of the infinite stars." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66772-never-love-a-wild-thing-mr-bell-holly-advised-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:10:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Truman Capote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66772-never-love-a-wild-thing-mr-bell-holly-advised-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never love a wild thing, Mr. Bell,' Holly advised him. 'That was Doc's mistake. He was always lugging home wild things. A hawk with a hurt wing. One time it was a full-grown bobcat with a broken leg. But you can't give your heart to a wild thing: the more you do, the stronger they get. Until they're strong enough to run into the woods. Or fly into a tree. Then a taller tree. Then the sky. That's how you'll end up, Mr. Bell. If you let yourself love a wild thing. You'll end up looking at the sky.&quot;
&quot;She's drunk,&quot; Joe Bell informed me. 
&quot;Moderately,&quot; Holly confessed....Holly lifted her martini. &quot;Let's wish the Doc luck, too,&quot; she said, touching her glass against mine. &quot;Good luck: and believe me, dearest Doc -- it's better to look at the sky than live there. Such an empty place; so vague. Just a country where the thunder goes and things disappear." -- Truman Capote]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34708-she-was-still-hugging-the-cat-poor-slob-she-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:10:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Truman Capote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34708-she-was-still-hugging-the-cat-poor-slob-she-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was still hugging the cat. &quot;Poor slob,&quot; she said, tickling his head, &quot;poor slob without a name. It's a little inconvenient, his not having a name. But I haven't any right to give him one: he'll have to wait until he belongs to somebody. We just sort of took up by the river one day, we don't belong to each other: he's an independent, and so am I. I don't want to own anything until I know I've found the place where me and things belong together. I'm not quite sure where that is just yet. But I know what it's like.&quot; She smiled, and let the cat drop to the floor. &quot;It's like Tiffany's,&quot; she said.

[...]

It calms me down right away, the quietness and the proud look of it; nothing very bad could happen to you there, not with those kind men in their nice suits, and that lovely smell of silver and alligator wallets. If I could find a real-life place that made me feel like Tiffany's, then I'd buy some furniture and give the cat a name." -- Truman Capote]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52574-the-answer-is-never-the-answer-what-s-really-interesting-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:12:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Ken Kesey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52574-the-answer-is-never-the-answer-what-s-really-interesting-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The answer is never the answer. What's really interesting is the mystery. If you seek the mystery instead of the answer, you'll always be seeking. I've never seen anybody really find the answer. They think they have, so they stop thinking. But the job is to seek mystery, evoke mystery, plant a garden in which strange plants grow and mysteries bloom. The need for mystery is greater than the need for an answer." -- Ken Kesey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84943-this-world-belongs-to-the-strong-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:12:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Ken Kesey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84943-this-world-belongs-to-the-strong-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This world . . . belongs to the strong, my friend!  The ritual of our existence is based on the strong getting stronger by devouring the weak.  We must face up to this.  No more than right that it should be this way.  We must learn to accept it as a law of the natural world.  The rabbits accept their role in the ritual and recognize the wolf is the strong.  In defense, the rabbit becomes sly and frightened and elusive and he digs holes and hides when the wolf is about.  And he endures, he goes on.  He knows his place.  He most certainly doesn't challenge the wolf to combat.  Now, would that be wise?  Would it?" -- Ken Kesey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25-we-are-all-in-the-gutter-but-some-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:14:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25-we-are-all-in-the-gutter-but-some-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all in the gutter, but some of us are looking at the stars." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6856-if-one-cannot-enjoy-reading-a-book-over-and-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:15:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6856-if-one-cannot-enjoy-reading-a-book-over-and-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If one cannot enjoy reading a book over and over again, there is no use in reading it at all." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1231-be-kind-for-everyone-you-meet-is-fighting-a-harder</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:34:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Plato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1231-be-kind-for-everyone-you-meet-is-fighting-a-harder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be kind, for everyone you meet is fighting a harder battle." -- Plato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8808-wise-men-speak-because-they-have-something-to-say-fools</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:35:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Plato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8808-wise-men-speak-because-they-have-something-to-say-fools]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wise men speak because they have something to say; fools because they have to say something." -- Plato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22763-when-we-read-another-person-thinks-for-us-we-merely</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:35:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by arthur schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22763-when-we-read-another-person-thinks-for-us-we-merely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we read, another person thinks for us: we merely repeat his mental process. In learning to write, the pupil goes over with his pen what the teacher has outlined in pencil: so in reading; the greater part of the work of thought is already done for us. This is why it relieves us to take up a book after being occupied with our own thoughts. And in reading, the mind is, in fact, only the playground of another’s thoughts. So it comes about that if anyone spends almost the whole day in reading, and by way of relaxation devotes the intervals to some thoughtless pastime, he gradually loses the capacity for thinking; just as the man who always rides, at last forgets how to walk. This is the case with many learned persons: they have read themselves stupid." -- arthur schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27925-reading-is-merely-a-surrogate-for-thinking-for-yourself-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:36:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27925-reading-is-merely-a-surrogate-for-thinking-for-yourself-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reading is merely a surrogate for thinking for yourself; it means letting someone else direct your thoughts. Many books, moreover, serve merely to show how many ways there are of being wrong, and how far astray you yourself would go if you followed their guidance. You should read only when your own thoughts dry up, which will of course happen frequently enough even to the best heads; but to banish your own thoughts so as to take up a book is a sin against the holy ghost; it is like deserting untrammeled nature to look at a herbarium or engravings of landscapes." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8705-a-dream-you-dream-alone-is-only-a-dream-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:37:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8705-a-dream-you-dream-alone-is-only-a-dream-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A dream you dream alone is only a dream. A dream you dream together is reality." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12444-i-believe-in-everything-until-it-s-disproved-so-i-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:37:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12444-i-believe-in-everything-until-it-s-disproved-so-i-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in everything until it's disproved. So I believe in fairies, the myths, dragons. It all exists, even if it's in your mind. Who's to say that dreams and nightmares aren't as real as the here and now?" -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3026-if-you-live-to-be-a-hundred-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:39:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3026-if-you-live-to-be-a-hundred-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you live to be a hundred, I want to live to be a hundred minus one day so I never have to live without you." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46292-we-ll-be-friends-forever-won-t-we-pooh-asked-piglet-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:40:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46292-we-ll-be-friends-forever-won-t-we-pooh-asked-piglet-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We'll be Friends Forever, won't we, Pooh?' asked Piglet.
Even longer,' Pooh answered." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9333-did-you-ever-stop-to-think-and-forget-to-start</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:40:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9333-did-you-ever-stop-to-think-and-forget-to-start]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did you ever stop to think, and forget to start again?" -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6052-sometimes-if-you-stand-on-the-bottom-rail-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:40:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6052-sometimes-if-you-stand-on-the-bottom-rail-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, if you stand on the bottom rail of a bridge and lean over to watch the river slipping slowly away beneath you, you will suddenly know everything there is to be known." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14485-but-i-don-t-want-to-go-among-mad-people-alice</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:42:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14485-but-i-don-t-want-to-go-among-mad-people-alice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I don’t want to go among mad people,&quot; Alice remarked.
&quot;Oh, you can’t help that,&quot; said the Cat: &quot;we’re all mad here. I’m mad. You’re mad.&quot;
&quot;How do you know I’m mad?&quot; said Alice.
&quot;You must be,&quot; said the Cat, or you wouldn’t have come here." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2424-would-you-tell-me-please-which-way-i-ought-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:42:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2424-would-you-tell-me-please-which-way-i-ought-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Would you tell me, please, which way I ought to go from here?&quot;
&quot;That depends a good deal on where you want to get to.&quot;
&quot;I don't much care where –&quot;
&quot;Then it doesn't matter which way you go." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1139-she-generally-gave-herself-very-good-advice-though-she-very</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:42:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1139-she-generally-gave-herself-very-good-advice-though-she-very]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She generally gave herself very good advice, (though she very seldom followed it)." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9467-alice-laughed-there-s-no-use-trying-she-said-one-can-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:42:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9467-alice-laughed-there-s-no-use-trying-she-said-one-can-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alice laughed. 'There's no use trying,' she said. 'One can't believe impossible things.'

I daresay you haven't had much practice,' said the Queen. 'When I was your age, I always did it for half-an-hour a day. Why, sometimes I've believed as many as six impossible things before breakfast. There goes the shawl again!" -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:43:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lolita, light of my life, fire of my loins. My sin, my soul. Lo-lee-ta: the tip of the tongue taking a trip of three steps down the palate to tap, at three, on the teeth. Lo. Lee. Ta. She was Lo, plain Lo, in the morning, standing four feet ten in one sock. She was Lola in slacks. She was Dolly at school. She was Dolores on the dotted line. But in my arms she was always Lolita. Did she have a precursor? She did, indeed she did. In point of fact, there might have been no Lolita at all had I not loved, one summer, an initial girl-child. In a princedom by the sea. Oh when? About as many years before Lolita was born as my age was that summer. You can always count on a murderer for a fancy prose style. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, exhibit number one is what the seraphs, the misinformed, simple, noble-winged seraphs, envied. Look at this tangle of thorns." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38129-literature-was-not-born-the-day-when-a-boy-crying</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 09:44:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38129-literature-was-not-born-the-day-when-a-boy-crying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Literature was not born the day when a boy crying &quot;wolf, wolf&quot; came running out of the Neanderthal valley with a big gray wolf at his heels; literature was born on the day when a boy came crying &quot;wolf, wolf&quot; and there was no wolf behind him." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
