<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/33597-jillbertini]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/33597-jillbertini" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 12:53:41 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2627-the-trouble-with-having-an-open-mind-of-course-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 12:53:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jillbertini add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2627-the-trouble-with-having-an-open-mind-of-course-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble with having an open mind, of course, is that people will insist on coming along and trying to put things in it." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498578-that-is-what-literature-offers-a-language-powerful-enough-to-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 08:32:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jillbertini add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498578-that-is-what-literature-offers-a-language-powerful-enough-to-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That is what literature offers—a language powerful enough to say how it is. It isn't a hiding place. It is a finding place." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584289-there-is-still-a-popular-fantasy-long-since-disproved-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 08:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jillbertini add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584289-there-is-still-a-popular-fantasy-long-since-disproved-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is still a popular fantasy, long since disproved by both psychoanalysis and science, and never believed by any poet or mystic, that it is possible to have a thought without a feeling. It isn't. When we are objective we are subjective too. When we are neutral we are involved. When we say ‘I think’ we don't leave our emotions outside the door. To tell someone not to be emotional is to tell them to be dead." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134827-too-many-of-us-are-hung-up-on-what-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 11:34:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jillbertini add a quote by Terry McMillan ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134827-too-many-of-us-are-hung-up-on-what-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Too many of us are hung up on what we don't have, can't have, or won't ever have. We spend too much energy being down, when we could use that same energy – if not less of it – doing, or at least trying to do, some of the things we really want to do." -- Terry McMillan ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177066-love-takes-off-the-masks-that-we-fear-we-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 17:36:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jillbertini add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177066-love-takes-off-the-masks-that-we-fear-we-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love takes off the masks that we fear we cannot live without and know we cannot live within. I use the word &quot;love&quot; here not merely in the personal sense but as a state of being, or a state of grace - not in the infantile American sense of being made happy but in the tough and universal sense of quest and daring and growth." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/724212-she-reaches-down-into-her-bulging-tote-bag-and-pulls</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 16:29:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jillbertini add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/724212-she-reaches-down-into-her-bulging-tote-bag-and-pulls]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She reaches down into her bulging tote bag and pulls out a small plastic box with a hinged lid. It contains a round pill box with a threaded lid from which she tips out a vitamin pill, a fish-oil pill, and the enzyme tablet that lets her stomach digest milk. Inside the hinged plastic box she also carries packets of salt, pepper, horseradish, and hand-wipes, a doll size bottle of Tabasco sauce, chlorine pills for treating drinking water, Pepto-Bismol chews, and God knows what else. If you go to a concert, Bina has opera glasses. If you need to sit on the grass, she whips out a towel. Ant traps, a corkscrew, candles and matches, a dog muzzle, a penknife, a tiny aerosol can of freon, a magnifying glass - Landsman has seen everything come out of that overstuffed cowhide at one time or another." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12425-when-i-dare-to-be-powerful-to-use-my-strength</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 13:03:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jillbertini add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12425-when-i-dare-to-be-powerful-to-use-my-strength]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I dare to be powerful, to use my strength in the service of my vision, then it becomes less and less important whether I am afraid." -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/499847-ours-is-only-a-little-power-seems-like-next-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 14:51:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jillbertini add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/499847-ours-is-only-a-little-power-seems-like-next-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ours is only a little power, seems like, next to theirs,&quot; Moss said. &quot;But it goes down deep. It's all roots. It's like an old blackberry thicket. And a wizard's power's like a fir tree, maybe, great and tall and grand, but it'll blow right down in a storm. Nothing kills a blackberry bramble." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
