<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/33697-linda-sardisco]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/33697-linda-sardisco" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 18:35:41 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706708-an-honest-bookstore-would-post-the-following-sign-above-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 18:35:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[linda add a quote by Roger Ebert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706708-an-honest-bookstore-would-post-the-following-sign-above-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An honest bookstore would post the following sign above its 'self-help' section: 'For true self-help, please visit our philosophy, literature, history and science sections, find yourself a good book, read it, and think about it." -- Roger Ebert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59937-everyone-at-some-point-in-their-lives-wakes-up-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 07:38:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[linda add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59937-everyone-at-some-point-in-their-lives-wakes-up-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone, at some point in their lives, wakes up in the middle of the night with the feeling that they are all alone in the world, and that nobody loves them now and that nobody will ever love them, and that they will never have a decent night's sleep again and will spend their lives wandering blearily around a loveless landscape, hoping desperately that their circumstances will improve, but suspecting, in their heart of hearts, that they will remain unloved forever. The best thing to do in these circumstances is to wake somebody else up, so that they can feel this way, too." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/749475-when-you-slip-on-a-banana-peel-people-laugh-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 17:00:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[linda add a quote by Nora Ephron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/749475-when-you-slip-on-a-banana-peel-people-laugh-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you slip on a banana peel, people laugh at you. But when you tell people you slipped on a banana peel, it's your laugh." -- Nora Ephron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22263-there-is-only-one-way-to-read-which-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 11:55:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[linda add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22263-there-is-only-one-way-to-read-which-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is only one way to read, which is to browse in libraries and bookshops, picking up books that attract you, reading only those, dropping them when they bore you, skipping the parts that drag-and never, never reading anything because you feel you ought, or because it is part of a trend or a movement.  Remember that the book which bores you when you are twenty or thirty will open doors for you when you are forty or fifty-and vise versa.  Don’t read a book out of its right time for you.  " -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
