<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/337087-briana]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/337087-briana" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 09:29:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391669-you-ve-got-this-life-and-while-you-ve-got-it-you-d</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 09:29:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Briana add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391669-you-ve-got-this-life-and-while-you-ve-got-it-you-d]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've got this life and while you've got it, you'd better kiss like you only have one moment, try to hold someone's hand like you will never get another chance to, look into people's eyes like they're the last you'll ever see, watch someone sleeping like there's no time left, jump if you feel like jumping, run if you feel like running, play music in your head when there is none, and eat cake like it's the only one left in the world!" -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357281-they-say-a-good-love-is-one-that-sits-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 09:29:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Briana add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357281-they-say-a-good-love-is-one-that-sits-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They say a good love is one that sits you down, gives you a drink of water, and pats you on top of the head. But I say a good love is one that casts you into the wind, sets you ablaze, makes you burn through the skies and ignite the night like a phoenix; the kind that cuts you loose like a wildfire and you can't stop running simply because you keep on burning everything that you touch! I say that's a good love; one that burns and flies, and you run with it!" -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17158-the-miracle-isn-t-that-i-finished-the-miracle-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 09:29:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Briana add a quote by John Bingham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17158-the-miracle-isn-t-that-i-finished-the-miracle-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The miracle isn't that I finished. The miracle is that I had the courage to start." -- John Bingham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171410-we-are-walking-down-the-street-holding-hands-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 09:30:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Briana add a quote by Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171410-we-are-walking-down-the-street-holding-hands-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are walking down the street holding hands. There is a playground at the end of the block, and I run to the swings and I climb on and Henry takes the one next to me facing the opposite direction. And we swing higher and higher passing each other, sometimes in synch and sometimes streaming past each other so fast that it seems we are going to collide. And we laugh and laugh, and nothing can ever be sad, no one can be lost or dead or far away. Right now we are here and nothing can mar our perfection or steal the joy of this perfect moment." -- Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76115-it-was-being-a-runner-that-mattered-not-how-fast</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 09:30:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Briana add a quote by John Bingham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76115-it-was-being-a-runner-that-mattered-not-how-fast]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was being a runner that mattered, not how fast or how far I could run. The joy was in the act of running and in the journey, not in the destination. We have a better chance of seeing where we are when we stop trying to get somewhere else. We can enjoy every moment of movement, as long as where we are is as good as where we'd like to be. That's not to say that you need to be satisfied  forever with where you are today. But you need to honor what you've accomplished, rather than thinking of what's left to be done (p. 159)." -- John Bingham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123323-if-she-know-how-strongly-he-felt-she-d-have-run</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 09:30:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Briana add a quote by Patricia Briggs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123323-if-she-know-how-strongly-he-felt-she-d-have-run]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If she know how strongly he felt, she'd have run out the door. He wasn't used to the possessive, or the savage joy she brought to his heart. It ate at his control, so he turned his attention to the music. He understood music." -- Patricia Briggs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107805-the-same-stream-of-life-that-runs-through-my-veins</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 09:30:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Briana add a quote by Rabindranath Tagore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107805-the-same-stream-of-life-that-runs-through-my-veins]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The same stream of life that runs through my veins night and day runs through the world and dances in rhythmic measures. It is the same life that shoots in joy through the dust of the earth in numberless blades of grass and breaks into tumultuous waves of leaves and flowers." -- Rabindranath Tagore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325827-and-now-i-know-why-they-invented-words-for-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 09:31:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Briana add a quote by Lauren Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325827-and-now-i-know-why-they-invented-words-for-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And now I know why they invented words for love, why they had to: It's the only thing that can come close to describing what I feel in that moment, the baffling mixture of pain and pleasure and fear and joy, all running sharply through me at once." -- Lauren Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
