<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/337145-cat]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/337145-cat" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 22:38:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76662-do-you-know-i-always-thought-unicorns-were-fabulous-monsters</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 22:38:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76662-do-you-know-i-always-thought-unicorns-were-fabulous-monsters]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you know, I always thought unicorns were fabulous monsters, too? I never saw one alive before!&quot;

Well, now that we have seen each other,&quot; said the unicorn, &quot;if you'll believe in me, I'll believe in you." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65611-i-am-an-excitable-person-who-only-understands-life-lyrically</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 20:19:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65611-i-am-an-excitable-person-who-only-understands-life-lyrically]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am an excitable person who only understands life lyrically, musically, in whom feelings are much stronger as reason. I am so thirsty for the marvelous that only the marvelous has power over me. Anything I can not transform into something marvelous, I let go. Reality doesn't impress me. I only believe in intoxication, in ecstasy, and when ordinary life shackles me, I escape, one way or another. No more walls." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15244-there-were-always-in-me-two-women-at-least-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 20:19:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15244-there-were-always-in-me-two-women-at-least-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There were always in me, two women at least, one woman desperate and bewildered, who felt she was drowning and another who would leap into a scene, as upon a stage, conceal her true emotions because they were weaknesses, helplessness, despair, and present to the world only a smile, an eagerness, curiosity, enthusiasm, interest." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18404-everything-with-me-is-either-worship-and-passion-or-pity</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 20:19:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18404-everything-with-me-is-either-worship-and-passion-or-pity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything with me is either worship and passion or pity and understanding. I hate rarely, though when I hate, I hate murderously. For example now, I hate the bank and everything connected with it. I also hate Dutch paintings, penis-sucking, parties, and cold rainy weather. But I am much more preoccupied with loving." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75659-i-talk-too-much-because-i-have-been-made-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 20:20:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Djuna Barnes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75659-i-talk-too-much-because-i-have-been-made-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I talk too much because I have been made so miserable by what you are keeping hushed." -- Djuna Barnes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14303-writing-is-like-sex-first-you-do-it-for-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 20:21:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14303-writing-is-like-sex-first-you-do-it-for-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing is like sex. First you do it for love, then you do it for your friends, and then you do it for money." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4819-when-you-consider-things-like-the-stars-our-affairs-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 20:21:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Virginia Woolf ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4819-when-you-consider-things-like-the-stars-our-affairs-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you consider things like the stars, our affairs don't seem to matter very much, do they?" -- Virginia Woolf ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/773-when-the-day-of-judgment-dawns-and-people-great-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 20:22:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/773-when-the-day-of-judgment-dawns-and-people-great-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the Day of Judgment dawns and people, great and small, come marching in to receive their heavenly rewards, the Almighty will gaze upon the mere bookworms and say to Peter, “Look, these need no reward. We have nothing to give them. They have loved reading." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11475-nothing-thicker-than-a-knife-s-blade-separates-happiness-from-melancholy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 20:22:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11475-nothing-thicker-than-a-knife-s-blade-separates-happiness-from-melancholy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing thicker than a knife's blade separates happiness from melancholy." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12863-i-can-only-note-that-the-past-is-beautiful-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 20:23:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12863-i-can-only-note-that-the-past-is-beautiful-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can only note that the past is beautiful because one never realises an emotion at the time. It expands later, and thus we don't have complete emotions about the present, only about the past." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50907-i-am-prone-to-envy-it-is-one-of-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 20:24:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Augusten Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50907-i-am-prone-to-envy-it-is-one-of-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am prone to envy. It is one of my three default emotions, the others being greed and rage. I have also experienced compassion and generosity, but only fleetingly and usually while drunk, so I have little memory." -- Augusten Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79704-this-is-growing-up-having-to-stomp-out-love-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 20:28:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Michelle Tea]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79704-this-is-growing-up-having-to-stomp-out-love-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is growing up, having to stomp out love, this is how people turn terrible." -- Michelle Tea]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4952-everywhere-i-go-i-m-asked-if-i-think-the-university</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 20:30:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4952-everywhere-i-go-i-m-asked-if-i-think-the-university]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everywhere I go I'm asked if I think the university stifles writers. My opinion is that they don't stifle enough of them. There's many a best-seller that could have been prevented by a good teacher." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4951-the-truth-does-not-change-according-to-our-ability-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 20:30:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4951-the-truth-does-not-change-according-to-our-ability-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth does not change according to our ability to stomach it." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3443-when-one-door-of-happiness-closes-another-opens-but-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 13:17:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Helen Keller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3443-when-one-door-of-happiness-closes-another-opens-but-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When one door of happiness closes, another opens; but often we look so long at the closed door that we do not see the one which has been opened for us." -- Helen Keller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7038-kiss-me-and-you-will-see-how-important-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 20:33:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7038-kiss-me-and-you-will-see-how-important-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kiss me, and you will see how important I am." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/922-i-took-a-deep-breath-and-listened-to-the-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 20:33:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/922-i-took-a-deep-breath-and-listened-to-the-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I took a deep breath and listened to the old brag of my heart. I am, I am, I am." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2009 08:26:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30407-first-of-all-love-is-a-joint-experience-between-two</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 10:27:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by carson mccullers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30407-first-of-all-love-is-a-joint-experience-between-two]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First of all, love is a joint experience between two persons — but the fact that it is a joint experience does not mean that it is a similar experience to the two people involved. There are the lover and the beloved, but these two come from different countries. Often the beloved is only a stimulus for all the stored-up love which had lain quiet within the lover for a long time hitherto. And somehow every lover knows this. He feels in his soul that his love is a solitary thing. He comes to know a new, strange loneliness and it is this knowledge which makes him suffer. So there is only one thing for the lover to do. He must house his love within himself as best he can; he must create for himself a whole new inward world — a world intense and strange, complete in himself. Let it be added here that this lover about whom we speak need not necessarily be a young man saving for a wedding ring — this lover can be man, woman, child, or indeed any human creature on this earth.

Now, the beloved can also be of any description. The most outlandish people can be the stimulus for love. A man may be a doddering great-grandfather and still love only a strange girl he saw in the streets of Cheehaw one afternoon two decades past. The preacher may love a fallen woman. The beloved may be treacherous, greasy-headed, and given to evil habits. Yes, and the lover may see this as clearly as anyone else — but that does not affect the evolution of his love one whit. A most mediocre person can be the object of a love which is wild, extravagant, and beautiful as the poison lilies of the swamp. A good man may be the stimulus for a love both violent and debased, or a jabbering madman may bring about in the soul of someone a tender and simple idyll. Therefore, the value and quality of any love is determined solely by the lover himself.

It is for this reason that most of us would rather love than be loved. Almost everyone wants to be the lover. And the curt truth is that, in a deep secret way, the state of being beloved is intolerable to many. The beloved fears and hates the lover, and with the best of reasons. For the lover is forever trying to strip bare his beloved. The lover craves any possible relation with the beloved, even if this experience can cause him only pain." -- carson mccullers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159950-how-can-the-dead-be-truly-dead-when-they-still</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 10:27:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Carson McCullers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159950-how-can-the-dead-be-truly-dead-when-they-still]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How can the dead be truly dead when they still live in the souls of those who are left behind?" -- Carson McCullers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17678-many-persons-have-a-wrong-idea-of-what-constitutes-true</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2009 11:04:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Helen Keller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17678-many-persons-have-a-wrong-idea-of-what-constitutes-true]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many persons have a wrong idea of what constitutes true happiness. It is not attained through self-gratification but through fidelity to a worthy purpose." -- Helen Keller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18405-and-sometimes-i-believe-your-relentless-analysis-of-june-leaves</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 14:14:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18405-and-sometimes-i-believe-your-relentless-analysis-of-june-leaves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And sometimes I believe your relentless analysis of June leaves something out, which is your feeling for her beyond knowledge, or in spite of knowledge. I often see how you sob over what you destroy, how you want to stop and just worship; and you do stop, and then a moment later you are at it again with a knife, like a surgeon.
What will you do after you have revealed all there is to know about June? Truth. What ferocity in your quest of it. You destroy and you suffer. In some strange way I am not with you, I am against you. We are destined to hold two truths. I love you and I fight you. And you, the same. We will be stronger for it, each of us, stronger with our love and our hate. When you caricature and nail down and tear apart, I hate you. I want to answer you, not with weak or stupid poetry but with a wonder as strong as your reality. I want to fight your surgical knife with all the occult and magical forces of the world." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38359-i-drank-to-drown-my-sorrows-but-the-damned-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 22:02:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Frida Kahlo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38359-i-drank-to-drown-my-sorrows-but-the-damned-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I drank to drown my sorrows, but the damned  things learned how to swim." -- Frida Kahlo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57169-an-elegant-woman-is-a-woman-who-despises-you-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 22:04:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Salvador Dali]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57169-an-elegant-woman-is-a-woman-who-despises-you-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An elegant woman is a woman who despises you and has no hair under her arms." -- Salvador Dali]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94242-since-i-don-t-smoke-i-decided-to-grow-a-mustache</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 22:04:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Salvador Dalí]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94242-since-i-don-t-smoke-i-decided-to-grow-a-mustache]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Since I don't smoke, I decided to grow a mustache - it is better for the health.
However, I always carried a jewel-studded cigarette case in which, instead of tobacco, were carefully placed several mustaches, Adolphe Menjou style. I offered them politely to my friends: &quot;Mustache? Mustache? Mustache?&quot;
Nobody dared to touch them. This was my test regarding the sacred aspect of mustaches." -- Salvador Dalí]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178997-love-involves-a-peculiar-unfathomable-combination-of-understanding-and-misunderstanding</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 10:18:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Diane Arbus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178997-love-involves-a-peculiar-unfathomable-combination-of-understanding-and-misunderstanding]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love involves a peculiar unfathomable combination of understanding and misunderstanding" -- Diane Arbus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70721-all-forms-of-art-are-consciousness-expanders-and-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 16:22:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70721-all-forms-of-art-are-consciousness-expanders-and-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All forms of art are consciousness expanders, and I am convinced that they will take us further, and more consciously, than drugs." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42716-love-they-say-enslaves-and-passion-is-a-demon-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 12:49:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42716-love-they-say-enslaves-and-passion-is-a-demon-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love, they say, enslaves and passion is a demon and many have been lost for love. I know this is true, but I know too that without love we grope the tunnels of our lives and never see the sun. When I fell in love it was as though I looked into a mirror for the first time and saw myself. I lifted my hand in bewilderment and felt my cheeks, my neck. This was me. And when I had looked at myself and grown accustomed to who I was, I was not afraid to hate parts of me because I wanted to be worthy of the mirror bearer." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24309-love-is-the-one-thing-stronger-than-desire-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 12:49:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24309-love-is-the-one-thing-stronger-than-desire-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is the one thing stronger than desire and the only proper reason to resist temptation." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130289-when-i-look-at-my-life-i-realise-that-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 12:49:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130289-when-i-look-at-my-life-i-realise-that-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I look at my life I realise that the mistakes I have made, the things I really regret, were not errors of judgement but failures of feeling." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
