<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/337706-riley]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/337706-riley" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 22:12:12 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59937-everyone-at-some-point-in-their-lives-wakes-up-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 22:12:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[riley add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59937-everyone-at-some-point-in-their-lives-wakes-up-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone, at some point in their lives, wakes up in the middle of the night with the feeling that they are all alone in the world, and that nobody loves them now and that nobody will ever love them, and that they will never have a decent night's sleep again and will spend their lives wandering blearily around a loveless landscape, hoping desperately that their circumstances will improve, but suspecting, in their heart of hearts, that they will remain unloved forever. The best thing to do in these circumstances is to wake somebody else up, so that they can feel this way, too." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13155-it-is-a-curious-thing-the-death-of-a-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 22:11:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[riley add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13155-it-is-a-curious-thing-the-death-of-a-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a curious thing, the death of a loved one. We all know that our time in this world is limited, and that eventually all of us will end up underneath some sheet, never to wake up. And yet it is always a surprise when it happens to someone we know. It is like walking up the stairs to your bedroom in the dark, and thinking there is one more stair than there is. Your foot falls down, through the air, and there is a sickly moment of dark surprise as you try and readjust the way you thought of things." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16160-but-who-can-say-what-s-best-that-s-why-you-need</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 22:44:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[riley add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16160-but-who-can-say-what-s-best-that-s-why-you-need]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But who can say what's best? That's why you need to grab whatever chance you have of happiness where you find it, and not worry about other people too much. My experience tells me that we get no more than two or three such chances in a life time, and if we let them go, we regret it for the rest of our lives." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206168-enduring-and-forgiving-are-two-different-things-you-must-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 22:55:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[riley add a quote by Hiromu Arakawa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206168-enduring-and-forgiving-are-two-different-things-you-must-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;i&gt;Enduring&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;forgiving&lt;/i&gt; are two different things.  You must not forgive the cruelty of this world.  It's our duty as human beings to be angry at injustice.  But we must also endure it.  Because someone must sever this chain of hatred." -- Hiromu Arakawa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266841-a-lesson-without-pain-is-meaningless-for-you-cannot-gain</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 22:55:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[riley add a quote by Hiromu Arakawa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266841-a-lesson-without-pain-is-meaningless-for-you-cannot-gain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A lesson without pain is meaningless. For you cannot gain anything without sacrificing something else in return, but once you have overcome it and made it your own...you will gain an irreplaceable fullmetal heart." -- Hiromu Arakawa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137227-real-love-amounts-to-withholding-the-truth-even-when-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2012 13:36:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[riley add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137227-real-love-amounts-to-withholding-the-truth-even-when-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Real love amounts to withholding the truth, even when you're offered the perfect opportunity to hurt someone's feelings" -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39529-hugh-and-i-have-been-together-for-so-long-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2012 13:36:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[riley add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39529-hugh-and-i-have-been-together-for-so-long-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hugh and I have been together for so long that in order to arouse extraordinary passion, we need to engage in physical combat. Once, he hit me on the back of the head with a broken wineglass, and I fell to the floor pretending to be unconscious. That was romantic, or would have been had he rushed to my side rather than stepping over my body to fetch the dustpan." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145140-a-book-is-made-from-a-tree-it-is-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 22:03:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[riley add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145140-a-book-is-made-from-a-tree-it-is-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book is made from a tree. It is an assemblage of flat, flexible parts (still called &quot;leaves&quot;) imprinted with dark pigmented squiggles. One glance at it and you hear the voice of another person, perhaps someone dead for thousands of years. Across the millennia, the author is speaking, clearly and silently, inside your head, directly to you. Writing is perhaps the greatest of human inventions, binding together people, citizens of distant epochs, who never knew one another. Books break the shackles of time ― proof that humans can work magic." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198886-it-s-not-that-you-should-never-love-something-so-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 08:30:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[riley add a quote by Patrick Ness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198886-it-s-not-that-you-should-never-love-something-so-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not that you should never love something so much that it can control you.
It's that you need to love something that much so you can never be controlled.
It's not a weakness.
It's your best strength." -- Patrick Ness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399123-stories-are-wild-creatures-the-monster-said-when-you-let</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 15:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[riley add a quote by Patrick Ness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399123-stories-are-wild-creatures-the-monster-said-when-you-let]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;i&gt;Stories are wild creatures&lt;/i&gt;, the monster said. &lt;i&gt;When you let them loose, who knows what havoc they might wreak?&lt;/i&gt;" -- Patrick Ness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/567103-and-this-even-more-wonderful-and-mysterious-is-also-true</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 21:10:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[riley add a quote by Elizabeth Wein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/567103-and-this-even-more-wonderful-and-mysterious-is-also-true]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And this, even more wonderful and mysterious, is also true: when I read it, when I read what Julie's written, she is instantly alive again, whole and undamaged. With her words in my mind while I'm reading, she is as real as I am. Gloriously daft, drop-dead charming, full of bookish nonsense and foul language, brave and generous. She's &lt;i&gt;right here&lt;/i&gt;. Afraid and exhausted, alone, but &lt;i&gt;fighting&lt;/i&gt;. Flying in silver moonlight in a plane that can't be landed, stuck in the climb—alive, alive, ALIVE." -- Elizabeth Wein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/795895-oh-julie-wouldn-t-i-know-if-you-were-dead-wouldn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 21:10:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[riley add a quote by Elizabeth Wein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/795895-oh-julie-wouldn-t-i-know-if-you-were-dead-wouldn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh Julie, wouldn’t I know if you were dead? Wouldn’t I feel it happening, like a jolt of electricity to my heart?" -- Elizabeth Wein]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
