<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/339101-laura]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/339101-laura" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 18:00:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81428-d-on-t-ever-apologize-to-an-author-for-buying-something-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 18:00:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81428-d-on-t-ever-apologize-to-an-author-for-buying-something-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[D]on't ever apologize to an author for buying something in paperback, or taking it out from a library (that's what they're there for. Use your library). Don't apologize to this author for buying books second hand, or getting them from bookcrossing or borrowing a friend's copy. What's important to me is that people read the books and enjoy them, and that, at some point in there, the book was bought by someone. And that people who like things, tell other people. The most important thing is that people read... " -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42627-most-people-don-t-realize-how-important-librarians-are-i-ran</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 18:02:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42627-most-people-don-t-realize-how-important-librarians-are-i-ran]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most people don't realize how important librarians are. I ran across a book recently which suggested that the peace and prosperity of a culture was solely related to how many librarians it contained. Possibly a slight overstatement. But a culture that doesn't value its librarians doesn't value ideas and without ideas, well, where are we?" -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46677-i-would-like-to-see-anyone-prophet-king-or-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 18:02:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46677-i-would-like-to-see-anyone-prophet-king-or-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would like to see anyone, prophet, king or God, convince a thousand cats to do the same thing at the same time." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4994-we-are-the-music-makers-and-we-are-the-dreamers</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 09:07:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Arthur William Edgar O'Shaughnessy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4994-we-are-the-music-makers-and-we-are-the-dreamers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are the music makers, and we are the dreamers of dreams." -- Arthur William Edgar O'Shaughnessy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67591-in-my-fool-hardy-youth-when-my-friends-were-dreaming</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 15:43:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Alberto Manguel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67591-in-my-fool-hardy-youth-when-my-friends-were-dreaming]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In my fool hardy youth, when my friends were dreaming of heroic deeds in the realms of engineering and law, finance and national politics, I dreamt of becoming a librarian. " -- Alberto Manguel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9766-in-the-shop-window-you-have-promptly-identified-the-cover</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2008 15:06:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9766-in-the-shop-window-you-have-promptly-identified-the-cover]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the shop window you have promptly identified the cover with the title you were looking for. Following this visual trail, you have forced your way through the shop past the thick barricade of Books You Haven't Read, which are frowning at you from the tables and shelves, trying to cow you...And thus you pass the outer girdle of ramparts, but then you are attacked by the infantry of Books That If You Had More Than One Life You Would Certainly Also Read But Unfortunately Your Days Are Numbered. With a rapid maneuver you bypass them and move into the phalanxes of the Books You Mean To Read But There Are Others You Must Read First, the Books Too Expensive Now And You'll Wait Till They're Remaindered, the Books ditto When They Come Out in Paperback, Books You Can Borrow From Somebody, Books That Everybody's Read So It's As If You Had Read Them, Too. " -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17808-did-you-ever-hear-anyone-say-that-work-had-better</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2008 15:12:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Joseph Henry Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17808-did-you-ever-hear-anyone-say-that-work-had-better]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did you ever hear anyone say, 'That work had better be banned because I might read it and it might be very damaging to me'?" -- Joseph Henry Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63137-libraries-will-get-you-through-times-of-no-money-better</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2008 15:16:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Anne Herbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63137-libraries-will-get-you-through-times-of-no-money-better]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Libraries will get you through times of no money better than money will get you through times of no libraries." -- Anne Herbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98663-she-d-always-been-a-little-excitable-a-little-more-passionate</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 10:05:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Sarah Beth Durst]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98663-she-d-always-been-a-little-excitable-a-little-more-passionate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She'd always been a little excitable, a little more passionate about books than your average person, but she was supposed to be -- she was a librarian, after all." -- Sarah Beth Durst]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4195-you-see-i-don-t-belive-that-libraries-should-be-drab</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 10:07:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Monty Python]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4195-you-see-i-don-t-belive-that-libraries-should-be-drab]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You see, I don't belive that libraries should be drab places where people sit in silence, that has been the main reason for our policy of employing wild animals as librarians." -- Monty Python]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11540-you-get-a-little-moody-sometimes-but-i-think-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 10:09:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11540-you-get-a-little-moody-sometimes-but-i-think-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You get a little moody sometimes but I think that's because you like to read. People that like to read are always a little fucked up." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8681-it-had-become-a-chimney-poking-from-a-vertical-universe</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 08:24:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by China Miéville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8681-it-had-become-a-chimney-poking-from-a-vertical-universe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It had become a chimney poking from a vertical universe of bookshelves. 

There was motion below her. There were people on the shelves. 

They clung to the edges of the cases and moved across them in expert scuttles. They wore ropes and hooks and carried picks on which they sometimes hung. Dangling from straps they carried notebooks, pens, magnifying glasses, ink pads, and stamps. 

The men and women took books from the shelves as they went, checked their details, leaning against their ropes, replaced them, pulled out little pads and made notes, sometimes carried the books with them to another place and reshelved it there. 

... 

I'm Margarita Staples.&quot; She bowed in her harness. 'Extreme librarian. Bookaneer." -- China Miéville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17845-wicked-people-never-have-time-for-reading-it-s-one-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 06:31:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17845-wicked-people-never-have-time-for-reading-it-s-one-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wicked people never have time for reading. It's one of the reasons for their wickedness." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11780-the-best-moments-in-reading-are-when-you-come-across</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 06:31:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Alan Bennett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11780-the-best-moments-in-reading-are-when-you-come-across]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best moments in reading are when you come across something - a thought, a feeling, a way of looking at things - which you had thought special and particular to you. And now, here it is, set down by someone else, a person you have never met, someone even who is long dead. And it is as if a hand has come out, and taken yours" -- Alan Bennett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11996-eating-and-reading-are-two-pleasures-that-combine-admirably</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 06:34:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11996-eating-and-reading-are-two-pleasures-that-combine-admirably]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eating and reading are two pleasures that combine admirably." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19297-reader-s-bill-of-rights-1-the-right-to-not-read</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 06:34:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Daniel Pennac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19297-reader-s-bill-of-rights-1-the-right-to-not-read]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reader's Bill of Rights

1. The right to not read 

2. The right to skip pages 

3. The right to not finish 

4. The right to reread 

5. The right to read anything 

6. The right to escapism 

7. The right to read anywhere 

8. The right to browse 

9. The right to read out loud 

10. The right to not defend your tastes" -- Daniel Pennac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7507-remember-to-always-be-yourself-unless-you-suck</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2009 11:53:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7507-remember-to-always-be-yourself-unless-you-suck]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember to always be yourself. Unless you suck." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7807-sometimes-i-feel-discriminated-against-but-it-does-not-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2009 05:50:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by ZORA NEALE HURSTON]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7807-sometimes-i-feel-discriminated-against-but-it-does-not-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, I feel discriminated against, but it does not make me angry. It merely astonishes me. How &lt;i&gt;can&lt;/i&gt; any deny themselves the pleasure of my company? It’s beyond me." -- ZORA NEALE HURSTON]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 09:39:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.

So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18637-librarians-dusty-possess-a-vast-store-of-politeness-these-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 09:40:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Garrison Keillor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18637-librarians-dusty-possess-a-vast-store-of-politeness-these-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Librarians, Dusty, possess a vast store of politeness. These are people who get asked regularly the dumbest questions on God's green earth. These people tolerate every kind of crank and eccentric and mouth breather there is." -- Garrison Keillor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15392-i-really-didn-t-realize-the-librarians-were-you-know-such</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 09:40:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Michael Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15392-i-really-didn-t-realize-the-librarians-were-you-know-such]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I really didn't realize the librarians were, you know, such a dangerous group.
They are subversive. You think they're just sitting there at the desk, all quiet and everything. They're like plotting the revolution, man. I wouldn't mess with them. You know, they've had their budgets cut. They're paid nothing. Books are falling apart. The libraries are just like the ass end of everything, right? 

" -- Michael Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99088-as-she-always-did-on-any-really-important-day-penelope</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 13:19:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Anna Godbersen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99088-as-she-always-did-on-any-really-important-day-penelope]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As she always did on any really important day, Penelope Hayes wore red." -- Anna Godbersen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150265-confession-time-i-doubt-i-would-ever-have-picked</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 09:33:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Bill Willingham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150265-confession-time-i-doubt-i-would-ever-have-picked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["    Confession time: I doubt I would ever have picked up one of Marjorie’s books, had I not met her in person. The reason is they’re categorized as Romances, which is where they are shelved in bookstores. Though I have no justification for avoiding it, the romance section is an area in bookstores I seldom wander into. Her novels also have traditional-looking romance book covers, which are occasionally a bit off-putting to us mighty manly men.

    Then again, who knows? I don’t carry many biases where good storytelling is concerned. I’m willing to find it anywhere, as too many of my friends will attest, when I try to drag them to wonderful movies that they aren’t eager to go to, simply because they fall under the chick-flick rubric. So, in any case, I’m glad I did meet Marjorie Liu in person, because it would have been a shame to miss out on the work of an author this talented due to whatever degree of cultural prejudices I might still possess. I trust you who read this won’t make the same mistake. " -- Bill Willingham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157825-she-d-even-violated-the-only-sensible-rule-of-dieting-she-d</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 13:24:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Susan Donovan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157825-she-d-even-violated-the-only-sensible-rule-of-dieting-she-d]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She'd even violated the only sensible rule of dieting she'd ever run across, the sage advice of the Muppets' Miss Piggy, who recommended never eating anything bigger than your head." -- Susan Donovan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 12:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The person, be it gentleman or lady, who has not pleasure in a good novel, must be intolerably stupid." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 12:49:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always imagined that Paradise will be a kind of library." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/802-in-a-good-bookroom-you-feel-in-some-mysterious-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 12:49:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/802-in-a-good-bookroom-you-feel-in-some-mysterious-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a good bookroom you feel in some mysterious way that you are absorbing the wisdom contained in all the books through your skin, without even opening them." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75358-it-is-a-curious-thought-but-it-is-only-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 22:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Agatha Christie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75358-it-is-a-curious-thought-but-it-is-only-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a curious thought, but it is only when you see people looking ridiculous that you realize just how much you love them.  " -- Agatha Christie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224075-we-are-all-four-of-us-blood-relatives-and-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 22:04:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224075-we-are-all-four-of-us-blood-relatives-and-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are, all four of us, blood relatives, and we speak a kind of esoteric, family language, a sort of semantic geometry in which the shortest distance between any two points is a fullish circle." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4974-you-will-do-foolish-things-but-do-them-with-enthusiasm</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 12:12:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Colette]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4974-you-will-do-foolish-things-but-do-them-with-enthusiasm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You will do foolish things, but do them with enthusiasm." -- Colette]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
