<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/339461-dawn]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/339461-dawn" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 19:21:54 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920978-if-you-allow-your-consciousness-to-drift-toward-your-lower</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 19:21:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dawn add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920978-if-you-allow-your-consciousness-to-drift-toward-your-lower]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you allow your consciousness to drift toward your lower abdomen during breathing, then your breath will naturally delve deeper within you. If you allow your consciousness to experiencce the gratitude and joy of breathing, then your breath will naturally become light. Your breathing will naturally achieve a deep lightness as you consider inhaling as an expression of thanks to your body and exhaling as an expression of thanks to the Heavens above. Then you can lose yourself in your breath. You can follow your breath within and without your body, losing yourself until you become the breath itself." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/925866-we-have-the-noble-desire-to-help-others-and-benefit</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 19:22:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dawn add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/925866-we-have-the-noble-desire-to-help-others-and-benefit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have the Noble Desire to help others and benefit the world, without expecting any return or recognition. What makes us great is not our knowledge, skill, money, or power. What makes us great is not our knowledge, skill, money, or power. What makes us truly great is this noble desire, this passion that transcends all separation, goes beyond one's limitations, and wants to hug others and embrace the whole world. This is not something that we need to learn, because we already have it. It just needs to be acknowledged and awakened." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916907-change-is-the-very-nature-of-nature-if-there-s-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 19:22:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dawn add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916907-change-is-the-very-nature-of-nature-if-there-s-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Change is the very nature of Nature. if there's one thing that doesn't change, it is the fact that everything changes. In the Korean tradition of Tao, this is called impermanence. The teaching about impermanence can be summarized like this: Anything that has a beginning must have an end. Anything that is created will change. Impermanence is the very nature of things. Realizing that nothing is permanent is the true beginning of enlightenment. Suffering comes from attachment that wants to hold something permanently that is not permanent in its intrinsic nature. Awakening to the truth of impermanence frees you from attachment." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511614-i-existed-before-i-received-this-body-i-am-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 19:22:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dawn add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511614-i-existed-before-i-received-this-body-i-am-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I existed before I received this body. I am the external and fundamental life energy of the universe." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
