<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/339924-lou]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/339924-lou" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 23:29:06 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6267-and-by-the-way-everything-in-life-is-writable-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 23:29:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6267-and-by-the-way-everything-in-life-is-writable-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And by the way, everything in life is writable about if you have the outgoing guts to do it, and the imagination to improvise. The worst enemy to creativity is self-doubt." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1323-here-s-what-i-think-mr-wind-up-bird-said-may-kasahara</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2008 16:02:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1323-here-s-what-i-think-mr-wind-up-bird-said-may-kasahara]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's what I think, Mr. Wind-Up Bird,&quot; said May Kasahara. &quot;Everybody's born with some different thing at the core of their existence. And that thing, whatever it is, becomes like a heat source that runs each person from the inside. I have one too, of course. Like everybody else. But sometimes it gets out of hand. It swells or shrinks inside me, and it shakes me up. What I'd really like to do is find a way to communicate that feeling to another person. But I can't seem to do it. They just don't get it. Of course, the problem could be that I'm not explaining it very well, but I think it's because they're not listening very well. They pretend to be listening, but they're not, really. So I get worked up sometimes, and I do some crazy things." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2008 16:06:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be the change that you wish to see in the world." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103252-i-regret-that-it-takes-a-life-to-learn-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 23:28:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103252-i-regret-that-it-takes-a-life-to-learn-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I regret that it takes a life to learn how to live." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60737-she-was-elusive-she-was-today-she-was-tomorrow-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 23:28:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Jerry Spinelli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60737-she-was-elusive-she-was-today-she-was-tomorrow-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was elusive. She was today. She was tomorrow. She was the faintest scent of a cactus flower, the flitting shadow of an elf owl. We did not know what to make of her. In our minds we tried to pin her to a cork board like a butterfly, but the pin merely went through and away she flew." -- Jerry Spinelli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1251-a-painter-should-begin-every-canvas-with-a-wash-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 23:28:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Leonardo da Vinci]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1251-a-painter-should-begin-every-canvas-with-a-wash-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A painter should begin every canvas with a wash of black, because all things in nature are dark except where exposed by the light." -- Leonardo da Vinci]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83316-i-realize-full-well-how-hard-it-must-be-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 23:28:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83316-i-realize-full-well-how-hard-it-must-be-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I realize full well how hard it must be to go on living alone in a place from which someone has left you, but there is nothing so cruel in this world as the desolation of having nothing to hope for." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12357-i-wish-it-need-not-have-happened-in-my-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 23:28:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12357-i-wish-it-need-not-have-happened-in-my-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish it need not have happened in my time,&quot; said Frodo.
&quot;So do I,&quot; said Gandalf, &quot;and so do all who live to see such times. But that is not for them to decide. All we have to decide is what to do with the time that is given us." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22433-to-know-one-s-own-state-is-not-a-simple-matter</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 15:51:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22433-to-know-one-s-own-state-is-not-a-simple-matter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To know one’s own state is not a simple matter. One cannot look directly at one’s own face with one’s own eyes, for example. One has no choice but to look at one’s reflection in the mirror. Through experience, we come to believe that the image is correct, but that is all." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83318-so-what-can-i-do-now-she-spoke-up-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 15:58:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83318-so-what-can-i-do-now-she-spoke-up-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So what can I do now?&quot; she spoke up a minute later.
&quot;Nothing,&quot; I said. &quot;Just think about what comes before words. You owe that to the dead. As time goes on, you'll understand. What lasts, lasts; what doesn't, doesn't. Time solves most things. And what time can't solve, you have to solve yourself. Is that too much to ask?&quot;
&quot;A little,&quot; she said, trying to smile.
&quot;Well, of course it is,&quot; I said, trying to smile too.
&quot;I doubt that this makes sense to most people. But I think I'm right. People die all the time. Life is a lot more fragile than we think. So you should treat others in a way that leaves no regrets. Fairly, and if posible, sincerely. It's too easy not to make the effort, then weep and wring your hands after the person dies. Personally, I don't buy it.&quot;
Yuki leaned against the car door. &quot;But that's real hard, isn't it?&quot; she said.
&quot;Real hard,&quot; I said. &quot;But it's worth trying for." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16160-but-who-can-say-what-s-best-that-s-why-you-need</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 15:59:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16160-but-who-can-say-what-s-best-that-s-why-you-need]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But who can say what's best? That's why you need to grab whatever chance you have of happiness where you find it, and not worry about other people too much. My experience tells me that we get no more than two or three such chances in a life time, and if we let them go, we regret it for the rest of our lives." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2008 04:59:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2008 04:59:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the only people for me are the mad ones, the ones who are mad to live, mad to talk, mad to be saved, desirous of everything at the same time, the ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn like fabulous yellow roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2798-i-like-too-many-things-and-get-all-confused-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2008 05:00:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2798-i-like-too-many-things-and-get-all-confused-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like too many things and get all confused and hung-up running from one falling star to another till i drop. This is the night, what it does to you. I had nothing to offer anybody except my own confusion." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 13:51:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes fate is like a small sandstorm that keeps changing directions. You change direction but the sandstorm chases you. You turn again, but the storm adjusts. Over and over you play this out, like some ominous dance with death just before dawn. Why? Because this storm isn't something that blew in from far away, something that has nothing to do with you. This storm is you. Something &lt;i&gt;inside&lt;/i&gt; of you. So all you can do is give in to it, step right inside the storm, closing your eyes and plugging up your ears so the sand doesn't get in, and walk through it, step by step. There's no sun there, no moon, no direction, no sense of time. Just fine white sand swirling up into the sky like pulverized bones. That's the kind of sandstorm you need to imagine.

An you really will have to make it through that violent, metaphysical, symbolic storm. No matter how metaphysical or symbolic it might be, make no mistake about it: it will cut through flesh like a thousand razor blades. People will bleed there, and &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; will bleed too. Hot, red blood. You'll catch that blood in your hands, your own blood and the blood of others.

And once the storm is over you won't remember how you made it through, how you managed to survive. You won't even be sure, in fact, whether the storm is really over. But one thing is certain. When you come out of the storm you won't be the same person who walked in. That's what this storm's all about." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99616-they-tell-us-that-the-only-thing-we-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2008 14:11:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99616-they-tell-us-that-the-only-thing-we-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They tell us that the only thing we have to fear is fear itself,but I don't believe that.&quot; he said. 

Then, a moment later, he added: &quot;Oh,the fear is there, all right. It comes to us in many different forms, at different times, and overwhelms us. But the most frightening thing we can do at such times is to turn our backs on it, to close our eyes. For then we take the most precious thing inside us and surrender it to something else. In my case, that something was the wave." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45194-quiet-is-peace-tranquility-quiet-is-turning-down-the-volume</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 10:30:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45194-quiet-is-peace-tranquility-quiet-is-turning-down-the-volume]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Quiet is peace. Tranquility. Quiet is turning down the volume knob on life. Silence is pushing the off button. Shutting it down. All of it. - Amir" -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6910-it-didn-t-matter-in-the-end-how-old-they-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2009 02:35:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6910-it-didn-t-matter-in-the-end-how-old-they-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It didn't matter in the end how old they had been, or that they were girls, but only that we had loved them, and that they hadn't heard us calling, still do not hear us, up here in the tree house, with our thinning hair and soft bellies, calling them out of those rooms where they went to be alone for all time, alone in suicide, which is deeper than death, and where we will never find the pieces to put them back together." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84958-so-i-walked-back-to-my-room-and-collapsed-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 14:56:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84958-so-i-walked-back-to-my-room-and-collapsed-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So I walked back to my room and collapsed on the bottom bunk, thinking that if people were rain, I was drizzle and she was a hurricane." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37443-there-are-a-hundred-things-she-has-tried-to-chase</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 07:21:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37443-there-are-a-hundred-things-she-has-tried-to-chase]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are a hundred things she has tried to chase away the things she won't remember and that she can't even let herself think about because that's when the birds scream and the worms crawl and somewhere in her mind it's always raining a slow and endless drizzle.

You will hear that she has left the country, that there was a gift she wanted you to have, but it is lost before it reaches you. Late one night the telephone will sign, and a voice that might be hers will say something that you cannot interpret before the connection crackles and is broken.

Several years later, from a taxi, you will see someone in a doorway who looks like her, but she will be gone by the time you persuade the driver to stop. You will never see her again. 

Whenever it rains you will think of her.  " -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110727-on-rainy-afternoons-embroidering-with-a-group-of-friends-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 11:24:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110727-on-rainy-afternoons-embroidering-with-a-group-of-friends-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On rainy afternoons, embroidering with a group of friends on the begonia porch, she would lose the thread of the conversation and a tear of nostalgia would salt her palate when she saw the strips of damp earth and the piles of mud that the earthworms had pushed up in the garden. Those secret tastes, defeated in the past by oranges and rhubarb, broke out into an irrepressible urge when she began to weep. She went back to eating earth. The first time she did it almost out of curiosity, sure that the bad taste would be the best cure for the temptation. And, in fact, she could not bear the earth in her mouth. But she persevered, overcome by the growing anxiety, and little by little she was getting back her ancestral appetite, the taste of primary minerals, the unbridled satisfaction of what was the original food. She would put handfuls of earth in her pockets, and ate them in small bits without being seen, with a confused feeling of pleasure and rage, as she instructed her girl friends in the most difficult needlepoint and spoke about other men, who did not deserve the sacrifice of having one eat the whitewash on the walls because of them. The handfuls of earth made the only man who deserved that show of degradation less remote and more certain, as if the ground that he walked on with his fine patent leather boots in another part of the world were transmitting to her the weight and the temperature of his blood in a mineral savor that left a harsh aftertaste in her mouth and a sediment of peace in her heart." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188007-even-after-all-this-time-the-sun-never-says-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 15:08:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Hafiz of Shiraz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188007-even-after-all-this-time-the-sun-never-says-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even after all this time 
The sun never says to the earth, 
&quot;you owe me.&quot;  
Look what happens with a love like that.  It lights the whole sky." -- Hafiz of Shiraz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212808-behind-every-man-now-alive-stand-thirty-ghosts-for-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 13:07:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212808-behind-every-man-now-alive-stand-thirty-ghosts-for-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Behind every man now alive stand thirty ghosts, for that is the ratio by which the dead outnumber the living. Since the dawn of time, roughly a hundred billion human beings have walked the planet Earth.

Now this is an interesting number, for by a curious coincidence there are approximately a hundred billion stars in our local universe, the Milky Way. So for every man who has ever lived, in this Universe there shines a star.

But every one of those stars is a sun, often far more brilliant and glorious than the small, nearby star we call the Sun. And many--perhaps most--of those alien suns have planets circling them. So almost certainly there is enough land in the sky to give every member of the human species, back to the first ape-man, his own private, world-sized heaven--or hell.

How many of those potential heavens and hells are now inhabited, and by what manner of creatures, we have no way of guessing; the very nearest is a million times farther away than Mars or Venus, those still remote goals of the next generation. But the barriers of distance are crumbling; one day we shall meet our equals, or our masters, among the stars.

Men have been slow to face this prospect; some still hope that it may never become reality. Increasing numbers, however are asking; 'Why have such meetings not occurred already, since we ourselves are about to venture into space?'

Why not, indeed? Here is one possible answer to that very reasonable question. But please remember: this is only a work of fiction.

The truth, as always, will be far stranger." -- Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311235-that-was-the-only-time-as-i-stood-there-looking</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 16:33:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311235-that-was-the-only-time-as-i-stood-there-looking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That was the only time, as I stood there, looking at that strange rubbish, feeling the wind coming across those empty fields, that I started to imagine just a little fantasy thing, because this was Norfolk after all, and it was only a couple of weeks since I’d lost him. I was thinking about the rubbish, the flapping plastic in the branches, the shore-line of odd stuff caught along the fencing, and I half-closed my eyes and imagined this was the spot where everything I'd ever lost since my childhood had washed up, and I was now standing here in front of it, and if I waited long enough, a tiny figure would appear on the horizon across the field, and gradually get larger until I'd see it was Tommy, and he'd wave, maybe even call. The fantasy never got beyond that --I didn't let it-- and though the tears rolled down my face, I wasn't sobbing or out of control. I just waited a bit, then turned back to the car, to drive off to wherever it was I was supposed to be." -- Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302971-alles-ist-erlaubt-alles-au-er-schweigen</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 14:48:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Daniel Glattauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302971-alles-ist-erlaubt-alles-au-er-schweigen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alles ist erlaubt, alles außer schweigen." -- Daniel Glattauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20116-people-have-a-habit-of-inventing-fictions-they-will-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20116-people-have-a-habit-of-inventing-fictions-they-will-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People have a habit of inventing fictions they will believe wholeheartedly in order to ignore the truth they cannot accept." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266123-some-things-are-hard-to-write-about-after-something-happens</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 23:54:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266123-some-things-are-hard-to-write-about-after-something-happens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some things are hard to write about. After something happens to you, you go to write it down, and either you over dramatize it, or underplay it, exaggerate the wrong parts or ignore the important ones. At any rate, you never write it quite the way you want to." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68202-some-people-turn-sad-awfully-young-no-special-reason-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 00:03:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68202-some-people-turn-sad-awfully-young-no-special-reason-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people turn sad awfully young. No special reason, it seems, but they seem almost to be born that way. They bruise easier, tire faster, cry quicker, remember longer and, as I say, get sadder younger than anyone else in the world. I know, for I'm one of them." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124696-all-i-ever-wanted-was-a-world-without-maps</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 04:14:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124696-all-i-ever-wanted-was-a-world-without-maps]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All I ever wanted was a world without maps." -- Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83202-death-is-not-the-opposite-of-life-but-a-part</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 03:53:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lou add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83202-death-is-not-the-opposite-of-life-but-a-part]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death is not the opposite of life, but a part of it." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
