<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/340146-martha-garvey]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/340146-martha-garvey" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2012 18:12:07 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64558-to-be-fully-alive-fully-human-and-completely-awake-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2012 18:12:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Pema Chodron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64558-to-be-fully-alive-fully-human-and-completely-awake-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be fully alive, fully human, and completely awake is to be continually thrown out of the nest." -- Pema Chodron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/554214-what-s-so-wonderful-about-experiments-is-that-often-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 15:08:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Susie Bright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/554214-what-s-so-wonderful-about-experiments-is-that-often-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What's so wonderful about experiments is that often they &lt;i&gt;don't&lt;/i&gt; work. They &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; blow up in the oven; the Bride of Frankenstein does crawl out and strangle you with a black leotard while you shout your last prayers. It's only once you've tasted your own shocking failures, harebrained ideas, and sudden departures that you will realize something quite wonderful." -- Susie Bright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59181-fabulous-if-you-possess-it-you-don-t-need-to-ask</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 11:51:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Tony Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59181-fabulous-if-you-possess-it-you-don-t-need-to-ask]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fabulous. If you possess it, you don’t need to ask what it is. When you attempt to delineate it, you move away from it. Fabulous is one of those words that provide a measure of the degree to which a person or event manifests a particular oppressed subculture’s most distinctive, invigorating features. What are the salient features of fabulousness? Irony. Tragic History. Defiance. Gender-fuck. Glitter. Drama. It is not butch. It is not hot. The cathexis surrounding fabulousness is not necessarily erotic. The fabulous is not delineated by age or beauty. It is raw materials reworked into illusion. To be truly fabulous, one must completely triumph over tragedy, age, and physical insufficiencies. The fabulous is the rapturous embrace of difference, the discovering of self not in that which has rejected you but in that which makes you unlike, the dislike, the other." -- Tony Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405976-only-to-the-extent-that-we-expose-ourselves-over-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 10:58:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Pema Chodron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405976-only-to-the-extent-that-we-expose-ourselves-over-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only to the extent that we expose ourselves over and over to annihilation can that which is indestructible be found in us." -- Pema Chodron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541149-everybody-loves-something-even-if-it-s-only-tortillas</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 10:58:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Pema Chodron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541149-everybody-loves-something-even-if-it-s-only-tortillas]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody loves something, even if it's only tortillas." -- Pema Chodron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331134-people-are-really-trying-their-best-just-like-being-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 11:09:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by David Rakoff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331134-people-are-really-trying-their-best-just-like-being-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People are really trying their best. Just like being happy and sad, you will find yourself on both sides of the equation many times over your lifetime, either saying or hearing the wrong thing. Let's all give each other a pass, shall we?" -- David Rakoff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6670-don-t-be-afraid-people-are-so-afraid-don-t-be-afraid</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 23:08:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Tony Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6670-don-t-be-afraid-people-are-so-afraid-don-t-be-afraid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't be afraid; people are so afraid; don't be afraid to live in the raw wind, naked, alone...Learn at least this: What you are capable of. Let nothing stand in your way." -- Tony Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57633-the-smallest-indivisible-human-unit-is-two-people-not-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 23:11:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Tony Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57633-the-smallest-indivisible-human-unit-is-two-people-not-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The smallest indivisible human unit is two people, not one; one is a fiction. From such nets of souls societies, the social world, human life springs." -- Tony Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/376551-you-ll-find-my-friend-that-what-you-love-will-take</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 23:13:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Tony Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/376551-you-ll-find-my-friend-that-what-you-love-will-take]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You'll find, my friend, that what you love will take you places you never dreamed you'd go." -- Tony Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192925-if-you-re-going-to-be-passionate-about-something-be-passionate</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 18:06:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Daniel Golston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192925-if-you-re-going-to-be-passionate-about-something-be-passionate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're going to be passionate about something, be passionate about learning. If you're going to fight something, fight for those in need. If you're going to question something, question authority. If you're going to lose something, lose your inhibitions. If you're going to gain something, gain respect and confidence. And if you're going to hate something, hate the false idea that you are not capable of your dreams.
" -- Daniel Golston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/617744-higher-than-the-beasts-lower-than-the-angels-stuck-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 04:31:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Ford Madox Ford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/617744-higher-than-the-beasts-lower-than-the-angels-stuck-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Higher than the beasts, lower than the angels, stuck in our idiot Eden." -- Ford Madox Ford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60487-all-of-the-designers-i-have-met-up-to-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2013 09:39:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by David Rakoff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60487-all-of-the-designers-i-have-met-up-to-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All of the designers I have met up to this point have been very nice, although upon being introduced to Karl Lagerfeld, he looks me up and down and dismisses me with the not super-kind, &quot;What can you write that hasn't been written already?&quot; 

He's absolutely right, I have no idea. I can but try. The only thing I can come up with right now is that Lagerfeld's powdered white ponytail has dusted the shoulders of his suit with what looks like dandruff but isn't....seated on a tiny velvet chair, with his large doughy rump dominating the miniature piece of furniture like a loose, flabby, ass-flavored muffin over-risen from its pan, he resembles a Daumier caricature of some corpulent, overfed, inhumane oligarch drawn sitting on a commode, stuffing his greedy throat with the corpses of dead children, while from his other end he shits out huge, malodorous piles of tainted money. How's that for new and groundbreaking, Mr. L.?
" -- David Rakoff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406063-it-s-not-your-job-to-like-me---it-s-mine</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2013 18:16:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Byron Katie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406063-it-s-not-your-job-to-like-me---it-s-mine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not your job to like me - it's mine" -- Byron Katie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/380632-how-do-you-react-when-you-think-you-need-people-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2013 18:17:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Byron Katie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/380632-how-do-you-react-when-you-think-you-need-people-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How do you react when you think you need people's love? Do you become a slave for their approval? Do you live an inauthentic life because you can't bear the thought that they might disapprove of you? Do you try to figure out how they would like you to be, and then try to become that, like a chameleon? In fact, you never really get their love. You turn into someone you aren't, and then when they say &quot;I love you,&quot; you can't believe it, because they're loving a facade. They're loving someone who doesn't even exist, the person you're pretending to be. It's difficult to seek other people's love. It's deadly. In seeking it, you lose what is genuine. This is the prison we create for ourselves as we seek what we already have." -- Byron Katie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117612-the-miracle-of-love-comes-to-you-in-the-presence</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2013 18:17:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Byron Katie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117612-the-miracle-of-love-comes-to-you-in-the-presence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The miracle of love comes to you in the presence of the uninterpreted moment. If you are mentally somewhere else, you miss real life." -- Byron Katie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121153-you-move-totally-away-from-reality-when-you-believe-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2013 18:17:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Byron Katie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121153-you-move-totally-away-from-reality-when-you-believe-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You move totally away from reality when you believe that there is a legitimate reason to suffer&quot;." -- Byron Katie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165931-you-know-that-feeling-at-the-end-of-the-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 12:53:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165931-you-know-that-feeling-at-the-end-of-the-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know that feeling at the end of the day, when the anxiety of that-which-I-must-do falls away and, for maybe the first time that day, you see, with some clarity, the people you love and the ways you have, during that day, slightly ignored them, turned away from them to get back to what you were doing, blurted out some mildly hurtful thing, projected, instead of the deep love you really feel, a surge of defensiveness or self-protection or suspicion?  That moment when you think, Oh God, what have I done with this day?  And what am I doing with my life?  And how must I change to avoid catastrophic end-of-life regrets?

I feel like that now: tired of the Me I've always been, tired of making the same mistakes, repetitively stumbling after the same small ego strokes, being caught in the same loops of anxiety and defensiveness.  At the end of my life, I know I won't be wishing I'd held more back, been less effusive, more often stood on ceremony, forgiven less, spent more days oblivious to the secret wishes and fears of the people around me...  

--&quot;Buddha Boy" -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/671492-don-t-be-afraid-to-be-confused-try-to-remain-permanently</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 12:56:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/671492-don-t-be-afraid-to-be-confused-try-to-remain-permanently]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't be afraid to be confused. Try to remain permanently confused. Anything is possible. Stay open, forever, so open it hurts, and then open up some more, until the day you die, world without end, amen." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114863-america-is-and-always-has-been-undecided-about-whether-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 12:57:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114863-america-is-and-always-has-been-undecided-about-whether-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["America is, and always has been, undecided about whether it will be the United States of Tom or the United States of Huck.  The United States of Tom looks at misery and says: Hey, I didn't do it.  It looks at inequity and says: All my life I busted my butt to get where I am, so don't come crying to me.  Tom likes kings, codified nobility, unquestioned privilege.  Huck likes people, fair play, spreading the truck around.  Whereas Tom knows, Huck wonders.  Whereas Huck hopes, Tom presumes.  Whereas Huck cares, Tom denies.  These two parts of the American Psyche have been at war since the beginning of the nation, and come to think of it, these two parts of the World Psyche have been at war since the beginning of the world, and the hope of the nation and of the world is to embrace the Huck part and send the Tom part back up the river, where it belongs." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/466286-dad-had-once-said-trust-your-mind-rob-if-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 12:58:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/466286-dad-had-once-said-trust-your-mind-rob-if-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dad had once said, Trust your mind, Rob.  If it smells like shit but has writing across it that says Happy Birthday and a candle stuck down in it, what is it?

Is there icing on it? he'd said.

Dad had done that thing of squinting his eyes when an answer was not quite there yet." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287385-i-was-going-to-die-sooner-or-later-whether-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 07:13:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287385-i-was-going-to-die-sooner-or-later-whether-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was going to die, sooner or later, whether or not I had even spoken myself. My silences had not protected me. Your silences will not protect you.... What are the words you do not yet have? What are the tyrannies you swallow day by day and attempt to make your own, until you will sicken and die of them, still in silence? We have been socialized to respect fear more than our own need for language.&quot;

I began to ask each time: &quot;What's the worst that could happen to me if I tell this truth?&quot; Unlike women in other countries, our breaking silence is unlikely to have us jailed, &quot;disappeared&quot; or run off the road at night. Our speaking out will irritate some people, get us called bitchy or hypersensitive and disrupt some dinner parties. And then our speaking out will permit other women to speak, until laws are changed and lives are saved and the world is altered forever.

Next time, ask: What's the worst that will happen? Then push yourself a little further than you dare. Once you start to speak, people will yell at you. They will interrupt you, put you down and suggest it's personal. And the world won't end.

And the speaking will get easier and easier. And you will find you have fallen in love with your own vision, which you may never have realized you had. And you will lose some friends and lovers, and realize you don't miss them. And new ones will find you and cherish you. And you will still flirt and paint your nails, dress up and party, because, as I think Emma Goldman said, &quot;If I can't dance, I don't want to be part of your revolution.&quot; And at last you'll know with surpassing certainty that only one thing is more frightening than speaking your truth. And that is not speaking." -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2213-if-i-didn-t-define-myself-for-myself-i-would-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 08:49:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Audre Lorde ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2213-if-i-didn-t-define-myself-for-myself-i-would-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I didn't define myself for myself, I would be crunched into other people's fantasies for me and eaten alive." -- Audre Lorde ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12425-when-i-dare-to-be-powerful-to-use-my-strength</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 08:49:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12425-when-i-dare-to-be-powerful-to-use-my-strength]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I dare to be powerful, to use my strength in the service of my vision, then it becomes less and less important whether I am afraid." -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27421-your-silence-will-not-protect-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 08:49:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martha add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27421-your-silence-will-not-protect-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your silence will not protect you." -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
