<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/340156-julia-fierro]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/340156-julia-fierro" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 06:14:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334492-i-read-the-way-a-person-might-swim-to-save</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 06:14:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334492-i-read-the-way-a-person-might-swim-to-save]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read the way a person might swim, to save his or her life. I wrote that way too." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52789-grown-ups-never-understand-anything-by-themselves-and-it-is-tiresome</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 21:31:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52789-grown-ups-never-understand-anything-by-themselves-and-it-is-tiresome]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Grown-ups never understand anything by themselves, and it is tiresome for children to be always and forever explaining things to them" -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56217-times-are-bad-children-no-longer-obey-their-parents-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 21:32:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Cicero. M Tullius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56217-times-are-bad-children-no-longer-obey-their-parents-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Times are bad.  Children no longer obey their parents, and everyone is writing a book." -- Cicero. M Tullius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21574-look-at-children-of-course-they-may-quarrel-but-generally</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 21:33:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by His Holiness the Dahai Lama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21574-look-at-children-of-course-they-may-quarrel-but-generally]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look at children.  Of course they may quarrel, but generally speaking they do not harbor ill feelings as much or as long as adults do.  Most adults have the advantage of education over children, but what is the use of an education if they show a big smile while hiding negative feelings deep inside?  Children dont usually act in such a manner.  If they feel angry with someone, they express it, and then it is finished.  They can still play with that person the following day." -- His Holiness the Dahai Lama]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25373-that-s-the-nature-of-being-a-parent-sabine-has-discovered</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 21:34:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Ursula Hegi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25373-that-s-the-nature-of-being-a-parent-sabine-has-discovered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's the nature of being a parent, Sabine has discovered. You'll love your children far more than you ever loved your parents, and -- in the recognition that your own children cannot fathom the depth of your love -- you come to understand the tragic, unrequited love of your own parents." -- Ursula Hegi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275738-i-don-t-remember-who-said-this-but-there-really-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 21:34:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275738-i-don-t-remember-who-said-this-but-there-really-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't remember who said this, but there really are places in the heart you don't even know exist until you love a child." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17254-all-children-mythologise-their-birth-it-is-a-universal-trait</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 21:35:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Diane Setterfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17254-all-children-mythologise-their-birth-it-is-a-universal-trait]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All children mythologise their birth. It is a universal trait. You want to know someone? Heart, mind and soul? Ask him to tell you about when he was born. What you get won’t be the truth: it will be a story. And nothing is more telling than a story. " -- Diane Setterfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115631-a-first-child-is-your-own-best-foot-forward-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 21:39:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115631-a-first-child-is-your-own-best-foot-forward-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A first child is your own best foot forward, and how you do cheer those little feet as they strike out. You examine every turn of flesh for precocity, and crow it to the world. But the last one: the baby who trails her scent like a flag of surrender through your life when there will be no more coming after--oh, that' s love by a different name." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189249-may-what-i-do-flow-from-me-like-a-river</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 21:40:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189249-may-what-i-do-flow-from-me-like-a-river]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May what I do flow from me like a river, no forcing and no holding back, the way it is with children." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24091-it-is-a-curious-situation-that-the-sea-from-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 21:41:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Rachel Carson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24091-it-is-a-curious-situation-that-the-sea-from-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a curious situation that the sea, from which life first arose should now be threatened by the activities of one form of that life. But the sea, though changed in a sinister way, will continue to exist; the threat is rather to life itself." -- Rachel Carson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142806-it-is-the-custom-of-every-good-mother-after-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 21:44:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142806-it-is-the-custom-of-every-good-mother-after-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is the custom of every good mother after her children are asleep to rummage in their minds and put things straight for next morning, repacking into their proper places the many articles that have wandered during the day. If you could keep awake (but of course you can’t) you would see your own mother doing this, and you would find it very interesting to watch her. It is quite like tidying up drawers. You would see her on her knees, I expect, lingering humorously over some of your contents, wondering where on earth you had picked this thing up, making discoveries sweet and not so sweet, pressing this to her cheek as if it were as nice as a kitten, and hurriedly stowing that out of sight. When you wake in the morning, the naughtinesses and evil passions with which you went to bed have been folded up small and placed at the bottom of your mind; and on the top, beautifully aired, are spread out prettier thoughts, ready for you to put on." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24999-it-was-then-that-hook-bit-him-not-the-pain</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 21:45:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24999-it-was-then-that-hook-bit-him-not-the-pain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was then that Hook bit him.
Not the pain of this but its unfairness was what dazed Peter. It made him quite helpless. He could only stare, horrified. Every child is affected thus the first time he is treated unfairly. All he thinks he has a right to when he comes to you to be yours is fairness. After you have been unfair to him he will love you again, but he will never afterwards be quite the same boy. No one ever gets over the first unfairness; no one except Peter." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234443-if-i-had-lady-spider-legs-i-would-weave-a-sky</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 21:47:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234443-if-i-had-lady-spider-legs-i-would-weave-a-sky]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I had lady-spider legs, I would weave a sky where the stars lined up. Matresses would be tied down tight to their trucks, bodies would never crash through windshields. The moon would rise above the wine-dark sea and give babies only to maidens and musicians who had prayed long and hard. Lost girls wouldn't need compasses or maps. They would find gingerbread paths to lead them out of the forest and home again. They would never sleep in silver boxes with white velvet sheets, not until they were wrinkled-paper grandmas and ready for the trip. " -- Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82811-you-stayed-around-your-children-as-long-as-you-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 22:03:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Meg Wolitzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82811-you-stayed-around-your-children-as-long-as-you-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You stayed around your children as long as you could, inhaling the ambient gold shavings of their childhood, and at the last minute you tried to see them off into life and hoped that the little piece of time you’d given them was enough to prevent them from one day feeling lonely and afraid and hopeless.  You wouldn’t know the outcome for a long time." -- Meg Wolitzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239284-that-s-most-interesting-but-i-was-no-more-a-mind-reader</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 22:07:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239284-that-s-most-interesting-but-i-was-no-more-a-mind-reader]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's most interesting. But I was no more a mind-reader then than today. I
was weeping for an altogether different reason. When I watched you dancing that day, I saw something else. I saw a new world coming rapidly. More
scientific, efficient, yes. More cures for the old sicknesses. Very good. But a
harsh, cruel world. And I saw a little girl, her eyes tightly closed, holding to her breast the old kind world, one that she knew in her heart could not
remain, and she was holding it and pleading, never to let her go. That is what I saw. It wasn't really you, what you were doing, I know that. But I saw you and it broke my heart. And I've never forgotten." -- Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/616337-parenthood-doesn-t-improve-one-s-character-it-exposes-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 22:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Leslie A. Gordon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/616337-parenthood-doesn-t-improve-one-s-character-it-exposes-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Parenthood doesn’t improve one’s character, it exposes it." -- Leslie A. Gordon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/639012-it-s-the-silliness--the-profligacy-and-the-silliness--that-s-so-dizzying-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 22:10:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Caitlin Moran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/639012-it-s-the-silliness--the-profligacy-and-the-silliness--that-s-so-dizzying-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's the silliness--the profligacy, and the silliness--that's so dizzying: a seven-year-old will run downstairs, kiss you hard, and then run back upstairs again, all in less than 30 seconds.  It's as urgent an item on their daily agenda as eating or singing.  It's like being mugged by Cupid." -- Caitlin Moran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/684977-it-is-not-true-that-love-is-not-love-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 22:11:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Andrew Solomon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/684977-it-is-not-true-that-love-is-not-love-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not true that &quot;love is not love which alters when it alteration finds.&quot; Love alters all the time; it is fluid, in perceptual flux, an evolving business across a lifetime." -- Andrew Solomon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/659594---how-does-it-feel-to-have-a-daughter--</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 22:12:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Clarice Lispector]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/659594---how-does-it-feel-to-have-a-daughter--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["- How does it feel to have a daughter?
- At times it's like holding a warm egg in my hand." -- Clarice Lispector]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440593-when-the-world-according-to-garp-was-published-people-who-d</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 22:12:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440593-when-the-world-according-to-garp-was-published-people-who-d]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When (The World According To) Garp was published, people who’d lost children wrote to me. ‘’I lost one, too,’’ they told me. I confessed to them that I hadn’t lost any children. I’m just a father with a good imagination. In my imagination, I lose my children every day. (afterword)" -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311076-memories-particularly-of-when-they-weren-t-being-what-parents-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 22:14:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311076-memories-particularly-of-when-they-weren-t-being-what-parents-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Memories particularly of when they weren’t being what parents are nine-tenths of the time, the taskmasters, the examples, the moral authorities, the nags of pick-that-up and you’re-going-to-be-late, keepers of the diary of her duties and routines, memories, rather, of when they found one another afresh, beyond the tensions between parental mastery and inept childish uncertainty, of those moments of respite in a family’s life when they could reach one another in calm" -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256898-no-one-is-ever-quite-ready-everyone-is-always-caught</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 22:16:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Marisa de los Santos]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256898-no-one-is-ever-quite-ready-everyone-is-always-caught]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one is ever quite ready; everyone is always caught off guard. Parenthood chooses you. And you open your eyes, look at what you've got, say &quot;Oh, my gosh,&quot; and recognize that of all the balls there ever were, this is the one you should not drop. It's not a question of choice." -- Marisa de los Santos]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26204-i-would-have-let-him-go-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 22:17:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26204-i-would-have-let-him-go-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[". . . I would have let him go one finger at a time, until, without his realizing, he'd be floating without me.  And then I thought, perhaps that is what it means to be a [parent] - to teach your child to live without you." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331077-parenthood-it-s-about-guiding-the-next-generation-and-forgiving-the-last</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 22:18:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Peter Krause (Parenthood)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331077-parenthood-it-s-about-guiding-the-next-generation-and-forgiving-the-last]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Parenthood...It's about guiding the next generation, and forgiving the last." -- Peter Krause (Parenthood)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/546841-being-a-parent-is-dirty-and-scary-and-beautiful-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 22:20:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Jill Smokler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/546841-being-a-parent-is-dirty-and-scary-and-beautiful-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being a parent is dirty and scary and beautiful and hard and miraculous and exhausting and thankless and joyful and frustrating all at once. It’s everything. (Confessions of a Scary Mommy, Gallery Books 2012)." -- Jill Smokler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282132-maybe-children-just-want-whatever-it-is-they-don-t-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 22:21:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Laura Moriarty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282132-maybe-children-just-want-whatever-it-is-they-don-t-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe children just want whatever it is they don't get. And then they grow up and give their children what they wanted, be it silence or information, affection or independence--so that child, in turn, craves something else. With every generation the pendulum swings from opposite to opposite, stillness and peace so elusive." -- Laura Moriarty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313859-the-fullness-ends-when-we-give-nature-her-ransom-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 22:24:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by John Updike]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313859-the-fullness-ends-when-we-give-nature-her-ransom-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fullness ends when we give Nature her ransom, when we make children for her. Then she is through with us, and we become, first inside, and then outside, junk. Flower stalks." -- John Updike]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29539-then-the-carousel-started-and-i-watched-her-go-round</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2013 19:37:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29539-then-the-carousel-started-and-i-watched-her-go-round]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then the carousel started, and I watched her go round and round...All the kids tried to grap for the gold ring, and so was old Phoebe, and I was sort of afraid she's fall off the goddam horse, but I didn't say or do anything.  The thing with kids is, if they want to grab for the gold ring, you have to let them do it, and not say anything.  If they fall off, they fall off, but it is bad to say anything to them." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245020-children-live-in-the-same-world-we-do-to-kid</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 16:47:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Lionel Shriver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245020-children-live-in-the-same-world-we-do-to-kid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Children live in the same world we do. To kid ourselves that we can shelter them from it isn't just naive it's a vanity." -- Lionel Shriver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286637-a-lot-of-people-get-so-hung-up-on-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 16:47:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Lionel Shriver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286637-a-lot-of-people-get-so-hung-up-on-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A lot of people get so hung up on what they can't have that they don't think for a second about whether they really want it." -- Lionel Shriver]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
