<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/341074-realbadger]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/341074-realbadger" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 23:59:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58832-good-item-seven-the-had-had-and-that-that-problem</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 23:59:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[realbadger add a quote by Jasper Fforde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58832-good-item-seven-the-had-had-and-that-that-problem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good. Item seven. The &lt;i&gt;had had&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;that that&lt;/i&gt; problem. Lady Cavendish, weren’t you working on this?’ 

Lady Cavendish stood up and gathered her thoughts. ‘Indeed. The uses of &lt;i&gt;had had&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;that that&lt;/i&gt; have to be strictly controlled; they can interrupt the imaginotransference quite dramatically, causing readers to go back over the sentence in confusion, something we try to avoid.’

 ‘Go on.’

 ‘It’s mostly an unlicensed-usage problem. At the last count David Copperfield alone had had &lt;i&gt;had had&lt;/i&gt; sixty three times, all but ten unapproved. Pilgrim’s Progress may also be a problem due to its &lt;i&gt;had had/that that&lt;/i&gt; ratio.’

 ‘So what’s the problem in Progress?’ 

 ‘That that had &lt;i&gt;that that&lt;/i&gt; ten times but had had &lt;i&gt;had had&lt;/i&gt; only thrice. Increased &lt;i&gt;had had&lt;/i&gt; usage had had to be overlooked, but not if the number exceeds that &lt;i&gt;that that&lt;/i&gt; usage.’

 ‘Hmm,’ said the Bellman, ‘I thought &lt;i&gt;had had&lt;/i&gt; had had TGC’s approval for use in Dickens? What’s the problem?’ 

 ‘Take the first &lt;i&gt;had had&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;that that&lt;/i&gt; in the book by way of example,’ said Lady Cavendish. ‘You would have thought that that first &lt;i&gt;had had&lt;/i&gt; had had good occasion to be seen as &lt;i&gt;had&lt;/i&gt;, had you not? &lt;i&gt;Had&lt;/i&gt; had had approval but &lt;i&gt;had had&lt;/i&gt; had not; equally it is true to say that that &lt;i&gt;that that&lt;/i&gt; had had approval but that that other &lt;i&gt;that that&lt;/i&gt; had not.’ 

 ‘So the problem with that other &lt;i&gt;that that&lt;/i&gt; was that…?’

 ‘That that other-other &lt;i&gt;that that&lt;/i&gt; had had approval.’ 

 ‘Okay’ said the Bellman, whose head was in danger of falling apart like a chocolate orange, ‘let me get this straight: David Copperfield, unlike Pilgrim’s Progress, had had &lt;i&gt;had&lt;/i&gt;, had had &lt;i&gt;had had&lt;/i&gt;. &lt;i&gt;Had had&lt;/i&gt; had had TGC’s approval?’

 There was a very long pause. ‘Right,’ said the Bellman with a sigh, ‘that’s it for the moment. I’ll be giving out assignments in ten minutes. Session’s over – and let’s be careful out there." -- Jasper Fforde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190920-may-it-american-independence-be-to-the-world-what-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 22:02:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[realbadger add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190920-may-it-american-independence-be-to-the-world-what-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May it [American independence] be to the world, what I believe it will be, (to some parts sooner, to others later, but finally to all,) the signal of arousing men to burst the chains under which monkish ignorance and superstition had persuaded them to bind themselves, and to assume the blessings and security of self-government. That form which we have substituted, restores the free right to the unbounded exercise of reason and freedom of opinion. All eyes are opened, or opening, to the rights of man. The general spread of the light of science has already laid open to every view the palpable truth, that the mass of mankind has not been born with saddles on their backs, nor a favored few booted and spurred, ready to ride them legitimately...  These are grounds of hope for others. For ourselves, let the annual return of this day forever refresh our recollections of these rights, and an undiminished devotion to them.

[&lt;i&gt;Letter to Roger C. Weightman on the anniversary of the signing of the Declaration of Independence in 1776, 24 June 1826. This was Jefferson's last letter&lt;/i&gt;]" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
