<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/341472-jessica]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/341472-jessica" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 22:12:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193843-so-that-s-who-finnick-loves-i-think-not-his-string</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 22:12:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193843-so-that-s-who-finnick-loves-i-think-not-his-string]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So that's who Finnick loves, I think. Not his string of fancy lovers in the Capitol. But a poor, mad girl back home. " -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132445-there-is-nothing-in-the-world-so-easy-to-explain</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 22:13:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Susanna Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132445-there-is-nothing-in-the-world-so-easy-to-explain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing in the world so easy to explain as failure - it is, after all, what everybody does all the time." -- Susanna Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282025-i-reached-out-my-hand-england-s-rivers-turned-and-flowed</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 22:13:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Susanna Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282025-i-reached-out-my-hand-england-s-rivers-turned-and-flowed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I reached out my hand, England's rivers turned and flowed the other way...
I reached out my hand, my enemies's blood stopt in their veins...
I reached out my hand; thought and memory flew out of my enemies' heads like a flock of starlings;
My enemies crumpled like empty sacks.
I came to them out of mists and rain;
I came to them in dreams at midnight;
I came to them in a flock of ravens that filled a northern sky at dawn;
When they thought themselves safe I came to them in a cry that broke the silence of a winter wood...

The rain made a door for me and I went through it;
The stones made a throne for me and I sat upon it;
Three kingdoms were given to me to be mine forever;
England was given to me to be mine forever.
The nameless slave wore a silver crown;
The nameless slave was a king in a strange country...

The weapons that my enemies raised against me are venerated in Hell as holy relics;
Plans that my enemies made against me are preserved as holy texts;
Blood that I shed upon sncient battlefields is scraped from the stained earth by Hell's sacristans and placed in a vessel of silver and ivory.
I gave magic to England, a valuable inheritance
But Englishmen have despised my gift
Magic shall be written upon the sky by the rain but they shall not be able to read it;
Magic shall be written on the faces of the stony hills but their minds shall not be able to contain it;
In winter the barren trees shall be a black writing but they shall not understand it...

Two magicians shall appear in England...
The first shall fear me; the second shall long to behold me;
The first shall be governed by thieves and murderers; the second shall conspire at his own destruction;
The first shall bury his heart in a dark wood beneath the snow, yet still feel its ache;
The second shall see his dearest posession in his enemy's hand...

The first shall pass his life alonel he shall be his own gaoler;
The second shall tread lonely roads, the storm above his head, seeking a dark tower upon a high hillside...

I sit upon a black throne in the shadows but they shall not see me.
The rain shall make a door for me and I shall pass through it;
The stones shall make a throne for me and I shall sit upon it...

The nameless slave shall wear a silver crown
The nameless slave shall be a king in a strange country..." -- Susanna Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/281017-he-gave-her-his-heart-she-took-it-and-placed</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 22:17:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Susanna Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/281017-he-gave-her-his-heart-she-took-it-and-placed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He gave her his heart. She took it and placed it quietly in the pocket of her gown. No one observed what she did." -- Susanna Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140244-do-not-be-deceived-wormwood-our-cause-is-never-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 22:23:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140244-do-not-be-deceived-wormwood-our-cause-is-never-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not be deceived, Wormwood.  Our cause is never more in danger than when a human, no longer desiring, but still intending, to do our Enemy's will, looks round upon a universe from which every trace of Him seems to have vanished, and asks why he has been forsaken, and still obeys." -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/577634-ultimately-the-purpose-of-magic-is-to-free-our-potential</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2012 14:45:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Philip Carr-Gomm]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/577634-ultimately-the-purpose-of-magic-is-to-free-our-potential]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ultimately, the purpose of magic is to free our potential, not bind us to ideas." -- Philip Carr-Gomm]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/577651-not-long-not-long-my-father-said-not-long-shall</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2012 14:56:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Susanna Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/577651-not-long-not-long-my-father-said-not-long-shall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not long, not long my father said
Not long shall you be ours
The Raven King knows all too well
Which are the fairest flowers.

The priest was all too worldly
Though he prayed and rang his bell
The Raven King three candles lit
The priest said it was well

Her arms were all too feeble
Though she claimed to love me so
The Raven King stretched out his hand
She sighed and let me go

The land is all too shallow
It is painted on the sky
And trembles like the wind-shook rain
When the Raven King goes by 

For always and for always
I pray remember me
Upon the moors, beneath the stars
With the King’s wild company." -- Susanna Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/604042-the-risks-involved-in-the-pursuit-of-magic-are--put-simply--either</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 20:54:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Philip Carr-Gomm]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/604042-the-risks-involved-in-the-pursuit-of-magic-are--put-simply--either]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The risks involved in the pursuit of magic are--put simply--either getting frightened by unpleasant perceptions or becoming deluded. Unfortunately it is possible to suffer from both symptoms at the same time." -- Philip Carr-Gomm]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
