<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/343576-amber-macpherson]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/343576-amber-macpherson" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 14:10:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95770-how-in-such-an-alien-and-inhuman-world-can-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 14:10:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95770-how-in-such-an-alien-and-inhuman-world-can-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How, in such an alien and inhuman world, can so powerless a creature as man preserve his aspirations untarnished? A strange mystery it is that nature, omnipotent but blind, in the revolutions of her secular hurryings through the abysses of space, has brought forth at last a child, subject still to her power, but gifted with sight, with knowledge of good and evil, with the capacity of judging all the works of his unthinking mother. In spite of death, the mark and seal of the parental control, man is yet free, during his brief years, to examine, to criticize, to know, and in imagination to create. To him alone, in the world with which he is aquainted, this freedom belongs; and in this lies his superiority to the resistless forces that control his outward life." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8202-most-men-lead-lives-of-quiet-desperation-and-go-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 14:10:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8202-most-men-lead-lives-of-quiet-desperation-and-go-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most men lead lives of quiet desperation and go to the grave with the song still in them." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/869-benedicto-may-your-trails-be-crooked-winding-lonesome-dangerous-leading</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 14:11:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/869-benedicto-may-your-trails-be-crooked-winding-lonesome-dangerous-leading]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Benedicto: May your trails be crooked, winding, lonesome, dangerous, leading to the most amazing view. May your mountains rise into and above the clouds. May your rivers flow without end, meandering through pastoral valleys tinkling with bells, past temples and castles and poets towers into a dark primeval forest where tigers belch and monkeys howl, through miasmal and mysterious swamps and down into a desert of red rock, blue mesas, domes and pinnacles and grottos of endless stone, and down again into a deep vast ancient unknown chasm where bars of sunlight blaze on profiled cliffs, where deer walk across the white sand beaches, where storms come and go as lightning clangs upon the high crags, where something strange and more beautiful and more full of wonder than your deepest dreams waits  for you -- beyond that next turning of the canyon walls." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95774-a-celibate-clergy-is-an-especially-good-idea-because-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 14:12:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95774-a-celibate-clergy-is-an-especially-good-idea-because-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A celibate clergy is an especially good idea, because it tends to suppress any hereditary propensity toward fanaticism." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106912-returning-home-is-the-most-difficult-part-of-long-distance-hiking</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 09:00:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Cindy Ross]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106912-returning-home-is-the-most-difficult-part-of-long-distance-hiking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Returning home is the most difficult part of long-distance hiking; You have grown outside the puzzle and your piece no longer fits." -- Cindy Ross]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109398-how-inappropriate-to-call-this-planet-earth-when-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 11:44:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amber add a quote by Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109398-how-inappropriate-to-call-this-planet-earth-when-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How inappropriate to call this planet &quot;Earth,&quot; when it is clearly &quot;Ocean." -- Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
