<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/344353-brandi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/344353-brandi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 14:16:07 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48482-you-shall-know-the-truth-and-the-truth-shall-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 14:16:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandi add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48482-you-shall-know-the-truth-and-the-truth-shall-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You shall know the truth and the truth shall make you odd." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62793-if-i-could-tell-you-what-it-meant-there-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 14:17:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandi add a quote by Isadora Duncan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62793-if-i-could-tell-you-what-it-meant-there-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I could tell you what it meant, there would be no point in dancing it" -- Isadora Duncan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3356-i-like-nonsense-it-wakes-up-the-brain-cells-fantasy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 14:18:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandi add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3356-i-like-nonsense-it-wakes-up-the-brain-cells-fantasy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like nonsense, it wakes up the brain cells. Fantasy is a necessary ingredient in living." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113611-literacy-is-a-bridge-from-misery-to-hope-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 14:19:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandi add a quote by Kofi Annan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113611-literacy-is-a-bridge-from-misery-to-hope-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Literacy is a bridge from misery to hope. It is a tool for daily life in modern society. It is a bulwark against poverty, and a building block of development, an essential complement to investments in roads, dams, clinics and factories. Literacy is a platform for democratization, and a vehicle for the promotion of cultural and national identity. Especially for girls and women, it is an agent of family health and nutrition. For everyone, everywhere, literacy is, along with education in general, a basic human right.... Literacy is, finally, the road to human progress and the means through which every man, woman and child can realize his or her full potential." -- Kofi Annan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73243-there-are-two-ways-to-get-enough-one-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 11:08:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandi add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73243-there-are-two-ways-to-get-enough-one-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two ways to get enough. One is to continue to accumulate more and more. The other is to desire less." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 11:13:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandi add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what you shall do; Love the earth and sun and the animals, despise riches, give alms to every one that asks, stand up for the stupid and crazy, devote your income and labor to others, hate tyrants, argue not concerning God, have patience and indulgence toward the people, take off your hat to nothing known or unknown or to any man or number of men, go freely with powerful uneducated persons and with the young and with the mothers of families, read these leaves in the open air every season of every year of your life, re-examine all you have been told at school or church or in any book, dismiss whatever insults your own soul, and your very flesh shall be a great poem and have the richest fluency not only in its words but in the silent lines of its lips and face and between the lashes of your eyes and in every motion and joint of your body." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
