<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/34522-timothy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/34522-timothy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 23:22:09 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 23:22:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8-talent-hits-a-target-no-one-else-can-hit-genius</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 23:28:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8-talent-hits-a-target-no-one-else-can-hit-genius]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Talent hits a target no one else can hit. Genius hits a target no one else can see." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71-the-fool-doth-think-he-is-wise-but-the-wise</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 23:28:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71-the-fool-doth-think-he-is-wise-but-the-wise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fool doth think he is wise, but the wise man knows himself to be a fool." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39025-a-nation-of-sheep-will-beget-a-government-of-wolves</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2012 01:50:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Edward R. Murrow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39025-a-nation-of-sheep-will-beget-a-government-of-wolves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A nation of sheep will beget a government of wolves." -- Edward R. Murrow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107022-the-obscure-we-see-eventually-the-completely-obvious-it-seems</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2012 01:54:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Edward R. Murrow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107022-the-obscure-we-see-eventually-the-completely-obvious-it-seems]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The obscure we see eventually. The completely obvious, it seems, takes longer." -- Edward R. Murrow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11540-you-get-a-little-moody-sometimes-but-i-think-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 06:22:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11540-you-get-a-little-moody-sometimes-but-i-think-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You get a little moody sometimes but I think that's because you like to read. People that like to read are always a little fucked up." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/326131-there-are-no-ideas-in-the-south-just-barbecue</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 06:24:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/326131-there-are-no-ideas-in-the-south-just-barbecue]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are no ideas in the South, just barbecue." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584441-men-always-say-that-as-the-defining-compliment-don-t-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 07:37:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584441-men-always-say-that-as-the-defining-compliment-don-t-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men always say that as the defining compliment, don’t they? She’s a cool girl. Being the Cool Girl means I am a hot, brilliant, funny woman who adores football, poker, dirty jokes, and burping, who plays video games, drinks cheap beer, loves threesomes and anal sex, and jams hot dogs and hamburgers into her mouth like she’s hosting the world’s biggest culinary gang bang while somehow maintaining a size 2, because Cool Girls are above all hot. Hot and understanding. Cool Girls never get angry; they only smile in a chagrined, loving manner and let their men do whatever they want. Go ahead, shit on me, I don’t mind, I’m the Cool Girl.

Men actually think this girl exists. Maybe they’re fooled because so many women are willing to pretend to be this girl. For a long time Cool Girl offended me. I used to see men – friends, coworkers, strangers – giddy over these awful pretender women, and I’d want to sit these men down and calmly say: You are not dating a woman, you are dating a woman who has watched too many movies written by socially awkward men who’d like to believe that this kind of woman exists and might kiss them. I’d want to grab the poor guy by his lapels or messenger bag and say: The bitch doesn’t really love chili dogs that much – no one loves chili dogs that much! And the Cool Girls are even more pathetic: They’re not even pretending to be the woman they want to be, they’re pretending to be the woman a man wants them to be. Oh, and if you’re not a Cool Girl, I beg you not to believe that your man doesn’t want the Cool Girl. It may be a slightly different version – maybe he’s a vegetarian, so Cool Girl loves seitan and is great with dogs; or maybe he’s a hipster artist, so Cool Girl is a tattooed, bespectacled nerd who loves comics. There are variations to the window dressing, but believe me, he wants Cool Girl, who is basically the girl who likes every fucking thing he likes and doesn’t ever complain. (How do you know you’re not Cool Girl? Because he says things like: “I like strong women.” If he says that to you, he will at some point fuck someone else. Because “I like strong women” is code for “I hate strong women.”)" -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/574850-sleep-is-like-a-cat-it-only-comes-to-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 07:50:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/574850-sleep-is-like-a-cat-it-only-comes-to-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sleep is like a cat: It only comes to you if you ignore it." -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/638800-tampon-commercial-detergent-commercial-maxi-pad-commercial-windex-commercial--</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 07:51:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/638800-tampon-commercial-detergent-commercial-maxi-pad-commercial-windex-commercial--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tampon commercial, detergent commercial, maxi pad commercial, windex commercial - you'd think all women do is clean and bleed." -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/581714-there-s-no-app-for-a-bourbon-buzz-on-a-warm</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 07:53:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/581714-there-s-no-app-for-a-bourbon-buzz-on-a-warm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's no app for a bourbon buzz on a warm day in a cool, dark bar. The world will always want a drink." -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/611297-because-isn-t-that-the-point-of-every-relationship-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 07:53:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/611297-because-isn-t-that-the-point-of-every-relationship-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because isn’t that the point of every relationship: to be known by someone else, to be understood? He gets me. She gets me. Isn’t that the simple magic phrase?" -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/657205-i-was-told-love-should-be-unconditional-that-s-the-rule</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 07:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/657205-i-was-told-love-should-be-unconditional-that-s-the-rule]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was told love should be unconditional.  That's the rule, everyone says so.  But if love has no boundaries, no limits, no conditions, why should anyone try to do the right thing ever?  If I know I am loved no matter what, where is the challenge? I am supposed to love Nick despite all his shortcomings.  And Nick is supposed to love me despite my quirks.  But clearly, neither of us does.  It makes me think that everyone is very wrong, that love should have many conditions.  Love should require both partners to be their very best at all times." -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/672484-it-s-humbling-to-become-the-very-thing-you-once-mocked</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 07:54:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/672484-it-s-humbling-to-become-the-very-thing-you-once-mocked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s humbling, to become the very thing you once mocked." -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/683272-she-s-easy-to-like-i-ve-never-understood-why-that-s-considered</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 07:55:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/683272-she-s-easy-to-like-i-ve-never-understood-why-that-s-considered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She’s easy to like. I’ve never understood why that’s considered a compliment - that just anyone could like you." -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/917546-the-amy-of-today-was-abrasive-enough-to-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 09:17:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/917546-the-amy-of-today-was-abrasive-enough-to-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Amy of today was abrasive enough to want to hurt, sometimes.  I speak specifically of the Amy of today, who was only remotely like the woman I fell in love with.  It had been an awful fairy-tale reverse transformation.  Over just a few years, the old Amy, the girl of the big laugh and the east ways, literally shed herself, a pile of skin and soul on the floor, and out stepped this new, brittle, bitter Amy.  My wife was no longer my wife but a razor-wire knot daring me to unloop her, and I was not up to the job with my thick, numb, nervous fingers.  Country fingers.  Flyover fingers untrained in the intricate, dangerous work of solving Amy.  When I'd hold up the bloody stumps, she'd sigh and turn to her secret mental notebook on which she tallied all my deficiencies, forever noting disappointments, frailties, shortcomings.  My old Amy, damn, she was fun.  She was fun.  She made me laugh.  I'd forgotten that.  And she laughed,  From the bottom of her throat, from right behind that small finger-shaped hollow, which is the best place to laugh from.  She released her grievances like handfuls of birdseed:  They are there, and they are gone." -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
