<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/345361-jeania]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/345361-jeania" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 08:00:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442553-if-ever-you-have-had-a-romantic-uncalculating-friendship--</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 08:00:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by Harriet Beecher Stowe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442553-if-ever-you-have-had-a-romantic-uncalculating-friendship--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If ever you have had a romantic, uncalculating friendship, - a boundless worship and belief in some hero of your soul, - if ever you have so loved, that all cold prudence, all selfish worldly considerations have gone down like drift-wood before a river flooded with new rain from heaven, so that you even forgot yourself, and were ready to cast your whole being into the chasm of existence, as an offering before the feet of another, and all for nothing, - if you awoke bitterly betrayed and deceived, still give thanks to God that you have had one glimpse of heaven.  The door now shut will open again. Rejoice that the noblest capability of your eternal inheritance has been made known to you; treasure it, as the highest honor of your being, that ever you could so feel, -that so divine a guest ever possessed your soul." -- Harriet Beecher Stowe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 08:09:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/803831-being-in-love-is-a-good-thing-but-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 08:26:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/803831-being-in-love-is-a-good-thing-but-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being in love is a good thing, but it is not the best thing. There are many things below it, but there are also things above it. You cannot make it the basis of a whole life. It is a noble feeling, but it is still a feeling. Now no feeling can be relied on to last in its full intensity, or even to last at all. Knowledge can last, principles can last, habits can last but feelings come and go. And in fact, whatever people say, the state called ‘being in love’ usually does not last. If the old fairy-tale ending ‘They lived happily ever after’ is taken to mean ‘They felt for the next fifty years exactly as they felt the day before they were married,’ then it says what probably never was nor ever would be true, and would be highly undesirable if it were. Who could bear to live in that excitement for even five years? What would become of your work, your appetite, your sleep, your friendships? But, of course, ceasing to be ‘in love’ need not mean ceasing to love. Love in this second sense — love as distinct from ‘being in love’ — is not merely a feeling. It is a deep unity, maintained by the will and deliberately strengthened by habit; reinforced by (in Christian marriages) the grace which both partners ask, and receive, from God. They can have this love for each other even at those moments when they do not like each other; as you love yourself even when you do not like yourself. They can retain this love even when each would easily, if they allowed themselves, be ‘in love’ with someone else. ‘Being in love’ first moved them to promise fidelity: this quieter love enables them to keep the promise. it is on this love that the engine of marriage is run: being in love was the explosion that started it." -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161647-he-looked-at-her-and-tried-to-discover-behind-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 09:39:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161647-he-looked-at-her-and-tried-to-discover-behind-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He looked at her and tried to discover behind her lascivious expression the familiar features that he loved tenderly. It was as if he were looking at two images through the same lens, at two images superimposed one on the other with one showing through the other. These two images showing through each other were telling him that &lt;I&gt;everything&lt;/i&gt; was in the girl, that her soul was terrifyingly amorphous, that it held faithfulness and unfaithfulness, treachery and innocence, flirtatiousness and chastity. This disorderly jumble seemed disgusting to him, like the variety to be found in a pile of garbage. Both images continued to show through each other, and the young man understood that the girl differed only on the surface from other women, but deep down was the same as they: full of all possible thoughts, feelings, and vices, which justified all his secret misgivings and fits of jealousy. The impression that certain outlines delineated her as an individual was only a delusion to which the other person, the one who was looking, was subject--namely himself. It seemed to him that the girl he loved was a creation of his desire, his thoughts, and his faith and that the &lt;I&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; girl now standing in front of him was hopelessly other, hopelessly alien, hopelessly &lt;i&gt;ambiguous&lt;/i&gt;. He hated her." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104368-it-is-an-illusion-that-youth-is-happy-an-illusion</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 09:41:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104368-it-is-an-illusion-that-youth-is-happy-an-illusion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is an illusion that youth is happy, an illusion of those who have lost it; but the young know they are wretched for they are full of the truthless ideal which have been instilled into them, and each time they come in contact with the real, they are bruised and wounded. It looks as if they were victims of a conspiracy; for the books they read, ideal by the necessity of selection, and the conversation of their elders, who look back upon the past through a rosy haze of forgetfulness, prepare them for an unreal life. They must discover for themselves that all they have read and all they have been told are lies, lies, lies; and each discovery is another nail driven into the body on the cross of life." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6766-i-can-listen-no-longer-in-silence-i-must-speak</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 13:36:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6766-i-can-listen-no-longer-in-silence-i-must-speak]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can listen no longer in silence.  I must speak to you by such means as are within my reach.  You pierce my soul.  I am half agony, half hope.  Tell me not that I am too late, that such precious feelings are gone for ever.  I offer myself to you again with a heart even more your own than when you almost broke it, eight years and a half ago.  Dare not say that man forgets sooner than  woman, that his love has an earlier death.  I have loved none but you. Unjust I may have been, weak and resentful I have been, but never inconstant.  You alone have brought me to Bath. For you alone, I think and plan.  Have you not seen this? Can you fail to have understood my wishes?  I had not waited even these ten days, could I have read your feelings, as I think you must have penetrated mine.  I can hardly write.  I am every instant hearing something which overpowers me.  You sink your voice, but I can distinguish the tones of that voice when they would be lost on others. Too good, too excellent creature!  You do us justice, indeed. You do believe that there is true attachment and constancy among men. Believe it to be most fervent, most undeviating, in F. W.

I must go, uncertain of my fate; but I shall return hither, or follow your party, as soon as possible.  A word, a look, will be enough to decide whether I enter your father's house this evening or never." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/562250-i-want-a-girl-because-i-want-to-bring-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 12:51:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/562250-i-want-a-girl-because-i-want-to-bring-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want a girl because I want to bring her up so that she shan't make the mistakes I've made. When I look back upon the girl I was I hate myself. But I never had a chance. I'm going to bring up my daughter so that she's free and can stand on her own feet. I´m not going to bring a child into the world, and love her, and bring her up, just so that some man may want to sleep with her so much that he's willing to provide her with board and lodging for the rest of her life." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21075-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-volcanoes-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2013 09:13:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21075-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-volcanoes-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a temporary madness, it erupts like volcanoes and then subsides.  And when it subsides, you have to make a decision.  You have to work out whether your roots have so entwined together that it is inconceivable that you should ever part.  Because this is what love is.  Love is not breathlessness, it is not excitement, it is not the promulgation of promises of eternal passion, it is not the desire to mate every second minute of the day, it is not lying awake at night imagining that he is kissing every cranny of your body.  No, don't blush, I am telling you some truths.  That is just being &quot;in love&quot;, which any fool can do.  Love itself is what is left over when being in love has burned away, and this is both an art and a fortunate accident." -- Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/817433-martin-looked-at-alejandra-with-a-pained-expression-how-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2013 20:10:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by Ernesto Sabato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/817433-martin-looked-at-alejandra-with-a-pained-expression-how-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Martin looked at Alejandra with a pained expression. How he detested that face of hers, her boutique-face, the one that she seemed to put on deliberately in order to play her role in that frivolous world; a face that seemed to linger on once she found herself alone with him, its abominable features fading away only very slowly, as there gradually emerged one or another of the faces that belonged to him alone, a face he waited for as one awaits a beloved traveler amid a repulsive crowd. But as Bruno said, the word person means &quot;mask&quot;, and each of us has many masks; that of father, professor, lover....But which is the real one? And is there in fact one that is the real one? At certain moments Martin thought that the Alejandra that he was now seeing there before him, laughing at Bobby's jokes, was not, could not be the same Alejandra that he knew, and above all could not be the more profound, the marvelous and fearsome Alejandra that he loved. But at other times (and as the weeks went by the more he began to be convinced of it), he was inclined to think, as Bruno did, that all these Alejandras were real and that that boutique-face was genuine too and in some way or other expressed a sort of reality inherent in Alejandra's soul: a reality--and heaven only knew how many others there were!---that was foreign to him, that did not belong to him and never would. And then, when she came to him still bearing the faint traces of those other personalities, as though she had not had the time (or the desire?) to transform herself, Martin discovered--in a certain sarcastic grin on her lips, in a certain way of moving her hands, in a certain glint in her eyes--the lingering signs of a strange existence: like someone who has been around a garbage dump and still retains something of its foul stench in our presence." -- Ernesto Sabato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/817439-up-there-in-my-little-room-i-was-reading-revolutionary</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2013 20:19:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by Ernesto Sabato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/817439-up-there-in-my-little-room-i-was-reading-revolutionary]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Up there in my little room I was reading revolutionary works and had the feeling that the whole world might explode at any moment; then when I went out, I found life going on as usual, peacefully and calmly: office workers were going off to their jobs, tradesmen were selling their wares in their shops, and one could even see people lazing on benches in the squares, just sitting there watching the hours go by: all of them equally dull and monotonous. Once again, and this would not be the last time, I felt more or less as though I were a stranger in the world, as though I had awakened in it all of a sudden and had no notion of its laws and meaning. I wandered aimlessly about the streets of Buenos Aires, I watched its people, I sat down on a bench in the Plaza Constitucion and meditated. Then I would return to my little room, feeling lonelier than ever. And it was only when I buried myself in books that I seemed to be in touch with reality again, as though that existence out in the streets were, by contrast, a sort of vast dream unfolding in the minds of hypnotized people. It took me many years to realize that in those streets, those public sqaures, and even in those business establishments and offices of Buenos Aires there were thousands who thought or felt more or less as I did at that moment: lonely anguished people, people pondering the sense and nonsense of life, people who had the feeling that they were seeing a world that had gone to sleep round about them, a world made up of men and women who had been hypnotized or turned into robots." -- Ernesto Sabato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/817440-get-a-move-on-perico-and-go-ask-him-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2013 20:24:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by Ernesto Sabato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/817440-get-a-move-on-perico-and-go-ask-him-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Get a move on, Perico, and go ask him for the battery charger,&quot; and the apprentice hurried out, but everything was like a dream and what was the point of any of it: battery chargers, wrenches, mechanics, and he felt sorry for the terrified little boy because, he thought, all of us are dreaming and why punish kids and why fix cars and have crushes on nice boys and then get married and have children who also dream that they're alive, who have to suffer, go off to war or fight or give up hope all on account of mere dreams. He was simply drifting along now, like a boat without a crew swept along by shifting currents, and moving mechanically like those invalids who have lost almost all will and consciousness and yet allow themselves to be moved by the nurses and obey the instructions they are given with the obscure remains of that will and that consciousness without knowing why. The 493, he thought, I go as far as Chacarita and then I take the subway to Florida and then I walk from there to the hotel. So he got on the 493 and mechanically asked for a ticket, and for half an hour continued to see ghosts dreaming of things that kept them very busy; at the Florida stop he went out the exit on the Calle San Martin, walked along the Corrientes to Reconquista and from there headed for the Warszawa rooming house, Accommodations for Gentlemen, went up dirty, dilapidated stairs to the fourth floor, and threw himself on the wretched bed as though he had been wandering through labyrinths for centuries." -- Ernesto Sabato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/817466-she-wanted-to-leave-the-house-and-dance-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2013 21:14:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by Diamela Eltit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/817466-she-wanted-to-leave-the-house-and-dance-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She wanted to leave the house and dance the world away until she fell down dead. For her, every passing minute meant more lost time. Inside the house, she was condemned to live a cloistered life, whereas outside those confining walls, the entire world was enjoying itself. It was like an eternal party..." -- Diamela Eltit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39009-read-read-read-read-everything----trash-classics-good-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2013 21:47:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39009-read-read-read-read-everything----trash-classics-good-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Read, read, read. Read everything -- trash, classics, good and bad, and see how they do it. Just like a carpenter who works as an apprentice and studies the master. Read! You'll absorb it.
Then write. If it's good, you'll find out. If it's not, throw it out of the window." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/817518-and-oh-what-a-mercy-it-is-that-these-women</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2013 23:50:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by Frank Yerby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/817518-and-oh-what-a-mercy-it-is-that-these-women]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And oh, what a mercy it is that these women do not exercise their powers oftener! We can't resist them, if they do. Let them show ever so little inclination, and men go down on their knees at once-old or ugly, it is all the same. And this I set down as a positive truth. A woman with fair opportunities, and without an absolute hump, may marry WHOM SHE LIKES. Only let us be thankful that the darlings are like the beasts of the field, and don't know their own power. They would overcome us entirely if they did." -- Frank Yerby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177996-liking-is-probably-the-best-form-of-ownership-and-ownership</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2013 09:42:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by José Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177996-liking-is-probably-the-best-form-of-ownership-and-ownership]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Liking is probably the best form of ownership, and ownership the worst form of liking." -- José Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93190-you-re-beautiful-but-you-re-empty-one-couldn-t-die-for-you-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2013 09:50:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93190-you-re-beautiful-but-you-re-empty-one-couldn-t-die-for-you-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're beautiful, but you're empty...One couldn't die for you. Of course, an ordinary passerby would think my rose looked just like you. But my rose, all on her own, is more important than all of you together, since she's the one I've watered. Since she's the one I put under glass, since she's the one I sheltered behind the screen. Since she's the one for whom I killed the caterpillars (except the two or three butterflies). Since she's the one I listened to when she complained, or when she boasted, or even sometimes when she said nothing at all. Since she's my rose." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341741-if-you-tame-me-then-we-shall-need-each-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2013 10:44:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341741-if-you-tame-me-then-we-shall-need-each-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…if you tame me, then we shall need each other. To me, you will be unique in all the world. To you, I shall be unique in all the world…if you tame me, it will be as if the sun came to shine on my life. I shall know the sound of a step that will be different from all the others. Other steps send me hurrying back underneath the ground. Yours will call me, like music, out of my burrow" -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1226736-he-and-she-belonged-to-each-other-for-always-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 07:41:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1226736-he-and-she-belonged-to-each-other-for-always-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He and she belonged to each other for always: he understood that now. The impulse which had first drawn them together again, in spite of reason, in spite of themselves almost, that deep-seated instinctive need that each had of the other, would never again wholly let them go." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1396-isn-t-it-enough-to-see-that-a-garden-is-beautiful</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 19:39:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeania add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1396-isn-t-it-enough-to-see-that-a-garden-is-beautiful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't it enough to see that a garden is beautiful without having to believe that there are fairies at the bottom of it too?" -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
