<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/345679-jeff-benner]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/345679-jeff-benner" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 18:15:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3535-once-there-were-brook-trout-in-the-streams-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 18:15:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3535-once-there-were-brook-trout-in-the-streams-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once there were brook trout in the streams in the mountains. You could see them standing in the amber current where the white edges of their fins wimpled softly in the flow. They smelled of moss in your hand. Polished and muscular and torsional. On their backs were vermiculate patterns that were maps of the world in its becoming. Maps and mazes. Of a thing which could not be put back. Not be made right again. In the deep glens where they lived all things were older than man and they hummed of mystery." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189325-i-m-tempted-to-point-out-that-our-dealings-however-unusual</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 18:13:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Joseph O'Neill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189325-i-m-tempted-to-point-out-that-our-dealings-however-unusual]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm tempted to point out that our dealings, however unusual and close, were the dealings of businessmen. My ease with this state of affairs no doubt reveals a shortcoming on my part, but it's the same quality that enables me to thrive at work, where so many of the brisk, tough, successful men I meet are secretly sick to their stomachs and their quarterlies, are being eaten alive by bosses and clients and all-seeing wives and judgmental offspring, and are, in sum, desperate to be taken at face value and very happy to reciprocate the courtesy. This chronic and, I think, peculiarly male strain of humiliation explains the slight affection that bonds so many of us, but such affection depends on a certain reserve. Chuck observed the code, and so did I; neither pressed the other on delicate subjects." -- Joseph O'Neill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44666-you-forget-what-you-want-to-remember-and-you-remember</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 18:13:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44666-you-forget-what-you-want-to-remember-and-you-remember]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You forget what you want to remember, and you remember what you want to forget." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189921-but-surely-everyone-can-also-testify-to-another-less-reckonable</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 18:22:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Joseph O'Neill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189921-but-surely-everyone-can-also-testify-to-another-less-reckonable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But surely everyone can also testify to another, less reckonable kind of homesickness, one having to do with unsettlements that cannot be located in spaces of geography or history; and accordingly it's my belief that the communal, contractual phenomenon of New York cricket is underwritten, there where the print is finest, by the same agglomeration of unspeakable individual longings that underwrites cricket played anywhere--longings concerned with horizons and potentials sighted or hallucinated and in any event lost long ago, tantalisms that touch on the undoing of losses too private and reprehensible to be acknowledged to oneself, let alone to others.  I cannot be the first to wonder if what we see, when we see men in white take to a cricket field, is men imagining an environment of justice." -- Joseph O'Neill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119543-literature-has-to-remain-frustrating-to-withhold-something-remain</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 03:31:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Tom McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119543-literature-has-to-remain-frustrating-to-withhold-something-remain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Literature has to remain frustrating — to withhold something, remain incomplete — or it’s not literature anymore, but rather entertainment, edification or interpretation. That’s literature’s USP: staying unresolved, keeping its most vital messages unspoken, creating a zone of noise where everything and nothing is said at the same time." -- Tom McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
