<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/347233-geoffrey-h-goodwin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/347233-geoffrey-h-goodwin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2011 19:54:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202964-we-re-the-unmended-the-untended-cold-soldiers-of-the-shoe</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2011 19:54:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202964-we-re-the-unmended-the-untended-cold-soldiers-of-the-shoe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're the unmended, the untended,
cold soldiers of the shoe. We're the neglected,
the never resurrected, agonies of the few.
We're the once kissed, unmissed and always
refused. Because we're the unfinished
and feared and we're never pursued.

And just that easily, on my behalf,
I come around. Because I'm burning.
The beast of War feeds only on the meats of War.
And now I'm for carnage.
Here's how my anguish frees.
Destroy everyone of course. Because I'm unwanted
and unsafe. And I'll take tears away with torments and rape,
killings and fears not even the dead will escape.
Encircling the Guilty, Ashamed, Blameless and
Enslaved. Absolved. Butchering their prejudice.

Patience. Their Value. Because I'm without value.
I'm the coming of every holocaust. Turning no lost.
Rending tissue, sinew and bone. Excepting no suffering.
By me all levees will break. All silos heave.
I will walk heavy.
And I will walk strange.

Because I am too soon.
Because without Her, I am only revolutions
Of ruin.

Because I am too soon.
Because without You, I am only revolutions
Of ruin.

I'm the prophecy prophecies pass.
Why need dies at last.
How oceans dry. Islands drown.
And skies of salt crash to the ground.
I turn the powerful. Defy the weak.
Only grass grows down abandoned streets.

For a greater economy shall follow Us
and it will be undone.
And a greater autonomy shall follow Us
and it too will be undone.
And a greater feeling shall follow Love
and it too we will blow to dust.
For I am longings without trust. The cycloidal haste
freedom from Hailey forever wastes.
Dust cares for only dust.
And time only for Us.

Because I am too soon.
Because without Her, I am only revolutions
Of ruin.

Because I am too soon.
Because without You, I am only revolutions
Of ruin.

We are always sixteen..." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75699-a-gun-is-psychologically-a-penis-substitute-and-a-symbol-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2011 18:46:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Adam Hall]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75699-a-gun-is-psychologically-a-penis-substitute-and-a-symbol-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A gun is psychologically a penis-substitute and a symbol of power: the age-range of toy-shop clientele begins at about six or seven, rises sharply just before puberty and declines soon after the discovery of the phallus and its promise of power.  From then on, guns are for kids and for the effete freaks and misfits who must seek psycho-orgasmic relief by shooting pheasants." -- Adam Hall]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279962-the-main-rule-of-writing-is-that-if-you-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 21:42:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279962-the-main-rule-of-writing-is-that-if-you-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The main rule of writing is that if you do it with enough assurance and confidence, you’re allowed to do whatever you like. (That may be a rule for life as well as for writing. But it’s definitely true for writing.) So write your story as it needs to be written. Write it honestly, and tell it as best you can. I’m not sure that there are any other rules. Not ones that matter." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53414-writing-is-like-driving-at-night-in-the-fog-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2012 12:46:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by E.L. Doctorow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53414-writing-is-like-driving-at-night-in-the-fog-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing is like driving at night in the fog. You can only see as far as your headlights, but you can make the whole trip that way." -- E.L. Doctorow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/505888-i-ve-often-thought-that-there-isn-t-any-i-at-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 04:58:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Aleister Crowley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/505888-i-ve-often-thought-that-there-isn-t-any-i-at-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've often thought that there isn't any &quot;I&quot; at all; that we are simply the means of expression of something else; that when we think we are ourselves, we are simply the victims of a delusion." -- Aleister Crowley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4952-everywhere-i-go-i-m-asked-if-i-think-the-university</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 14:04:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4952-everywhere-i-go-i-m-asked-if-i-think-the-university]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everywhere I go I'm asked if I think the university stifles writers. My opinion is that they don't stifle enough of them. There's many a best-seller that could have been prevented by a good teacher." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393092-when-you-stare-into-the-abyss-the-abyss-stares-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 14:06:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche, Фридрих Ницше]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393092-when-you-stare-into-the-abyss-the-abyss-stares-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you stare into the abyss the abyss stares back at you." -- Friedrich Nietzsche, Фридрих Ницше]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14033-question-i-am-interested-in-so-many-things-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 17:09:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14033-question-i-am-interested-in-so-many-things-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Question: I am interested in so many things, and I have a terrible fear because my mother keeps telling me that I'm just going to be exploring the rest of my life and never get anything done. But I find it really hard to set my ways and say, &quot;Well, do I want to do this, or should I try to exploit that, or should I escape and completely do one thing?&quot;

Anaïs Nin: One word I would banish from the dictionary is 'escape.' Just banish that and you'll be fine. Because that word has been misused regarding anybody who wanted to move away from a certain spot and wanted to grow. He was an escapist. You know if you forget that word you will have a much easier time. Also you're in the prime, the beginning of your life; you should experiment with everything, try everything.... We are taught all these dichotomies, and I only learned later that they could work in harmony. We have created false dichotomies; we create false ambivalences, and very painful one's sometimes -the feeling that we have to choose. But I think at one point we finally realize, sometimes subconsciously, whether or not we are really fitted for what we try and if it's what we want to do.

You have a right to experiment with your life. You will make mistakes. And they are right too. No, I think there was too rigid a pattern. You came out of an education and are supposed to know your vocation. Your vocation is fixed, and maybe ten years later you find you are not a teacher anymore or you're not a painter anymore. It may happen. It has happened. I mean Gauguin decided at a certain point he wasn't a banker anymore; he was a painter. And so he walked away from banking. I think we have a right to change course. But society is the one that keeps demanding that we fit in and not disturb things. They would like you to fit in right away so that things work now." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/319610-anything-you-can-imagine-is-probably-true-and-the-worst</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2012 23:08:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Will Christopher Baer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/319610-anything-you-can-imagine-is-probably-true-and-the-worst]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anything you can imagine is probably true.  And the worst you can imagine is probably worth money." -- Will Christopher Baer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230626-all-forms-of-madness-bizarre-habits-awkwardness-in-society-general</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 10:52:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Roman Payne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230626-all-forms-of-madness-bizarre-habits-awkwardness-in-society-general]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All forms of madness, bizarre habits, awkwardness in society, general clumsiness, are justified in the person who creates good art." -- Roman Payne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93846-all-your-questions-can-be-answered-if-that-is-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 09:39:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93846-all-your-questions-can-be-answered-if-that-is-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All your questions can be answered, if that is what you want.  But once you learn your answers, you can never unlearn them." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146155-behind-every-beautiful-thing-there-s-some-kind-of-pain</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2013 21:17:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Bob Dylan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146155-behind-every-beautiful-thing-there-s-some-kind-of-pain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Behind every beautiful thing, there's some kind of pain." -- Bob Dylan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60443-there-is-an-ancient-tribal-proverb-i-once-heard-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 20:48:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60443-there-is-an-ancient-tribal-proverb-i-once-heard-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is an ancient tribal proverb I once heard in India.  It says that before we can see properly we must first shed our tears to clear the way." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53088-i-have-been-a-believer-in-the-magic-of-language</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 19:44:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Katherine Dunn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53088-i-have-been-a-believer-in-the-magic-of-language]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have been a believer in the magic of language since, at a very early age, I discovered that some words got me into trouble and others got me out. " -- Katherine Dunn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291843-the-sinister-the-terrible-never-deceive-the-state-in-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 15:36:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Thomas Ligotti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291843-the-sinister-the-terrible-never-deceive-the-state-in-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sinister, the terrible never deceive: the state in which they leave us is always one of enlightenment.  And only this condition of vicious insight allows us a full grasp of the world, all things considered, just as a frigid melancholy grants us full possession of ourselves.  We may hide from horror only in the heart of horror. (“The Medusa”)" -- Thomas Ligotti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39526-you-have-decided-being-scared-is-caused-mostly-by-thinking</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 10:28:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39526-you-have-decided-being-scared-is-caused-mostly-by-thinking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have decided being scared is caused mostly by thinking. " -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98625-writing-is-nothing-more-than-a-guided-dream</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 18:29:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98625-writing-is-nothing-more-than-a-guided-dream]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing is nothing more than a guided dream." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80562-the-novelist-with-christian-concerns-will-find-in-modern-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 09:54:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80562-the-novelist-with-christian-concerns-will-find-in-modern-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The novelist with Christian concerns will find in modern life distortions which are repugnant to him, and his problem will be to make these appear as distortions to an audience which is used to seeing them as natural; and he may well be forced to take ever more violent means to get his vision across to this hostile audience.  When you can assume that your audience holds the same beliefs you do, you can relax a little and use more normal ways of talking to it; when you have to assume that it does not, then you have to make your vision apparent by shock -- to the hard of hearing you shout, and for the almost blind you draw large and startling figures." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162411-if-all-insects-on-earth-disappeared-within-50-years-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 09:03:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Biologist Jonas Salk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162411-if-all-insects-on-earth-disappeared-within-50-years-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["if all insects on Earth disappeared, within 50 years all life on
Earth would end. If all human beings disappeared from the Earth,
within 50 years all forms of life would flourish." -- Biologist Jonas Salk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/641188-the-artistic-life-is-a-long-lovely-suicide</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 18:05:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/641188-the-artistic-life-is-a-long-lovely-suicide]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The artistic life is a long, lovely suicide." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17931-if-you-want-to-really-hurt-you-parents-and-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 11:08:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17931-if-you-want-to-really-hurt-you-parents-and-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to really hurt you parents, and you don't have the nerve to be gay, the least you can do is go into the arts. I'm not kidding. The arts are not a way to make a living. They are a very human way of making life more bearable. Practicing an art, no matter how well or badly, is a way to make your soul grow, for heaven's sake. Sing in the shower. Dance to the radio. Tell stories. Write a poem to a friend, even a lousy poem. Do it as well as you possible can. You will get an enormous reward. You will have created something." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/937204-you-are-so-brave-and-quiet-i-forget-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 20:58:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/937204-you-are-so-brave-and-quiet-i-forget-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are so brave and quiet I forget you are suffering." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/963003-screenplays-are-structure-and-that-s-all-they-are-the-quality</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 14:29:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/963003-screenplays-are-structure-and-that-s-all-they-are-the-quality]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Screenplays are structure, and that’s all they are. The quality of writing—which is crucial in almost every other form of literature—is not what makes a screenplay work. Structure isn’t anything else but telling the story, starting as late as possible, starting each scene as late as possible. You don’t want to begin with “Once upon a time,” because the audience gets antsy." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/614684-i-m-not-afraid-of-death-it-s-the-stake-one-puts</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 06:08:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Jean Giraudoux]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/614684-i-m-not-afraid-of-death-it-s-the-stake-one-puts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not afraid of death. It's the stake one puts up in order to play the game of life." -- Jean Giraudoux]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/375072-i-didn-t-want-to-wake-up-i-was-having-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 13:29:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Ned Vizzini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/375072-i-didn-t-want-to-wake-up-i-was-having-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I didn't want to wake up. I was having a much better time asleep. And that's really sad. It was almost like a reverse nightmare, like when you wake up from a nightmare you're so relieved. I woke up into a nightmare." -- Ned Vizzini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177458-here-is-a-lesson-in-creative-writing-first-rule-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 18:45:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177458-here-is-a-lesson-in-creative-writing-first-rule-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here is a lesson in creative writing.

First rule: Do not use semicolons. They are transvestite hermaphrodites representing absolutely nothing. All they do is show you've been to college.

And I realize some of you may be having trouble deciding whether I am kidding or not. So from now on I will tell you when I'm kidding.

For instance, join the National Guard or the Marines and teach democracy. I'm kidding.

We are about to be attacked by Al Qaeda. Wave flags if you have them. That always seems to scare them away. I'm kidding.

If you want to really hurt your parents, and you don't have the nerve to be gay, the least you can do is go into the arts. I'm not kidding. The arts are not a way to make a living. They are a very human way of making life more bearable. Practicing an art, no matter how well or badly, is a way to make your soul grow, for heaven's sake. Sing in the shower. Dance to the radio. Tell stories. Write a poem to a friend, even a lousy poem. Do it as well as you possibly can. You will get an enormous reward. You will have created something." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2203-it-is-what-you-read-when-you-don-t-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 15:45:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2203-it-is-what-you-read-when-you-don-t-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is what you read when you don't have to that determines what you will be when you can't help it." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1129963-non-fiction-non-fiction-listen-reality-is-what-got-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 12:45:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffrey H. add a quote by Justin Alcala]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1129963-non-fiction-non-fiction-listen-reality-is-what-got-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Non fiction? Non fiction?! Listen, reality is what got me into this mess in the first place." -- Justin Alcala]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
