<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/349918-joanna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/349918-joanna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 22:52:06 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 22:52:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6597-poets-have-been-mysteriously-silent-on-the-subject-of-cheese</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2010 14:49:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6597-poets-have-been-mysteriously-silent-on-the-subject-of-cheese]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Poets have been mysteriously silent on the subject of cheese." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59027-i-think-we-ought-to-live-happily-ever-after</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 08:16:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by Diana Wynne Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59027-i-think-we-ought-to-live-happily-ever-after]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think we ought to live happily ever after." -- Diana Wynne Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113091-wil-wheaton-says-don-t-be-a-dick</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 07:24:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by Wil Wheaton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113091-wil-wheaton-says-don-t-be-a-dick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wil Wheaton Says: Don't be a dick." -- Wil Wheaton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7507-remember-to-always-be-yourself-unless-you-suck</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2012 18:28:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7507-remember-to-always-be-yourself-unless-you-suck]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember to always be yourself. Unless you suck." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35497-after-nourishment-shelter-and-companionship-stories-are-the-thing-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 20:21:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35497-after-nourishment-shelter-and-companionship-stories-are-the-thing-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After nourishment, shelter and companionship, stories are the thing we need most in the world." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34409-hey-girls-you-re-beautiful-don-t-look-at-those-stupid-magazines</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 14:36:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by Gerard Way]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34409-hey-girls-you-re-beautiful-don-t-look-at-those-stupid-magazines]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hey, girls, you're beautiful. Don't look at those stupid magazines with sticklike models. Eat healthy and exercise. That's all. Don't let anyone tell you you're not good enough. You're good enough, you are too good. Love your family with all your heart and listen to it. You are gorgeous, whether you're a size 4 or 14. It doesn't matter what you look like on the outside, as long as you're a good person, as long as you respect others. I know it's been told hundreds of times before, but it's true. Hey, girls, you are beautiful." -- Gerard Way]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/602541-don-t-gobblefunk-around-with-words</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2012 15:09:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by Roald Dahl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/602541-don-t-gobblefunk-around-with-words]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't gobblefunk around with words." -- Roald Dahl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/517832-before-i-opened-my-computer-in-the-parking-lot-today</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 09:13:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by Diane Keaton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/517832-before-i-opened-my-computer-in-the-parking-lot-today]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Before I opened my computer in the parking lot today, I relived one of my favorite memories. It's the one with Woody and me sitting on the steps of the Metropolitan Museum after it's closed. We're watching people parade out of the museum in summer shorts and sandals. The trees to the south are planted in parallel lines. The water in the fountain shoots up with a mist that almost reaches the steps we sit on. We look at silver-haired ladies in red-and-white-print dresses. We separate the mice from the men, the tourists from the New Yorkers, the Upper East Siders from the West Siders. The hot-pretzel vendor sells us a wad of dough in knots with clumps of salt stuck on top. We make our usual remarks about the crazies and wonder what it would be like to live in a penthouse apartment on Fifth Avenue overlooking the Met. We laugh and say the same things we always say. We hold hands and keep sitting, just sitting, as the sun beings to set. It's a perfect afternoon." -- Diane Keaton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/428374-her-son-lives-he-has-her-eyes-precisely-her-eyes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 09:13:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/428374-her-son-lives-he-has-her-eyes-precisely-her-eyes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her son lives. He has her eyes, precisely her eyes. You remember the shape and color of Lily Evans's eyes, I am sure?" -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21756-in-this-dirty-minded-world-you-are-either-someone-s-wife</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 09:14:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21756-in-this-dirty-minded-world-you-are-either-someone-s-wife]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In this dirty minded world, you are either someone's wife or someone's whore. And if you're not either people think there is something wrong with you....but there is nothing wrong with me" -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413047-everybody-has-a-secret-world-inside-of-them-i-mean</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2012 16:27:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413047-everybody-has-a-secret-world-inside-of-them-i-mean]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody has a secret world inside of them. I mean everybody. All of the people in the whole world, I mean everybody — no matter how dull and boring they are on the outside. Inside them they've all got unimaginable, magnificent, wonderful, stupid, amazing worlds... Not just one world. Hundreds of them. Thousands, maybe." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485209-set-wide-the-window-let-me-drink-the-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 11:37:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485209-set-wide-the-window-let-me-drink-the-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Set wide the window. Let me drink the day." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/718380-there-are-no-mistakes-only-journeys</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 21:11:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by Sibella Court]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/718380-there-are-no-mistakes-only-journeys]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are no mistakes, only journeys." -- Sibella Court]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383235-he-tried-to-drown-his-troubles-but-they-knew-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 13:41:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by Rita Mae Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383235-he-tried-to-drown-his-troubles-but-they-knew-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He tried to drown his troubles but they knew how to swim." -- Rita Mae Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/454548-fat-is-usually-the-first-insult-a-girl-throws-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 14:12:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/454548-fat-is-usually-the-first-insult-a-girl-throws-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fat’ is usually the first insult a girl throws at another girl when she wants to hurt her.

I mean, is ‘fat’ really the worst thing a human being can be? Is ‘fat’ worse than ‘vindictive’, ‘jealous’, ‘shallow’, ‘vain’, ‘boring’ or ‘cruel’? Not to me; but then, you might retort, what do I know about the pressure to be skinny? I’m not in the business of being judged on my looks, what with being a writer and earning my living by using my brain…

I went to the British Book Awards that evening. After the award ceremony I bumped into a woman I hadn’t seen for nearly three years. The first thing she said to me? ‘You’ve lost a lot of weight since the last time I saw you!’

‘Well,’ I said, slightly nonplussed, ‘the last time you saw me I’d just had a baby.’

What I felt like saying was, ‘I’ve produced my third child and my sixth novel since I last saw you. Aren’t either of those things more important, more interesting, than my size?’ But no – my waist looked smaller! Forget the kid and the book: finally, something to celebrate!

I’ve got two daughters who will have to make their way in this skinny-obsessed world, and it worries me, because I don’t want them to be empty-headed, self-obsessed, emaciated clones; I’d rather they were independent, interesting, idealistic, kind, opinionated, original, funny – a thousand things, before ‘thin’. And frankly, I’d rather they didn’t give a gust of stinking chihuahua flatulence whether the woman standing next to them has fleshier knees than they do. Let my girls be Hermiones, rather than Pansy Parkinsons." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/349942-she-remembered-one-of-her-boyfriends-asking-offhandedly-how-many</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 11:28:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by Eleanor Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/349942-she-remembered-one-of-her-boyfriends-asking-offhandedly-how-many]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She remembered one of her boyfriends asking, offhandedly, how many books she read in a year. &quot;A few hundred,&quot; she said.
&quot;How do you have the time?&quot; he asked, gobsmacked.
She narrowed her eyes and considered the array of potential answers in front of her. Because I don't spend hours flipping through cable complaining there's nothing on? Because my entire Sunday is not eaten up with pre-game, in-game, and post-game talking heads? Because I do not spend every night drinking overpriced beer and engaging in dick-swinging contests with the other financirati? Because when I am waiting in line, at the gym, on the train, eating lunch, I am not complaining about the wait/staring into space/admiring myself in reflective surfaces? I am reading!
&quot;I don't know,&quot; she said, shrugging." -- Eleanor Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/779-love-doesn-t-just-sit-there-like-a-stone-it-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 11:29:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joanna add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/779-love-doesn-t-just-sit-there-like-a-stone-it-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love doesn't just sit there, like a stone, it has to be made, like bread; remade all the time, made new." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
