<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/350237-jorma]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/350237-jorma" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 19:58:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49262-if-i-had-my-life-to-live-over-i-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 19:58:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jorma add a quote by Erma Bombeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49262-if-i-had-my-life-to-live-over-i-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["IF I HAD MY LIFE TO LIVE OVER

I would have talked less and listened more.

I would have invited friends over to dinner even if the carpet was stained and the sofa faded.

I would have eaten the popcorn in the &quot;good&quot; living room and worried much less about the dirt when someone wanted to light a fire in the fireplace.

I would have taken the time to listen to my grandfather rambling about his youth.

I would never have insisted the car windows be rolled up on a summer day because my hair had just been teased and sprayed.

I would have burned the pink candle sculped like a rose before it melted 
in storage.

I would have sat on the lawn with my children and not worried about grass stains.

I would have cried and laughed less while watching television, and more 
while watching life.

I would have gone to bed when I was sick, instead of pretending the earth would go into a holding pattern if I weren't there for the day.

I would never have bought anything just because it was practical, wouldn't show soil or was guaranteed to last a lifetime.

Instead of wishing away nine months of pregnancy, I'd have cherished every moment, realising that the wonderment growing inside me was the only chance in life to assist God in a miracle.

When my kids kissed me impetuously, I would never have said, &quot;Later. Now go get washed up for dinner.&quot;

There would have been more &quot;I love you's&quot; and more &quot;I'm sorry's&quot;

. . . but mostly, given another shot at life, I would seize every minute . . . 
look at it and really see it . . . and never give it back." -- Erma Bombeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13715-some-books-should-be-tasted-some-devoured-but-only-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 20:00:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jorma add a quote by Sir Francis Bacon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13715-some-books-should-be-tasted-some-devoured-but-only-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some books should be tasted, some devoured, but only a few should be chewed and digested thoroughly." -- Sir Francis Bacon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160654-i-m-calm-rachel-insisted-every-time-i-m-around-you-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 13:39:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jorma add a quote by Rick Riordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160654-i-m-calm-rachel-insisted-every-time-i-m-around-you-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm calm,&quot; Rachel insisted. &quot;Every time I'm around you, some monsters attack us. What's to be nervous about?&quot;
&quot;Look,&quot; I said. &quot;I'm sorry about the band room. I hope they didn't kick you our or anything.&quot;
&quot;Nah. They asked me a lot of questions about you. I played dumb.&quot;
&quot;Was it hard?&quot; Annabeth asked." -- Rick Riordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277594-butch-hesitated-annabeth-s-okay-you-gotta-cut-her-some-slack</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 14:13:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jorma add a quote by Rick Riordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277594-butch-hesitated-annabeth-s-okay-you-gotta-cut-her-some-slack]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Butch hesitated. &quot;Annabeth's okay. You gotta cut her some slack. She had a vision telling her to come here, to find a guy with one shoe. That was supposed to be the answer to her problem.&quot;

&quot;What Problem?&quot; Piper asked.

&quot;She's been looking for one of our campers, who's been missing three days,&quot;  Butch said. &quot;She's going out of her mind with worry. She hoped he'd be here.&quot;

&quot;Who?&quot; Jason asked.

&quot;Her boyfriend,&quot; Butch said, &quot;A guy named Percy Jackson." -- Rick Riordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240131-athena-called-annabeth-chase-my-own-daughter-annabeth-squeezed-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 14:14:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jorma add a quote by Rick Riordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240131-athena-called-annabeth-chase-my-own-daughter-annabeth-squeezed-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Athena called, &quot;Annabeth Chase, my own daughter.&quot;
Annabeth squeezed my arm, then walked forward and knelt at her mother's feet.
Athena smiled. &quot;You, my daughter, have exceeded all expectations. You have used your wits, your strength, and your courage to defend this city, and our seat of power. It has come to our attention that Olympus is...well, trashed. The Titan lord did much damage that will have to be repaired. We could rebuild it by magic, of course, and make it just as it was. But the gods feel that the city could be improved. We will take this as an opportunity. And you, my daughter, will design these improvements.&quot;
Annabeth looked up, stunned. &quot;My...my lady?&quot;
Athena smiled wryly. &quot;You are an architect, are you not? You have studied the techniques of Daedalus himself. Who better to redesign Olympus and make it a monument that will last for another eon?&quot;
&quot;You mean...I can design whatever I want?&quot;
&quot;As your heart desires,&quot; the goddess said. &quot;Make us a city for the ages.&quot;
&quot;As long as you have plenty of statues of me,&quot; Apollo added.
&quot;And me,&quot; Aphrodite agreed.
&quot;Hey, and me!&quot; Ares said. &quot;Big statues with huge wicked swords and-&quot;
All right!&quot; Athena interrupted. &quot;She gets the point. Rise, my daughter, official architect of Olympus." -- Rick Riordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240072-hephaestus-glowered-up-at-us-i-didn-t-make-you-did</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 14:16:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jorma add a quote by Rick Riordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240072-hephaestus-glowered-up-at-us-i-didn-t-make-you-did]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hephaestus glowered up at us. “I didn’t make you, did I?”

Uh,” Annabeth said, “no, sir.”

Good,” the god grumbled. “Shoddy workmanship." -- Rick Riordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240126-i-ve-got-this-apollo-stepped-forward-his-fiery-armor-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 14:25:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jorma add a quote by Rick Riordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240126-i-ve-got-this-apollo-stepped-forward-his-fiery-armor-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've got this.&quot; Apollo stepped forward. His fiery armor was so bright it was hard to look at, and his matching Ray-Bans and perfect smile made him look like a male model for battle gear. &quot;God of medicine, at your service.&quot;

He passed his hand over Annabeth's face and spoke an incantation. Immediately the bruises faded. Her cuts and scars disappeared. Her arm straightened, and she sighed in her sleep.

Apollo grinned. &quot;She'll be fine in a few minutes. Just enough time for me to compose a poem about our victory: 'Apollo and his friends save Olympus.' Good, eh?&quot;

Thanks, Apollo,&quot; I said. &quot;I'll, um, let you handle the poetry." -- Rick Riordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407928-you-saved-the-world-annabeth-said-we-saved-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 14:26:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jorma add a quote by Rick Riordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407928-you-saved-the-world-annabeth-said-we-saved-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You saved the world,&quot; annabeth said.
&quot;We saved the world.&quot;
&quot;And Rachel is the new Oracle, which means she won't be dating anybody.&quot;
&quot;You don't sound disappointed,&quot; I noticed.
Annabeth shrugged. &quot;Oh, I don't care.&quot;
&quot;Uh-huh.&quot;
She raised an eyebrow. &quot;You got something to say to me, Seaweed Brain?&quot;
&quot;You'd probably kick my butt.&quot;
&quot;You know I'd kick your butt.&quot;
I brushed the cake off my hands. &quot;When I was at the River Styx, turning invulnerable . . . Nico said I had to concentrate on one thing that kept me anchored to the world, that made me want to stay mortal.&quot;
Annabeth kept her eyes on the horizon. &quot;Yeah?&quot;
&quot;Then up on Olympus,&quot; I said, &quot;when they wanted to make me a god and stuff, I kept thinking—&quot;
&quot;Oh, you so wanted to.&quot;
&quot;Well, maybe a little. But I didn't, because I thought—I didn't want things to stay the same for eternity, because
things could always get better. And I was thinking . . .&quot; My throat felt really dry.
&quot;Anyone in particular?&quot; Annabeth asked, her voice soft.
I looked over and saw that she was trying not to smile.
&quot;You're laughing at me,&quot; I complained.
&quot;I am not!&quot;
&quot;You are so not making this easy.&quot;
Then she laughed for real, and she put her hands around my neck. &quot;I am never, ever going to make things easy for
you, Seaweed Brain. Get used to it.&quot;
When she kissed me, I had the feeling my brain was melting right through my body. I could've stayed that way forever, except a voice behind us growled, &quot;Well, it's about time!&quot;
Suddenly the pavilion was filled with torchlight and campers. Clarisse led the way as the eavesdroppers charged and hoisted us both onto their shoulders.
&quot;Oh, come on!&quot; I complained. &quot;Is there no privacy?&quot;
&quot;The lovebirds need to cool off!&quot; Clarisse said with glee.
&quot;The canoe lake!&quot; Connor Stoll shouted. and they dumped us in the water." -- Rick Riordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410285-annabeth-my-fatal-flaw-that-s-what-the-sirens-showed-me-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 14:28:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jorma add a quote by Rick Riordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410285-annabeth-my-fatal-flaw-that-s-what-the-sirens-showed-me-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Annabeth:My fatal flaw.  That's what the Sirens showed me. My fatal flaw is hubris. 
Percy: the brown stuff they spread on veggie sandwiches?
Annabeth:No, Seaweed Brain. That's HUMMUS. hubris is worse.
Percy: what could be worse than hummus? 
Annabeth: Hubris means deadly pride, Percy. Thinking you can do things better than anyone else... Even the gods." -- Rick Riordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395071-right-before-the-game-she-strolled-up-to-me-hey</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 14:28:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jorma add a quote by Rick Riordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395071-right-before-the-game-she-strolled-up-to-me-hey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Right before the game, she strolled up to me. &quot;Hey, Seaweed Brain.&quot;
&quot;Will you stop calling me that?&quot;
She knows I hate that name, mostly because I never have a good comeback. She's the daughter of Athena, which doesn't give me a lot of ammunition. I mean, &quot;Owl-head&quot; and &quot;Wise Girl&quot; are kind of lame insults." -- Rick Riordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407880-annabeth-came-up-to-me-she-was-dressed-in-black</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 14:29:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jorma add a quote by Rick Riordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407880-annabeth-came-up-to-me-she-was-dressed-in-black]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Annabeth came up to me. She was dressed in black camouflage with her Celestial bronze knife strapped to her arm and her laptop bag slung over her shoulder—ready for stabbing or surfing the Internet, whichever came first." -- Rick Riordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407882-whoa-connor-stoll-said-back-up-zoom-in-right-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 14:32:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jorma add a quote by Rick Riordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407882-whoa-connor-stoll-said-back-up-zoom-in-right-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whoa,&quot; Connor Stoll said. &quot;Back up. Zoom in right there.&quot;
&quot;What?&quot; Annabeth said nervously. &quot;You see invaders?&quot;
&quot;No, right there—Dylan's Candy Bar.&quot; Connor grinned at his brother. &quot;Dude, it's open. And everyone is asleep. Are you thinking what I'm thinking?&quot;
&quot;Connor!&quot; Katie Gardner scolded. She sounded like her mother, Demeter. &quot;This is serious. You are not going to loot a candy store in the middle of a war!&quot;
&quot;Sorry,&quot; Connor muttered, but he didn't sound very ashamed." -- Rick Riordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410321-okay-annabeth-said-what-exactly-do-you-smell-something-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 14:33:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jorma add a quote by Rick Riordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410321-okay-annabeth-said-what-exactly-do-you-smell-something-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Okay,&quot; Annabeth said.  &quot;What exactly do you smell?&quot;
&quot;Something bad,&quot; Tyson answered.
&quot;Great,&quot; Annabeth grumbled.  &quot;That clears it up." -- Rick Riordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 07:50:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jorma add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that is gold does not glitter,
Not all those who wander are lost;
The old that is strong does not wither,
Deep roots are not reached by the frost.

From the ashes a fire shall be woken,
A light from the shadows shall spring;
Renewed shall be blade that was broken,
The crownless again shall be king." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38750-and-that-s-the-thing-about-people-who-mean-everything-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 09:32:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jorma add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38750-and-that-s-the-thing-about-people-who-mean-everything-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And that's the thing about people who mean everything they say. They think everyone else does too." -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11241-everyone-must-leave-something-behind-when-he-dies-my-grandfather</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 09:36:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jorma add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11241-everyone-must-leave-something-behind-when-he-dies-my-grandfather]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone must leave something behind when he dies, my grandfather said. A child or a book or a painting or a house or a wall built or a pair of shoes made. Or a garden planted. Something your hand touched some way so your soul has somewhere to go when you die, and when people look at that tree or that flower you planted, you're there. 

It doesn't matter what you do, he said, so long as you change something from the way it was before you touched it into something that's like you after you take your hands away. The difference between the man who just cuts lawns and a real gardener is in the touching, he said. The lawn-cutter might just as well not have been there at all; the gardener will be there a lifetime." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
