<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/351102-lynn]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/351102-lynn" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 15:13:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33329-the-willingness-to-forgive-is-a-sign-of-spiritual-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 15:13:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33329-the-willingness-to-forgive-is-a-sign-of-spiritual-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The willingness to forgive is a sign of spiritual and emotional maturity.  It is one of the great virtues to which we all should aspire.  Imagine a world filled with individuals willing both to apologize and to accept an apology.  Is there any problem that could not be solved among people who possessed the humility and largeness of spirit and soul to do either -- or both -- when needed?" -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16841-with-time-and-perspective-we-recognize-that-such-problems-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 15:20:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lynn add a quote by Jeffery R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16841-with-time-and-perspective-we-recognize-that-such-problems-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With time and perspective we recognize that such problems in life do come for a purpose, if only to allow the one who faces such despair to be convinced that he really does need divine strength beyond himself, that she really does need the offer of heaven’s hand. Those who feel no need for mercy usually never seek it and almost never bestow it. Those who have never had a heartache or a weakness or felt lonely or forsaken never have had to cry unto heaven for relief of such personal pain. Surely it is better to find the goodness of God and the grace of Christ, even at the price of despair, than to risk living our lives in a moral or material complacency that has never felt any need for faith or forgiveness, any need for redemption or relief." -- Jeffery R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
