<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/351333-roberto-musa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/351333-roberto-musa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 08:06:21 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1098099-es-harto-sabido-que-cuando-las-personas-se-aventuran-por</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 08:06:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roberto add a quote by Susan Sontag]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1098099-es-harto-sabido-que-cuando-las-personas-se-aventuran-por]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Es harto sabido que cuando las personas se aventuran por los confines últimos de la consciencia , arriesgan su cordura, o lo que es lo mismo, su humanidad.

La Imaginación Pornográfica" -- Susan Sontag]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1098108-today-whether-we-are-doing-algebra-or-playing-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 08:07:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roberto add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1098108-today-whether-we-are-doing-algebra-or-playing-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today, whether we are doing algebra or playing with the computer, we are, in effect, benefitting from some inheritance of the quest for a perfect language.

For a Polyglot Federation" -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1098121-every-one-is-familiar-with-the-phenomenon-of-feeling-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 08:10:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roberto add a quote by William James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1098121-every-one-is-familiar-with-the-phenomenon-of-feeling-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every one is familiar with the phenomenon of feeling more or less alive on different days. Every one knows on any given day that there are energies slumbering in him which the incitements of that day do not call forth, but which he might display if these were greater. Most of us feel as if we lived habitually with a sort of cloud weighing on us, below our highest notch of clearness in discernment, sureness in reasoning, or firmness in deciding. Compared with what we ought to be, we are only half awake." -- William James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1098124-that-certainly-seems-a-satisfactory-explanation-does-it-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 08:10:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roberto add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1098124-that-certainly-seems-a-satisfactory-explanation-does-it-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["– That certainly seems a satisfactory explanation, does it not?
– Yes dear, if you can believe him.
– I don't. But that does not affect the wonderful beauty of his answer." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1098169-the-custom-of-eating-the-lover-after-consummination-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 08:19:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roberto add a quote by Jean Henri Fabre]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1098169-the-custom-of-eating-the-lover-after-consummination-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The custom of eating the lover after consummination of the nuptials, of making a meal of the exhausted pigmy, who is henceforth good for nothing, is not so difficult to understand, since insects can hardly be accused of sentimentality; but to devour him during the act surpasses anything the most morbid mind could imagine. I have seen the thing with my own eyes, and I have not yet recovered from my surprise." -- Jean Henri Fabre]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333723-those-who-know-nothing-of-foreign-languages-know-nothing-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 08:20:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roberto add a quote by Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333723-those-who-know-nothing-of-foreign-languages-know-nothing-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who know nothing of foreign languages know nothing of their own." -- Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1098184---i-should-be-doing-my-homework-now-but-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 08:23:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roberto add a quote by Bill Watterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1098184---i-should-be-doing-my-homework-now-but-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["- I should be doing my homework now. But the way I look at it, playing in the snow is a lot more important. Out here I'm learning real skills that I can apply throughout the rest of my life.

- Such as?

- Procrastination and rationalization." -- Bill Watterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1098193-i-have-drawn-from-books-written-by-learned-experts-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 08:25:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roberto add a quote by Joseph Wood Krutch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1098193-i-have-drawn-from-books-written-by-learned-experts-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have drawn from books written by learned experts and also upon my observation of living creatures in whom I have long delighted and with whom I have perhaps more sympathy than some of those who remain austerely scientific. The intuitions of a lover are not always to be trusted; but neither are those of the loveless." -- Joseph Wood Krutch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1099095-we-have-a-task-before-us-which-must-be-speedily</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 12:18:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roberto add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1099095-we-have-a-task-before-us-which-must-be-speedily]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have a task before us which must be speedily performed. We know that it will be ruinous to make delay. The most important crisis of our life calls, trumpet-tongued, for immediate energy and action. We glow, we are consumed with eagerness to commence the work, with the anticipation of whose glorious result our whole souls are on fire. It must, it shall be undertaken to-day, and yet we put it off until to-morrow, and why? There is no answer, except that we feel perverse, using the word with no comprehension of the principle. To-morrow arrives, and with it a more impatient anxiety to do our duty, but with this very increase of anxiety arrives, also, a nameless, a positively fearful, because unfathomable, craving for delay. This craving gathers strength as the moments fly. The last hour for action is at hand. We tremble with the violence of the conflict within us,-of the definite with the indefinite-of the substance with the shadow. But, if the contest have proceeded thus far, it is the shadow which prevails,-we struggle in vain. The clock strikes, and is the knell of our welfare. At the same time, it is the chanticleer- note to the ghost that has so long overawed us. It flies-it disappears-we are free. The old energy returns. We will labor now. Alas, it is too late!" -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
