<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/353657-leighanne]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/353657-leighanne" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 20:05:58 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114021-what-should-i-do-about-the-wild-and-the-tame</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 20:05:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leighanne add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114021-what-should-i-do-about-the-wild-and-the-tame]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What should I do about the wild and the tame? The wild heart that wants to be free, and the tame heart that wants to come home. I want to be held. I don't want you to come too close. I want you to scoop me up and bring me home at nights. I don't want to tell you where I am. I want to keep a place among the rocks where no one can find me. I want to be with you." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152137-on-more-than-one-occasion-i-have-been-ready-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 20:06:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leighanne add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152137-on-more-than-one-occasion-i-have-been-ready-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On more than one occasion I have been ready to abandon my whole life for love. To alter everything that makes sense to me and to move into a different world where the only known will be the beloved. Such a sacrifice must be the result of love... or is it that the life itself was already worn out? I had finished with that life, perhaps, and could not admit it, being stubborn or afraid, or perhaps did not known it, habit being a great binder. I think it is often so that those most in need of change choose to fall in love and then throw up their hands and blame it all on fate. But it is not fate, at least, not if fate is something outside of us; it is a choice made in secret after nights of longing.
... I may be cynical when I say that very rarely is the beloved more than a shaping spirit for the lover's dreams... To be a muse may be enough. The pain is when the dreams change, as they do, as they must. Suddenly the enchanted city fades and you are left alone again in the windy desert. As for your beloved, she didn't understand you.
The truth is, you never understood yourself." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137368-there-is-no-sense-in-loving-someone-you-can-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 20:07:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leighanne add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137368-there-is-no-sense-in-loving-someone-you-can-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no sense in loving someone you can never wake up to except by chance." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23178-there-are-many-forms-of-love-and-affection-some-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 20:08:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leighanne add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23178-there-are-many-forms-of-love-and-affection-some-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are many forms of love and affection, some people can spend their whole lives together without knowing each other's names. Naming is a difficult and time-consuming process; it concerns essences, and it means power. But on the wild nights who can call you home? Only the one who knows your name." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64685-what-is-it-that-you-contain-the-dead-time-light</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 20:15:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leighanne add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64685-what-is-it-that-you-contain-the-dead-time-light]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is it that you contain?  The dead.  Time.  Light patterns of millennia opening in your gut.  Every minute, in each of you, a few million potassium atoms succumb to radioactive decay.  The energy that powers these tiny atomic events has been locked inside potassium atoms ever since a star-sized bomb exploded nothing into being.  Potassium, like uranium and radium, is a long-lived radioactive nuclear waste of the supernova bang that accounts for you.

Your first parent was a star." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/444704-when-my-husband-had-an-affair-with-someone-else-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 20:22:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leighanne add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/444704-when-my-husband-had-an-affair-with-someone-else-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When my husband had an affair with someone else I watched his eyes glaze over when we ate dinner together and I heard him singing to himself without me, and when he tended the garden it was not for me.

He was courteous and polite; he enjoyed being at home, but in the fantasy of his home I was not the one who sat opposite him and laughed at his jokes. He didn't want to change anything; he liked his life. The only thing he wanted to change was me.

It would have been better if he had hated me, or if he had abused me, or if he had packed his new suitcases and left.

As it was he continued to put his arm round me and talk about being a new wall to replace the rotten fence that divided our garden from his vegetable patch. I knew he would never leave our house. He had worked for it.

Day by day I felt myself disappearing. For my husband I was no longer a reality, I was one of the things around him. I was the fence which needed to be replaced. I watched myself in the mirror and saw that I was mo longer vivid and exciting. I was worn and gray like an old sweater you can't throw out but won't put on.

He admitted he was in love with her, but he said he loved me.

Translated, that means, I want everything. Translated, that means, I don't want to hurt you yet. Translated, that means, I don't know what to do, give me time.

Why, why should I give you time? What time are you giving me? I am in a cell waiting to be called for execution.

I loved him and I was in love with him. I didn't use language to make a war-zone of my heart.

'You're so simple and good,' he said, brushing the hair from my face.

He meant, Your emotions are not complex like mine. My dilemma is poetic.

But there was no dilemma. He no longer wanted me, but he wanted our life

Eventually, when he had been away with her for a few days and returned restless and conciliatory, I decided not to wait in my cell any longer. I went to where he was sleeping in another room and I asked him to leave. Very patiently he asked me to remember that the house was his home, that he couldn't be expected to make himself homeless because he was in love.

'Medea did,' I said, 'and Romeo and Juliet and Cressida, and Ruth in the Bible.'

He asked me to shut up. He wasn't a hero.

'Then why should I be a heroine?'

He didn't answer, he plucked at the blanket.

I considered my choices.

I could stay and be unhappy and humiliated.

I could leave and be unhappy and dignified.

I could Beg him to touch me again.

I could live in hope and die of bitterness.

I took some things and left. It wasn't easy, it was my home too.

I hear he's replaced the back fence." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122987-poor-me-there-s-nothing-so-sweet-as-wallowing-in-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 20:26:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leighanne add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122987-poor-me-there-s-nothing-so-sweet-as-wallowing-in-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Poor me. There's nothing so sweet as wallowing in it is there? Wallowing is sex for depressives." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120138-the-body-can-endure-compromise-and-the-mind-can-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 20:26:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leighanne add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120138-the-body-can-endure-compromise-and-the-mind-can-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The body can endure compromise and the mind can be seduced by it. Only the heart protests. The heart. Carbon-based primitive in a silicon world." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42146-although-wherever-you-are-going-is-always-in-front-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 20:27:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leighanne add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42146-although-wherever-you-are-going-is-always-in-front-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Although wherever you are going is always  in front of you, there is no such thing as straight ahead." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
