<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/354489-bo]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/354489-bo" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 19:35:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33504-there-are-blonde-and-blondes-and-it-is-almost-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 19:35:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Raymond Chandler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33504-there-are-blonde-and-blondes-and-it-is-almost-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are blonde and blondes and it is almost a joke word nowadays.  All blondes have their points, except perhaps the metallic ones who are as blonde as a Zulu under the bleach and as to disposition as soft as a sidewalk.  There is the small cute blonde who cheeps and twitters, and the big statuesque blonde who straight-arms you with an ice-blue glare.  There is the blonde who gives you the up-from-under look and smells lovely and shimmers and hangs on your arm and is always very, very tired when you take her home.  She makes that helpless gesture and has that goddamned headache and you would like to slug her except that you found  about the headache before you invested too much time and money and hope in her.  Because the headache will always be there, a weapon that never wears out and is as deadly as the bravo’s rapier or Lucrezia’s poison vial.  
	There is the soft and willing alcoholic blonde who doesn’t care what she wears as long as it is mink or where she goes as long as it is the Starlight Roof and there is plenty of dry champagne.  There is the small perky blonde who is a little pale and wants to pay her own way and is full of sunshine and common sense and knows judo from the ground up and can toss a truck driver over her shoulder without missing more than one sentence out of the editorial in the Saturday Review.  There is the pale, pale blonde with anemia of some non-fatal but incurable type.  She very languid and very shadowy and she speaks softly out of nowhere and you can’t lay a finger on her because in the first place you don’t want to and in the second place she is reading the Wasteland or Dante in the original, or Kafka or Kierkegaard or studying Provencal.  She adores music and when the New York Philharmonic is playing Hindesmith she can tell you which one of the six bass viols came in a quarter of a beat too late.  I hear Toscanini can also.  That makes two of them.   
And lastly there is the gorgeous show piece who will outlast three kingpin racketeers and then marry a couple of millionaires at a million a head and end up with a pale rose villa at Cap d’Antibes, and Alfa Romeo town car complete with pilot and co-pilot, and a stable of shopworn aristocrats, all of whom she will treat with the affectionate absentmindedness of an elderly duke saying good night to his butler." -- Raymond Chandler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33505-why-of-course-the-people-don-t-want-war-why-should</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 19:37:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Hermann Goering]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33505-why-of-course-the-people-don-t-want-war-why-should]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why of course the people don't want war. Why should some poor slob on a farm want to risk his life in a war when the best he can get out of it is to come back to his farm in one piece? Naturally the common people don't want war: neither in Russia, nor in England, nor for that matter in Germany. That is understood. But after all it is the leaders of a country who determine the policy and it is always a simple matter to drag the people along, whether it is a democracy or fascist dictorship, or a parliament or a communist dictatorship. Voice or no voice, the people can always be brought to the bidding of the leaders. That is easy. All you have to do is tell them they are being attacked, and denounce the peace makers for lack of patriotism and exposing the country to danger. It works the same in any country." -- Hermann Goering]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33506-you-are-nearing-the-land-that-is-life-you-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 19:38:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33506-you-are-nearing-the-land-that-is-life-you-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are nearing the land that is life; you will recognize it by its seriousness." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
