<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/354874-lucy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/354874-lucy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 10:03:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/623398-with-the-historical-radar-of-marx-s-theories-on-whose-screen</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 10:03:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucy add a quote by Amadeo Bordiga]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/623398-with-the-historical-radar-of-marx-s-theories-on-whose-screen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With the historical radar of Marx’s theories, on whose screen observers who have not swallowed the alcohol of the intoxicating bourgeois ideology cannot read lies, in the fog of the depths off Nantacket, in the dark of the walled tomb of the living in Marcinelle, in the bitterness of the slime of the stagnant ponds of the Arabian Desert, while the forces of the Revolution seem to be hiding and Great Capital carouses in the bright sunlight, we have again found, at his inexhaustible work, the Old Mole who undermines the curse of the infamous social forms, who prepares for the not near, but most certain, destructive explosion." -- Amadeo Bordiga]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114782-men-make-their-own-history-but-they-do-not-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 23:37:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucy add a quote by Karl Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114782-men-make-their-own-history-but-they-do-not-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men make their own history, but they do not make it as they please; they do not make it under self-selected circumstances, but under circumstances existing already, given and transmitted from the past. The tradition of all dead generations weighs like a nightmare on the brains of the living. And just as they seem to be occupied with revolutionizing themselves and things, creating something that did not exist before, precisely in such epochs of revolutionary crisis they anxiously conjure up the spirits of the past to their service, borrowing from them names, battle slogans, and costumes in order to present this new scene in world history in time-honored disguise and borrowed language." -- Karl Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/478403-art-is-sanctioned-pornography</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 04:42:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucy add a quote by Stewart Home]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/478403-art-is-sanctioned-pornography]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Art is sanctioned pornography" -- Stewart Home]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/478404-live-now-die-later</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 04:42:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucy add a quote by Stewart Home]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/478404-live-now-die-later]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Live now, die later!" -- Stewart Home]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/619598-chus-martinez-is-a-transsexual-collective-phantom-anybody-can-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 04:46:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucy add a quote by Chus Martinez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/619598-chus-martinez-is-a-transsexual-collective-phantom-anybody-can-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chus Martinez is a transsexual collective phantom. Anybody can be Chus Martinez!" -- Chus Martinez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198401-cities-have-the-capability-of-providing-something-for-everybody-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 13:38:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucy add a quote by Jane Jacobs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198401-cities-have-the-capability-of-providing-something-for-everybody-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cities have the capability of providing something for everybody, only because, and only when, they are created by everybody." -- Jane Jacobs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364-the-truth-is-rarely-pure-and-never-simple</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 00:22:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucy add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364-the-truth-is-rarely-pure-and-never-simple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is rarely pure and never simple." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47188-life-should-not-be-a-journey-to-the-grave-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 03:10:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucy add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47188-life-should-not-be-a-journey-to-the-grave-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life should not be a journey to the grave with the intention of arriving safely in a pretty and well preserved body, but rather to skid in broadside in a cloud of smoke, thoroughly used up, totally worn out, and loudly proclaiming &quot;Wow! What a Ride!" -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/637-i-hate-to-advocate-drugs-alcohol-violence-or-insanity-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 03:11:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucy add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/637-i-hate-to-advocate-drugs-alcohol-violence-or-insanity-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hate to advocate drugs, alcohol, violence, or insanity to anyone, but they've always worked for me." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533425-i-m-sorry-i-am-developing-a-new-board-game-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 09:54:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucy add a quote by José N. Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533425-i-m-sorry-i-am-developing-a-new-board-game-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’M SORRY

I am developing a new board game. It’s called “I’m Sorry.” It’s also a form of “Self-Help Psychological Therapy!”

You take turns moving around the board like Monopoly. But if you land on a Yellow or Green “I’m Sorry Space”… you have to make a Phone call. Both green and yellow cards are labeled- the same with things like: Your Ex, Parental figure, friend, co-worker, boss, children, etc. You get the point…

If you land on the yellow space, the game stops, everyone gets quiet and you have to call that person up – on speakerphone. You apologize for something you’ve done in your past. Come on you know you are not perfect and you probably screwed up, hurt or disappointed everyone in your past at one time or another. So you call and you apologize. You explain what you did to them wrong if they forgive you, you move forward 10 places and everyone cheers! No forgiveness back- you move back to the beginning.

If you land on the green space- it’s similar. But you call the person up and you try to explain to them how, in someway, they hurt you in the past. If they apologize… cheers and you move forward 10 spaces. No apology… move backward ten spaces. They curse at you- game over.

In the original packaging of the yellow and green cards, are mixed in a set of “I’m Sorry Cards.” If you are lucky enough to get to pick up an “I’m Sorry Card,” it’s like a Get Out of Jail Free Card, and you don’t have to make the call.

The only catch is that the cards come hermetically sealed. After opening up the package, and the cards are exposed to air, all of the “I’m Sorry Cards,” magically turn into “Deal With it Cards!” And so, you really never get a free ride. In reality, every time you pick up a yellow or green card, you have to- Deal with It!

Of course you can always order a new factory set of sealed of “I’m Sorry Cards.” But they only last about 30 minutes and are very expensive, so you’ll have to play fast. Cute Game? Hey, don’t steal my idea!!!" -- José N. Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
