<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/35523-nicole]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/35523-nicole" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2008 12:46:45 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11555-i-didn-t-have-a-chance-to-buy-you-anything-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2008 12:46:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Annie Proulx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11555-i-didn-t-have-a-chance-to-buy-you-anything-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I didn't have a chance to buy you anything,&quot; she said, then held both closed hands toward him. Uncurled her fingers. In each cupped palm a brown egg. He took them. They were cold. He thought it a tender, wonderful thing to do. She had given him something, the eggs, after all, only a symbol, but they had come from her hands as a gift. To him. It didn't matter that he'd bought them himself at the supermarket the day before. He imagined she understood him, that she had to love him to know that it was the outstreched hands, the giving, that mattered." -- Annie Proulx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18255-if-only-my-mother-had-a-book-to-hold-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 15:42:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Brock Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18255-if-only-my-mother-had-a-book-to-hold-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If only my mother had a book to hold, she wouldn't have looked so lonely. And maybe this was another reason why people read: not so they would feel less lonely, but so that other people would think they looked less lonely with a book in their hands and therefore not pity them and leave them alone." -- Brock Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35408-i-have-heard-it-said-that-a-complicated-childhood-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 19:54:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35408-i-have-heard-it-said-that-a-complicated-childhood-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have heard it said that a complicated childhood can lead to a life in the arts. I tell you this story of my father and me to let you know I am qualified to be a comedian." -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44593-at-every-moment-i-convinced-myself-that-i-was-gathering</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 10:54:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Edmund White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44593-at-every-moment-i-convinced-myself-that-i-was-gathering]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At every moment I convinced myself that I was gathering material for the novel of my life - all experienced from the philosophical distance of the author. Even these humiliating occasions when I was robbed could be used as material. Life was a field trip. " -- Edmund White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49018-i-m-not-a-drug-salesman-i-m-a-writer-what-makes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 15:23:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49018-i-m-not-a-drug-salesman-i-m-a-writer-what-makes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not a drug salesman. I'm a writer.&quot;

&quot;What makes you think a writer isn't a drug salesman?" -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50047-he-has-the-memory-of-a-convict-the-balls-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 18:15:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50047-he-has-the-memory-of-a-convict-the-balls-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has the memory of a convict, the balls of a fireman, and the eyesight of a housebreaker. When there is crime to fight, Landsman tears around Sitka like a man with his pant leg caught on a rocket. It's like there's a film score playing behind him, heavy on the castanets. The problem comes in the hours when he isn't working, when his thoughts start blowing out the open window of his brain like pages from the blotter. Sometimes it takes a heavy paperweight to pin them down." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64901-i-thought-everyone-would-be-familiar-with-this-figure-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2008 17:49:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64901-i-thought-everyone-would-be-familiar-with-this-figure-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I thought everyone would be familiar with this figure: if I'd studied a thing in school I assumed it was general knowledge. I hadn't yet discovered that I lived in a sort of transparent balloon, drifting over the world without making much contact with it, and that the people I knew appeared to me at a different angle from the one at which they appeared to themselves; and that the reverse was also true. I was smaller to others, up there in my balloon, than I was to myself. I was also blurrier." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64902-she-wasn-t-ready-to-settle-down-she-told-her-friends</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2008 17:52:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64902-she-wasn-t-ready-to-settle-down-she-told-her-friends]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She wasn't ready to settle down, she told her friends. That was one way of putting it. Another was would have been that she had not found anyone to settle down with. There had been several men in her life, but they hadn't been convincing. They'd been somewhat like her table - quickly acquired, brightened up a little, but temporary. The time for that kind of thing was running out, however. She was tired of renting." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66273-i-ll-tell-you-said-beatty-smiling-at-his-cards-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 18:10:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66273-i-ll-tell-you-said-beatty-smiling-at-his-cards-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'll tell you,&quot; said Beatty, smiling at his cards. &quot;That made you for a little while a drunkard. Read a few lines and off you go over the cliff. Bang, you're ready to blow up the world, chop off heads, knock down women and children, destroy authority. I know. I've been through it all." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21922-i-ate-them-like-salad-books-were-my-sandwich-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 18:12:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21922-i-ate-them-like-salad-books-were-my-sandwich-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I ate them like salad, books were my sandwich for lunch, my tiffin and dinner and midnight munch. I tore out the pages, ate them with salt, doused them with relish, gnawed on the bindings, turned the chapters with my tongue! Books by the dozen, the score and the billion. I carried so many home I was hunchbacked for years. Philosophy, art history, politics, social science, the poem, the essay, the grandiose play, you name 'em, I ate 'em." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70578-her-big-heart-did-not-as-is-so-sadly-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 19:28:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Dorothy Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70578-her-big-heart-did-not-as-is-so-sadly-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her big heart did not, as is so sadly often the case, inhabit a big bosom." -- Dorothy Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73294-she-had-such-control-of-tone-in-her-text-messages</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 18:31:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Keith Gessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73294-she-had-such-control-of-tone-in-her-text-messages]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had such control of &lt;i&gt;tone&lt;/i&gt;, in her text messages, she was the Edith Wharton of text messaging." -- Keith Gessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83138-but-what-i-did-was-the-kind-of-thing-you-d</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2008 17:58:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Jim Shepard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83138-but-what-i-did-was-the-kind-of-thing-you-d]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But what I did was the kind of thing you'd do and the kind of thing you've done: I felt bad for him and for myself and I went on with my week and then my summer and I started telling my story to whoever would listen. And my story was this: I survived camp. I survived my brother. I survived my own bad feelings. Love me for being so sad about it. Love me for knowing what I did. Love me for being in the lifeboat after everyone else went under. And my story made me feel better and it made me feel worse. And it worked." -- Jim Shepard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119429-julia-s-vocabulary-was-chock-full-of-strangely-archaic-words---spiffing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 20:30:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Kate Atkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119429-julia-s-vocabulary-was-chock-full-of-strangely-archaic-words---spiffing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Julia's vocabulary was &quot;chock-full&quot; of strangely archaic words - &quot;spiffing,&quot; &quot;crumbs,&quot; &quot;jeepers&quot; - that seemed to have originated in some prewar girls' annual rather than in Julia's own life. For Jackson, words were functional, they helped you get to places and explain things. For Julia, they were freighted with inexplicable emotion." -- Kate Atkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122741-past-a-certain-point-it-is-not-interesting-to-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 18:54:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Martha Cooley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122741-past-a-certain-point-it-is-not-interesting-to-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Past a certain point it is not interesting  to think about childhood as the central drama and adulthood as its reprise." -- Martha Cooley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125486-but-that-s-what-i-mean-you-re-ms-hempel-forever-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 14:44:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Sarah Shun-lien Bynum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125486-but-that-s-what-i-mean-you-re-ms-hempel-forever-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But that's what I mean: you're Ms. Hempel forever. At least to us." -- Sarah Shun-lien Bynum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128506-i-enjoyed-making-them-and-if-it-s-great-reverence-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2009 04:44:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128506-i-enjoyed-making-them-and-if-it-s-great-reverence-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I enjoyed making them, and if it's great reverence you're looking for, or earnest expressions of gratitude - well, then you don't work with kids." -- Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129092-i-protested-a-man-is-known-by-his-deeds-oh</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 10:59:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by M. T. Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129092-i-protested-a-man-is-known-by-his-deeds-oh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I protested, 'A man is known by his deeds.' 

Oh, that's sure,' said Bono. 'Just like a house is known by its deeds. The deeds say who owns it, who sold it, and who'll be buying a new one when it gets knocked down." -- M. T. Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23479-empedocles-claims-that-in-utero-our-backbone-is-one-long</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 11:00:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by M.T. Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23479-empedocles-claims-that-in-utero-our-backbone-is-one-long]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Empedocles claims that in utero, our backbone is one long solid; and that through the constriction of the womb and the punishments of birth it must be snapped again and again to form our vertebrae; that for the child to have a spine, his back must first be broken." -- M.T. Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134598-that-s-what-archie-did---built-a-house-nobody-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 20:17:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Robert Cormier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134598-that-s-what-archie-did---built-a-house-nobody-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's what Archie did - built a house nobody could anticipate a need for, except himself, a house that was invisible to everyone else." -- Robert Cormier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138615-the-other-girls-in-the-village-never-felt-restless-nhamo</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2009 18:16:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Nancy Farmer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138615-the-other-girls-in-the-village-never-felt-restless-nhamo]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The other girls in the village never felt restless. Nhamo was like a pot of boiling water. 'I want...I want...,' she whispered to herself, but she didn't know what she wanted and she had no idea how to find it. " -- Nancy Farmer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138616-she-took-to-reading-with-a-fervor-so-extreme-baba</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2009 18:17:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Nancy Farmer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138616-she-took-to-reading-with-a-fervor-so-extreme-baba]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She took to reading with a fervor so extreme, Baba Joseph had to take the books from her hands by force. 'Your eyes are not tractors. They are not meant to pull heavy loads,' he said sternly." -- Nancy Farmer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139175-it-is-a-terrible-thing-this-kindess-that-human-beings</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 18:33:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139175-it-is-a-terrible-thing-this-kindess-that-human-beings]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a terrible thing, this kindess that human beings do not lose. Terrible, because when we are finally naked in the dark and cold, it is all we have. We who are so rich, so full of strength, we end up with that small change. We have nothing else to give. " -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156754-a-clinton-staffer-tells-me-his-theory-think-about-frank</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 08:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156754-a-clinton-staffer-tells-me-his-theory-think-about-frank]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A Clinton staffer tells me his theory. Think about Frank Sinatra, he says: born to sing. Think about Willie Mays: born to play ball. These guys got their power from living lives perfectly suited to their natures. Same with Clinton: his life is perfectly suited to his nature. " -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157560-you-need-the-noise-of-your-friends-in-space</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2009 09:28:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by M. T. Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157560-you-need-the-noise-of-your-friends-in-space]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You need the noise of your friends in space." -- M. T. Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158940-sometimes-i-had-the-feeling-that-all-of-us-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2009 11:33:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Bernhard Schlink]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158940-sometimes-i-had-the-feeling-that-all-of-us-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I had the feeling that all of us in his family were like pets to him. The dog you take for a walk, the cat you play with and that curls up in your lap, purring, to be stroked - you can be fond of them, you can even need them to a certain extent, and nonetheless the whole thing - buying pet food, cleaning up the cat box, and trips to the vet - is really too much. Your life is elsewhere. " -- Bernhard Schlink]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158942-it-is-hard-for-me-to-imagine-that-i-felt</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2009 11:34:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Bernhard Schlink]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158942-it-is-hard-for-me-to-imagine-that-i-felt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is hard for me to imagine that I felt good about behaving like that. I also remember that the smallest gesture of affection would bring a lump to my throat, whether it was directed at me or at someone else. Sometimes all it took was a scene in a movie. This juxtaposition of callousness and extreme sensitivity seemed suspicious even to me. " -- Bernhard Schlink]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159139-i-got-that-familiar-mania---there-is-information-somewhere</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 14:47:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Elizabeth McCracken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159139-i-got-that-familiar-mania---there-is-information-somewhere]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I got that familiar mania - there is information somewhere here, and I can find it, I have to. A good librarian is not so different from a prospector, her whole brain a divining rod. She walks to books and stands and wonders: here? Is the answer here? The same blind faith in finding, even when hopeless. If someone caught me when I was in the throes of tracking something elusive, I would have told them: but it's out there. I can feel it." -- Elizabeth McCracken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159220-i-had-never-wanted-to-be-one-of-those-girls</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 19:05:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Elizabeth McCracken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159220-i-had-never-wanted-to-be-one-of-those-girls]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had never wanted to be one of those girls in love with boys who would not have me. Unrequited love - plain desperate aboveboard boy-chasing - turned you into a salesperson, and what you were selling was something he didn't want, couldn't use, would never miss. Unrequited love was deciding to be useless, and I could never abide uselessness.

Neither could James. He understood. In such situations, you do one of two things - you either walk away and deny yourself, or you do sneaky things to get what you need. You attend weddings, you go for walks. You say, yes. Yes, you're my best friend, too." -- Elizabeth McCracken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164652-i-was-gushing-and-i-knew-it-i-surprised-myself</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2009 08:39:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164652-i-was-gushing-and-i-knew-it-i-surprised-myself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was gushing and I knew it. I surprised myself with my eagerness to please, felt myself saying too much, explaining too much, overinvolved and overexcited in the way you are when you're a kid and you think you've found a soul mate in the new boy down the street and you feel yourself drawn by the force of the courtship and so act as you don't normally do and a lot more openly than you may even want to." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
