<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/355784-alysson]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/355784-alysson" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 15:49:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7515-i-will-say-it-one-last-time-demonation-the-feeling</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 15:49:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Clive Barker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7515-i-will-say-it-one-last-time-demonation-the-feeling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will say it one last time: Demonation! The feeling of it! &lt;i&gt;There are no words&lt;/i&gt; -how can there be?- to describe what it feels like to &lt;i&gt;become&lt;/i&gt; words, to feel your life encoded, and laid out in black ink on white paper. All my love and hatred, melted into words.  It was like the End of the World." -- Clive Barker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10764-i-dreamed-i-spoke-in-another-s-language-i-dreamed-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 15:49:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Clive Barker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10764-i-dreamed-i-spoke-in-another-s-language-i-dreamed-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I dreamed I spoke in another's language,
I dreamed I lived in another's skin,
I dreamed I was my own beloved,
I dreamed I was a tiger's kin.

I dreamed that Eden lived inside me,
And when I breathed a garden came,
I dreamed I knew all of Creation,
I dreamed I knew the Creator's name.

I dreamed--and this dream was the finest--
That all I dreamed was real and true,
And we would live in joy forever,
You in me, and me in you." -- Clive Barker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32341-a-man-kills-the-thing-he-loves-and-he-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 15:50:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Clive Barker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32341-a-man-kills-the-thing-he-loves-and-he-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man kills the thing he loves, and he must die a little himself." -- Clive Barker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32343-we-re-too-much-ourselves-afraid-of-letting-go-of-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 15:51:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Clive Barker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32343-we-re-too-much-ourselves-afraid-of-letting-go-of-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We’re too much ourselves. Afraid of letting go of what we are, in case we are nothing, and holding on so tight, we lose everything else." -- Clive Barker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32344-perhaps-sunlight-had-always-been-luminous-and-doorways-signs-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 15:51:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Clive Barker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32344-perhaps-sunlight-had-always-been-luminous-and-doorways-signs-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps sunlight had always been luminous, and doorways signs of greater passage than that of one room to another. But she’d not noticed it until now." -- Clive Barker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32354-in-this-sense-love-is-of-a-different-order-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 15:52:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Clive Barker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32354-in-this-sense-love-is-of-a-different-order-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In this sense love is of a different order to any other phenomenon, for it may be both an event and a sign of that invisible mechanism I spoke of before; perhaps the finest sign, the most certain. In it’s throes we need neither luck nor science. We are the wheel, and the man who profits by it. We are the star, and the darkness it pierces. We are the butterfly, brief and beautiful." -- Clive Barker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 15:52:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 15:53:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9081-to-absent-friends-lost-loves-old-gods-and-the-season</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 16:21:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9081-to-absent-friends-lost-loves-old-gods-and-the-season]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To absent friends, lost loves, old gods, and the season of mists; and may each and every one of us always give the devil his due." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13169-one-describes-a-tale-best-by-telling-the-tale-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 16:24:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13169-one-describes-a-tale-best-by-telling-the-tale-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One describes a tale best by telling the tale. You see? The way one describes a story, to oneself or to the world, is by telling the story. It is a balancing act and it is a dream. The more accurate the map, the more it resembles the territory. The most accurate map possible would be the territory, and thus would be perfectly accurate and perfectly useless. 
The tale is the map that is the territory.
You must remember this." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9609-maybe-memories-are-like-karaoke-where-you-realize-up-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 19:45:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9609-maybe-memories-are-like-karaoke-where-you-realize-up-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["maybe memories are like karaoke-where you realize up on the stage, with all those lyrics scrawling across the screen's bottom, and with everybody clapping at you, that you didn't know even half the lyrics to your all-time favourite song. Only afterwards, when someone else is up on stage humiliating themselves amid the clapping and laughing, do you realize that what you liiked most about your favourite song was precisely your ignorance of its full meaning- and you read more into it than maybe existed in the first place. I think it's better to not know the lyrics to your life." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65736-a-few-years-ago-it-dawned-on-me-that-everybody</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 19:46:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65736-a-few-years-ago-it-dawned-on-me-that-everybody]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A few years ago it dawned on me that everybody past a certain age ... pretty much constantly dreams of being able to escape from their lives. They don't want to be who they are any more. They want out. This list includes Thurston Howell the Third, Ann-Margret, the cat members of Rent, Václav Havel, space shuttle astronauts and Snuffleupagus. It's universal." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406-all-god-does-is-watch-us-and-kill-us-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:10:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406-all-god-does-is-watch-us-and-kill-us-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All God does is watch us and kill us when we get boring. We must never, ever be boring." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19071-the-one-you-love-and-the-one-who-loves-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:10:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19071-the-one-you-love-and-the-one-who-loves-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The one you love and the one who loves you are never, ever the same person." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22892-it-s-only-after-we-ve-lost-everything-that-we-re-free-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:10:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22892-it-s-only-after-we-ve-lost-everything-that-we-re-free-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's only after we've lost everything that we're free to do anything." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16831-we-all-die-the-goal-isn-t-to-live-forever-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:10:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16831-we-all-die-the-goal-isn-t-to-live-forever-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all die. The goal isn't to live forever, the goal is to create something that will." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17521-it-s-so-hard-to-forget-pain-but-it-s-even-harder</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:10:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17521-it-s-so-hard-to-forget-pain-but-it-s-even-harder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's so hard to forget pain, but it's even harder to remember sweetness.  We have no scar to show for happiness. We learn so little from peace." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43717-nothing-of-me-is-original-i-am-the-combined-effort</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:10:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43717-nothing-of-me-is-original-i-am-the-combined-effort]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing of me is original. I am the combined effort of everyone I've ever known." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5451-at-the-time-my-life-just-seemed-too-complete-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:11:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5451-at-the-time-my-life-just-seemed-too-complete-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the time, my life just seemed too complete, and maybe we have to break everything to make something better out of ourselves." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43751-this-is-your-life-and-its-ending-one-moment-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:11:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43751-this-is-your-life-and-its-ending-one-moment-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is your life and its ending one moment at a time." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16041-the-only-difference-between-a-suicide-and-a-martyrdom-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:11:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16041-the-only-difference-between-a-suicide-and-a-martyrdom-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only difference between a suicide and a martyrdom really is the amount of press coverage." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43400-no-matter-how-careful-you-are-there-s-going-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:11:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43400-no-matter-how-careful-you-are-there-s-going-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No matter how careful you are, there's going to be the sense you missed something, the collapsed feeling under your skin that you didn't experience it all. There's that fallen heart feeling that you rushed right through the moments where you should've been paying attention.
Well, get used to that feeling. That's how your whole life will feel some day.
This is all practice." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109756-and-when-they-start-talking-and-they-always-do-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:16:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Paul Neilan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109756-and-when-they-start-talking-and-they-always-do-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And when they start talking, and they always do, you find that each of them has a story they want to tell. Everyone, no matter how old or young, has some lesson they want to teach. And I sit there and listen and learn all about life from people who have no idea how to  live it." -- Paul Neilan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75668-nobody-knows-how-to-just-shut-the-fuck-up-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:16:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Paul Neilan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75668-nobody-knows-how-to-just-shut-the-fuck-up-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody knows how to just shut the fuck up and look out the window anymore." -- Paul Neilan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24838-the-world-is-your-oyster-too-bad-you-re-allergic-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:16:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Paul Neilan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24838-the-world-is-your-oyster-too-bad-you-re-allergic-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is your oyster...
        ...too bad you're allergic to shellfish." -- Paul Neilan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53495-often-a-school-is-your-best-bet-perhaps-not-for-education</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:17:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Max Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53495-often-a-school-is-your-best-bet-perhaps-not-for-education]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Often, a school is your best bet-perhaps not for education but certainly for protection from an undead attack." -- Max Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42133-tv-and-the-internet-are-good-because-they-keep-stupid</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:18:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42133-tv-and-the-internet-are-good-because-they-keep-stupid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["TV and the Internet are good because they keep stupid people from spending too much time out in public." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13332-here-s-my-theory-about-meetings-and-life-the-three-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:19:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13332-here-s-my-theory-about-meetings-and-life-the-three-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's my theory about meetings and life: the three things you can't fake are erections, competence and creativity." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24112-all-families-are-psychotic-everybody-has-basically-the-same-family</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:19:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24112-all-families-are-psychotic-everybody-has-basically-the-same-family]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All families are psychotic. Everybody has basically the same family - it's just reconfigured slightly different from one to the next." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100637-and-then-i-felt-sad-because-i-realized-that-once</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 21:19:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alysson add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100637-and-then-i-felt-sad-because-i-realized-that-once]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And then I felt sad because I realized that once people are broken in certain ways, they can't ever be fixed, and this is something nobody ever tells you when you are young and it never fails to surprise you as you grow older as you see the people in your life break one by one. You wonder when your turn is going to be, or if it's already happened." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
