<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/359057-meaghan-o-malley]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/359057-meaghan-o-malley" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 07:33:46 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157843-anger-it-s-a-paralyzing-emotion-you-can-t-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 07:33:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157843-anger-it-s-a-paralyzing-emotion-you-can-t-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anger ... it's a paralyzing emotion ... you can't get anything done. People sort of think it's an interesting, passionate, and igniting feeling — I don't think it's any of that — it's helpless ... it's absence of control — and I need all of my skills, all of the control, all of my powers ... and anger doesn't provide any of that — I have no use for it whatsoever.&quot;

[Interview with CBS radio host Don Swaim, September 15, 1987.]" -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120721-feelings-like-disappointment-embarrassment-irritation-resentment-anger-jealousy-and-fear</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 07:32:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120721-feelings-like-disappointment-embarrassment-irritation-resentment-anger-jealousy-and-fear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…feelings like disappointment, embarrassment, irritation, resentment, anger, jealousy, and fear, instead of being bad news, are actually very clear moments that teach us where it is that we’re holding back. They teach us to perk up and lean in when we feel we’d rather collapse and back away. They’re like messengers that show us, with terrifying clarity, exactly where we’re stuck. This very moment is the perfect teacher, and, lucky for us, it’s with us wherever we are." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248996-a-void-in-my-chest-was-beginning-to-fill-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 07:34:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Rachel Sontag]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248996-a-void-in-my-chest-was-beginning-to-fill-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A void in my chest was beginning to fill with anger. Quiet, defeated anger that guaranteed me the right to my hurt, that believed no one could possibly understand that hurt." -- Rachel Sontag]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295254-usually-adult-males-who-are-unable-to-make-emotional-connections</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 14:04:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295254-usually-adult-males-who-are-unable-to-make-emotional-connections]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Usually adult males who are unable to make emotional connections with the women they choose to be intimate with are frozen in time, unable to allow themselves to love for fear that the loved one will abandon them.  If the first woman they passionately loved, the mother, was not true to her bond of love, then how can they trust that their partner will be true to love. Often in their adult relationships these men act out again and again to test their partner's love. While the rejected adolescent boy imagines that he can no longer receive his mother's love because he is not worthy, as a grown man he may act out in ways that are unworthy and yet demand of the woman in his life that she offer him unconditional love. This testing does not heal the wound of the past, it merely reenacts it, for ultimately the woman will become weary of being tested and end the relationship, thus reenacting the abandonment.  This drama confirms for many men that they cannot put their trust in love. They decide that it is better to put their faith in being powerful, in being dominant." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205101-relationships-are-treated-like-dixie-cups-they-are-the-same</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 14:07:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205101-relationships-are-treated-like-dixie-cups-they-are-the-same]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Relationships are treated like Dixie cups. They are the same. They are disposable. If it does not work, drop it, throw it away, get another.
Committed bonds (including marriage) cannot last when this is the prevailing logic. Most of us are unclear about what to do to protect and strengthen caring bonds when our self-centered needs are not being met." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299903-to-return-to-love-to-get-the-love-we-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 14:08:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299903-to-return-to-love-to-get-the-love-we-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To return to love, to get the love we always wanted but never had, to have the love we want but are not prepared to give, we seek romantic relationships.  We believe these relationships, more than any other, will rescue and redeem us.  True love does have the power to redeem but only if we are ready for redemption.  Love saves us only if we want to be saved." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/731640-one-of-the-best-guides-to-how-to-be-self-loving</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 14:10:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Bell Hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/731640-one-of-the-best-guides-to-how-to-be-self-loving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the best guides to how to be self-loving is to give ourselves the love we are often dreaming about receiving from others. There was a time when I felt lousy about my over-forty body, saw myself as too fat, too this, or too that. Yet I fantasized about finding a lover who would give me the gift of being loved as I am. It is silly, isn't it, that I would dream of someone else offering to me the acceptance and affirmation I was withholding from myself. This was a moment when the maxim &quot;You can never love anybody if you are unable to love yourself&quot; made clear sense.  And I add, &quot;Do not expect to receive the love from someone else you do not give yourself." -- Bell Hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150188-genuine-love-is-rarely-an-emotional-space-where-needs-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 14:15:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150188-genuine-love-is-rarely-an-emotional-space-where-needs-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Genuine love is rarely an emotional space where needs are instantly gratified. To know love we have to invest time and commitment...'dreaming that love will save us, solve all our problems or provide a steady state of bliss or security only keeps us stuck in wishful fantasy, undermining the real power of the love -- which is to transform us.' Many people want love to function like a drug, giving them an immediate and sustained high. They want to do nothing, just passively receive the good feeling." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232775-one-of-the-most-subversive-institutions-in-the-united-states</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 14:22:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232775-one-of-the-most-subversive-institutions-in-the-united-states]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the most subversive institutions in the United States  is the public library.." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/516826-it-still-took-years-for-me-to-let-go-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 14:23:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/516826-it-still-took-years-for-me-to-let-go-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It still took years for me to let go of learned pattern's of behavior that negated my capacity to give and receive love.  One pattern that made the practice of love especially difficult was my constantly choosing to be with men who were emotionally wounded, who were not that interested in loving, even though they desired to be loved.  I wanted to know love but was afraid to be intimate.  By choosing men who were not interested in being loving, I was able to practice giving love but always within an unfufilling context.  Naturally, my need to receive love was not met. I got what I was accustomed to getting. Care and affection, usually mingled with a degree of unkindness, neglect, and on some occasions, out right cruelty." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139391-he-who-had-done-more-than-any-human-being-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 14:28:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139391-he-who-had-done-more-than-any-human-being-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He, who had done more than any human being to draw her out of the caves of her secret, folded life, now threw her down into deeper recesses of fear and doubt.  The fall was greater than she had ever known, because she had ventured so far into emotion and had abandoned herself to it." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41290-eternity-is-said-not-to-be-an-extension-of-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 14:31:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41290-eternity-is-said-not-to-be-an-extension-of-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eternity is said not to be an extension of time but an absence of time, and sometimes it seemed to me that her abandonment touched that strange mathematical point of endlessness, a point with no width, occupying no space." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7915-each-friend-represents-a-world-in-us-a-world-possibly</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 13:45:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7915-each-friend-represents-a-world-in-us-a-world-possibly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each friend represents a world in us, a world possibly not born until they arrive, and it is only by this meeting that a new world is born." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/345798-livid-adj-fuck-you-for-cheating-on-me-fuck-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 14:23:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by David Levithan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/345798-livid-adj-fuck-you-for-cheating-on-me-fuck-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["livid, &lt;i&gt;adj.&lt;/i&gt;

Fuck You for cheating on me.  Fuck you for reducing it to the word cheating.  As if this were a card game, and you sneaked a look at my hand.  Who came up with the term &lt;i&gt;cheating,&lt;/i&gt; anyway?  A cheater, I imagine.  Someone who thought &lt;i&gt;liar&lt;/i&gt; was too harsh.  Someone who thought &lt;i&gt;devastator&lt;/i&gt; was too emotional.  The same person who thought, oops, he’d gotten &lt;i&gt;caught with his hand in the cookie jar.&lt;/i&gt;  Fuck you.  This isn’t about slipping yourself an extra twenty dollars of Monopoly money.  These are our lives.  You went and broke our lives.  You are so much worse than a cheater.  You killed something.  And you killed it when its back was turned." -- David Levithan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209141-cheating-is-easy-there-s-no-swank-to-infidelity-to-borrow</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 14:23:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209141-cheating-is-easy-there-s-no-swank-to-infidelity-to-borrow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cheating is easy. There's no swank to infidelity. To borrow against the trust someone has placed in you costs nothing at first. You get away with it, you take a little more and a little more until there is no more to draw on. Oddly, your hands should be full with all that taking but when you open them there's nothing there." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260522-soon-he-was-online-every-night-until-one-or-two</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 14:29:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Suzanne Finnamore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260522-soon-he-was-online-every-night-until-one-or-two]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Soon he was online every night until one or two a.m. Often he would wake up at three of four a.m. and go back online. He would shut down the computer screen when I walked in. In the past, he used to take the laptop to bed with him and we would both be on our laptops, hips touching. He stopped doing that, slipping off to his office instead and closing the door even when A was asleep. He started closing doors behind him. I was steeped in denial, but my body knew." -- Suzanne Finnamore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234703-we-have-to-recognise-that-there-cannot-be-relationships-unless</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 08:15:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Cornel West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234703-we-have-to-recognise-that-there-cannot-be-relationships-unless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have to recognise that there cannot be relationships unless there is commitment, unless there is loyalty, unless there is love, patience, persistence." -- Cornel West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20591-loyalty-is-weird-it-kicks-in-when-you-dont-expect</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 08:20:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Russell Banks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20591-loyalty-is-weird-it-kicks-in-when-you-dont-expect]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Loyalty is weird, it kicks in when you dont expect it and the people who deserve loyalty least seem to get it the most." -- Russell Banks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293867-the-very-good-people-did-not-convince-me-i-felt</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 08:25:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293867-the-very-good-people-did-not-convince-me-i-felt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The very good people did not convince me; I felt they'd never been tempted. But you knew; you understood; you felt the world outside tugging at one with all its golden hands - and you hated the things it asked of one; you hated happiness bought by disloyalty and cruelty and indifference. That was what I'd never known before - and it's better than anything I've known." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/747864-a-smiling-bantering-humouring-watchful-and-incessant-lie-a-lie</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 12:34:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/747864-a-smiling-bantering-humouring-watchful-and-incessant-lie-a-lie]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A smiling, bantering, humouring, watchful and incessant lie. A lie by day, a lie by night, a lie in every touch and every look; a lie in every caress and every quarrel; a lie in every word and in every silence." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189555-there-are-only-four-great-arts-music-painting-sculpture-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 12:52:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189555-there-are-only-four-great-arts-music-painting-sculpture-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are only four great arts: music, painting, sculpture, and ornamental pastry - architecture being the least banal derivative of the latter." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4953-i-don-t-deserve-any-credit-for-turning-the-other-cheek</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 12:55:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4953-i-don-t-deserve-any-credit-for-turning-the-other-cheek]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't deserve any credit for turning the other cheek as my tongue is always in it." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51154-where-love-rules-there-is-no-will-to-power-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 12:55:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51154-where-love-rules-there-is-no-will-to-power-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where love rules, there is no will to power, and where power predominates, love is lacking. The one is the shadow of the other." -- Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1939-i-can-with-one-eye-squinted-take-it-all-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 12:55:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1939-i-can-with-one-eye-squinted-take-it-all-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can, with one eye squinted, take it all as a blessing." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18410-i-think-we-are-well-advised-to-keep-on-nodding</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 09:22:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18410-i-think-we-are-well-advised-to-keep-on-nodding]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think we are well advised to keep on nodding terms with the  people we used to be, whether we find them attractive company or not.  Otherwise they turn up unannounced and surprise us, come hammering on the mind's door at 4 a.m. of a bad night and demand to know who deserted them, who betrayed them, who is going to make amends." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55615-i-am-vertical-but-i-would-rather-be-horizontal-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 09:25:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55615-i-am-vertical-but-i-would-rather-be-horizontal-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I Am Vertical

But I would rather be horizontal.
I am not a tree with my root in the soil
Sucking up minerals and motherly love
So that each March I may gleam into leaf,
Nor am I the beauty of a garden bed
Attracting my share of Ahs and spectacularly painted,
Unknowing I must soon unpetal.
Compared with me, a tree is immortal
And a flower-head not tall, but more startling,
And I want the one's longevity and the other's daring.

Tonight, in the infinitesimal light of the stars,
The trees and flowers have been strewing their cool odors.
I walk among them, but none of them are noticing.
Sometimes I think that when I am sleeping
I must most perfectly resemble them--
Thoughts gone dim.
It is more natural to me, lying down.
Then the sky and I are in open conversation,
And I shall be useful when I lie down finally:
The the trees may touch me for once, and the flowers have time for me.

&quot;I Am Vertical&quot;, 28 March 1961" -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18132-occupied-in-observing-mr-bingley-s-attentions-to-her-sister-elizabeth</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 09:25:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18132-occupied-in-observing-mr-bingley-s-attentions-to-her-sister-elizabeth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Occupied in observing Mr. Bingley’s attentions to her sister, Elizabeth was far from suspecting that she was herself becoming an object of some interest in the eyes of his friend. Mr. Darcy had at first scarcely allowed her to be pretty: he had looked at her without admiration at the ball; and when they next met, he looked at her only to criticise. But no sooner had he made it clear to himself and his friends that she had hardly a good feature in her face, than he began to find it was rendered uncommonly intelligent by the beautiful expression of her dark eyes. To this discovery succeeded some others equally mortifying. Though he had detected with a critical eye more than one failure of perfect symmetry in her form, he was forced to acknowledge her figure to be light and pleasing; and in spite of his asserting that her manners were not those of the fashionable world, he was caught by their easy playfulness. Of this she was perfectly unaware: to her he was only the man who made himself agreeable nowhere, and who had not thought her handsome enough to dance with." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22263-there-is-only-one-way-to-read-which-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 09:26:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22263-there-is-only-one-way-to-read-which-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is only one way to read, which is to browse in libraries and bookshops, picking up books that attract you, reading only those, dropping them when they bore you, skipping the parts that drag-and never, never reading anything because you feel you ought, or because it is part of a trend or a movement.  Remember that the book which bores you when you are twenty or thirty will open doors for you when you are forty or fifty-and vise versa.  Don’t read a book out of its right time for you.  " -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300691-here-i-am-a-bundle-of-past-recollections-and-future</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 09:27:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300691-here-i-am-a-bundle-of-past-recollections-and-future]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here I am, a bundle of past recollections and future dreams, knotted up in a reasonably attractive bundle of flesh. I remember what this flesh has gone through; I dream of what it may go through." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312281-mysteries-of-attraction-could-not-always-be-explained-through-logic</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 09:29:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Meaghan add a quote by Lisa Kleypas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312281-mysteries-of-attraction-could-not-always-be-explained-through-logic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mysteries of attraction could not always be explained through logic. Sometimes the fractures in two separate souls became the very hinges that held them together." -- Lisa Kleypas]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
