<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/359831-clare]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/359831-clare" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 15:15:23 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137653-maybe-mistakes-are-what-make-our-fate-without-them-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 15:15:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clare add a quote by Candace Bushnell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137653-maybe-mistakes-are-what-make-our-fate-without-them-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe mistakes are what make our fate... without them what would shape our lives? Maybe if we had never veered off course we wouldn't fall in love, have babies, or be who we are. After all, things change, so do cities, people come into your life and they go. But it's comforting to know that the ones you love are always in your heart... and if you're very lucky, a plane ride away" -- Candace Bushnell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/896465-peeta-and-i-grow-back-together-there-are-still-moments</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 20:28:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clare add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/896465-peeta-and-i-grow-back-together-there-are-still-moments]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Peeta and I grow back together. There are still moments when he clutches the back of a chair and hangs on until the flashbacks are over. I wake screaming from nightmares of mutts and lost children. But his arms are there to comfort me. And eventually his lips. On the night I feel that thing again, the hunger that overtook me on the beach, I know this would have happened anyway. That what I need to survive is not Gale's fire, kindled with rage and hatred. I have plenty of fire myself. What I need is the dandelion in the spring. The bright yellow that means rebirth instead of destruction. The promise that life can go on, no matter how bad our losses. That it can be good again. And only Peeta can give me that. So after, when he whispers, &quot;You love me. Real or not real?&quot; I tell him, &quot;Real." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116153-i-heard-what-you-said-i-m-not-the-silly-romantic</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 18:45:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clare add a quote by Shana Abe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116153-i-heard-what-you-said-i-m-not-the-silly-romantic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I heard what you said. I’m not the silly romantic you think. I don’t want the heavens or the shooting stars. I don’t want gemstones or gold. I have those things already. I want…a steady hand. A kind soul. I want to fall asleep, and wake, knowing my heart is safe. I want to love, and be loved." -- Shana Abe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76393-i-have-a-history-of-making-decisions-very-quickly-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 18:46:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clare add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76393-i-have-a-history-of-making-decisions-very-quickly-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have a history of making decisions very quickly about men.  I have always fallen in love fast and without measuring risks.  I have a tendency not only to see the best in everyone, but to assume that everyone is emotionally capable of reaching his highest potential.  I have fallen in love more times than I care to count with the highest potential of a man, rather than with the man himself, and I have hung on to the relationship for a long time (sometimes far too long) waiting for the man to ascend to his own greatness.  Many times in romance I have been a victim of my own optimism." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271046-if-he-s-not-calling-you-it-s-because-you-are-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 18:46:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clare add a quote by Greg Behrendt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271046-if-he-s-not-calling-you-it-s-because-you-are-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If he’s not calling you, it’s because you are not on his mind. If he creates expectations for you, and then doesn’t follow through on little things, he will do same for big things. Be aware of this and realize that he’s okay with disappointing you. Don’t be with someone who doesn’t do what they say they’re going to do.  If he’s choosing not to make a simple effort that would put you at ease and bring harmony to a recurring fight, then he doesn’t respect your feelings and needs. “Busy” is another word for “asshole.” “Asshole” is another word for the guy you’re dating. You deserve a fcking phone call." -- Greg Behrendt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84061-it-isn-t-possible-to-love-and-part-you-will-wish</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 18:48:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clare add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84061-it-isn-t-possible-to-love-and-part-you-will-wish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It isn't possible to love and part.  You will wish that it was.  You can transmute love, ignore it, muddle it, but you can never pull it out of you. I know by experience that the poets are right:  love is eternal." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6766-i-can-listen-no-longer-in-silence-i-must-speak</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 18:48:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clare add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6766-i-can-listen-no-longer-in-silence-i-must-speak]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can listen no longer in silence.  I must speak to you by such means as are within my reach.  You pierce my soul.  I am half agony, half hope.  Tell me not that I am too late, that such precious feelings are gone for ever.  I offer myself to you again with a heart even more your own than when you almost broke it, eight years and a half ago.  Dare not say that man forgets sooner than  woman, that his love has an earlier death.  I have loved none but you. Unjust I may have been, weak and resentful I have been, but never inconstant.  You alone have brought me to Bath. For you alone, I think and plan.  Have you not seen this? Can you fail to have understood my wishes?  I had not waited even these ten days, could I have read your feelings, as I think you must have penetrated mine.  I can hardly write.  I am every instant hearing something which overpowers me.  You sink your voice, but I can distinguish the tones of that voice when they would be lost on others. Too good, too excellent creature!  You do us justice, indeed. You do believe that there is true attachment and constancy among men. Believe it to be most fervent, most undeviating, in F. W.

I must go, uncertain of my fate; but I shall return hither, or follow your party, as soon as possible.  A word, a look, will be enough to decide whether I enter your father's house this evening or never." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36501-perhaps-after-all-romance-did-not-come-into-one-s-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 18:50:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clare add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36501-perhaps-after-all-romance-did-not-come-into-one-s-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps, after all, romance did not come into one’s life with pomp and blare, like a gay knight riding down; perhaps it crept to one’s side like an old friend through quiet ways; perhaps it revealed itself in seeming prose, until some sudden shaft of illumination flung athwart its pages betrayed the rhythm and the music, perhaps . . . perhaps . . . love unfolded naturally out of a beautiful friendship, as a golden-hearted rose slipping from its green sheath." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167151-i-was-thinking-as-i-watched-her-how-little-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 18:48:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clare add a quote by Willa Cather]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167151-i-was-thinking-as-i-watched-her-how-little-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was thinking, as I watched her, how little it mattered-- about her teeth, for instance. I know so many women who have kept all the things that she had lost, but whose inner glow has faded. Whatever else was gone, Antonia had not lost the fire of life." -- Willa Cather]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265919-but-she-still-had-that-something-which-fires-the-imagination</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 18:48:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clare add a quote by Willa Cather]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265919-but-she-still-had-that-something-which-fires-the-imagination]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But she still had that something which fires the imagination, could still stop one's breath for a moment by a look or gesture that somehow revealed the meaning in common things. She had only to stand in the orchard, to put her hand on a little crab tree and look up at the apples, to make you feel the goodness of planting and tending and harvesting at last. All the strong things of her heart came out in her body, that had been so tireless in serving generous emotions. It was no wonder that her sons stood tall and straight. She was a rich mine of life, like the founders of early races." -- Willa Cather]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
