<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/36029-neha]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/36029-neha" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 06:25:53 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28486-now-i-know-that-our-world-is-no-more-permanent</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 06:25:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neha add a quote by Arthur Golden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28486-now-i-know-that-our-world-is-no-more-permanent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now I know that our world is no more permanent than a wave rising on the ocean. Whatever our struggles and triumphs, however we may suffer them, all too soon they bleed into a wash, just like watery ink on paper." -- Arthur Golden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5722-anyway-i-keep-picturing-all-these-little-kids-playing-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 06:29:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neha add a quote by J. D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5722-anyway-i-keep-picturing-all-these-little-kids-playing-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyway, I keep picturing all these little kids playing some game in this big field of rye and all.  Thousands of little kids, and nobody's around - nobody big, I mean - except me.  And I'm standing on the edge of some crazy cliff.  What I have to do, I have to catch everybody if they start to go over the cliff - I mean if they're running and they don't look where they're going I have to come out from somewhere and catch them.  That's all I do all day.  I'd just be the catcher in the rye and all.  I know it's crazy, but that's the only thing I'd really like to be." -- J. D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 06:36:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neha add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
