<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/360913-sarah-b]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/360913-sarah-b" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 19:15:32 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29305-dr-armonson-stitched-up-her-wrist-wounds-within-five-minutes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 19:15:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29305-dr-armonson-stitched-up-her-wrist-wounds-within-five-minutes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dr. Armonson stitched up her wrist wounds. Within five minutes of the transfusion he declared her out of danger. Chucking her under the chin, he said, &quot;What are you doing here, honey? You're not even old enough to know how bad life gets.&quot;

And it was then Cecilia gave orally what was to be her only form of suicide note, and a useless one at that, because she was going to live: &quot;Obviously, Doctor,&quot; she said, &quot;you've never been a thirteen-year-old girl." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223672-i-m-a-supporter-of-gay-rights-and-not-a-closet</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 22:05:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Paul Newman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223672-i-m-a-supporter-of-gay-rights-and-not-a-closet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm a supporter of gay rights.  And not a closet supporter either.  From the time I was a kid, I have never been able to understand attacks upon the gay community.  There are so many qualities that make up a human being... by the time I get through with all the things that I really admire about people, what they do with their private parts is probably so low on the list that it is irrelevant." -- Paul Newman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117773-the-moon-is-whole-all-the-time-but-we-can-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 08:53:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Alice Sebold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117773-the-moon-is-whole-all-the-time-but-we-can-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The moon is whole all the time, but we can’t always see it.  What we see is an almost moon or not-quite moon.  The rest is hiding just out of view, but there’s only one moon, so we follow it in the sky.  We plan our lives based on its rhythms and tides." -- Alice Sebold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257801-and-then-came-months-of-memories-connected-to-nothing-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 12:44:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Barbara Gowdy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257801-and-then-came-months-of-memories-connected-to-nothing-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And then came months of memories connected to nothing and telling me nothing, and in this ambiguous atmosphere I stopped thinking of him as doomed. The memories themselves were generally pleasant. For at least a week I kept reliving the time he removed a splinter from my foot using surgical tweezers. Strangely, during this same week, a black Labrador retriever was accompanying me around town, appearing out of nowhere and trotting alongside me to the subway or or the grocery store. As with the splinter memory, I had a sense of information being conveyed but through a medium too opaque to be grasped." -- Barbara Gowdy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391915-no-he-said-and-he-snapped-his-fingers-you-ll-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2011 10:02:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Melissa Bank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391915-no-he-said-and-he-snapped-his-fingers-you-ll-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No,&quot; he said, and he snapped his fingers. &quot;You'll come work for me at K----. And be a real associate editor.&quot;
I said, &quot;I could bring you up on charges for that.&quot;
&quot;What?&quot;
&quot;Work harassment in the sexual place." -- Melissa Bank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/593362-as-time-went-by-it-mattered-less-and-less-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 11:21:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Ann-Marie MacDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/593362-as-time-went-by-it-mattered-less-and-less-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As time went by, it mattered less and less that in 1969 a rocket went from Florida to the moon and men walked there. Good men. People's dads. Those were only events, scattered in time. Draw them close, rub them between thumb and finger till they look like larvae, soften like silk, distend to knot, to weave. It takes a village to kill a child." -- Ann-Marie MacDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/829041-technology-proposes-itself-as-the-architect-of-our-intimacies</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 11:27:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Sherry Turkle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/829041-technology-proposes-itself-as-the-architect-of-our-intimacies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Technology proposes itself as the architect of our intimacies." -- Sherry Turkle]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
