<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/361227-emmy-woessner]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/361227-emmy-woessner" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 09:02:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6363-when-despair-for-the-world-grows-in-me-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 09:02:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmy add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6363-when-despair-for-the-world-grows-in-me-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When despair for the world grows in me and I wake in the night at the least sound in fear of what my life and my children's lives may be, I go and lie down where the wood drake rests in his beauty on the water, and the great heron feeds. I come into the peace of wild things who do not tax their lives with forethought of grief. I come into the presence of still water. And I feel above me the day-blind stars waiting with their light. For a time I rest in the grace of the world, and am free." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134218-a-corporation-essentially-is-a-pile-of-money-to-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 09:04:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmy add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134218-a-corporation-essentially-is-a-pile-of-money-to-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A corporation, essentially, is a pile of money to which a number of persons have sold their moral allegiance." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15454-the-smart-way-to-keep-people-passive-and-obedient-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 08:24:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmy add a quote by Noam Chomsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15454-the-smart-way-to-keep-people-passive-and-obedient-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The smart way to keep people passive and obedient is to strictly limit the spectrum of acceptable opinion, but allow very lively debate within that spectrum...." -- Noam Chomsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494647-the-world-is-like-a-ride-in-an-amusement-park</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 19:22:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emmy add a quote by Bill Hicks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494647-the-world-is-like-a-ride-in-an-amusement-park]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is like a ride in an amusement park, and when you choose to go on it you think it's real because that's how powerful our minds are. The ride goes up and down, around and around, it has thrills and chills, and it's very brightly colored, and it's very loud, and it's fun for a while. Many people have been on the ride a long time, and they begin to wonder, &quot;Hey, is this real, or is this just a ride?&quot; And other people have remembered, and they come back to us and say, &quot;Hey, don't worry; don't be afraid, ever, because this is just a ride.&quot; And we … kill those people. &quot;Shut him up! I've got a lot invested in this ride, shut him up! Look at my furrows of worry, look at my big bank account, and my family. This has to be real.&quot; It's just a ride. But we always kill the good guys who try and tell us that, you ever notice that? And let the demons run amok … But it doesn't matter, because it's just a ride. And we can change it any time we want. It's only a choice. No effort, no work, no job, no savings of money. Just a simple choice, right now, between fear and love. The eyes of fear want you to put bigger locks on your doors, buy guns, close yourself off. The eyes of love instead see all of us as one. Here's what we can do to change the world, right now, to a better ride. Take all that money we spend on weapons and defenses each year and instead spend it feeding and clothing and educating the poor of the world, which it would pay for many times over, not one human being excluded, and we could explore space, together, both inner and outer, forever, in peace." -- Bill Hicks]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
