<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/362282-jenn]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/362282-jenn" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 18:44:24 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139732-letting-go-is-the-lesson-letting-go-is-always-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 18:44:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Susan Gordon Lydon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139732-letting-go-is-the-lesson-letting-go-is-always-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Letting go is the lesson. Letting go is always the lesson. Have you ever noticed how much of our agony is all tied up with craving and loss?" -- Susan Gordon Lydon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223694-so-that-s-how-we-live-our-lives-no-matter-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 18:44:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223694-so-that-s-how-we-live-our-lives-no-matter-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So that’s how we live our lives.  No matter how deep and fatal the
loss, no matter how important the thing that's stolen from us - that's
snatched right out of our hands - even if we are left completely
changed, with only the outer layer of skin from before, we continue to
play out our lives this way, in silence.  We draw ever nearer to the
end of our allotted span of time, bidding it farewell as it trails off
behind.  Repeating, often adroitly, the endless deeds of the everyday.
 Leaving behind a feeling of insurmountable emptiness...
Maybe, in some distant place, everything is already, quietly, lost.
Or at least there exists a silent place where everything can
disappear, melting together in a single, overlapping figure.  And as
we live our lives we discover - drawing toward us the thin threads
attached to each - what has been lost.  I closed my eyes and tried to
bring to mind as many beautiful lost things as I could.  Drawing them
closer, holding on to them.  Knowing all the while that their lives
are fleeting." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/766-where-you-used-to-be-there-is-a-hole-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 18:45:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Edna St. Vincent Millay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/766-where-you-used-to-be-there-is-a-hole-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where you used to be, there is a hole in the world, which I find myself constantly walking around in the daytime, and falling in at night.  I miss you like hell." -- Edna St. Vincent Millay]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
