<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/362587-harajyuku]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/362587-harajyuku" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 23:10:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20171-there-are-three-rules-for-writing-a-novel-unfortunately-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 23:10:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harajyuku add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20171-there-are-three-rules-for-writing-a-novel-unfortunately-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are three rules for writing a novel. Unfortunately, no one knows what they are." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133466-and-yet-i-have-been-fashioned-so-painstakingly-thought-cincinnatus</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 17:30:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harajyuku add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133466-and-yet-i-have-been-fashioned-so-painstakingly-thought-cincinnatus]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And yet I have been fashioned so painstakingly,' thought Cincinnatus as he wept in the darkness. 'The curvature of my spine has been calculated so well, so mysteriously. I feel, tightly rolled up in my calves, so many miles that I could yet run in my lifetime. My head is so comfortable.' A clock struck a half, pertaining to some unknown hour. (Invitation to a beheading)" -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473761-at-the-entrance-to-the-original-tower-there-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 21:41:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harajyuku add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473761-at-the-entrance-to-the-original-tower-there-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the entrance to the original tower, there is a stone into which Jung carved some words with his own hand: 'Cold or not, God is present." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228783-you-seem-to-be-under-the-impression-that-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 21:32:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harajyuku add a quote by Natsume Soseki]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228783-you-seem-to-be-under-the-impression-that-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You seem to be under the impression that there is a special breed of bad humans. There is no such thing as a stereotype bad man in this world. Under normal conditions, everybody is more or less good, or, at least, ordinary. But tempt them, and they may suddenly change. That is what is so frightening about men." -- Natsume Soseki]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104595-the-tragedy-of-preparedness-has-scarcely-been-handled-save-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 21:37:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harajyuku add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104595-the-tragedy-of-preparedness-has-scarcely-been-handled-save-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The tragedy of preparedness has scarcely been handled, save by the Greeks. Life is indeed dangerous, but not in the way morality would have us believe. It is indeed unmanageable, but the essence of it is not a battle. It is unmanageable because it is a romance, and its essence is romantic beauty." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/597505-for-that-little-incident-had-impressed-the-three-women-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 21:40:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harajyuku add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/597505-for-that-little-incident-had-impressed-the-three-women-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For that little incident had impressed the three women more than might be supposed. It remained as a goblin footfall, as a hint that all is not for the best in the best of all possible worlds, and that beneath these superstructures of wealth and art there wanders an ill-fed boy, who has recovered his umbrella indeed, but who has left no address behind him, and no name." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110964-i-love-mankind-he-said-but-i-find-to-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 21:41:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harajyuku add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110964-i-love-mankind-he-said-but-i-find-to-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love mankind, he said, &quot;but I find to my amazement that the more I love mankind as a whole, the less I love man in particular." -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98267-i-believe-like-a-child-that-suffering-will-be-healed</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 21:42:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harajyuku add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98267-i-believe-like-a-child-that-suffering-will-be-healed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe like a child that suffering will be healed and made up for, that all the humiliating absurdity of human contradictions will vanish like a pitiful mirage, like the despicable fabrication of the impotent and infinitely small Euclidean mind of man, that in the world's finale, at the moment of eternal harmony, something so precious will come to pass that it will suffice for all hearts, for the comforting of all resentments, for the atonement of all the crimes of humanity, for all the blood that they've shed; that it will make it not only possible to forgive but to justify all that has happened." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/343151-he-did-not-want-to-play-he-wanted-to-meet</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 21:34:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harajyuku add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/343151-he-did-not-want-to-play-he-wanted-to-meet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He did not want to play. He wanted to meet in the real world the unsubstantial image which his soul so constantly beheld. He did not know where to seek it or how, but a premonition which led him on told him that this image would, without any overt act of his, encounter him. They would meet quietly as if they had known each other and had made their tryst, perhaps at one of the gates or in some more secret place. They would be alone, surrounded by darkness and silence: and in that moment of supreme tenderness he would be transfigured.
He would fade into something impalpable under her eyes and then in a moment he would be transfigured. Weakness and timidity and inexperience would fall from him in that magic moment." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470-it-is-a-far-far-better-thing-that-i-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 17:02:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harajyuku add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470-it-is-a-far-far-better-thing-that-i-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a far, far better thing that I do, than I have ever done; it is a far, far better rest that I go to than I have ever known." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302478-you-could-not-give-up-a-human-heart-as-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 23:14:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harajyuku add a quote by T.H. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302478-you-could-not-give-up-a-human-heart-as-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You could not give up a human heart as you could give up drinking. The drink was yours, and you could give it up: but your lover’s soul was not your own: it was not at your disposal; you had a duty towards it." -- T.H. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1271596-sorrow-and-profound-fatigue-are-at-the-heart-of-dewey-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 23:23:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Harajyuku add a quote by Truman Capote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1271596-sorrow-and-profound-fatigue-are-at-the-heart-of-dewey-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sorrow and profound fatigue are at the heart of Dewey's silence. It had been his ambition to learn &quot;exactly what happened in that house that night.&quot; Twice now he'd been told, and the two versions were very much alike, the only serious discrepancy being that Hickock attributed all four deaths to Smith, while Smith contended that Hickock had killed the two women. But the confessions, though they answered 
questions of how and why, failed to satisfy his sense of meaningful design. The crime was a psychological accident, virtually an impersonal act; the victims might as well have been killed by lightning. Except for one thing: they had experienced prolonged terror, they had suffered. And Dewey could not forget their sufferings. Nonetheless, he found it possible to look at the man beside him without anger - with, rather, a measure of sympathy - for Perry Smith's life had been no bed of roses but pitiful, an ugly and lonely progress toward one mirage and then another. Dewey's sympathy, however, was not deep enough to accommodate either forgiveness or mercy. He hoped to see Perry and his partner hanged - hanged back to back." -- Truman Capote]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
