<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/362894-sandra-clark]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/362894-sandra-clark" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 17:19:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5346-despair-is-the-price-one-pays-for-setting-oneself-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 17:19:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5346-despair-is-the-price-one-pays-for-setting-oneself-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Despair is the price one pays for setting oneself an impossible aim. It is, one is told, the unforgivable sin, but it is a sin the corrupt or evil man never practices. He always has hope. He never reaches the freezing-point of knowing absolute failure. Only the man of goodwill carries always in his heart this capacity for damnation." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102372-we-want-to-be-on-the-winning-team-but-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2010 16:32:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Paul Farmer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102372-we-want-to-be-on-the-winning-team-but-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We want to be on the winning team, but at the risk of turning our backs on the losers, no, it is not worth it.  So we fight the long defeat." -- Paul Farmer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7845-i-feel-like-a-wet-seed-wild-in-the-hot</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 21:59:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7845-i-feel-like-a-wet-seed-wild-in-the-hot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I feel like a wet seed wild in the hot blind earth." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83380-the-struggle-of-literature-is-in-fact-a-struggle-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 20:41:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83380-the-struggle-of-literature-is-in-fact-a-struggle-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The struggle of literature is in fact a struggle to escape from the confines of language; it stretches out from the utmost limits of what can be said; what stirs literature is the call and attraction of what is not in the dictionary." -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13620-it-is-no-measure-of-health-to-be-well-adjusted</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2009 22:10:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by J. Krishnamurti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13620-it-is-no-measure-of-health-to-be-well-adjusted]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is no measure of health to be well adjusted to a profoundly sick society." -- J. Krishnamurti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109349-the-first-task-of-the-doctor-is-political-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2009 22:17:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Michel Foucault]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109349-the-first-task-of-the-doctor-is-political-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first task of the doctor is ... political: the struggle against disease must begin with a war against bad government.&quot; Man will be totally and definitively cured only if he is first liberated..." -- Michel Foucault]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54041-let-s-face-it-we-re-undone-by-each-other-and-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2009 22:30:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Judith Butler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54041-let-s-face-it-we-re-undone-by-each-other-and-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let's face it. We're undone by each other. And if we're not, we're missing something. If this seems so clearly the case with grief, it is only because it was already the case with desire. One does not always stay intact. It may be that one wants to, or does, but it may also be that despite one's best efforts, one is undone, in the face of the other, by the touch, by the scent, by the feel, by the prospect of the touch, by the memory of the feel. And so when we speak about my sexuality or my gender, as we do (and as we must), we mean something complicated by it. Neither of these is precisely a possession, but both are to be understood as modes of being dispossessed, ways of being for another, or, indeed, by virtue of another." -- Judith Butler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61062-by-aladdin-s-lamplit-scrotum-man-everything-is-a-story-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2010 16:32:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Christopher Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61062-by-aladdin-s-lamplit-scrotum-man-everything-is-a-story-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By Aladdin's lamplit scrotum, man! Everything is a story. What is there but stories? Stories are the only truth." -- Christopher Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11144-an-intellectual-yes-and-never-deny-it-an-intellectual-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 13:20:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11144-an-intellectual-yes-and-never-deny-it-an-intellectual-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An intellectual? Yes. And never deny it. An intellectual is someone whose mind watches itself. I like this, because I am happy to be both halves, the watcher and the watched. &quot;Can they be brought together?&quot; This is a practical question. We must get down to it. &quot;I despise intelligence&quot; really means: &quot;I cannot bear my doubts." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225066-illness-is-the-night-side-of-life-a-more-onerous</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2010 15:31:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Susan Sontag]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225066-illness-is-the-night-side-of-life-a-more-onerous]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Illness is the night side of life, a more onerous citizenship. Everyone who is born holds dual citizenship, in the kingdom of the well and in the kingdom of the sick. Although we all prefer to use the good passport, sooner or later each of us is obliged, at least for a spell, to identify ourselves as citizens of that other place." -- Susan Sontag]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67565-sarcasm-the-last-refuge-of-modest-and-chaste-souled-people-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 10:45:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Dostoyevsky Fyodor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67565-sarcasm-the-last-refuge-of-modest-and-chaste-souled-people-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sarcasm: the last refuge of modest and chaste-souled people when the PRIVACY of their soul is coarsely and intrusively invaded." -- Dostoyevsky Fyodor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18298-if-you-ask-me-what-i-came-to-do-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 10:49:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Émile Zola]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18298-if-you-ask-me-what-i-came-to-do-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you ask me what I came to do in this world, I, an artist, will answer you: I am here to live out loud." -- Émile Zola]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25225-all-knowledge-that-is-about-human-society-and-not-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 10:52:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Edward Said]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25225-all-knowledge-that-is-about-human-society-and-not-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All knowledge that is about human society, and not about the natural world, is historical knowledge, and therefore rests upon judgment and interpretation. This is not to say that facts or data are nonexistent, but that facts get their importance from what is made of them in interpretation… for interpretations depend very much on who the interpreter is, who he or she is addressing, what his or her purpose is, at what historical moment the interpretation takes place." -- Edward Said]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142386-for-life-is-the-best-thing-we-have-in-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 20:56:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Patti Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142386-for-life-is-the-best-thing-we-have-in-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For life is the best thing we have in this existence. And if we should desire to believe in something, it should be a beacon within. This beacon being the sun, sea, and sky, our children, our work, our companions and, most simply put, the embodiment of love." -- Patti Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/373049-the-fiction-of-ayn-rand-is-as-low-as-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 18:18:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/373049-the-fiction-of-ayn-rand-is-as-low-as-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fiction of Ayn Rand is as low as you can get re fiction. I hope you picked it up off the floor of the subway and threw it in the nearest garbage pail. She makes Mickey Spillane look like Dostoevsky." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/433841-if-freud-turns-to-literature-to-describe-traumatic-experience-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 09:38:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Cathy Caruth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/433841-if-freud-turns-to-literature-to-describe-traumatic-experience-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If Freud turns to literature to describe traumatic experience, it is because literature, like psychoanalysis, is interested in the complex relation between knowing and not knowing, and it is at this specific point at which knowing and not knowing intersect that the psychoanalytic theory of traumatic experience and the language of literature meet." -- Cathy Caruth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 21:56:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always imagined that Paradise will be a kind of library." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155150-the-secret-of-theory-is-that-truth-does-not-exist</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 22:09:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Jean Baudrillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155150-the-secret-of-theory-is-that-truth-does-not-exist]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The secret of theory is that truth does not exist." -- Jean Baudrillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170195-the-aim-of-literature-is-the-creation-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2011 18:25:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Donald Barthelme]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170195-the-aim-of-literature-is-the-creation-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The aim of literature ... is the creation of a strange object covered with fur which breaks your heart." -- Donald Barthelme]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/482727-the-worst-possible-outlook-is-indifference-that-says-i-can-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 18:14:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Stéphane Hessel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/482727-the-worst-possible-outlook-is-indifference-that-says-i-can-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worst possible outlook is indifference that says, “I can’t do anything about it; I’ll just get by.” Behaving like that deprives you of one of the essentials of being human: the capacity and the freedom to feel outraged. That freedom is indispensable, as is the political involvement that goes with it." -- Stéphane Hessel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53180-the-bricoleur-says-levi-strauss-is-someone-who-uses-the-means</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 13:34:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Jacques Derrida]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53180-the-bricoleur-says-levi-strauss-is-someone-who-uses-the-means]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The bricoleur, says Levi-Strauss, is someone who uses ‘the means at hand,’ that is, the instruments he finds at his disposition around him, those which are already there, which had not been especially conceived with an eye to the operation for which they are to be used and to which one tries by trial and error to adapt them, not hesitating to change them whenever it appears necessary, or to try several of them at once, even if their form and their origin are heterogenous – and so forth.  There is therefor a critique of language in the form of bricolage, and it has even been said that bricolage is critical language itself…If one calls bricolage the necessity of borrowing one’s concepts from the text of a heritage which is more or less coherent or ruined, it must be said that every discourse is bricoleur." -- Jacques Derrida]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/864038-i-lie-in-a-bathtub-of-cold-water-still-sweating</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 13:59:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sandra add a quote by Kiese Laymon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/864038-i-lie-in-a-bathtub-of-cold-water-still-sweating]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I lie in a bathtub of cold water, still sweating and singing love songs to myself. I put the gun to my head and cock it.

I think of my Grandma and remember that old feeling of being so in love that nothing matters except seeing and being seen by her. I drop the gun to my chest. I'm so sad and I can't really see a way out of what I'm feeling but I'm leaning on memory for help. Faster. Slower. I think I want to hurt myself more than I'm already hurting. I'm not the smartest boy in the world by a long shot, but even in my funk I know that easy remedies like eating your way out of sad, or fucking your way out of sad, or lying your way out of sad, or slanging your way out of sad, or robbing your way out of sad, or gambling your way out of sad, or shooting your way out of sad, are just slower, more acceptable ways for desperate folks, and especially paroled black boys in our country, to kill ourselves and others close to us in America." -- Kiese Laymon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
