<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/363540-jenifer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/363540-jenifer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 22:40:12 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236997-why-do-we-care-about-singers-wherein-lies-the-power</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 22:40:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Salmon Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236997-why-do-we-care-about-singers-wherein-lies-the-power]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why do we care about singers? Wherein lies the power of songs? Maybe it derives from the sheer strangeness of there being singing in the world.  The note, the scale, the chord; melodies, harmonies, arrangements; symphonies, ragas, chinese operas,jazz, the blues: that such things should exist, that we should have discovered the magical intervals and distances that yield the poor cluster of notes, all within the span of a human hand from which we can build our cathedrals of sound, is alchemical a mystery as mathematics, or wine, or love.  Maybe the birds taught us. Maybe not. Maybe we are just creatures in search of exaltation. We don't have much of it. Our lives are not what we deserve; they are, let us agree, in many painful ways deficient. Song turns them into something else. Song shows us a world that is worthy of our yearning, it shows us our selves as they might be, if we were worthy of the world. " -- Salmon Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2851-i-would-rather-be-ashes-than-dust-i-would-rather</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 22:40:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Jack London]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2851-i-would-rather-be-ashes-than-dust-i-would-rather]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would rather be ashes than dust!
I would rather that my spark should burn out in a brilliant blaze than it should be stifled by dry-rot.
I would rather be a superb meteor, every atom of me in magnificent glow, than a sleepy and permanent planet.
The function of man is to live, not to exist.
I shall not waste my days trying to prolong them.
I shall use my time." -- Jack London]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158453-it-can-be-crazy-hard-to-keep-your-faith-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 22:40:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Andrew Klavan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158453-it-can-be-crazy-hard-to-keep-your-faith-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It can be crazy hard. To keep your faith, to keep going. It can be harder than I ever would have imagined. Sometimes things happen to you, really bad things that aren't fair, things that make you feel so terrible you're not even sure who you are anymore or whether you're right or wrong, good or bad. Sometimes you feel like there's no one to turn to, and you're all alone and so scared you can hardly move and so tired you just want to curl up in a ball and go to sleep forever. I guess that's kind of the way Alex felt that last night I saw him. And that's the way I felt now. But I guess I had one advantage over Alex. I guess in some way I'd been training for this time my whole life. I'd been training every day, even in simple things, little things. I trained to keep my mind sharp when I went to school. I trained in karate to keep my body and spirit strong. Even when I just went to church, or when I prayed by myself, it was a kind of training: I was training to remember that I was not alone. I was never alone." -- Andrew Klavan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31723-the-world-will-give-you-that-once-in-awhile-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 22:46:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31723-the-world-will-give-you-that-once-in-awhile-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world will give you that once in awhile, a brief timeout; the boxing bell rings and you go to your corner, where somebody dabs mercy on your beat-up life." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300648-i-don-t-really-care-i-shouldn-t-have-to-care-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2010 11:51:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Gayle Forman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300648-i-don-t-really-care-i-shouldn-t-have-to-care-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't really care.  I shouldn't have to care.  I shouldn't have to work this hard.  I realize now that dying is easy. Living is hard." -- Gayle Forman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290403-someday-i-would-like-to-go-home-the-exact-location</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2010 17:30:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Henry Rollins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290403-someday-i-would-like-to-go-home-the-exact-location]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Someday, I would like to go home. The exact location of this place, I don't know, but someday I would like to go. There would be a pleasing feeling of familiarity and a sense of welcome in everything I saw. People would greet me warmly. They would remind me of the length of my absence and the thousands of miles I had travelled in those restless years, but mostly, they would tell me that I had been missed, and that things were better now I had returned. Autumn would come to this place of welcome, this place I would know to be home. Autumn would come and the air would grow cool, dry and magic, as it does that time of the year. At night, I would walk the streets but not feel lonely, for these are the streets of my home town. These are the streets that I had thought about while far away, and now I was back, and all was as it should be. The trees and the falling leaves would welcome me. I would look up at the moon, and remember seeing it in countries all over the world as I had restlessly journeyed for decades, never remembering it looking the same as when viewed from my hometown." -- Henry Rollins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66512-i-believe-in-pink-i-believe-that-laughing-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2011 21:17:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66512-i-believe-in-pink-i-believe-that-laughing-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in pink. I believe that laughing is the best calorie burner. I believe in kissing, kissing a lot. I believe in being strong when everything seems to be going wrong. I believe that happy girls are the prettiest girls. I believe that tomorrow is another day and I believe in miracles." -- Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 20:18:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one can make you feel inferior without your consent." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 20:18:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65903-some-things-don-t-matter-much-like-the-color-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 08:52:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65903-some-things-don-t-matter-much-like-the-color-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["some things don't matter much. Like the color of a house. How big is that in the overall scheme of life? But lifting a person's heart--now, that matters. The whole problem with people is...they know what matters, but they don't choose it...The hardest thing on earth is choosing what matters." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/507878-but-there-are-certain-meanings-that-are-lost-forever-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 09:24:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/507878-but-there-are-certain-meanings-that-are-lost-forever-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But there are certain meanings that are lost forever the moment they are explained in words." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/531965-the-problem-of-palestine-was-that-everyone-wanted-things-simple</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 21:28:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Amy Wilentz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/531965-the-problem-of-palestine-was-that-everyone-wanted-things-simple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem of Palestine was that everyone wanted things simple: everyone was an extremist because everyone wanted things simple. It was the problem of humanity. Good and evil, as if there were only those two. The interesting thing was to seek truth and then face it." -- Amy Wilentz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/561649-i-m-sure-that-sounds-odd-but-looking-at-me-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 20:05:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Ka Hancock]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/561649-i-m-sure-that-sounds-odd-but-looking-at-me-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm sure that sounds odd, but looking at me and seeing me are two very different things." -- Ka Hancock]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270015-why-can-t-people-just-sit-and-read-books-and-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 18:04:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by David Baldacci]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270015-why-can-t-people-just-sit-and-read-books-and-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why can't people just sit and read books and be nice to each other?" -- David Baldacci]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95040-small-mistakes-tend-to-lead-to-large-ones-ours-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 18:05:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by David Baldacci]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95040-small-mistakes-tend-to-lead-to-large-ones-ours-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Small mistakes tend to lead to large ones. Ours is a lifetime appoinment, and all you have is your reputation. Once it's gone, it doesn't comeback." -- David Baldacci]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/210035-when-a-poor-man-gives-something-that-is-a-sacrifice</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 18:05:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by David baldacci]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/210035-when-a-poor-man-gives-something-that-is-a-sacrifice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a poor man gives something, that is a sacrifice indeed. When a rich man gives something, it hardly rises to the same level." -- David baldacci]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/567287-i-think-the-overriding-message-would-be-that-love-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2012 20:27:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Ka Hancock]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/567287-i-think-the-overriding-message-would-be-that-love-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think the overriding message would be that love is serious business.  True, down-to-the-crap love is not for the shallow or faint of heart.  People are messy. Marriage is messy.  You have to bring your best self to the game despite your limitations." -- Ka Hancock]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533170-death-is-not-the-end-of-life-but-a-stage</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 08:27:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Jan-Philipp Sendker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533170-death-is-not-the-end-of-life-but-a-stage]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death is not the end of life, but a stage thereof." -- Jan-Philipp Sendker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/703221-the-essence-of-a-thing-is-invisible-to-the-eye</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 08:29:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Jan-Philipp Sendker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/703221-the-essence-of-a-thing-is-invisible-to-the-eye]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The essence of a thing is invisible to the eye, U May said.  Learn to perceive the essence of a thing.  Eyes are more likely to hinder you in that regard.  They distract us.  We love to be dazzled." -- Jan-Philipp Sendker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192060-the-beauty-of-a-woman-is-not-in-the-clothes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 00:04:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192060-the-beauty-of-a-woman-is-not-in-the-clothes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The beauty of a woman is not in the clothes she wears, the figure that she carries, or the way she combs her hair. The beauty of a woman is seen in her eyes, because that is the doorway to her heart, the place where love resides. True beauty in a woman is reflected in her soul. It's the caring that she lovingly gives, the passion that she shows &amp; the beauty of a woman only grows with passing years." -- Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/662709-and-so-there-must-be-in-life-something-like-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 19:26:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Jan-Philipp Sendker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/662709-and-so-there-must-be-in-life-something-like-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And so there must be in life something like a catastrophic turning point, when the world as we know ceases to exist. A moment that transform us into a different person from one heartbeat to the next." -- Jan-Philipp Sendker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/523647-if-every-person-in-this-room-made-it-a-rule</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 23:42:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by R.J. Palacio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/523647-if-every-person-in-this-room-made-it-a-rule]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If every person in this room made it a rule that wherever you are, whenever you can, you wil try to act a little kinder than is necessary - the world really would be a better place. And if you do this, if you act just a little kinder than is necessary, someone else, somewhere, someday, may recognize in you, in every single one of you, the face of God." -- R.J. Palacio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/562757-i-wish-every-day-could-be-halloween-we-could-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 23:42:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by R. J. Palacio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/562757-i-wish-every-day-could-be-halloween-we-could-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish every day could be Halloween. We could all wear masks all the time. Then we could walk around and get to know each other before we got to see what we looked like under the masks." -- R. J. Palacio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/594379-no-no-it-s-not-all-random-if-it-really-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 23:43:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by R.J. Palacio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/594379-no-no-it-s-not-all-random-if-it-really-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["no, no, it's not all random, if it really was all random, the universe would abandon us completely. and the universe doesn't. it takes care of its most fragile creations in ways we can't see. like with parents who adore you blindly. and a big sister who feels guilty for being human over you. and a little gravelly-voiced kid whose friends have left him over you. and even a pink-haired girl who carries your picture in her wallet. maybe it is a lottery, but the universe makes it all even out in the end. the universe takes care of all its birds." -- R.J. Palacio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69032-reading-one-book-is-like-eating-one-potato-chip</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 12:23:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Diane Duane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69032-reading-one-book-is-like-eating-one-potato-chip]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reading one book is like eating one potato chip." -- Diane Duane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40152-he-smiled-understandingly-much-more-than-understandingly-it-was-one-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2013 23:32:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40152-he-smiled-understandingly-much-more-than-understandingly-it-was-one-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He smiled understandingly-much more than understandingly. It was one of those rare smiles with a quality of eternal reassurance in it, that you may come across four or five times in life. It faced--or seemed to face--the whole eternal world for an instant, and then concentrated on you with an irresistible prejudice in your favor. It understood you just as far as you wanted to be understood, believed in you as you would like to believe in yourself, and assured you that it had precisely the impression of you that, at your best, you hoped to convey." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10867-there-are-only-the-pursued-the-pursuing-the-busy-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2013 23:32:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10867-there-are-only-the-pursued-the-pursuing-the-busy-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are only the pursued, the pursuing, the busy and the tired." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/676344-what-i-love-about-the-ministry-of-jesus-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 20:28:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Rachel Held Evans]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/676344-what-i-love-about-the-ministry-of-jesus-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I love about the ministry of Jesus is that he identified the poor as blessed and the rich as needy...and then he went and ministered to them both. This, I think, is the difference between charity and justice. Justice means moving beyond the dichotomy between those who need and those who supply and confronting the frightening and beautiful reality that we desperately need one another." -- Rachel Held Evans]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/868697-if-you-are-looking-for-verses-with-which-to-support</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 20:32:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by Rachel Held Evans]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/868697-if-you-are-looking-for-verses-with-which-to-support]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are looking for verses with which to support slavery, you will find them.  If you are looking for verses with which to abolish slavery, you will find them.  If you are looking for verses with which to oppress women, you will find them.  If you are looking for for verses with which to liberate or honor women, you will find them.  If you are looking for reasons to wage war, you will find them.  If you are looking for reasons to promote peace, you will find them.  If you are looking for an out-dated, irrelevant ancient text, you will find it.  If you are looking for truth, believe me, you will find it. This is why there are times when the most instructive question to bring to the text is not &quot;what does it say?&quot;, but &quot;what am I looking for?&quot;  I suspect Jesus knew this when he said, &quot;ask and it will be given to you, seek and you will find, knock and the door will be opened.&quot;  If you want to do violence in this world, you will always find the weapons.  If you want to heal, you will always find the balm." -- Rachel Held Evans]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/741840-but-good-friends-are-nothing-to-each-other-if-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 09:03:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenifer add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/741840-but-good-friends-are-nothing-to-each-other-if-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["but good friends are nothing to each other if they are not supportive." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
