<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/364576-steve-allison]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/364576-steve-allison" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 18:07:17 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27688-for-me-trees-have-always-been-the-most-penetrating-preachers</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 18:07:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Herman Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27688-for-me-trees-have-always-been-the-most-penetrating-preachers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For me, trees have always been the most penetrating preachers. I revere them when they live in tribes and families, in forests and groves. And even more I revere them when they stand alone. They are like lonely persons. Not like hermits who have stolen away out of some weakness, but like great, solitary men, like Beethoven and Nietzsche. In their highest boughs the world rustles, their roots rest in infinity; but they do not lose themselves there, they struggle with all the force of their lives for one thing only: to fulfil themselves according to their own laws, to build up their own form, to represent themselves. Nothing is holier, nothing is more exemplary than a beautiful, strong tree. When a tree is cut down and reveals its naked death-wound to the sun, one can read its whole history in the luminous, inscribed disk of its trunk: in the rings of its years, its scars, all the struggle, all the suffering, all the sickness, all the happiness and prosperity stand truly written, the narrow years and the luxurious years, the attacks withstood, the storms endured. And every young farmboy knows that the hardest and noblest wood has the narrowest rings, that high on the mountains and in continuing danger the most indestructible, the strongest, the ideal trees grow.

     Trees are sanctuaries. Whoever knows how to speak to them, whoever knows how to listen to them, can learn the truth. They do not preach learning and precepts, they preach, undeterred by particulars, the ancient law of life.

     A tree says: A kernel is hidden in me, a spark, a thought, I am life from eternal life. The attempt and the risk that the eternal mother took with me is unique, unique the form and veins of my skin, unique the smallest play of leaves in my branches and the smallest scar on my bark. I was made to form and reveal the eternal in my smallest special detail.

     A tree says: My strength is trust. I know nothing about my fathers, I know nothing about the thousand children that every year spring out of me. I live out the secret of my seed to the very end, and I care for nothing else. I trust that God is in me. I trust that my labor is holy. Out of this trust I live.

     When we are stricken and cannot bear our lives any longer, then a tree has something to say to us: Be still! Be still! Look at me! Life is not easy, life is not difficult. Those are childish thoughts. Let God speak within you, and your thoughts will grow silent. You are anxious because your path leads away from mother and home. But every step and every day lead you back again to the mother. Home is neither here nor there. Home is within you, or home is nowhere at all.

     A longing to wander tears my heart when I hear trees rustling in the wind at evening. If one listens to them silently for a long time, this longing reveals its kernel, its meaning. It is not so much a matter of escaping from one's suffering, though it may seem to be so. It is a longing for home, for a memory of the mother, for new metaphors for life. It leads home. Every path leads homeward, every step is birth, every step is death, every grave is mother.

     So the tree rustles in the evening, when we stand uneasy before our own childish thoughts: Trees have long thoughts, long-breathing and restful, just as they have longer lives than ours. They are wiser than we are, as long as we do not listen to them. But when we have learned how to listen to trees, then the brevity and the quickness and the childlike hastiness of our thoughts achieve an incomparable joy. Whoever has learned how to listen to trees no longer wants to be a tree. He wants to be nothing except what he is. That is home. That is happiness." -- Herman Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144836-within-the-core-of-each-of-us-is-the-child</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 18:16:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Rhawn Joseph]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144836-within-the-core-of-each-of-us-is-the-child]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["within the core of each of us is the child we once were. This child constitutes the foundation of what we have become, who we are, and what we will be." -- Rhawn Joseph]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156835-we-cannot-live-only-for-ourselves-a-thousand-fibers-connect</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 17:23:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156835-we-cannot-live-only-for-ourselves-a-thousand-fibers-connect]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We cannot live only for ourselves. A thousand fibers connect us with our fellow men; and among those fibers, as sympathetic threads, our actions run as causes, and they come back to us as effects." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78652-it-is-better-to-fail-in-originality-than-to-succeed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 17:23:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78652-it-is-better-to-fail-in-originality-than-to-succeed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to fail in originality than to succeed in imitation." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70552-real-strength-never-impairs-beauty-or-harmony-but-it-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 17:24:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Melville Herman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70552-real-strength-never-impairs-beauty-or-harmony-but-it-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Real strength never impairs beauty or harmony, but it often bestows it, and in everything imposingly beautiful, strength has much to do with the magic." -- Melville Herman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66333-truth-uncompromisingly-told-will-always-have-its-jagged-edges</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 17:24:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66333-truth-uncompromisingly-told-will-always-have-its-jagged-edges]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Truth uncompromisingly told will always have its jagged edges." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164668-not-only-is-the-universe-stranger-than-we-think-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 16:45:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Werner Heisenberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164668-not-only-is-the-universe-stranger-than-we-think-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not only is the Universe stranger than we think, it is stranger than we can think." -- Werner Heisenberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159230-clutter-and-mess-show-us-that-life-is-being-lived-tidiness</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 02:28:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159230-clutter-and-mess-show-us-that-life-is-being-lived-tidiness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Clutter and mess show us that life is being lived...Tidiness makes me think of held breath, of suspended animation... Perfectionism is a mean, frozen form of idealism, while messes are the artist's true friend. What people somehow forgot to mention when we were children was that we need to make messes in order to find out who we are and why we are here." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/941-the-opposite-of-a-correct-statement-is-a-false-statement</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2012 09:22:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Niels Bohr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/941-the-opposite-of-a-correct-statement-is-a-false-statement]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opposite of a correct statement is a false statement. But the opposite of a profound truth may well be another profound truth." -- Niels Bohr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19493-here-is-the-world-beautiful-and-terrible-things-will-happen</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 04:44:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19493-here-is-the-world-beautiful-and-terrible-things-will-happen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here is the world.  Beautiful and terrible things will happen.  Don't be afraid." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18980-ultimately-man-should-not-ask-what-the-meaning-of-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 04:44:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18980-ultimately-man-should-not-ask-what-the-meaning-of-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ultimately, man should not ask what the meaning of his life is, but rather must recognize that it is he who is asked. In a word, each man is questioned by life; and he can only answer to life by answering for his own life; to life he can only respond by being responsible." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
