<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/365679-nancy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/365679-nancy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 18:58:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 18:58:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many books, so little time." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1149-be-careful-about-reading-health-books-you-may-die-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 19:05:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1149-be-careful-about-reading-health-books-you-may-die-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be careful about reading health books. You may die of a misprint." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63481-religion-has-convinced-people-that-there-s-an-invisible-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 05:56:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63481-religion-has-convinced-people-that-there-s-an-invisible-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Religion has convinced people that there's an invisible man ... living in the sky. Who watches everything you do every minute of every day. And the invisible man has a list of ten specific things he doesn't want you to do. And if you do any of these things, he will send you to a special place, of burning and fire and smoke and torture and anguish for you to live forever, and suffer, and suffer, and burn, and scream, until the end of time. But he loves you. He loves you. He loves you and he needs money." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140154-the-planet-is-fine-the-people-are-fucked</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 05:57:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140154-the-planet-is-fine-the-people-are-fucked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The planet is fine. The people are fucked." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67109-i-do-this-real-moron-thing-and-it-s-called-thinking</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 05:58:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67109-i-do-this-real-moron-thing-and-it-s-called-thinking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do this real moron thing, and it's called thinking. And apparently I'm not a very good American because I like to form my own opinions." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76453-we-re-so-self-important-so-arrogant-everybody-s-going-to-save-something</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 05:58:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76453-we-re-so-self-important-so-arrogant-everybody-s-going-to-save-something]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're so self-important. So arrogant. Everybody's going to save something now. Save the trees, save the bees, save the whales, save the snails. And the supreme arrogance? Save the planet! Are these people kidding? Save the planet? We don't even know how to take care of ourselves; we haven't learned how to care for one another. We're gonna save the fuckin' planet? . . . And, by the way, there's nothing wrong with the planet in the first place. The planet is fine. The people are fucked! Compared with the people, the planet is doin' great. It's been here over four billion years . . . The planet isn't goin' anywhere, folks. We are! We're goin' away. Pack your shit, we're goin' away. And we won't leave much of a trace. Thank God for that. Nothing left. Maybe a little Styrofoam. The planet will be here, and we'll be gone. Another failed mutation; another closed-end biological mistake." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114802-i-don-t-like-ass-kissers-flag-wavers-or-team-players</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 05:58:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114802-i-don-t-like-ass-kissers-flag-wavers-or-team-players]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't like ass kissers, flag wavers or team players. I like people who buck the system. Individualists. I often warn people: &quot;Somewhere along the way, someone is going to tell you, 'There is no &quot;I&quot; in team.' What you should tell them is, 'Maybe not. But there is an &quot;I&quot; in independence, individuality and integrity.'&quot; Avoid teams at all cost. Keep your circle small. Never join a group that has a name. If they say, &quot;We're the So-and-Sos,&quot; take a walk. And if, somehow, you must join, if it's unavoidable, such as a union or a trade association, go ahead and join. But don't participate; it will be your death. And if they tell you you're not a team player, congratulate them on being observant." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176057-people-say-i-m-going-to-sleep-now-as-if-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 05:09:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176057-people-say-i-m-going-to-sleep-now-as-if-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People say, 'I'm going to sleep now,' as if it were nothing. But it's really a bizarre activity. 'For the next several hours, while the sun is gone, I'm going to become unconscious, temporarily losing command over everything I know and understand. When the sun returns, I will resume my life.'

If you didn't know what sleep was, and you had only seen it in a science fiction movie, you would think it was weird and tell all your friends about the movie you'd seen.

They had these people, you know? And they would walk around all day and be OK? And then, once a day, usually after dark, they would lie down on these special platforms and become unconscious. They would stop functioning almost completely, except deep in their minds they would have adventures and experiences that were completely impossible in real life. As they lay there, completely vulnerable to their enemies, their only movements were to occasionally shift from one position to another; or, if one of the 'mind adventures' got too real, they would sit up and scream and be glad they weren't unconscious anymore. Then they would drink a lot of coffee.'

So, next time you see someone sleeping, make believe you're in a science fiction movie. And whisper, 'The creature is regenerating itself." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282383-here-in-britain-of-course-it-s-thank-fuck-we-got</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 09:05:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by Warren Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282383-here-in-britain-of-course-it-s-thank-fuck-we-got]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here in Britain, of course, it's Thank Fuck We Got Those Weird Jesus Bastards On The Boat Day" -- Warren Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
