<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/365981-angela]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/365981-angela" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:11:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606584-in-the-end-he-became-as-fragmentary-as-the-poems</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:11:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606584-in-the-end-he-became-as-fragmentary-as-the-poems]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the end he became as fragmentary as the poems of Sappho he never succeeded in restoring, and finally one morning he looked up into the face of the woman who’d been the greatest love of his life and failed to recognize her. And then there was another kind of blow inside his head; blood pooled in his brain for the last time, washing even the last fragments of his self away." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/466428-i-recalled-the-myth-that-i-had-once-heard-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:12:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Colum McCann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/466428-i-recalled-the-myth-that-i-had-once-heard-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I recalled the myth that I had once heard as a university student – thirty-six hidden saints in the world, all of them doing the work of humble men, carpenters, cobblers, shepherds. They bore the sorrows of the earth and they had a line of communication with God, all except one, the hidden saint, who was forgotten. The forgotten one was left to struggle on his own, with no line of communication to that which he so hugely needed. Corrigan had lost his line with God: he bore the sorrows on his own, the story of stories." -- Colum McCann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/336013-there-is-something-demoralizing-about-watching-two-people-get-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:15:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/336013-there-is-something-demoralizing-about-watching-two-people-get-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is something demoralizing about watching two people get more and more crazy about each other, especially when you are the only extra person in the room." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216474-in-my-younger-and-more-vulnerable-years-my-father-gave</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:15:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216474-in-my-younger-and-more-vulnerable-years-my-father-gave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In my younger and more vulnerable years my father gave me some advice that I've been turning over in my mind ever since.
&quot;Whenever you feel like criticizing any one,&quot; he told me, &quot;just remember that all the people in this world haven't had the advantages that you've had." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606587-the-byronic-hero-incapable-of-love-or-capable-only-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:17:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606587-the-byronic-hero-incapable-of-love-or-capable-only-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Byronic hero, incapable of love, or capable only of an impossible love, suffers endlessly. He is solitary, languid, his condition exhausts him. If he wants to feel alive, it must be in the terrible exaltation of a brief and destructive action." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606589-i-wanted-this-complex-language-this-surge-of-intellect-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:17:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Gary Shteyngart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606589-i-wanted-this-complex-language-this-surge-of-intellect-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted this complex language, this surge of intellect, to be processed into love. Isn’t how they used to do it a century ago, people reading poetry to one another?" -- Gary Shteyngart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606590-i-know-this-kind-of-girl-grace-was-saying-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:18:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Gary Shteyngart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606590-i-know-this-kind-of-girl-grace-was-saying-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know this kind of girl,” Grace was saying. “It’s the worst kind of combination of abuse and privilege, and growing up in this, like, greenhorn southern-Californian Asian upper-middle-class ghetto, where everyone is so shallow and money-craven." -- Gary Shteyngart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606593-about-how-she-had-seemingly-overnight-suffered-a-sudden-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:19:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606593-about-how-she-had-seemingly-overnight-suffered-a-sudden-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…about how she had seemingly overnight suffered a sudden and anomalous gigantism in her right breast, which she referred to as a titty; she had an almost parodic Québecois accent and described the ‘titty’s’ presenting history and possible diagnoses for almost twenty minutes before I was rolled away." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606594-he-actually-had-a-relationship-once-with-someone-who-d-committed</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:20:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Etgar Keret]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606594-he-actually-had-a-relationship-once-with-someone-who-d-committed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He actually had a relationship once with someone who’d committed suicide. Not emotional, physical. It happened in the army. He was serving in general-staff headquarters at the time, and he’d been brought up on charges of being seen with his boots unpolished. And just when he was walking past the tall staff headquarters building, someone dropped to the ground next to him, splattered. A girl-soldier, they said, with a broken heart, a corporal, Liat Something. Later he remembered hearing a kind of scream above him as she was falling. But he hadn’t looked up. The sound didn’t even register.

He reached the hearing all covered in her blood. They let him off. Liat Atlas. That was her name. They even called on him later, to testify at the military police investigation. It couldn’t go on this way, that much he knew. Maybe he needed therapy." -- Etgar Keret]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606595-perhaps-i-can-make-you-understand-let-s-start-from-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:21:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Nathanael West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606595-perhaps-i-can-make-you-understand-let-s-start-from-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps I can make you understand. Let’s start from the beginning. A man is hired to give advice to the readers of a newspaper. The job is a circulation stunt and the whole staff considers it a joke. He welcomes the job, for it might lead to a gossip column, and anyway he’s tired of being a leg man. He too considers the job a joke, but after several months at it, the joke begins to escape him. He sees that the majority of the letters are profoundly humble pleas for moral and spiritual advice, and they are inarticulate expressions of genuine suffering. He also discovers that his correspondents take him seriously. For the first time in his life, he is forced to examine the values by which he lives. This examination shows him that he is the victim of the joke and not its perpetrator." -- Nathanael West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150900-people-hasten-to-judge-in-order-not-to-be-judged</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:22:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150900-people-hasten-to-judge-in-order-not-to-be-judged]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People hasten to judge in order not to be judged themselves." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606596-as-you-flail-knowing-you-re-not-supposed-to-panic</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:22:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Jennifer Egan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606596-as-you-flail-knowing-you-re-not-supposed-to-panic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As you flail, knowing you’re not supposed to panic – panicking will drain your strength – your mind pulls away as it does so easily, so often, without your even noticing sometimes, leaving Robert Freeman Jr. to manage the current alone while you withdraw to the broader landscape, the water and buildings and streets, the avenues like endless hallways, your dorm full of sleeping students, the air thick with their communal breath. You slip through Sasha’s open window, floating over the sill lined with artifacts from her travels: a white seashell, a small gold pagoda, a pair of red dice. Her harp in one corner with its small wood stool. She’s asleep in her narrow bed, her burned red hair dark against the sheets. You kneel beside her, breathing the familiar smell of Sasha’s sleep, whispering into her ear some mix of I’m sorry and I believe in you and I’ll always be near you, protecting you, and I will never leave you, I’ll be curled around your heart for the rest of your life, until the water pressing my shoulders and chest crushes me awake and I hear Sasha screaming into my face: Fight! Fight! Fight!" -- Jennifer Egan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606597-and-she-loved-a-man-who-was-made-out-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:23:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Etgar Keret]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606597-and-she-loved-a-man-who-was-made-out-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And she loved a man who was made out of nothing. A few hours without him and right away she’d be missing him with her whole body, sitting in her office surrounded by polyethylene and concrete and thinking of him. And every time she’d boil water for coffee in her ground-floor office, she’d let the steam cover her face, imagining it was him stroking her cheeks, her eyelids and she’d wait for the day to be over, so she could go to her apartment building, climb the flight of stairs, turn the key in the door, and find him waiting for her, naked and still between the sheets of her empty bed." -- Etgar Keret]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606598-happy-birthday-your-thirteenth-is-important-maybe-your-first-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:24:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606598-happy-birthday-your-thirteenth-is-important-maybe-your-first-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happy birthday. Your thirteenth is important. Maybe your first really public day. Your thirteenth is the chance for people to recognize that important things are happening to you.
Things have been happening to you for the past half year. You have seven hairs in your left armpit now. Twelve in your right. Hard dangerous spirals of brittle black hair. Crunchy, animal hair. There are now more of the hard curled hairs around your privates than you can count without losing track. Other things. Your voice is rich and scratchy and moves between octaves without any warning. Your face has begun to get shiny when you don’t wash it. And two weeks of a deep and frightening ache this past spring left you with something dropped down from inside: your sack is now full and vulnerable, a commodity to be protected. Hefted and strapped in tight supporters that stripe your buttocks red. You have grown into a new fragility.

And dreams. For months there have been dreams like nothing before: moist and busy and distant, full of unyielding curves, frantic pistons, warmth and a great falling; and you have awakened through fluttering lids to a rush and a gush and a toe-curling scalp-snapping jolt of feeling from an inside deeper than you knew you had, spasms of a deep sweet hurt, the streetlights through your window blinds crackling into sharp stars against the black bedroom ceiling, and on you a dense white jam that lisps between legs, trickles and sticks, cools on you, hardens and clears until there is nothing but gnarled knots of pale solid animal hair in the morning shower, and in the wet tangle a clean sweet smell you can’t believe comes from anything you made inside you." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606599-she-quickly-discovered-that-the-world-is-divided-into-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:25:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606599-she-quickly-discovered-that-the-world-is-divided-into-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She quickly discovered that the world is divided into people who know how to be comfortable by themselves on a bar chair and people who do not." -- Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49905-does-it-break-my-heart-of-course-every-moment-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 09:28:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49905-does-it-break-my-heart-of-course-every-moment-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Does it break my heart, of course, every moment of every day, into more pieces than my heart was made of, I never thought of myself as quiet, much less silent, I never thought about things at all, everything changed, the distance that wedged itself between me and my happiness wasn't the world, it wasn't the bombs and burning buildings, it was me, my thinking, the cancer of never letting go, is ignorance bliss, I don't know, but it's so painful to think, and tell me, what did thinking ever do for me, to what great place did thinking ever bring me? I think and think and think, I've thought myself out of happiness one million times, but never once into it." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
