<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/366942-mallory]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/366942-mallory" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:11:54 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9529-it-may-be-unfair-but-what-happens-in-a-few</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:11:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9529-it-may-be-unfair-but-what-happens-in-a-few]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It may be unfair, but what happens in a few days, sometimes even a single day, can change the course of a whole lifetime..." -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11306-i-wondered-if-that-was-how-forgiveness-budded-not-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:12:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11306-i-wondered-if-that-was-how-forgiveness-budded-not-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wondered if that was how forgiveness budded; not with the fanfare of epiphany, but with pain gathering its things, packing up, and slipping away unannounced in the middle of the night." -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23318-grief-turns-out-to-be-a-place-none-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:14:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23318-grief-turns-out-to-be-a-place-none-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Grief turns out to be a place none of us know until we reach it. We anticipate (we know) that someone close to us could die, but we do not look beyond the few days or weeks that immediately follow such an imagined death. We misconstrue the nature of even those few days or weeks. We might expect if the death is sudden to feel shock. We do not expect this shock to be obliterative, dislocating to both body and mind. We might expect that we will be prostrate, inconsolable, crazy with loss. We do not expect to be literally crazy, cool customers who believe their husband is about to return and need his shoes." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23319-television-is-the-creamy-filling-that-distracts-us-from-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:15:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by David Niven]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23319-television-is-the-creamy-filling-that-distracts-us-from-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Television is the creamy filling that distracts us from the substance our lives" -- David Niven]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23320-sports-contained-the-truth-i-decided-the-unspoken-truth-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:15:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23320-sports-contained-the-truth-i-decided-the-unspoken-truth-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sports contained the truth, I decided, the unspoken truth (how quickly we damn ourselves when we start to talk, how small and inglorious we always sound), and it seemed hard to believe that I had never understood this before. They rewarded effortlessness and unself-consciousness; they confirmed that yes, there are rankings of skill and value and that everyone knows what they are (seeing those guys who were subbed with two seconds left before the end of a quarter, I’d think how girls’ coaches were never that heartless); they showed that the best things in the world to be were young and strong and fast. To play a great game of high school basketball-it was something I myself had never done, but I could tell-made you know what it was to be alive. How much in an adult life can compare to that? Granted, there are margaritas, or there’s no homework, but there are also puffy white bagels under neon lights in the conference room, there’s waiting for the plumber, making small talk with your boring neighbor." -- Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23321-she-nodded-jotting-something-in-her-notebook-you-re-writing-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:15:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23321-she-nodded-jotting-something-in-her-notebook-you-re-writing-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She nodded, jotting something in her notebook.
You’re writing that down? Has the interview started?”
Lee, whenever you’re talking to a reporter, you’re being interviewed." -- Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23322-it-s-not-lying-it-s-flirting</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:16:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Neil Strauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23322-it-s-not-lying-it-s-flirting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s not lying, it’s flirting." -- Neil Strauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23325-i-felt-like-a-racehorse-in-a-world-without-racetracks</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:16:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23325-i-felt-like-a-racehorse-in-a-world-without-racetracks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I felt like a racehorse in a world without racetracks or a champion college footballer suddenly confronted by Wall Street and a business suit, his days of glory shrunk to a little gold cup on his mantel with a date engraved on it like the date on a tombstone." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23327-that-s-one-of-the-reasons-i-never-wanted-to-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:17:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23327-that-s-one-of-the-reasons-i-never-wanted-to-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That’s one of the reasons I never wanted to get married. The last thing I wanted was infinite security and to be the place an arrow shoots off from. I wanted change and excitement and to shoot off in all directions myself, like the colored arrows from a Fourth of July rocket." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23328-when-they-asked-me-what-i-wanted-to-be-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:17:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23328-when-they-asked-me-what-i-wanted-to-be-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When they asked me what I wanted to be I said I didn’t know.
&quot;Oh, sure you know,&quot; the photographer said.
&quot;She wants,&quot; said Jay Cee wittily, &quot;to be everything." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/922-i-took-a-deep-breath-and-listened-to-the-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:17:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/922-i-took-a-deep-breath-and-listened-to-the-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I took a deep breath and listened to the old brag of my heart. I am, I am, I am." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23330-i-thought-marcus-was-going-to-be-in-my-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:18:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Megan McCafferty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23330-i-thought-marcus-was-going-to-be-in-my-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I thought Marcus was going to be in my life forever. Then I thought I was wrong. Now he’s back. But this time I know what’s certain: Marcus will be gone again, and back again and again and again because nothing is permanent. Especially people. Strangers become friends. Friends become lovers. Lovers become strangers. Strangers become friends once more, and over and over. Tomorrow, next week, fifty years from now, I know I’ll get another one-word postcard from Marcus, because this one doesn’t have a period signifying the end of the sentence.

Or the end of anything at all." -- Megan McCafferty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23335-because-the-song-is-us-and-the-song-is-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:21:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by David Levithan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23335-because-the-song-is-us-and-the-song-is-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because the song is us and the song is her and this time I’m going to use her name. Norah, Norah, Norah - no rhymes really. Just truth.

I shouldn’t want the song to end. I always think of each night as a song. Or each moment as a song. But now I’m seeing we don’t live in a single song. We move from song to song, from lyric to lyric, from chord to chord. There is no ending here. It’s an infinite playlist." -- David Levithan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23337-io-ritornai-da-la-santissima-onda-rifatto-s-come-piante</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:22:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Dante Alighieri]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23337-io-ritornai-da-la-santissima-onda-rifatto-s-come-piante]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Io ritornai da la santissima onda
rifatto sì come piante novelle
rinnovellate di novella fronda, 
puro e disposto a salire alle stelle." -- Dante Alighieri]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23338-you-yes-you-linger-inside-my-heart-the-same-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:22:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Megan McCafferty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23338-you-yes-you-linger-inside-my-heart-the-same-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You, yes, you, linger inside my heart
The same you who stopped us before we could start." -- Megan McCafferty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23339-only-twice-in-my-nearly-fifty-years-of-friendship-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:23:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Cecil B. DeMille]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23339-only-twice-in-my-nearly-fifty-years-of-friendship-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only twice in my nearly fifty years of friendship with David Belasco did he ever disappoint me; and I am glad that experience came early. When I was perhaps seven or eight years old, he promised me, many months before my birthday, that he would give me a pony. What boy would nurse that promise to his bosom for any number of months? When the 12th of August dawned, I was downstairs early, I think before anyone else was up. I looked out at the barnyard. No pony. I waited all day. No pony. I said nothing. No pony. There were other presents, of course, and all the other excitement of a small boy’s birthday: but underneath it I was having my very first experience of a forgotten promise." -- Cecil B. DeMille]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23340-the-solitude-of-writing-is-a-solitude-without-which-writing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:24:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Marguerite Duras]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23340-the-solitude-of-writing-is-a-solitude-without-which-writing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The solitude of writing is a solitude without which writing could not be produced, or would crumble, drained bloodless by the search for something else to write." -- Marguerite Duras]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23342-it-s-dark-now-and-i-am-very-tired-i-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:25:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23342-it-s-dark-now-and-i-am-very-tired-i-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s dark now and I am very tired. I love you, always. Time is nothing." -- Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23343-it-comes-out-so-quietly-that-i-have-to-ask</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:25:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23343-it-comes-out-so-quietly-that-i-have-to-ask]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It comes out so quietly that I have to ask her to repeat it: “It’s just that I thought maybe you were married to me." -- Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23344-story-is-what-happens-to-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:26:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by James V. Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23344-story-is-what-happens-to-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Story is what happens to people." -- James V. Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23345-after-all-what-was-adult-life-but-one-moment-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:26:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Tom Perrotta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23345-after-all-what-was-adult-life-but-one-moment-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After all, what was adult life but one moment of weakness piled on top of another? Most people just fell in line like obedient little children, doing exactly what society expected of them at any given moment, all the while pretending that they’d actually made some sort of choice." -- Tom Perrotta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23346-and-i-know-i-can-do-this-because-i-went</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:27:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Mark Haddon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23346-and-i-know-i-can-do-this-because-i-went]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I know I can do this because I went to London on my own, and because I solved the mystery…and I was brave and I wrote a book and that means I can do anything." -- Mark Haddon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18940-i-would-give-the-greatest-sunset-in-the-world-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:27:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18940-i-would-give-the-greatest-sunset-in-the-world-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would give the greatest sunset in the world for one sight of New York's skyline. Particularly when one can't see the details. Just the shapes. The shapes and the thought that made them. The sky over New York and the will of man made visible. What other religion do we need? And then people tell me about pilgrimages to some dank pesthole in a jungle where they go to do homage to a crumbling temple, to a leering stone monster with a pot belly, created by some leprous savage. Is it beauty and genius they want to see? Do they seek a sense of the sublime? Let them come to New York, stand on the shore of the Hudson, look and kneel. When I see the city from my window - no, I don't feel how small I am - but I feel that if a war came to threaten this, I would throw myself into space, over the city, and protect these buildings with my body." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54533-why-is-it-he-said-one-time-at-the-subway</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:28:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54533-why-is-it-he-said-one-time-at-the-subway]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why is it,&quot; he said, one time, at the subway entrance, &quot;I feel I've known you so many years?&quot;
&quot;Because I like you,&quot; she said, &quot;and I don't want anything from you." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23350-but-you-see-said-roark-quietly-i-have-let-s-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:28:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23350-but-you-see-said-roark-quietly-i-have-let-s-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But you see,&quot; said Roark quietly, &quot;I have, let’s say, sixty years to live. Most of that time will be spent working. I’ve chosen the work I want to do. If I find no joy in it, then I’m only condemning myself to sixty years of torture. And I can find the joy only if I do my work in the best way possible to me. But the best is a matter of standards—and I set my own standards. I inherit nothing. I stand at the end of no tradition. I may, perhaps, stand at the beginning of one." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27212-do-you-understand-sir-do-you-understand-what-it-means</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2008 17:11:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27212-do-you-understand-sir-do-you-understand-what-it-means]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you understand, sir, do you understand what it means when you have absolutely nowhere to turn?&quot; Marmeladov’s question came suddenly into his mind &quot;for every man must have somewhere to turn..." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/846-for-you-a-thousand-times-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 03:07:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/846-for-you-a-thousand-times-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For you, a thousand times over" -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16660-boys-laila-came-to-see-treated-friendship-the-way-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 03:08:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16660-boys-laila-came-to-see-treated-friendship-the-way-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Boys, Laila came to see, treated friendship the way they treated the sun: its existence undisputed; its radiance best enjoyed, not beheld directly." -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161-like-a-compass-needle-that-points-north-a-man-s-accusing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 17:32:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161-like-a-compass-needle-that-points-north-a-man-s-accusing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like a compass needle that points north, a man's accusing finger always finds a woman. Always." -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31140-you-changed-the-subject-from-what-the-empty-headed-girls-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 03:08:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mallory add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31140-you-changed-the-subject-from-what-the-empty-headed-girls-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You changed the subject.&quot;
&quot;From what?&quot;
&quot;The empty-headed girls who think you're sexy.&quot;
&quot;You know.&quot;
&quot;Know what?&quot;
&quot;That I only have eyes for you." -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
