<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/368260-haejin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/368260-haejin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 14:24:27 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208117-when-two-people-relate-to-each-other-authentically-and-humanly</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 14:24:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Martin Buber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208117-when-two-people-relate-to-each-other-authentically-and-humanly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When two people relate to each other authentically and humanly, God is the electricity that surges between them." -- Martin Buber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153501-start-writing-no-matter-what-the-water-does-not-flow</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Louis L'Amour]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153501-start-writing-no-matter-what-the-water-does-not-flow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Start writing, no matter what. The water does not flow until the faucet is turned on" -- Louis L'Amour]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209293-orange-is-one-of-god-s-favorite-colors----he-stuck-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Reggie Joiner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209293-orange-is-one-of-god-s-favorite-colors----he-stuck-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Orange] is one of God's favorite colors--- He stuck it right there between red and yellow as the second color in the rainbow.  He decorates entire forests with shades of orange every autumn.  It shows up in sunrises at the start of the day, sunsets at the end of the day, and in the glow of the moon at the right time of night." -- Reggie Joiner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153504-poem-by-howard-a-walter-character-i-would-be-true</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by John C. Maxwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153504-poem-by-howard-a-walter-character-i-would-be-true]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Poem by Howard A. Walter (Character)

I would be true, for there are those who trust me;
I would be pure, for there are those who care;
I would be strong, for there are those who suffer;
I would be brave, for there is much to dare.
I would be friend of all--- the foe, the friendless;
I would be giving, and forget the gift;
I would be humble, for I know my weakness;
I would look up, and laugh, and love, and lift." -- John C. Maxwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209296-orange-is-what-red-and-yellow-can-do-when-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Reggie Joiner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209296-orange-is-what-red-and-yellow-can-do-when-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Orange is what red and yellow can do when they combine efforts.  If you paint only with red, you will get what only red can do.  If you paint only with yellow, you will get what only yellow can do.  But when you paint with red and yellow, you will get new possibilities, fresh solutions, vibrant outcomes.  When you think orange, you see how two combined influences make a greater impact than just two influences.  As long as churches do only what churches are doing, they will get only the results they are presently getting.  and as long as families do only what families are doing, they will produce only the outcomes they are presently producing.    The church can be represented with yellow (&quot;bright lights&quot;) and families with red (&quot;warm hearts&quot;)." -- Reggie Joiner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29365-it-is-one-of-the-beautiful-compensations-of-life-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29365-it-is-one-of-the-beautiful-compensations-of-life-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is one of the beautiful compensations of life that no man can sincerely try to help another without helping himself." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209338-they-are-not-working-in-sync-working-on-the-same</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Reggie Joiner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209338-they-are-not-working-in-sync-working-on-the-same]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They are not working in sync.  Working on the same thing at the same time is not as effective as working on the same thing a the same time with the same strategy." -- Reggie Joiner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153513-there-was-a-very-cautious-man-who-never-laughed-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by John C. Maxwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153513-there-was-a-very-cautious-man-who-never-laughed-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was a very cautious man
Who never laughed or played
He never risked, he never tried,
He never sang or prayed.
And when he on day passed away,
His insurance was denied,
For since he never really lived,
They claimed he never really died.

(Anonymous poem)" -- John C. Maxwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209345-the-church-is-missionary-by-nature-because-god-through-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Craig Van Gelder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209345-the-church-is-missionary-by-nature-because-god-through-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The church is missionary by nature because God through the Spirit calls, creates, and commissions the church to communicate to the world that the redemptive reign of God has broken into human history." -- Craig Van Gelder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158218-ironically-it-was-the-father-s-blessing-that-actually-financed-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Tommy Tenney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158218-ironically-it-was-the-father-s-blessing-that-actually-financed-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ironically, it was the father's blessing that actually &quot;financed&quot; the prodigal son's trip away from the Father's face! and it was the son's new revelation of his poverty of heart that propelled him back into his Father's arms.  Sometimes we use the very blessings that God gives us to finance our journey away from the centrality of Christ.  It's very important that we return back to ground zero, to the ultimate eternal goal of abiding with the Father's in intimate communion.  (pg. 243)" -- Tommy Tenney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209360-the-lampstand-was-position-strategically-to-do-one-things-cast</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Reggie Joiner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209360-the-lampstand-was-position-strategically-to-do-one-things-cast]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The lampstand was position strategically to do one things: cast its light on the table and on the bread that represented God's provision and presence.  For generations the lampstand of the tabernacle stood to highlight the object that best represented God's goodness and provision, the same object that Jesus would one day use to symbolize His own body. (Jesus compares church to a lampstand in Revelation- a strong reminder of the church's responsibility).  Everything about these churches 0 their teaching, practices, and work-- was challenged for one reason in Revelation: They were losing their effectiveness as God's light to their communities." -- Reggie Joiner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161734-lack-of-interest-in-mission-is-not-fundamentally-caused-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Tim Dearborn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161734-lack-of-interest-in-mission-is-not-fundamentally-caused-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lack of interest in mission is not fundamentally caused by an absence of compassion or commitment, nor by lack of information or exhortation. And lack of interest in mission is not remedied by more shocking statistics, more gruesome stories or more emotionally manipulative commands to obedience. It is best remedied by intensifying peoples’ passion for Christ, so that the passions of his heart become the passions that propel our hearts." -- Tim Dearborn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209392-every-parent-will-leave-a-personal-legacy-though-not-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Reggie Joiner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209392-every-parent-will-leave-a-personal-legacy-though-not-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["every parent will leave a personal legacy (though not all parents will leave behind an inheritance). what i give to my children or what i do for my children is not as important as what i leave in them.   " -- Reggie Joiner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161735-passion-is-the-heart-set-free-to-pursue-that-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Perspectives Sutdy Guide]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161735-passion-is-the-heart-set-free-to-pursue-that-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Passion is the heart set free to pursue that which is truly worthy.  Those who set their hearts on that which is most worthy live with joy-filled abandonment. Their hearts are both seized and satisfied with ambition only for Jesus to be ardently worshipped.  That love comes to dominate and integrate all other desires so as to live in the freedom of single-minded purpose." -- Perspectives Sutdy Guide]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209380-it-is-important-to-note-that-the-lampstand-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Reggie Joiner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209380-it-is-important-to-note-that-the-lampstand-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is important to note that the lampstand in the tabernacle did not cast a broad light, illuminating everything in the tabernacle; the focus of its beam was specifically on the bread of presence.  Likewise, the church is not called to illuminate everything -- its light should be concentrated on showing others who God is.  For church leaders, our jobs are clear: we have to keep the wicks trimmed, the light burning, and the lampstand in its proper place.  if the light begins to dim, we must immediately move into action.  God's intention is for the church to be placed strategically in culture in order to show Himself to the world.  Anytime the church becomes ineffective in its role to illuminate Christ, it must rekindle and reinvent itself around its core purpose." -- Reggie Joiner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161736-god-desires-that-we-be-like-living-signs-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Tim Dearborn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161736-god-desires-that-we-be-like-living-signs-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God desires that we be like living signs of the kingdom, to provide visual aids of what life will look like one day when the kingdom is here fully. We will not bring the Kingdom or build the kingdom, but our privilege is to live out previews of “coming attractions,” revealing what this Kingdom will look like." -- Tim Dearborn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209404-god-is-at-work-telling-a-story-of-restoration-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Reggie Joiner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209404-god-is-at-work-telling-a-story-of-restoration-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God is at work telling a story of restoration and redemption through your family.  Never buy into the myth that you need to become the &quot;
right&quot; kind of parent before God can use you in your children's lives. Instead learn to cooperate with whatever God desires  to do in your heart today so your children will have a front-row seat to the grace and goodness of God." -- Reggie Joiner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166935-look-behind-you-what-have-you-learned-look-around-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by John Maxwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166935-look-behind-you-what-have-you-learned-look-around-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look behind you: What have you learned?
Look around you: What is happening to others?
Look above you: What does God expect of you?
Look besides you: What resources are available to you?" -- John Maxwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209406-the-first-priority-of-the-family-should-be-to-establish</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Reggie Joiner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209406-the-first-priority-of-the-family-should-be-to-establish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first priority of the family should be to establish a quality of relationship with each other that is a reflection of an authentic relationship with God.  That may have been what Paul was aiming at when he wrote to the church in Ephesians 5 and 6 about the family." -- Reggie Joiner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198417-up-until-the-1950s-the-subject-of-the-missionary-movement</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Walter C. Kaiser Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198417-up-until-the-1950s-the-subject-of-the-missionary-movement]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Up until the 1950s the subject of the missionary movement was referred to as &quot;missions&quot; in the plural form.  In fact, the term &quot;missions&quot; was first used in its current context by the Jesuits in the sixteenth century.  But the International Missionary Council discussions in the 1950s on the missio- Dei convinced most that the mission of the Triune God was prior to any of the number of missions by Christians during the two millennia of church history.  Consequently, since there was only one mission, the plural form has dropped out of familir usage and the singular form, &quot;mission,&quot; has replaced it for the most part.  Nevertheless, most churches and lay-persons hang on the plural missions.  For that reason, and to make our point clear here, we will refer to it in this work from time to time while alerting believers to the coming change." -- Walter C. Kaiser Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209411-jesus-said-i-when-i-am-lifted-up-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Reggie Joiner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209411-jesus-said-i-when-i-am-lifted-up-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jesus said, &quot; I, when I am lifted up from the earth, will draw all men to myself,&quot; knowing that the nature of a forgiving Christ on the cross would compel people to follow Him.  As long as the church remains an effective platform for God's light to reveal to the world the sacrifice Jesu samde, the church will be anturally irresistible.  Light is inherently inviting-- just think of a porch light left on late into the night.  Light communicates comfort, warmth, and healing.  It gives direction and hope so we can see better and understand more fully.  Most people I meet are looking for light. The problem is that the emphasis is of too many churches has gradually shifted and changed." -- Reggie Joiner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198419-it-was-ever-and-always-the-plain-offer-of-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Walter C. Kaiser Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198419-it-was-ever-and-always-the-plain-offer-of-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was ever and always the plain offer of God to all the peoples of the earth through his elected servants of the promise-plan." -- Walter C. Kaiser Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55677-if-you-are-humble-nothing-will-touch-you-neither-praise</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55677-if-you-are-humble-nothing-will-touch-you-neither-praise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are humble nothing will touch you, neither praise nor disgrace, because you know what you are." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203154-holiness-does-not-consist-in-doing-extraordinary-things-it-consists</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203154-holiness-does-not-consist-in-doing-extraordinary-things-it-consists]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Holiness does not consist in doing extraordinary things.  It consists in accepting, with a smile, what Jesus sends us.  It consists in accepting and following the will of God." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203155-prayer-makes-your-heart-bigger-until-it-is-capable-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203155-prayer-makes-your-heart-bigger-until-it-is-capable-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Prayer makes your heart bigger, until it is capable of containing the gift of God himself. Prayer begets faith, faith begets love, and love begets service on behalf of the poor." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203157-lord-make-me-an-instrument-of-your-peace-where-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Francis Of Assisi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203157-lord-make-me-an-instrument-of-your-peace-where-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lord, make me an instrument of your peace;
where there is hatred, let me sow love;
when there is injury, pardon;
where there is doubt, faith;
where there is despair, hope;
where there is darkness, light;
and where there is sadness, joy.
Grant that I may not so much seek
to be consoled as to console;
to be understood, as to understand,
to be loved as to love;
for it is in giving that we receive,
it is in pardoning that we are pardoned,
and it is in dying [to ourselves] that we are born to eternal life." -- Francis Of Assisi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128334-prayer-is-not-asking-prayer-is-putting-oneself-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128334-prayer-is-not-asking-prayer-is-putting-oneself-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Prayer is not asking. Prayer is putting oneself in the hands of God, at His disposition, and listening to His voice in the depth of our hearts." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203704-writing-about-the-spiritual-life-is-like-making-prints-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by robert durback]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203704-writing-about-the-spiritual-life-is-like-making-prints-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing about the spiritual life is like making prints from negatives...Often it is the dark forest that makes us speak about the open field.  Frequently prison makes us think about freedom, hunger helps us to appreciate food, and war gives us words for peace.  Not seldom are our vision of the future born out of the sufferings of the present and our hope for others out of our own despair. Only few &quot;happy endings&quot; make us happy but often someone's careful ad honest articulation of the ambiguities, uncertainties, and painful conditions of life gives us new hope.  The paradox is indeed that new life is born out of the pains of the old." -- robert durback]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203706-one-way-to-express-the-spiritual-crisis-of-our-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Henri Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203706-one-way-to-express-the-spiritual-crisis-of-our-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One way to express the spiritual crisis of our time is to say that most of us have an address but cannot be found there." -- Henri Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203707-to-live-a-spiritual-life-we-must-first-find-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 17:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Haejin add a quote by Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203707-to-live-a-spiritual-life-we-must-first-find-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To live a spiritual life we must first find the courage to enter into the desert of our loneliness and to change it by gentle and persistent efforts into a garden of solitude.  The movement from loneliness to solitude, however, is the beginning of any spiritual life because it it is the movement from the restless senses to the restful spirit,l from the outward-reaching cravings to the inward-reaching search, from the fearful clinging to the fearless play." -- Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
