<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/368937-jill]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/368937-jill" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 15:15:36 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35953-let-no-one-be-discouraged-by-the-belief-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 15:15:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jill add a quote by Robert F. Kennedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35953-let-no-one-be-discouraged-by-the-belief-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let no one be discouraged by the belief there is nothing one person can do against the enormous array of the world's ills, misery, ignorance, and violence.  Few will have the greatness to bend history, but each of us can work to change a small portion of events.  And in the total of all those acts will be written the history of a generation." -- Robert F. Kennedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49262-if-i-had-my-life-to-live-over-i-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 15:19:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jill add a quote by Erma Bombeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49262-if-i-had-my-life-to-live-over-i-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["IF I HAD MY LIFE TO LIVE OVER

I would have talked less and listened more.

I would have invited friends over to dinner even if the carpet was stained and the sofa faded.

I would have eaten the popcorn in the &quot;good&quot; living room and worried much less about the dirt when someone wanted to light a fire in the fireplace.

I would have taken the time to listen to my grandfather rambling about his youth.

I would never have insisted the car windows be rolled up on a summer day because my hair had just been teased and sprayed.

I would have burned the pink candle sculped like a rose before it melted 
in storage.

I would have sat on the lawn with my children and not worried about grass stains.

I would have cried and laughed less while watching television, and more 
while watching life.

I would have gone to bed when I was sick, instead of pretending the earth would go into a holding pattern if I weren't there for the day.

I would never have bought anything just because it was practical, wouldn't show soil or was guaranteed to last a lifetime.

Instead of wishing away nine months of pregnancy, I'd have cherished every moment, realising that the wonderment growing inside me was the only chance in life to assist God in a miracle.

When my kids kissed me impetuously, I would never have said, &quot;Later. Now go get washed up for dinner.&quot;

There would have been more &quot;I love you's&quot; and more &quot;I'm sorry's&quot;

. . . but mostly, given another shot at life, I would seize every minute . . . 
look at it and really see it . . . and never give it back." -- Erma Bombeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
