<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/369056-yz]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/369056-yz" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2009 18:58:13 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134014-and-at-this-hour-of-the-day-it-is-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2009 18:58:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Louis MacNeice]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134014-and-at-this-hour-of-the-day-it-is-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And at this hour of the day it is no good saying
'Take away this cup';
Having helped to fill it ourselves it is only logic
That now we should drink it up." -- Louis MacNeice]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134016-none-of-our-hearts-are-pure-we-always-have-mixed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2009 18:59:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Louis MacNeice]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134016-none-of-our-hearts-are-pure-we-always-have-mixed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["None of our hearts are pure, we always have mixed motives.
Are self deceivers, but the worst of all
Deceits is to murmur 'Lord, I am not worthy'
And, lying easy, turn your face to the wall. " -- Louis MacNeice]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134033-let-the-old-muse-loosen-her-stays-or-give-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2009 21:25:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Louis MacNeice]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134033-let-the-old-muse-loosen-her-stays-or-give-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let the old Muse loosen her stays
Or give me a new Muse with stockings and suspenders
And a smile like a cat,
With false eyelashes and finger-nails of carmine
And dressed by Schiaparelli, with a pill-box hat.
...
Give me a houri but houris are too easy,
Give me a nun;
We'll rape the angels off the golden reredos
Before we're done." -- Louis MacNeice]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134034-a-city-built-upon-mud-a-culture-built-upon-profit</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2009 21:57:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Louis MacNeice]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134034-a-city-built-upon-mud-a-culture-built-upon-profit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A city built upon mud;
A culture built upon profit;
Free speech nipped in the bud,
The minority always guilty.
Why should I want to go back
To you, Ireland, my Ireland?
...
Her mountains are still blue, her rivers flow
Bubbling over the boulders.
She is both a bore and a bitch;
Better close the horizon,
Send her no more fantasy, no more longings which
Are under a fatal tariff.
For common sense is the vogue
And she gives her children neither sense nor money
Who slouch around the world with a gesture and a brogue
And a faggot of useless memories." -- Louis MacNeice]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134035-i-cannot-drug-my-life-with-the-present-moment-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2009 22:23:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Louis MacNeice]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134035-i-cannot-drug-my-life-with-the-present-moment-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot drug my life with the present moment;
The present moment may rape--but all in vain--
The future, for the future remains a virgin
Who must be tried again." -- Louis MacNeice]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134091-give-those-who-are-gentle-strength-give-those-who-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 07:33:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Louis MacNeice]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134091-give-those-who-are-gentle-strength-give-those-who-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Give those who are gentle strength,
Give those who are strong a generous imagination,
And make their half-truth true and let the crooked 
Footpath find its parent road at length.
...
For never to begin
Anything new because we know there is nothing
New, is an academic sophistry--
The original sin.
I have already had friends
Among things and hours and people
But taking them one by one--odd hours and passing people;
Now I must make amends
And try to correlate event with instinct
And me with you or you with you with all,
No longer think of time as a waterfall
Abstracted from a river." -- Louis MacNeice]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158765-the-propounders-of-what-are-called-the-ethics-of-evolution</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2009 11:39:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Thomas Henry Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158765-the-propounders-of-what-are-called-the-ethics-of-evolution]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The propounders of what are called the &quot;ethics of evolution,&quot; when the 'evolution of ethics' would usually better express the object of their speculations, adduce a number of more or less interesting facts and more or less sound arguments, in favour of the origin of the moral sentiments, in the same way as other natural phenomena, by a process of evolution. I have little doubt, for my own part, that they are on the right track; but as the immoral sentiments have no less been evolved, there is, so far, as much natural sanction for the one as the other. The thief and the murderer follow nature just as much as the philanthropist. Cosmic evolution may teach us how the good and the evil tendencies of man may have come about; but, in itself, it is incompetent to furnish any better reason why what we call good is preferable to what we call evil than we had before." -- Thomas Henry Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160428-all-that-profligate-investment-of-energy-to-effect-a-splendid</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2009 16:59:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160428-all-that-profligate-investment-of-energy-to-effect-a-splendid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that profligate investment of energy to effect a splendid, momentary reversal of natural law. That such a reversal should demand so much and last such a short time was terrible; that people would go for it anyway was both terrible and wonderful.

...A game, or maybe even not that--maybe it was only &lt;i&gt;practice&lt;/i&gt; for a game, the way that all the sweat and trembling exhaustion in the Wilshire loft that day had just been practice. Practice for a show that only a few people would probably care to attend and which would probably close quickly." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154204-thus-though-we-cannot-make-our-sun-stand-still-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 19:11:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Andrew Marvell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154204-thus-though-we-cannot-make-our-sun-stand-still-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thus, though we cannot make our sun 
Stand still, yet we will make him run." -- Andrew Marvell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166681-i-have-done-this-before-in-other-cities-other-nights</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 11:02:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Lawrence Chua]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166681-i-have-done-this-before-in-other-cities-other-nights]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have done this before. In other cities, other nights. So often I can repeat each gesture without owning any of them." -- Lawrence Chua]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166682-place-has-ceased-to-be-of-importance-now-that-power</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 11:03:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Lawrence Chua]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166682-place-has-ceased-to-be-of-importance-now-that-power]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Place has ceased to be of importance now that power no longer lives at a fixed address. ... Power's location is less important than its velocity through temporary obstacles. The speed of a tank ramming through the baricade of history." -- Lawrence Chua]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166683-in-another-city-in-another-place-luk-would-have-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 11:03:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Lawrence Chua]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166683-in-another-city-in-another-place-luk-would-have-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In another city. In another place. Luk would have had to submit his plans for approval. Months would have been lost. Waiting. The Ministry in Charge. Public safety and all that. But the law is for people who don't know each other. We're all family here." -- Lawrence Chua]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166684-a-rocket-or-a-bridge-that-s-the-only-way-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 11:05:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Lawrence Chua]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166684-a-rocket-or-a-bridge-that-s-the-only-way-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A rocket or a bridge. That's the only way I can really describe it. If there is a river between our sleeping bodies, this is the bridge that crosses it. ... I can just fit my fist around the base without waking him. I love it so much I want to bite it." -- Lawrence Chua]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166686-sir-in-my-heart-there-was-a-kind-of-fighting</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 11:07:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166686-sir-in-my-heart-there-was-a-kind-of-fighting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sir, in my heart there was a kind of fighting 
That would not let me sleep." -- Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167215-now-i-know-what-development-means-air-conditioning-with-air-conditioning-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2009 06:44:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Lawrence Chua]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167215-now-i-know-what-development-means-air-conditioning-with-air-conditioning-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now I know what development means: air-conditioning.

With air-conditioning, we can have civilization, which exists only in temperate climates. " -- Lawrence Chua]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169287-this-development-signified-also-that-jazz-would-someday-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2009 11:28:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by LeRoi Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169287-this-development-signified-also-that-jazz-would-someday-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This development signified also that jazz would someday have to contend with the idea of its being an art (since that &lt;i&gt;was&lt;/i&gt; the white man's only way into it). The emergence of the white player meant that Afro-American culture had already become the expression of a particular kind of American experience, and what is most important, that this experience was available intellectually, that it could be learned." -- LeRoi Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169295-i-don-t-believe-in-god-so-i-don-t-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2009 11:47:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Frank O'Hara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169295-i-don-t-believe-in-god-so-i-don-t-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't believe in god, so I don't have to make elaborately sounded structures. ... Pain always produces logic, which is very bad for you. ... As for measure and other technical apparatus, that's just common sense: if you're going to buy a pair of pants you want them to be tight enough so everyone will want to go to bed with you. There's nothing metaphysical about it." -- Frank O'Hara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98909-we-mortals-men-and-women-devour-many-a-disappointment-between</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 12:12:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98909-we-mortals-men-and-women-devour-many-a-disappointment-between]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We mortals, men and women, devour many a disappointment between breakfast and dinner-time; keep back the tears and look a little pale about the lips, and in answer to inquiries say, &quot;Oh, nothing!&quot; Pride helps; and pride is not a bad thing when it only urges us to hide our hurts— not to hurt others." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176184-i-should-like-to-make-life-beautiful--i-mean-everybody-s-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 20:49:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176184-i-should-like-to-make-life-beautiful--i-mean-everybody-s-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I should like to make life beautiful--I mean everybody's life. And then all this immense expense of art, that seems somehow to lie outside life and make it no better for the world, pains one. It spoils my enjoyment of anything when I am made to think that most people are shut out from it.&quot;

I call that the fanaticism of sympathy,&quot; said Will, impetuously. &quot;You might say the same of landscape, of poetry, of all refinement. If you carried it out you ought to be miserable in your own goodness, and turn evil that you might have no advantage over others. The best piety is to enjoy--when you can. You are doing the most then to save the earth's character as an agreeable planet. And enjoyment radiates. It is of no use to try and take care of all the world; that is being taken care of when you feel delight--in art or in anything else. Would you turn all the youth of the world into a tragic chorus, wailing and moralising over misery? I suspect that you have some false belief in the virtues of misery, and want to make your life a martyrdom." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176185-for-my-part-i-am-very-sorry-for-him-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 20:53:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176185-for-my-part-i-am-very-sorry-for-him-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For my part I am very sorry for him. It is an uneasy lot at best, to be what we call highly taught and yet not to enjoy: to be present at this great spectacle of life and never to be liberated from a small hungry shivering self--never to be fully possessed by the glory we behold, never to have our consciousness rapturously transformed into the vividness of a thought, the ardour of a passion, the energy of an action, but always to be scholarly and uninspired, ambitious and timid, scrupulous and dimsighted. " -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32014-for-every-bourgeois-in-the-heat-of-youth-if-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 06:55:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32014-for-every-bourgeois-in-the-heat-of-youth-if-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For every bourgeois, in the heat of youth, if only for a day, for a minute, has believed himself capable of immense passions, of heroic enterprises.  The most mediocre libertine has dreamed of oriental princesses; every rotary carries about inside him the debris of a poet." -- Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/665914-the-alleged-sensitivity-of-neurotic-people-is-matched-by-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 14:15:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yz add a quote by Proust Marcel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/665914-the-alleged-sensitivity-of-neurotic-people-is-matched-by-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The alleged 'sensitivity' of neurotic people is matched by their egotism; they cannot abide the flaunting by others of the sufferings to which they pay an ever-increasing attention in themselves." -- Proust Marcel]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
