<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/36953-nikki-karam]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/36953-nikki-karam" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2012 07:16:10 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/646275-when-on-a-moonlit-night-you-see-a-wide-village</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2012 07:16:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nikki add a quote by Anton Chekhov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/646275-when-on-a-moonlit-night-you-see-a-wide-village]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When, on a moonlit night, you see a wide village street with its peasant houses, haystacks, sleeping willows, tranquility enters the soul; in this calm, wrapped in the shade of night, free from struggle, anxiety and passion, everything is gentle, wistful, beautiful, and it seems that the stars are watching over it tenderly and with love, and that this is taking place somewhere unearthly, and that all is well." -- Anton Chekhov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882238-children-never-forget-for-this-reason-it-was-so-important</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2013 08:22:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nikki add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882238-children-never-forget-for-this-reason-it-was-so-important]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...children never forget. For this reason, it was so important what one said, and what one did, and it was a relief when they went to bed. For now she need not think about anybody. She could be herself, by herself. And that was what now she often felt the need of-- to think; well, not even to think. To be silent; to be alone. All the being and the doing, expansive, glittering, vocal, evaporated; and one shrunk, with a sense of solemnity, to being oneself, a wedge-shaped core of darkness, something invisible to others." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/888792-it-struck-her-this-was-tragedy---not-palls-dust-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 09:42:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nikki add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/888792-it-struck-her-this-was-tragedy---not-palls-dust-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...it struck her, this was tragedy-- not palls, dust, and the shroud; but children coerced, their spirits subdued." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/981704-they-don-t-seem-able-to-love-us-just-the-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 18:35:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nikki add a quote by J. D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/981704-they-don-t-seem-able-to-love-us-just-the-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...they don't seem able to love us just the way we are. They don't seem able to love us unless they can keep changing us a little bit. They love their reasons for loving us almost as much as they love us, and most of the time more. It's not so good, that way." -- J. D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245965-people-don-t-do-right-because-of-the-fear-of-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 08:50:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nikki add a quote by Dorothy Allison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245965-people-don-t-do-right-because-of-the-fear-of-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People don't do right because of the fear of God or love of him. You do the right thing because the world doesn't make sense if you don't.&quot; (145)" -- Dorothy Allison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191691-every-ship-is-a-romantic-object-except-that-we-sail</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2009 15:50:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nikki add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191691-every-ship-is-a-romantic-object-except-that-we-sail]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every ship is a romantic object, except that we sail in. " -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/444895-the-people-dreamed-and-fought-and-slept-as-much-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 07:42:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nikki add a quote by Carson McCullers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/444895-the-people-dreamed-and-fought-and-slept-as-much-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The people dreamed and fought and slept as much as ever. And by habit they shortened their thoughts so that they would not wander out into the darkness beyond tomorrow." -- Carson McCullers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31090-reserving-judgements-is-a-matter-of-infinite-hope</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2009 16:25:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nikki add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31090-reserving-judgements-is-a-matter-of-infinite-hope]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reserving judgements is a matter of infinite hope." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206103-but-what-is-the-sense-in-forever-speculating-what-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 17:03:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nikki add a quote by Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206103-but-what-is-the-sense-in-forever-speculating-what-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But what is the sense in forever speculating what might have happened had such and such a moment turned out differently? One could presumably drive oneself to distraction in this way. In any case, while it is all very well to talk of 'turning points', one can surely only recognize such moments in retrospect. Naturally, when one looks back to such instances today, they may indeed take the appearance of being crucial, precious moments in one's life; but of course, at the time, this was not the impression one had. Rather, it was as though one had available a never-ending number of days, months, years in which to sort out the vagaries of one's relationship with Miss Kenton; an infinite number of further opportunities in which to remedy the effect of this or that misunderstanding. There was surely nothing to indicate at the time that such evidently small incidents would render whole dreams forever irredeemable." -- Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/370158-we-imagined-ourselves-as-the-sons-of-liberty-with-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 09:19:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nikki add a quote by Patti Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/370158-we-imagined-ourselves-as-the-sons-of-liberty-with-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We imagined ourselves as the Sons of Liberty with a mission to preserve, protect, and project the revolutionary spirit of rock and roll. We feared that the music which had given us sustenance was in danger of spiritual starvation. We feared it losing its sense of purpose, we feared it falling into fattened hands, we feared it floundering in a mire of spectacle, finance, and vapid technical complexity." -- Patti Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 13:59:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nikki add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100098-hail-nothing-full-of-nothing-nothing-is-with-thee</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 17:57:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nikki add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100098-hail-nothing-full-of-nothing-nothing-is-with-thee]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hail nothing full of nothing, nothing is with thee." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
