<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/36986-eli-brooke]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/36986-eli-brooke" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 12:07:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7756-the-continuous-narrative-of-existence-is-a-lie-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 12:07:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eli add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7756-the-continuous-narrative-of-existence-is-a-lie-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The continuous narrative of existence is a lie. There is no continuous narrative, there are lit-up moments, and the rest is dark." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196940-the-truth-about-stories-is-that-s-all-we-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 12:07:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eli add a quote by Thomas King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196940-the-truth-about-stories-is-that-s-all-we-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth about stories is, that's all we are." -- Thomas King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/544587-we-mostly-understand-ourselves-through-an-endless-series-of-stories</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 12:07:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eli add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/544587-we-mostly-understand-ourselves-through-an-endless-series-of-stories]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We mostly understand ourselves through an endless series of stories told to ourselves by ourselves and others. The so-called facts of our individual worlds are highly coloured and arbitrary, facts that fit whatever reality we have chosen to believe in. . . . It may be that to understand ourselves as fictions, is to understand ourselves as fully as we can." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/376462-you-want-to-tell-a-story-grow-a-heart-grow</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 17:38:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eli add a quote by Charles Yu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/376462-you-want-to-tell-a-story-grow-a-heart-grow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You want to tell a story? Grow a heart. Grow two. Now, with the second heart, smash the first one into bits." -- Charles Yu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728342-who-do-you-imagine-you-are-imagine-there-s-a-version</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 18:09:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eli add a quote by Charles Yu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728342-who-do-you-imagine-you-are-imagine-there-s-a-version]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who do you imagine you are? Imagine there's a version of you that sees all of it. A version that knows when versions are messing with the other ones, trying to get things off track, trying to erase things. A record of all the versions, partial and deleted and written over. All the changes. All truths about all parts of our self. We break ourselves up into parts. To lie to ourselves, to hide things from ourselves. You are not you. You are not what you think you are. You are bigger than you think. More complicated than you think. You are the only version of you that is you. There are less of you than you think, and more. There are a million versions of you, half a trillion. One for every particle, every quantum coin flip. Imagine this uncountable number of yous. You don't always have your own best interests at heart. It's true. You are your own best friend and your own worst enemy. . . . Only you know what you need to do. Imagine there is a perfect version of you. Out of all the oceans of oceans of you, there is exactly one who is perfectly you. And that's me. And I'm telling you that you are the only you." -- Charles Yu]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
