<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/370214-wangho]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/370214-wangho" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 03:41:19 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70377-only-in-the-stillness-of-thought-can-decisions-be-properly</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 03:41:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wangho add a quote by Eric Lustbader]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70377-only-in-the-stillness-of-thought-can-decisions-be-properly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only in the stillness of thought can decisions be properly made." -- Eric Lustbader]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/684180-i-never-used-an-outline-until-i-started-the-bourne</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 03:41:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wangho add a quote by Eric Van Lustbader]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/684180-i-never-used-an-outline-until-i-started-the-bourne]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I never used an outline until I started &quot;The Bourne Legacy&quot; project for which I was required to write an outline. To be honest, I thought I'd hate the idea, assuming that if I'd thought of all the ideas at the outset I'd have to incentive to actually write the book, because for me part of the joy of writing are the surprises you come upon as the book takes shape. But something curious and exciting happened. As I wrote the outline, some sections would be very detailed, others quite sketchy, so that whole portions of the book would be covered by one line, such as &quot;Bourne is chased by Khan through Budapest,&quot; which when I wrote the novel turned out to be 40-50 pages! Now I'll never write a novel without first doing an outline. Looking back on it, I used to get bogged down in extraneous characters and situations, especially during the first 100 pages (which I find the most difficult to write) that I would later have to scrap, wasting time and energy, and frustrating me. Now that never happens." -- Eric Van Lustbader]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
