<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/371642-sharon-hunter]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/371642-sharon-hunter" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 22:36:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184942-once-upon-a-time-he-said-out-loud-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 22:36:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by Kate DiCamillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184942-once-upon-a-time-he-said-out-loud-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time,&quot; he said out loud to the darkness. He said these words because they were the best, the most powerful words that he knew and just the saying of them comforted him." -- Kate DiCamillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445629-sometimes-the-best-way-to-help-someone-is-just-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 22:40:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by Veronica Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445629-sometimes-the-best-way-to-help-someone-is-just-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, the best way to help someone is just to be near them." -- Veronica Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251326-i-wish-i-could-help-you-i-whisper-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 22:40:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by Simone Elkeles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251326-i-wish-i-could-help-you-i-whisper-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish I could help you&quot; I whisper.
You are,&quot; he murmurs against my knee. &quot;just dont leave me, okay? Everyone leaves me." -- Simone Elkeles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38865-and-now-we-welcome-the-new-year-full-of-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 22:36:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38865-and-now-we-welcome-the-new-year-full-of-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And now we welcome the new year, full of things that have never been" -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150085-letting-go-doesn-t-mean-that-you-don-t-care-about-someone</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2012 00:05:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by Deborah Reber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150085-letting-go-doesn-t-mean-that-you-don-t-care-about-someone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Letting go doesn't mean that you don't care about someone anymore. It's just realizing that the only person you really have control over is yourself." -- Deborah Reber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391669-you-ve-got-this-life-and-while-you-ve-got-it-you-d</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:14:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391669-you-ve-got-this-life-and-while-you-ve-got-it-you-d]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've got this life and while you've got it, you'd better kiss like you only have one moment, try to hold someone's hand like you will never get another chance to, look into people's eyes like they're the last you'll ever see, watch someone sleeping like there's no time left, jump if you feel like jumping, run if you feel like running, play music in your head when there is none, and eat cake like it's the only one left in the world!" -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393586-i-don-t-know-why-people-are-afraid-of-lust-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:19:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393586-i-don-t-know-why-people-are-afraid-of-lust-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know why people are afraid of lust. Then I can imagine that they are very afraid of me, for I have a great lust for everything. A lust for life, a lust for how the summer-heated street feels beneath my feet, a lust for the touch of another's skin on my skin...a lust for everything. I even lust after cake. Yes, I am very lusty and very scary." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360550-she-didn-t-belong-anywhere-and-she-never-really-belonged-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:29:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360550-she-didn-t-belong-anywhere-and-she-never-really-belonged-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She didn't belong anywhere and she never really belonged to anyone. And everyone else belonged somewhere and to someone. People thought she was too wonderful. But she only wanted to belong to someone. People always thought she was too wonderful to belong to them or that something too wonderful would hurt too much to lose. And that's why she liked him-- because he just thought she was crazy." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405555-people-have-to-forgive-we-don-t-have-to-like-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:30:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405555-people-have-to-forgive-we-don-t-have-to-like-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People have to forgive. We don't have to like them, we don't have to be friends with them, we don't have to send them hearts in text messages, but we have to forgive them, to overlook, to forget. Because if we don't we are tying rocks to our feet, too much for our wings to carry!" -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/404303-there-are-people-who-are-generic-they-make-generic-responses</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:30:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/404303-there-are-people-who-are-generic-they-make-generic-responses]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are people who are generic. They make generic responses and they expect generic answers. They live inside a box and they think people who don't fit into their box are weird. But I'll tell you what, generic people are the weird people. They are like genetically-manipulated plants growing inside a laboratory, like indistinguishable faces, like droids. Like ignorance." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399619-no-i-am-not-bitter-i-am-not-hateful-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:30:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399619-no-i-am-not-bitter-i-am-not-hateful-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No, I am not bitter, I am not hateful, and I am not unforgiving. I just don't like you." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/396919-you-will-manage-to-keep-a-woman-in-love-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:31:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/396919-you-will-manage-to-keep-a-woman-in-love-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You will manage to keep a woman in love with you, only for as long as you can keep her in love with the person she becomes when she is with you." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395033-the-person-in-life-that-you-will-always-be-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:31:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395033-the-person-in-life-that-you-will-always-be-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The person in life that you will always be with the most, is yourself. Because even when you are with others, you are still with yourself, too! When you wake up in the morning, you are with yourself, laying in bed at night you are with yourself, walking down the street in the sunlight you are with yourself.What kind of person do you want to walk down the street with? What kind of person do you want to wake up in the morning with? What kind of person do you want to see at the end of the day before you fall asleep? Because that person is yourself, and it's your responsibility to be that person you want to be with. I know I want to spend my life with a person who knows how to let things go, who's not full of hate, who's able to smile and be carefree. So that's who I have to be." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357309-this-is-the-key-to-life-to-expect-everything-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:32:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357309-this-is-the-key-to-life-to-expect-everything-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is the key to life: To expect everything to be given to you from above, yet to be genuinely surprised and forever grateful, when they are. Expecting all good things to be yours, while not knowing how to take anything for granted. If there may be a key in life, this is the key." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440154-you-can-be-the-most-beautiful-person-in-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:33:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440154-you-can-be-the-most-beautiful-person-in-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can be the most beautiful person in the world and everybody sees light and rainbows when they look at you, but if you yourself don't know it, all of that doesn't even matter. Every second that you spend on doubting your worth, every moment that you use to criticize yourself; is a second of your life wasted, is a moment of your life thrown away. It's not like you have forever, so don't waste any of your seconds, don't throw even one of your moments away." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/359411-in-case-you-never-get-a-second-chance-don-t-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:33:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/359411-in-case-you-never-get-a-second-chance-don-t-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In case you never get a second chance: don't be afraid!&quot; &quot;And what if you do get a second chance?&quot; &quot;You take it!" -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/466011-the-day-i-understood-everything-was-the-day-i-stopped</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:33:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/466011-the-day-i-understood-everything-was-the-day-i-stopped]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The day I understood everything, was the day I stopped trying to figure everything out. The day I knew peace was the day I let everything go." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488135-the-strength-of-a-woman-is-not-measured-by-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:33:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488135-the-strength-of-a-woman-is-not-measured-by-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The strength of a woman is not measured by the impact that all her hardships in life have had on her; but the strength of a woman is measured by the extent of her refusal to allow those hardships to dictate her and who she becomes." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362419-what-does-it-mean-if-i-m-afraid-does-it-mean</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362419-what-does-it-mean-if-i-m-afraid-does-it-mean]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["‎&quot;What does it mean if i'm afraid? Does it mean something bad is going to happen?&quot; &quot;No, it doesn't mean something bad is going to happen. It just means that you have the chance to be brave." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357286-i-consider-myself-a-stained-glass-window-and-this-is-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:37:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357286-i-consider-myself-a-stained-glass-window-and-this-is-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I consider myself a stained-glass window. And this is how I live my life. Closing no doors and covering no windows; I am the multi-colored glass with light filtering through me, in many different shades. Allowing light to shed and fall into many many hues. My job is not to direct anything, but only to filter into many colors. My answer is destiny and my guide is joy. And there you have me." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/441053-you-re-going-to-meet-many-people-with-domineering-personalities-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:39:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/441053-you-re-going-to-meet-many-people-with-domineering-personalities-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're going to meet many people with domineering personalities: the loud, the obnoxious, those that noisily stake their claims in your territory and everywhere else they set foot on. This is the blueprint of a predator. Predators prey on gentleness, peace, calmness, sweetness and any positivity that they sniff out as weakness. Anything that is happy and at peace they mistake for weakness. It's not your job to change these people, but it's your job to show them that your peace and gentleness do not equate to weakness. I have always appeared to be fragile and delicate but the thing is, I am not fragile and I am not delicate. I am very gentle but I can show you that the gentle also possess a poison. I compare myself to silk. People mistake silk to be weak but a silk handkerchief can protect the wearer from a gunshot. There are many people who will want to befriend you if you fit the description of what they think is weak; predators want to have friends that they can dominate over because that makes them feel strong and important. The truth is that predators have no strength and no courage. It is you who are strong, and it is you who has courage. I have lost many a friend over the fact that when they attempt to rip me, they can't. They accuse me of being deceiving; I am not deceiving, I am just made of silk. It is they who are stupid and wrongly take gentleness and fairness for weakness. There are many more predators in this world, so I want you to be made of silk. You are silk." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/412413-i-cannot-have-a-man-who-is-afraid-of-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:40:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/412413-i-cannot-have-a-man-who-is-afraid-of-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot have a man who is afraid of everything, I don't have the time to soothe insecurities and fears, I cannot have a man who is standing on a stone by a creek, watching for the fish to swim by and every time he sees a fish he says &quot;Oh look, this fish scares me, I wonder what this fish means, this fish might mean- this, or this fish might mean- that&quot; for God's sake, they are just fish, and they don't mean anything! Such a sad thing, so many fine, strong men standing on top of little stones, pointing at fish all the time! Such a waste! Such a waste of time! I can only have a man who will leap into the water, not minding the damn fish and whatever other little things that scare him. I need to have someone who is braver than me; if I am a pirate, he has to be the pirate Captain, if I am a pirate Captain he has to be the flying dragon." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/387831-life-has-no-victims-there-are-no-victims-in-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:41:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/387831-life-has-no-victims-there-are-no-victims-in-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life has no victims. There are no victims in this life.

No one has the right to point fingers at his/her past and blame it for what he/she is today. We do not have the right to point our finger at someone else and blame that person for how we treat others, today.

Don’t hide in the corner, pointing fingers at your past. Don’t sit under the table, talking about someone who has hurt you. Instead, stand up and face your past! Face your fears! Face your pain! And stomach it all! You may have to do so kicking and screaming and throwing fits and crying- but by all means- face it!

This life makes no room for cowards." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/262988-i-m-not-like-a-car-you-can-fix-up-i-m</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2013 12:28:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/262988-i-m-not-like-a-car-you-can-fix-up-i-m]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not like a car you can fix up. I'm never gonna run right&quot;  Bella" -- Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
