<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/371823-heather]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/371823-heather" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 14:35:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229827-good-night-lisa-sleep-with-the-angels-her-eyes-stung</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 14:35:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Karen Marie Moning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229827-good-night-lisa-sleep-with-the-angels-her-eyes-stung]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good night, Lisa. Sleep with the angels.&quot;
Her eyes stung from quick tears. It had been her mother's nightly benediction: Sleep with the angels. But then he added words her mother never had: &quot;Then come back to earth and sleep with your devil, who would burn in hell for one night in your arms." -- Karen Marie Moning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22087-this-much-i-m-certain-of-it-doesn-t-happen-immediately-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 19:41:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22087-this-much-i-m-certain-of-it-doesn-t-happen-immediately-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This much I'm certain of: it doesn't happen immediately. You'll finish [the book] and that will be that, until a moment will come, maybe in a month, maybe a year, maybe even several years. You'll be sick or feeling troubled or deeply in love or quietly uncertain or even content for the first time in your life. It won't matter. Out of the blue, beyond any cause you can trace, you'll suddenly realize things are not how you perceived them to be at all. For some reason, you will no longer be the person you believed you once were. You'll detect slow and subtle shifts going on all around you, more importantly shifts in you. Worse, you'll realize it's always been shifting, like a shimmer of sorts, a vast shimmer, only dark like a room. But you won't understand why or how. You'll have forgotten what granted you this awareness in the first place&lt;br&gt;
...&lt;br&gt;
You might try then, as I did, to find a sky so full of stars it will blind you again. Only no sky can blind you now. Even with all that iridescent magic up there, your eye will no longer linger on the light, it will no longer trace constellations. You'll care only about the darkness and you'll watch it for hours, for days, maybe even for years, trying in vain to believe you're some kind of indispensable, universe-appointed sentinel, as if just by looking you could actually keep it all at bay. It will get so bad you'll be afraid to look away, you'll be afraid to sleep.&lt;br&gt;
Then no matter where you are, in a crowded restaurant or on some desolate street or even in the comforts of your own home, you'll watch yourself dismantle every assurance you ever lived by. You'll stand aside as a great complexity intrudes, tearing apart, piece by piece, all of your carefully conceived denials, whether deliberate or unconscious. And then for better or worse you'll turn, unable to resist, though try to resist you still will, fighting with everything you've got not to face the thing you most dread, what is now, what will be, what has always come before, the creature you truly are, the creature we all are, buried in the nameless black of a name.&lt;br&gt;
And then the nightmares will begin." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177566-i-think-it-s-good-for-a-person-to-spend-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 11:19:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Amy Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177566-i-think-it-s-good-for-a-person-to-spend-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think it's good for a person to spend time alone. It gives them an opportunity to discover who they are and to figure out why they are always alone." -- Amy Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/582201-for-a-long-while--for-many-years-in-fact--he</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 14:57:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Truman Capote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/582201-for-a-long-while--for-many-years-in-fact--he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For a long while- for many years, in fact- he had not thought of how it was before he came to the farm. His memory of those times was like a house where no one lives and where the furniture has rotted away. But tonight it was as if lamps had been lighted through all the gloomy dead rooms. It had begun to happen when he saw Tico Feo coming through the dusk with his splendid guitar. Until that moment he had not been lonesome. Now, recognizing his loneliness, he felt alive. He had not wanted to be alive. To be alive was to remember brown rivers where the fish run, and sunlight on a lady's hair." -- Truman Capote]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13233-write-something-even-if-it-s-just-a-suicide-note</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 12:27:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Gore Vidal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13233-write-something-even-if-it-s-just-a-suicide-note]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Write something, even if it's just a suicide note. " -- Gore Vidal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25930-style-is-knowing-who-you-are-what-you-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 12:27:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Gore Vidal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25930-style-is-knowing-who-you-are-what-you-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Style is knowing who you are, what you want to say, and not giving a damn." -- Gore Vidal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/590038-the-product-of-causes-his-origin-his-growth-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 12:49:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/590038-the-product-of-causes-his-origin-his-growth-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The product of causes ... his origin, his growth, his hopes and fears, his loves and his beliefs, are but the outcome of accidental collocations of atoms, that no fire, no heroism, no intensity of thought and feeling, can preserve an individual life beyond the grave; that all the labors of the ages, all the inspiration, all the noonday brightness of human genius are destined to extinction in the vast death of the solar system, that the whole temple of man's achievement must inevitably be buried beneath the debris of a universe in ruins—all these things, if not quite beyond dispute, are so nearly certain, that no philosophy which rejects them can hope to stand ..." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350-i-with-a-deeper-instinct-choose-a-man-who-compels</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 19:45:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350-i-with-a-deeper-instinct-choose-a-man-who-compels]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I, with a deeper instinct, choose a man who compels my strength, who makes enormous demands on me, who does not doubt my courage or my toughness, who does not believe me naïve or innocent, who has the courage to treat me like a woman." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17802-where-they-have-burned-books-they-will-end-in-burning</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 00:34:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Heinrich Heine ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17802-where-they-have-burned-books-they-will-end-in-burning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where they have burned books, they will end in burning human beings." -- Heinrich Heine ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111447-it-ought-to-make-us-feel-ashamed-when-we-talk</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 00:38:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Raymond Carver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111447-it-ought-to-make-us-feel-ashamed-when-we-talk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It ought to make us feel ashamed when we talk like we know what we're talking about when we talk about love." -- Raymond Carver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58950-she-was-ready-to-deny-the-existence-of-space-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 23:52:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58950-she-was-ready-to-deny-the-existence-of-space-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was ready to deny the existence of space and time rather than admit that love might not be eternal." -- Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298654-you-ve-got-to-work-with-your-mistakes-until-they-look</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 00:25:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Raymond Carver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298654-you-ve-got-to-work-with-your-mistakes-until-they-look]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've got to work with your mistakes until they look intended. Understand?" -- Raymond Carver]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
