<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/372512-lyndsey]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/372512-lyndsey" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 16:16:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52176-tears-have-a-purpose-they-are-what-we-carry-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 16:16:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Linda Hogan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52176-tears-have-a-purpose-they-are-what-we-carry-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["tears have a purpose. they are what we carry of the ocean, and perhaps we must become the sea, give ourselves to it, if we are to be transformed." -- Linda Hogan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52179-but-you-can-t-spend-your-whole-life-hoping-people-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 16:19:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Elizabeth McCracken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52179-but-you-can-t-spend-your-whole-life-hoping-people-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["but you can't spend your whole life hoping people will ask you the right questions. you must learn to love and answer the questions they already ask." -- Elizabeth McCracken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58841-you-ve-got-to-give-kids-really-beautiful-children-s-books-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 19:30:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Tony Millionaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58841-you-ve-got-to-give-kids-really-beautiful-children-s-books-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've got to give kids really beautiful children's books in order to turn them into revolutionaries. Because if they see these beautiful things when they're young, when they grow up they'll see the real world and say, 'Why is the world so ugly?! I remember when the world was beautiful.' And then they'll fight, and they'll have a revolution. They'll fight against all of our corruption in the world, they'll fight to try to make the world more beautiful. That's the job of a good children's book illustrator." -- Tony Millionaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 11:21:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think your pain and your heartbreak are unprecedented in the history of the world, but then you read. It was books that taught me that the things that tormented me most were the very things that connected me with all the people who were alive, or who had ever been alive." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/802-in-a-good-bookroom-you-feel-in-some-mysterious-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2008 12:53:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/802-in-a-good-bookroom-you-feel-in-some-mysterious-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a good bookroom you feel in some mysterious way that you are absorbing the wisdom contained in all the books through your skin, without even opening them." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7032-and-above-all-watch-with-glittering-eyes-the-whole-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2008 12:56:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Roald Dahl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7032-and-above-all-watch-with-glittering-eyes-the-whole-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And above all, watch with glittering eyes the whole world around you because the greatest secrets are always hidden in the most unlikely places. Those who don't believe in magic will never find it." -- Roald Dahl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/745-perhaps-all-the-dragons-in-our-lives-are-princesses-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2008 12:59:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/745-perhaps-all-the-dragons-in-our-lives-are-princesses-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps all the dragons in our lives are princesses who are only waiting to see us act, just once, with beauty and courage. Perhaps everything that frightens us is, in its deepest essence, something helpless that wants our love." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2008 12:59:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2008 13:05:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be patient toward all that is unsolved in your heart and try to love the questions themselves, like locked rooms and like books that are now written in a very foreign tongue. Do not now seek the answers, which cannot be given you because you would not be able to live them. And the point is, to live everything. Live the questions now. Perhaps you will then gradually, without noticing it, live along some distant day into the answer." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75114-above-all-what-you-have-as-young-people-that-s-vitally</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2008 21:14:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Abbie Hoffman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75114-above-all-what-you-have-as-young-people-that-s-vitally]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Above all, what you have as young people that's vitally needed to make social change, is impatience. You want it to happen now. There have to be enough people that say, &quot;We want it now, in our lifetime. &quot; We want to see apartheid in South Africa come down right now. We want to see the war in Central America stop right now. We want the CIA off our campus right now. We want an end to sexual harassment in our communities right now. Be adventurists in the sense of being bold and daring. Be opportunists and seize this opportunity, this moment in history, to go out and save our country. It's your turn now." -- Abbie Hoffman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 14:43:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to write the book that wants to be written. And if the book will be too difficult for grown-ups, then you write it for children." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4693-we-the-mortals-touch-the-metals-the-wind-the-ocean</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 14:50:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4693-we-the-mortals-touch-the-metals-the-wind-the-ocean]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We the mortals touch the metals,
the wind, the ocean shores, the stones,
knowing they will go on, inert or burning,
and I was discovering, naming all the these things:
it was my destiny to love and say goodbye." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33460-let-there-be-spaces-in-your-togetherness-and-let-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 14:55:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33460-let-there-be-spaces-in-your-togetherness-and-let-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let there be spaces in your togetherness, And let the winds of the heavens dance between you. Love one another but make not a bond of love: Let it rather be a moving sea between the shores of your souls. Fill each other's cup but drink not from one cup. Give one another of your bread but eat not from the same loaf. Sing and dance together and be joyous, but let each one of you be alone, Even as the strings of a lute are alone though they quiver with the same music. Give your hearts, but not into each other's keeping. For only the hand of Life can contain your hearts. And stand together, yet not too near together: For the pillars of the temple stand apart, And the oak tree and the cypress grow not in each other's shadow." -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122748-once-when-i-was-younger-i-went-out-and-sat</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 19:25:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Linda Hogan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122748-once-when-i-was-younger-i-went-out-and-sat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once when I was younger I went out and sat under the sky and looked up and asked it to take me back. What I should have done was gone to the swamp and bog and ask them to bring me back because, if anything is, mud and marsh are the origins of life. Now i think of the storm that made chaos, that the storm opened a door. It tried to make over a world the way it wanted it to be. At school I learned that storms create life, that lightning, with its nitrogen, is a beginning; bacteria and enzymes grow new life from decay out of darkness and water. It's into this that I want to fall, into swamp and mud and sludge and it seems like falling is the natural way of things; gravity needs no fuel, no wings. It needs only stillness and waiting and time." -- Linda Hogan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122749-i-ve-been-good-at-this-world-the-one-that-hits</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 19:30:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Linda Hogan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122749-i-ve-been-good-at-this-world-the-one-that-hits]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been good at this world, the one that hits you when you are born and makes you cry right from the start, so that crying is your first language. I've learned what I was supposed to learn, bu now it comes to me that in doing so I've unlearned other things. I've lost my sense; I cannot sense things. Yes, we are a shambles. And maybe Ama found the way; she found it when all the paths were washed away by rivers from the sky, when all the buildings were blown down by the breath of a God. For just one day, that one day, she found a way out of that shambles, a way around it. And it's this I want to find. But now she has no path back, no way to return even if she wanted to be here in this America. She will always live away from this world, in something of a twilight that is not one thing or the other, one time or the next. She lives in a point, a small point, between two weighted things and it is always rocking this scale, back and forth." -- Linda Hogan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 12:07:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.

So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118818-i-still-think-it-s-important-for-people-to-have-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 13:42:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Bell Hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118818-i-still-think-it-s-important-for-people-to-have-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I still think it's important for people to have a sharp, ongoing critique of marriage in patriarchal society — because once you marry within a society that remains patriarchal, no matter how alternative you want to be within your unit, there is still a culture outside you that will impose many, many values on you whether you want them to or not. " -- Bell Hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1262-love-does-not-begin-and-end-the-way-we-seem</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 10:03:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by James A. Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1262-love-does-not-begin-and-end-the-way-we-seem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love does not begin and end the way we seem to think it does. Love is a battle, love is a war; love is a growing up." -- James A. Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24731-for-while-the-tale-of-how-we-suffer-and-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2010 21:58:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24731-for-while-the-tale-of-how-we-suffer-and-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For, while the tale of how we suffer, and how we are delighted, and how we may triumph is never new, it always must be heard. There isn't any other tale to tell, it's the only light we've got in all this darkness." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113300-what-keeps-you-going-isn-t-some-fine-destination-but-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 19:41:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113300-what-keeps-you-going-isn-t-some-fine-destination-but-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What keeps you going isn't some fine destination but just the road you're on, and the fact that you know how to drive. You keep your eyes open, you see this damned-to-hell world you got born into, and you ask yourself, 'What life can I live that will let me breathe in &amp; out and love somebody or something and not run off screaming into the woods?" -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78817-there-are-ways-in-journeys-to-the-center-of-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 00:28:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Linda Hogan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78817-there-are-ways-in-journeys-to-the-center-of-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are ways in, journeys to the center of life, through time; through air, matter, dream and thought. The ways are not always mapped or charted, but sometimes being lost, if there is such a thing, is the sweetest place to be. And always, in this search, a person might find that she is already there, at the center of the world. It may be a broken world, but it is glorious nonetheless." -- Linda Hogan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8706-life-will-break-you-nobody-can-protect-you-from-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 00:36:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8706-life-will-break-you-nobody-can-protect-you-from-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life will break you. Nobody can protect you from that, and living alone won't either, for solitude will also break you with its yearning. You have to love. You have to feel. It is the reason you are here on earth. You are here to risk your heart. You are here to be swallowed up. And when it happens that you are broken, or betrayed, or left, or hurt, or death brushes near, let yourself sit by an apple tree and listen to the apples falling all around you in heaps, wasting their sweetness. Tell yourself you tasted as many as you could." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28069-i-attempted-briefly-to-consecrate-myself-in-the-public-library</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 00:38:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28069-i-attempted-briefly-to-consecrate-myself-in-the-public-library]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I attempted briefly to consecrate myself in the public library, believing every crack in my soul could be chinked with a book." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152331-at-some-point-in-my-life-i-d-honestly-hoped-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 00:40:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152331-at-some-point-in-my-life-i-d-honestly-hoped-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At some point in my life I'd honestly hoped love would rescue me from the cold, drafty castle I lived in.  But at another point, much earlier I think, I'd quietly begun to hope for nothing at all in the way of love, so as not to be disappointed.  It works.  It gets to be a habit." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173799-as-long-as-i-kept-moving-my-grief-streamed-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 00:41:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173799-as-long-as-i-kept-moving-my-grief-streamed-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As long as I kept moving, my grief streamed out behind me like a swimmer's long hair in water.  I knew the weight was there but it didn't touch me.  Only when I stopped did the slick, dark stuff of it come floating around my face, catching my arms and throat till I began to drown.  So I just didn't stop." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7692-if-there-is-no-love-in-the-world-we-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 19:19:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7692-if-there-is-no-love-in-the-world-we-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there is no love in the world, we will make a new world, and we will give it walls, and we will furnish it with soft, red interiors, from the inside out, and give it a knocker that resonates like a diamond falling to a jeweller's felt so that we should never hear it. Love me, because love doesn't exist, and I have tried everything that does." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198815-i-want-you-always-to-remember-me-will-you-remember</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 19:27:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198815-i-want-you-always-to-remember-me-will-you-remember]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want you always to remember me. Will you remember that I existed, and that I stood next to you here like this?" -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120284-letters-are-just-pieces-of-paper-i-said-burn-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 19:27:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120284-letters-are-just-pieces-of-paper-i-said-burn-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Letters are just pieces of paper,&quot; I said. &quot;Burn them, and what stays in your heart will stay; keep them, and what vanishes will vanish." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293323-solidarity-is-not-a-matter-of-altruism-solidarity-comes-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 22:56:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Aurora Levins Morales]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293323-solidarity-is-not-a-matter-of-altruism-solidarity-comes-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Solidarity is not a matter of altruism. Solidarity comes from the inability to tolerate the affront to our own integrity of passive or active collaboration in the oppression of others, and from the deep recognition that, like it or not, our liberation is bound up with that of every other being on the planet, and that politically, spiritually, in our heart of hearts we know anything else is unaffordable. 
(Aurora Levins Morales, Medicine Stories: History, Culture and the Politics of Integrity)" -- Aurora Levins Morales]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188869-books-remember-all-the-things-you-cannot-contain</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 23:09:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[lyndsey add a quote by Elizabeth McCracken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188869-books-remember-all-the-things-you-cannot-contain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books remember all the things you cannot contain." -- Elizabeth McCracken]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
