<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/373260-k]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/373260-k" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2007 19:34:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5614-cold-hearted-elinor-oh-worse-than-cold-hearted-ashamed-of-being-otherwise---marianne</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2007 19:34:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5614-cold-hearted-elinor-oh-worse-than-cold-hearted-ashamed-of-being-otherwise---marianne]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cold-hearted Elinor!  Oh!  Worse than cold-hearted!  Ashamed of being otherwise.--Marianne Dashwood" -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5632-college-is-just-a-place-where-they-let-you-pay</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2007 19:57:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Chris Onstad]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5632-college-is-just-a-place-where-they-let-you-pay]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["College is just a place where they let you pay them to tell you things you should be getting paid to learn on the job.  TRUE.

Don't take that teat, baby.  That is a raw tittie.  College is a red raw areola, and instead of milk it releases highly acidic French dressing. --&quot;Ray's Place&quot; 1/6/04" -- Chris Onstad]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5736-boredom-speaks-the-language-of-time-and-it-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2007 12:45:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Joseph Brodsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5736-boredom-speaks-the-language-of-time-and-it-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...boredom speaks the language of time, and it is to teach you the most valuable lesson in your life--...the lesson of your utter insignificance.  It is valuable to you, as well as to those you are to rub shoulders with.  'You are finite,' time tells you in a voice of boredom, 'and whatever you do is, from my point of view, futile.'  As music to your ears, this, of course, may not count; yet the sense of futility, of limited significance even of your best, most ardent actions is better than the illusion of their consequence and the attendant self-satisfaction." -- Joseph Brodsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5737-year-followed-struggling-year-for-me-and-all-that-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2007 12:47:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Gene Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5737-year-followed-struggling-year-for-me-and-all-that-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Year followed struggling year for me, and all that time I read--I suppose few have ever read so.  I began, as most young people do, by reading the books I enjoyed.  But I found that narrowed my pleasure..." -- Gene Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8051-until-a-man-is-twenty-five-he-still-thinks-every-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 12:22:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8051-until-a-man-is-twenty-five-he-still-thinks-every-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until a man is twenty-five, he still thinks, every so often, that under the right circumstances he could be the baddest motherfucker in the world. If I moved to a martial-arts monastery in China and studied real hard for ten years. If my family was wiped out by Colombian drug dealers and I swore myself to revenge. If I got a fatal disease, had one year to live, and devoted it to wiping out street crime. If I just dropped out and devoted my life to being bad." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17624-it-s-like-this-sometimes-when-you-ve-a-very-long-street</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 08:56:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Michael Ende]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17624-it-s-like-this-sometimes-when-you-ve-a-very-long-street]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...it's like this. Sometimes, when you've a very long street ahead of you, you think how terribly long it is and feel sure you'll never get it swept. And then you start to hurry. You work faster and faster and every time you look up there seems to be just as much left to sweep as before, and you try even harder, and you panic, and in the end you're out of breath and have to stop--and still the street stretches away in front of you. That's not the way to do it.

You must never think of the whole street at once, understand? You must only concentrate on the next step, the next breath, the next stroke of the broom, and the next, and the next. Nothing else.

That way you enjoy your work, which is important, because then you make a good job of it. And that's how it ought to be.

And all at once, before you know it, you find you've swept the whole street clean, bit by bit. what's more, you aren't out of breath. That's important, too... (28-29)" -- Michael Ende]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18116-even-if-i-turned-myself-in-it-wouldn-t-change-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 10:45:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Austin Grossman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18116-even-if-i-turned-myself-in-it-wouldn-t-change-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even if I turned myself in, it wouldn't change anything. It wouldn't make me one of them. I knew that when I got my powers, but really I knew it before then. I learned it as a child on my first day of school, on the warm rainy streets of Bangkok, and in college. If you're different you always know it, and you can't fix it even if you want to. What do you do when you find out your heart is the wrong kind? You take what you're given, and be the hero you can be. Hero to your own cold, inverted heart." -- Austin Grossman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48630-if-heaven-had-granted-me-five-more-years-i-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 10:12:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Hokusai Katsushika]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48630-if-heaven-had-granted-me-five-more-years-i-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If heaven had granted me five more years, I could have become a real painter." -- Hokusai Katsushika]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48629-from-around-the-age-of-six-i-had-the-habit</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 10:15:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Hokusai]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48629-from-around-the-age-of-six-i-had-the-habit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From around the age of six, I had the habit of sketching from life. I became an artist, and from fifty on began producing works that won some reputation, but nothing I did before the age of seventy was worthy of attention. At seventy-three, I began to grasp the structures of birds and beasts, insects and fish, and of the way plants grow. If I go on trying, I will surely understand them still better by the time I am eighty-six, so that by ninety I will have penetrated to their essential nature. At one hundred, I may well have a positively divine understanding of them, while at one hundred and thirty, forty, or more I will have reached the stage where every dot and every stroke I paint will be alive. May Heaven, that grants long life, give me the chance to prove that this is no lie." -- Hokusai]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48631-seasoning-one-s-claims-with-self-irony-and-modesty-cultivating-a-tolerance</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 10:16:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Jane Bennett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48631-seasoning-one-s-claims-with-self-irony-and-modesty-cultivating-a-tolerance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Seasoning one’s claims with self-irony and modesty, cultivating a tolerance for moral ambiguity, periodically practicing normative reticence, building up a resistance to the pleasure of purity, minding your own business, doing what you can to forget to wreak vengeance, defending negative freedom even if there is no such thing, and playing around are the best you can do. But that’s quite a lot." -- Jane Bennett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48632-the-place-joanne-is-building-inside-herself-has-rooms-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 10:20:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Mary Gaitskill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48632-the-place-joanne-is-building-inside-herself-has-rooms-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The place Joanne is building inside [herself] has rooms for all of this. Not just rooms. Beautiful ones. For Karl and Jerry and Karen and Nate in his cowboy hat and the hot-tub guy and movie directors and old-lady healers and people trying to love their asses and people who think they're stupid for it. In these rooms, each thing that looks crazy or stupid will be like a drawing you give your mother, regarded with complete acceptance and put on the wall. Not because it is good but because it is trying to understand something. In these rooms, there will be understanding. In these rooms, each madness and stupidity will be unfolded from its knot and smoothed with loving hands until the true thing inside lies revealed." -- Mary Gaitskill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48634-all-his-longings-came-out-as-a-kind-of-disdain</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 10:21:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Alan Hollinghurst]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48634-all-his-longings-came-out-as-a-kind-of-disdain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...all his longings came out as a kind of disdain for what he longed for." -- Alan Hollinghurst]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48635-leave-the-problems-of-god-to-god-and-karma-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 10:23:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by James Clavell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48635-leave-the-problems-of-god-to-god-and-karma-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Leave the problems of God to God and karma to karma. Today you're here and nothing you do will change that. Today you are alive and here and honored and blessed with good fortune. Look at this suset, it's beautiful, neh? This sunset exists. Tomorrow does not exist. There is only now. Please look. It is so beautiful and it will never happen ever again, never, not this sunset, never in all infinity. Lose yourself in it, make yourself one with nature and do not worry about karma, yours, mine, or that of the village." -- James Clavell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48636-he-is-going-he-realizes-he-is-going-and-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 10:24:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48636-he-is-going-he-realizes-he-is-going-and-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He is going, he realizes.  He is going, and will not be coming back as Brad.  He must try at least to retain this feeling of pity. If he can, whoever he becomes will inherit this feeling, and be driven to act on it, and will not, as Brad now sees he has done, waste his life on accumulation, trivia, self-protection, and vanity." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62331-my-particular-dread--the-vivid-possibility-that-left-me-staring-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 10:51:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62331-my-particular-dread--the-vivid-possibility-that-left-me-staring-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My particular dread--the vivid possibility that left me staring at tree shadows on the bedroom ceiling night after night--was having to lie in a small tent, alone in an inky wilderness, listening to a foraging bear outside and wondering what its intentions were.  I was especially riveted by an amateur photograph in Herrero's book, taken late at night by a camper with a flash at a campground out West.  The photograph caught four black bears as they puzzled over a suspended food bag.  The bears were clearly startled but not remotely alarmed by the flash.  It was not the size or demeanor of the bears that troubled me--they looked almost comically nonaggressive, like four guys who had gotten a Frisbee caught up a tree--but their numbers.  Up to that moment it had not occurred to me that bears might prowl in parties.  What on earth would I do if &lt;i&gt;four&lt;/i&gt; bears came into my camp?  Why, I would die, of course.  Literally shit myself lifeless.  I would blow my sphincter out my backside like one of those unrolling paper streamers you get at children's parties--I daresay it would even give a merry toot--and bleed to a messy death in my sleeping bag." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46700-to-avoid-criticism-say-nothing-do-nothing-be-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2009 00:41:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Aristotle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46700-to-avoid-criticism-say-nothing-do-nothing-be-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To avoid criticism say nothing, do nothing, be nothing." -- Aristotle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124076-how-sweet-it-was-to-be-scolded-by-such-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 17:27:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Margo Lanagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124076-how-sweet-it-was-to-be-scolded-by-such-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How sweet it was to be scolded by such a tiny.  " -- Margo Lanagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124077-you-are-pure-hearted-branza-and-lovely-and-you-have-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 17:34:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Margo Lanagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124077-you-are-pure-hearted-branza-and-lovely-and-you-have-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are pure-hearted, Branza, and lovely, and you have never done a moment's wrong.  But you are a living creature, born to make a real life, however it cracks your heart.  However sweet that other place was, it was not real.  It was an artifact of your mam's imagination; it was a dream of hers and a desire; you could not have stayed there forever and called yourself alive.  Now you are in the true world, and a great deal more is required of you.  Here you must befriend real wolves, and lure real birds down from the sky.  Here you must endure real people around you, and we are not uniformly kind; we are damaged and impulsive, each in our own way.  It is harder.  It is not safe.  But it is what you were born to. (357)" -- Margo Lanagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146422-the-neurons-that-do-expire-are-the-ones-that-made</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 17:00:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Nicholson Baker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146422-the-neurons-that-do-expire-are-the-ones-that-made]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The neurons that do expire are the ones that made imitation possible.  When you are capable of skillful imitation, the sweep of choices before you is too large; but when your brain loses its spare capacity, and along with it some agility, some joy in winging it, and the ambition to do things that don't suit it, then you finally have to settle down to do well the few things that your brain really can do well--the rest no longer seems pressing and distracting, because it is now permanently out of reach.  The feeling that you are stupider than you were is what finally interests you in the really complex subjects of life: in change, in experience, in the ways other people have adjusted to disappointment and narrowed ability.  You realize that you are no prodigy, your shoulders relax, and you begin to look around you, seeing local color unrivaled by blue glows of algebra and abstraction." -- Nicholson Baker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148740-there-are-things-about-ourselves-that-we-need-to-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 06:28:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Benjamin Hoff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148740-there-are-things-about-ourselves-that-we-need-to-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are things about ourselves that we need to get rid of; there are things we need to change. But at the same time, we do not need to be too desperate, too ruthless, too combative. Along the way to usefulness and happiness, many of those things will change themselves, and the others can be worked on as we go. The first thing we need to do is recognize and trust our own Inner Nature, and not lose sight of it." -- Benjamin Hoff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162802-it-s-a-very-american-illness-the-idea-of-giving-yourself</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2009 13:23:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162802-it-s-a-very-american-illness-the-idea-of-giving-yourself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s a very American illness, the idea of giving yourself away entirely to the idea of working in order to achieve some sort of brass ring that usually involves people feeling some way about you – I mean, people wonder why we walk around feeling alienated and lonely and stressed out." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165928-i-have-lunch-flirt-with-some-local-grandmothers-undercut-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2009 16:59:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165928-i-have-lunch-flirt-with-some-local-grandmothers-undercut-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have lunch, flirt with some local grandmothers, undercut my flirting by crotching myself on the corner of a table as I leave. -- &quot;The Great Divider" -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165929-the-mind-is-a-machine-that-is-constantly-asking-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2009 17:04:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165929-the-mind-is-a-machine-that-is-constantly-asking-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The mind is a machine that is constantly asking: What would I prefer?  Close your eyes, refuse to move, and watch what your mind does.  What it does is become discontent with That Which Is.  A desire arises, you satisfy that desire, and another arises in its place.  This wanting and rewanting is an endless cycle for which, turns out, there is already a name: samsara.  Samsara is at the heart of the vast human carnival: greed, neurosis, mad ambition, adultery, crimes of passion, the hacking to death of a terrified man on a hillside in the name of A More Pure And Thus Perfect Nation--and all of this takes place because we believe we will be made happy once our desires have been satisfied.  

I know this.  But still I'm full of desire...  --&quot;Buddha Boy" -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165931-you-know-that-feeling-at-the-end-of-the-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2009 17:12:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165931-you-know-that-feeling-at-the-end-of-the-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know that feeling at the end of the day, when the anxiety of that-which-I-must-do falls away and, for maybe the first time that day, you see, with some clarity, the people you love and the ways you have, during that day, slightly ignored them, turned away from them to get back to what you were doing, blurted out some mildly hurtful thing, projected, instead of the deep love you really feel, a surge of defensiveness or self-protection or suspicion?  That moment when you think, Oh God, what have I done with this day?  And what am I doing with my life?  And how must I change to avoid catastrophic end-of-life regrets?

I feel like that now: tired of the Me I've always been, tired of making the same mistakes, repetitively stumbling after the same small ego strokes, being caught in the same loops of anxiety and defensiveness.  At the end of my life, I know I won't be wishing I'd held more back, been less effusive, more often stood on ceremony, forgiven less, spent more days oblivious to the secret wishes and fears of the people around me...  

--&quot;Buddha Boy" -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167224-she-sometimes-thought-she-was-going-crazy-her-first-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2009 07:52:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Sarah Addison Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167224-she-sometimes-thought-she-was-going-crazy-her-first-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She sometimes thought she was going crazy.  Her first thought when she woke up was always how to get him out of her thoughts.  And she would keep watch, hoping to see him next door, while plotting ways to never have to see him again.  " -- Sarah Addison Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177645-don-t-touch-me-you-fat-ghost</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 20:51:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Steve Toltz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177645-don-t-touch-me-you-fat-ghost]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't touch me, you fat ghost!" -- Steve Toltz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146917-sometimes-a-kind-of-glory-lights-up-the-mind-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 05:15:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146917-sometimes-a-kind-of-glory-lights-up-the-mind-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes a kind of glory lights up the mind of a man. It happens to nearly everyone. You can feel it growing or preparing like a fuse burning toward dynamite. It is a feeling in the stomach, a delight of the nerves, of the forearms. The skin tastes the air, and every deep-drawn breath is sweet. Its beginning has the pleasure of a great stretching yawn; it flashes in the brain and the whole world glows outside your eyes. A man may have lived all of his life in the gray, and the land and trees of him dark and somber. The events, even the important ones, may have trooped by faceless and pale. And then -the glory- so that a cricket song sweetens his ears, the smell of the earth rises chanting to his nose, and dappling light under a tree blesses his eyes. Then a man pours outward, a torrent of him, and yet he is not diminished. And I guess a man's importance in the world can be measured by the quality and number of his glories. It is a lonely thing but it relates us to the world. It is the mother of all creativeness, and it sets each man separate from all other men. " -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175715-time-interval-is-a-strange-and-contradictory-matter-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 05:16:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175715-time-interval-is-a-strange-and-contradictory-matter-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time interval is a strange and contradictory matter in the mind. It would be reasonable to suppose that a routine time or an eventless time would seem interminable. It should be so, but it is not. It is the dull eventless times that have no duration whatever. A time splashed with interest, wounded with tragedy, crevassed with joy - that's the time that seems long in the memory. And this is right when you think about it. Eventlessness has no posts to drape duration on. From nothing to nothing is no time at all." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193994-i-am-messaging-you-to-say-that-i-love-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 09:32:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by M.T. Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193994-i-am-messaging-you-to-say-that-i-love-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am messaging you to say that I love you, and that you're completely wrong about me thinking you're stupid. I always thought you could teach me things. I was always waiting. You're not like the others. You say things that no one expects you to. You think you're stupid. You want to be stupid. But you're someone people could learn from." -- M.T. Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136848-i-couldn-t-think-of-anything-other-than-her-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 12:43:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[K add a quote by Steve Toltz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136848-i-couldn-t-think-of-anything-other-than-her-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I couldn't think of anything other than her and the components of her. For example, her red hair. But was I so primitive I let myself be bewitched by hair? I mean, really. Hair! It's just hair! Everyone has it! She puts it up, she lets it down. So what? And why did all the other parts of her have me wheezing with delight? I mean, who hasn't got a back, or a belly, or armpits? This whole finicky obsession serves to humiliate me even as I write it, sure, but I suppose it isn't that abnormal. That's what first love is all about. What happens is you meet a love object and immediately a hole inside you starts aching, the hole that is always there but you don't notice until someone comes along, plugs it up, and then runs away with the plug." -- Steve Toltz]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
