<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/373527-emily]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/373527-emily" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 10:23:17 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40559-oh-to-be-a-pear-tree-any-tree-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 10:23:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40559-oh-to-be-a-pear-tree-any-tree-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh to be a pear tree – any tree in bloom! With kissing bees singing of the beginning of the world!" -- Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120273-we-owe-it-to-each-other-to-tell-stories</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 10:23:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120273-we-owe-it-to-each-other-to-tell-stories]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We owe it to each other to tell stories." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97215-if-i-am-going-to-spend-eternity-visiting-this-moment</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 10:23:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97215-if-i-am-going-to-spend-eternity-visiting-this-moment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I am going to spend eternity visiting this moment and that, I'm grateful that so many of those moments are nice." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14748-to-understand-just-one-life-you-have-to-swallow-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2009 07:49:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14748-to-understand-just-one-life-you-have-to-swallow-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To understand just one life you have to swallow the world ... do you wonder, then, that I was a heavy child?" -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13945-a-poet-s-work-to-name-the-unnamable</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2009 07:49:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13945-a-poet-s-work-to-name-the-unnamable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A poet's work . . . to name the unnamable, to point at frauds, to take sides, start arguments, shape the world and stop it from going to sleep." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194625-i-remember-when-people-used-to-think-i-was-smart</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 15:13:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194625-i-remember-when-people-used-to-think-i-was-smart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I remember when people used to think I was smart.
I remember when people used to think my brain was useful.
Damaged by water, sure. And ready to seizure at any moment. But still useful, and maybe even a little bit beautiful and sacred and magical." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34201-the-world-even-the-smallest-parts-of-it-is-filled</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 15:14:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34201-the-world-even-the-smallest-parts-of-it-is-filled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world, even the smallest parts of it, is filled with things you don't know." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159730-you-read-a-book-for-the-story-for-each-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 15:14:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159730-you-read-a-book-for-the-story-for-each-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You read a book for the story, for each of its words,&quot; Gordy said, &quot;and you draw your cartoons for the story, for each of the words and images. And, yeah, you need to take that seriously, but you should also read and draw because really good books and cartoons give you a boner.&quot;

I was shocked:

&quot;Did you just say books should give me a boner?&quot;

&quot;Yes, I did.&quot;

&quot;Are you serious?&quot;

&quot;Yeah... don't you get excited about books?&quot;

&quot;I don't think that you're supposed to get THAT excited about books.&quot;

&quot;You should get a boner! You have to get a boner!&quot; Gordy shouted. &quot;Come on!&quot;

We ran into the Reardan High School Library.

&quot;Look at all these books,&quot; he said.

&quot;There aren't that many,&quot; I said. It was a small library in a small high school in a small town.

&quot;There are three thousand four hundred and twelve books here,&quot; Gordy said. &quot;I know that because I counted them.&quot;

&quot;Okay, now you're officially a freak,&quot; I said.

&quot;Yes, it's a small library. It's a tiny one. But if you read one of these books a day, it would still take you almost ten years to finish.&quot;

&quot;What's your point?&quot;

&quot;The world, even the smallest parts of it, is filled with things you don't know.&quot;

Wow. That was a huge idea.

Any town, even one as small as Reardan, was a place of mystery. And that meant Wellpinit, the smaller, Indian town, was also a place of mystery.

&quot;Okay, so it's like each of these books is a mystery. Every book is a mystery. And if you read all of the books ever written, it's like you've read one giant mystery. And no matter how much you learn, you keep on learning so much more you need to learn.&quot;

&quot;Yes, yes, yes, yes,&quot; Gordy said. &quot;Now doesn't that give you a boner?&quot;

&quot;I am rock hard,&quot; I said." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104081-life-is-a-constant-struggle-between-being-an-individual-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 15:15:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104081-life-is-a-constant-struggle-between-being-an-individual-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is a constant struggle between being an individual and being a member of the community." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30279-if-you-re-good-at-it-and-you-love-it-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 15:15:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30279-if-you-re-good-at-it-and-you-love-it-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're good at it, and you love it, and it helps you navigate the river of the world, then it can't be wrong." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111111-if-you-let-people-into-your-life-a-little-bit</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 15:15:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111111-if-you-let-people-into-your-life-a-little-bit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you let people into your life a little bit, they can be pretty damn amazing." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123639-do-you-understand-how-amazing-it-is-to-hear-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 15:16:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123639-do-you-understand-how-amazing-it-is-to-hear-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you understand how amazing it is to hear that from an adult?  Do you know how amazing it is to hear that from anybody?  It's one of the simplest sentences in the world, just four words, but they're the four hugest words in the world when they're put together.

You can do it." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172549-that-s-right-i-am-a-book-kisser</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 15:16:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172549-that-s-right-i-am-a-book-kisser]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's right, I am a book kisser." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71305-i-draw-because-words-are-too-unpredictable-i-draw-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 15:16:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71305-i-draw-because-words-are-too-unpredictable-i-draw-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I draw because words are too unpredictable.
I draw because words are too limited.
If you speak and write in English, or Spanish, or Chinese, or any other language, then only a certain percentage of human beings will get your meaning.
But when you draw a picture everybody can understand it. 
If I draw a cartoon of a flower, then every man, woman, and child in the world can look at it and say, &quot;That's a flower." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111373-i-think-the-world-is-a-series-of-broken-dams</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 15:17:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111373-i-think-the-world-is-a-series-of-broken-dams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think the world is a series of broken dams and floods, and my cartoons are tiny little lifeboats." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143261-but-something-magical-happened-to-me-when-i-went-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 15:18:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143261-but-something-magical-happened-to-me-when-i-went-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But something magical happened to me when I went to Reardan.

Overnight I became a good player.

I suppose it had something to do with confidence.  I mean, I'd always been the lowest Indian on the reservation totem pole - I wasn't expected to be good so I wasn't.  But in Reardan, my coach and the other players wanted me to be good.  They needed me to be good.  They expected me to be good.  And so I became good.

I wanted to live up to the expectations.

I guess that's what it comes down to.

The power of expectations.

And as they expected more of me, I expected more of myself, and it just grew and grew." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174387-i-hated-the-mountains-and-the-hills-the-rivers-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 07:41:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Jean Rhys]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174387-i-hated-the-mountains-and-the-hills-the-rivers-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hated the mountains and the hills, the rivers and the rain. I hated the sunsets of whatever colour, I hated its beauty and its magic and the secret I would never know. I hated its indifference and the cruelty which was part of its loveliness. Above all I hated her. For she belonged to the magic and the loveliness. She had left me thirsty and all my life would be thirst and longing for what I had lost before I found it." -- Jean Rhys]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2816-by-the-pricking-of-my-thumbs-something-wicked-this-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 07:41:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2816-by-the-pricking-of-my-thumbs-something-wicked-this-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By the pricking of my thumbs, 
Something wicked this way comes." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31808-the-letter-said-that-they-were-two-feet-high-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 12:38:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31808-the-letter-said-that-they-were-two-feet-high-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The letter said that they were two feet high, and green., and shaped like plumber's friends. Their suction cups were on the ground, and their shafts, which were extremely flexible, usually pointed to the sky. At the top of each shaft was a little hand with a green eye in its palm. The creatures were friendly, and they could see in four dimensions. They pitied Earthlings for being able to see only three. They had many wonderful things to teach Earthlings, especially about time. Billy promised to tell what some of those wonderful things were in his next letter.
Billy was working on his second letter when the first letter was published. The second letter started out like this:
The most important thing I learned on Tralfamadore was that when a person dies he only appears to die. He is still very much alive in the past, so it is very silly for people to cry at his funeral. All moments, past, present and future, always have existed, always will exist. The Tralfamadorians can look at all the different moments just that way we can look at a stretch of the Rocky Mountains, for instance. They can see how permanent all the moments are, and they can look at any moment that interests them. It is just an illusion we have here on Earth that one moment follows another one, like beads on a string, and that once a moment is gone it is gone forever.
When a Tralfamadorian sees a corpse, all he thinks is that the dead person is in a bad condition in that particular moment, but that the same person is just fine in plenty of other moments. Now, when I myself hear that somebody is dead, I simply shrug and say what the Tralfamadorians say about dead people, which is &quot;so it goes." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3872-i-am-a-tralfamadorian-seeing-all-time-as-you-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 12:38:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3872-i-am-a-tralfamadorian-seeing-all-time-as-you-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am a Tralfamadorian, seeing all time as you might see a stretch of the Rocky Mountains. All time is all time. It does not change. It does not lend itself to warnings or explanations. It simply is." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39866-he-ate-a-pear-it-was-a-hard-one-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 10:22:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39866-he-ate-a-pear-it-was-a-hard-one-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He ate a pear. It was a hard one. It fought back against his grinding teeth. It snapped in juicy protest." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
