<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/373589-lindsay-stares]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/373589-lindsay-stares" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 06:58:21 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13907-reputation-is-what-other-people-know-about-you-honor-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 06:58:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13907-reputation-is-what-other-people-know-about-you-honor-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reputation is what other people know about you. Honor is what you know about yourself." -- Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94681-some-prices-are-just-too-high-no-matter-how-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 06:59:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94681-some-prices-are-just-too-high-no-matter-how-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some prices are just too high, no matter how much you may want the prize. The one thing you can't trade for your heart's desire is your heart." -- Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126650-when-you-choose-an-action-you-choose-the-consequences-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 06:59:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126650-when-you-choose-an-action-you-choose-the-consequences-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you choose an action, you choose the consequences of that action. When you desire a consequence you had damned well better take the action that would create it." -- Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/343106-this-is-important-but-you-have-to-stay-absolutely-cool</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 07:01:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/343106-this-is-important-but-you-have-to-stay-absolutely-cool]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is important! But you have to stay absolutely cool. I may be completely off-base, and panicking prematurely.&quot;
&quot;I don't think so. I think you're panicking post-maturely. In fact, if you were panicking any later it would be practically posthumously. I've been panicking for days." -- Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408309-i-know-girls-who-pine-for-it-they-like-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 07:02:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408309-i-know-girls-who-pine-for-it-they-like-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know girls who pine for it. They like to play dress-up and pretend being Vor ladies of old, rescued from menace by romantic Vor youths. For some reason they never play 'dying in childbirth', or 'vomiting your guts out from the red dysentery', or 'weaving till you go blind and crippled from arthritis and dye poisoning', or 'infanticide'. Well, they do die romantically of disease sometimes, but somehow it's always an illness that makes you interestingly pale and everyone sorry and doesn't involve losing bowel control." -- Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395127-you-don-t-pay-back-your-parents-you-can-t-the-debt</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 07:03:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395127-you-don-t-pay-back-your-parents-you-can-t-the-debt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't pay back your parents.  You can't.  The debt you owe them gets collected by your children, who hand it down in turn.  It's a sort of entailment.  Or if you don't have children of the body, it's left as a debt to your common humanity.  Or to your God, if you possess or are possessed by one.

The family economy evades calculation in the gross planetary product.  It's the only deal I know where, when you give more than you get, you aren't bankrupted - but rather, vastly enriched." -- Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/444304-i-do-think-half-of-what-we-call-madness-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 07:03:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/444304-i-do-think-half-of-what-we-call-madness-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do think, half of what we call madness is just some poor slob dealing with pain by a strategy that annoys the people around him." -- Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352162-lakewalker-legends-say-the-gods-abandoned-the-world-when-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 07:03:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352162-lakewalker-legends-say-the-gods-abandoned-the-world-when-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lakewalker legends say the gods abandoned the world when the first malice came. And that they will return when the earth is entirely cleansed of its spawn. If you believe in gods.&quot;

&quot;Do you?&quot;

&quot;I believe they are not here, yes. It's a faith of sorts." -- Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346096-now-there-s-this-about-cynicism-sergeant-it-s-the-universe-s-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 07:04:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346096-now-there-s-this-about-cynicism-sergeant-it-s-the-universe-s-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now, there's this about cynicism, Sergeant. It's the universe's most supine moral position. Real comfortable. If nothing can be done, then you're not some kind of shit for not doing it, and you can lie there and stink to yourself in perfect peace." -- Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39985-in-everything-that-can-be-called-art-there-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 13:10:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Raymond Chandler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39985-in-everything-that-can-be-called-art-there-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In everything that can be called art there is a quality of redemption. It may be pure tragedy, if it is high tragedy, and it may be pity and irony, and it may be the raucous laughter of the strong man. But down these mean streets a man must go who is not himself mean, who is neither tarnished nor afraid.

The detective in this kind of story must be such a man. He is the hero; he is everything. He must be a complete man and a common man and yet an unusual man. He must be, to use a rather weathered phrase, a man of honor -- by instinct, by inevitability, without thought of it, and certainly without saying it. He must be the best man in his world and a good enough man for any world. I do not care much about his private life; he is neither a eunuch nor a satyr; I think he might seduce a duchess and I am quite sure he would not spoil a virgin; if he is a man of honor in one thing, he is that in all things.

He is a relatively poor man, or he would not be a detective at all. He is a common man or he could not go among common people. He has a sense of character, or he would not know his job. He will take no man's money dishonestly and no man's insolence without due and dispassionate revenge. He is a lonely man and his pride is that you will treat  him as a proud man or be very sorry you ever saw him. He talks as the man of his age talks -- that is, with rude wit, a lively sense of the grotesque, a disgust for sham, and a contempt for pettiness.

The story is the man's adventure in search of a hidden truth, and it would be no adventure if it did not happen to a man fit for adventure. He has a range of awareness that startles you, but it belongs to him by right, because it belongs to the world he lives in. If there  were enough like him, the world would be a very safe place to live in, without becoming too dull to be worth living in.  " -- Raymond Chandler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559426-the-realistic-style-is-easy-to-abuse-from-haste-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 13:19:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Raymond Chandler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559426-the-realistic-style-is-easy-to-abuse-from-haste-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The realistic style is easy to abuse: from haste, from lack of awareness, from inability to bridge the chasm that lies between what a writer would like to be able to say and what he actually knows how to say. It is easy to fake; brutality is not strength, flipness is not wit, edge-of-the-chair writing can be as boring as flat writing; dalliance with promiscuous blondes can be very dull stuff when described by goaty young men with no other purpose in mind than to describe dalliance with promiscuous blondes." -- Raymond Chandler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51633-but-you-know-as-well-as-i-patriotism-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 13:42:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51633-but-you-know-as-well-as-i-patriotism-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But you know as well as I, patriotism is a word; and one that generally comes to mean either &lt;i&gt;my country, right or wrong&lt;/i&gt;, which is infamous, or &lt;i&gt;my country is always right&lt;/i&gt;, which is imbecile." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
