<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/374325-caroline]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/374325-caroline" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 18:00:11 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/954701-on-the-other-side-of-that-big-ass-mirror-a-video</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 18:00:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caroline add a quote by Clinton Boomer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/954701-on-the-other-side-of-that-big-ass-mirror-a-video]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the other side of that big-ass mirror, a video camera was watching us. In about ten seconds, it was going to start spitting static at itself, and everything it saw was going to break up into a fuzzy, gray-white wash, rolling up and down, that wouldn’t be admissible as evidence on Judge Judy. Those missing frames would last a little less than a quarter of a minute, consolidate themselves back
into a semblance of reality, and then I would theoretically go walking right back out of here.

Between now and that moment, there stretched an infinite ocean of potential
time. Time enough to walk around the world. Time enough to fall in love, get
married on a white beach under purple stars, write a book of poems about
truest passion, have a few good and bloody screaming matches, get divorced in a court of autumn elves and gypsy moths, then set the ink-stained, tear-streaked pages of your text ablaze." -- Clinton Boomer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/954702-stupid-dire-warnings-of-imminent-doom-they-always-put-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 18:01:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caroline add a quote by Clinton Boomer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/954702-stupid-dire-warnings-of-imminent-doom-they-always-put-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stupid dire warnings of imminent doom.

They always put me in a bad mood." -- Clinton Boomer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/954704-magic-like-photoshop-can-do-just-about-anything-but-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 18:02:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caroline add a quote by Clinton Boomer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/954704-magic-like-photoshop-can-do-just-about-anything-but-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Magic, like Photoshop, can do just about anything... but you have to learn how to use it." -- Clinton Boomer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66591-all-right-said-susan-i-m-not-stupid-you-re-saying-humans</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 21:41:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caroline add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66591-all-right-said-susan-i-m-not-stupid-you-re-saying-humans]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All right,&quot; said Susan. &quot;I'm not stupid. You're saying humans need... &lt;i&gt;fantasies&lt;/i&gt; to make life bearable.&quot;

REALLY? AS IF IT WAS SOME KIND OF PINK PILL? NO. HUMANS NEED FANTASY TO BE HUMAN. TO BE THE PLACE WHERE THE FALLING ANGEL MEETS THE RISING APE.

&quot;Tooth fairies? Hogfathers? Little—&quot;

YES. AS PRACTICE. YOU HAVE TO START OUT LEARNING TO BELIEVE THE &lt;i&gt;LITTLE&lt;/i&gt; LIES.

&quot;So we can believe the big ones?&quot;

YES. JUSTICE. MERCY. DUTY. THAT SORT OF THING.

&quot;They're not the same at all!&quot;

YOU THINK SO? THEN TAKE THE UNIVERSE AND GRIND IT DOWN TO THE FINEST POWDER AND SIEVE IT THROUGH THE FINEST SIEVE AND THEN &lt;i&gt;SHOW&lt;/i&gt; ME ONE ATOM OF JUSTICE, ONE MOLECULE OF MERCY. AND YET—Death waved a hand. AND YET YOU ACT AS IF THERE IS SOME IDEAL ORDER IN THE WORLD, AS IF THERE IS SOME...SOME &lt;i&gt;RIGHTNESS&lt;/i&gt; IN THE UNIVERSE BY WHICH IT MAY BE JUDGED.

&quot;Yes, but people have &lt;i&gt;got&lt;/i&gt; to believe that, or what's the &lt;i&gt;point&lt;/i&gt;—&quot;

MY POINT EXACTLY." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
