<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/3748-kalilah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/3748-kalilah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 20:01:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153549-until-one-is-committed-there-is-hesitancy-the-chance-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 20:01:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by William Hutchison Murray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153549-until-one-is-committed-there-is-hesitancy-the-chance-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until one is committed, there is hesitancy, the chance to draw back, always ineffectiveness. Concerning all acts of initiative (and creation), there is one elementary truth, the ignorance of which kills countless ideas and splendid plans: that the moment one definitely commits one-self, then providence moves too. All sorts of things occur to help one that would never otherwise have occurred. A whole stream of events issues from the decision, raising in one's favor all manner of unforeseen incidents and meetings and material assistance, which no man could have dreamed would have come his way. Whatever you can do or dream you can, begin it. Boldness has genius, power and magic in it. Begin it now." -- William Hutchison Murray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 17:24:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't interest me what you do for a living. I want to know what you ache for, and if you dare to dream of meeting your heart's longing.
It doesn't interest me how old you are. I want to know if you will risk looking like a fool for love, for your dream, for the adventure of being alive. 
It doesn't interest me what planets are squaring your moon. I want to know if you have touched the center of your own sorrow, if you have been opened by life's betrayals or have become shriveled and closed from fear of further pain!I want to know if you can sit with pain, mine or your own, without moving to hide it or fade it, or fix it. 
I want to know if you can be with joy, mine or your own, if you can dance with wildness and let the ecstasy fill you to the tips of your fingers and toes without cautioning us to be careful, to be realistic, to remember the limitations of being human. 
It doesn't interest me if the story you are telling me is true. I want to know if you can disappoint another to be true to yourself; if you can bear the accusation of betrayal and not betray your own soul; if you can be faithlessand therefore trustworthy. 
I want to know if you can see beauty even when it's not pretty, every day,and if you can source your own life from its presence. 
I want to know if you can live with failure, yours and mine, and still stand on the edge of the lake and shout to the silver of the full moon, “Yes!”
It doesn't interest me to know where you live or how much money you have. I want to know if you can get up, after the night of grief and despair, weary and bruised to the bone, and do what needs to be done to feed the children. 
It doesn't interest me who you know or how you came to be here. I want to know if you will stand in the center of the fire with me and not shrink back. 
It doesn't interest me where or what or with whom you have studied. I want to know what sustains you, from the inside, when all else falls away. 
I want to know if you can be alone with yourself and if you truly like the company you keep in the empty moments." -- Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131573-it-was-like-something-you-have-dreaded-and-feared-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 17:30:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131573-it-was-like-something-you-have-dreaded-and-feared-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was like something you have dreaded and feared and dodged for years until it seemed like all your life, then despite everything it happened to you and all it was was just pain, all it did was hurt and so it was all over, all finished, all right." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131575-the-television-image-sanctified-conferred-identity-the-more-familiar-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 17:33:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by P.D. James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131575-the-television-image-sanctified-conferred-identity-the-more-familiar-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The television image sanctified, conferred identity. The more familiar the face, the more to be trusted. " -- P.D. James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131576-time-didn-t-heal-but-it-anesthetized-the-human-mind-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 17:34:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by P.D. James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131576-time-didn-t-heal-but-it-anesthetized-the-human-mind-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time didn't heal, but it anesthetized. The human mind could only feel so much." -- P.D. James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131578-absolute-nakedness-was-intrusive-confusing-to-the-senses-paradoxically-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 17:37:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by P.D. James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131578-absolute-nakedness-was-intrusive-confusing-to-the-senses-paradoxically-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Absolute nakedness was intrusive, confusing to the senses. Paradoxically, it both revealed and diminished identity." -- P.D. James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131580-people-were-excited-by-violence-what-after-all-was-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 17:38:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by P.D. James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131580-people-were-excited-by-violence-what-after-all-was-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People were excited by violence. What, after all, was the sexual act but a voluntarily endured assault, a momentary death?" -- P.D. James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131581-american-love-like-coke-in-green-glass-bottles-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 17:41:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131581-american-love-like-coke-in-green-glass-bottles-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["American love — like coke in green glass bottles...they don't make it anymore." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131583-you-don-t-dare-think-whole-even-to-yourself-the-entirety</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 17:45:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131583-you-don-t-dare-think-whole-even-to-yourself-the-entirety]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't dare think whole even to yourself the entirety of a dear hope or wish let alone a desperate one else you yourself have doomed it." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131584-what-sets-a-man-writhing-sleepless-in-bed-at-night</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 17:47:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131584-what-sets-a-man-writhing-sleepless-in-bed-at-night]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What sets a man writhing sleepless in bed at night is not having injured his fellow so much as having been wrong; the mere injury he can efface by destroying the victim and the witness but the mistake is his and that is one of his cats which he always prefers to choke to death with butter." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131585-we-shall-not-kill-and-maybe-next-time-we-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 17:48:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131585-we-shall-not-kill-and-maybe-next-time-we-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We shall not kill and maybe next time we even won't." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131588-a-man-or-a-race-either-if-he-s-any-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 17:51:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131588-a-man-or-a-race-either-if-he-s-any-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man or a race either if he's any good can survive his past without even needing to escape from it and not because of the high quite often only too rhetorical rhetoric of humanity but for the simple indubitable practical reason of his future: that capacity to survive and absorb and endure and still be steadfast." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131851-it-is-possible-to-cause-seemingly-biochemical-changes-through-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 14:47:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Steve Lopez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131851-it-is-possible-to-cause-seemingly-biochemical-changes-through-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is possible to cause seemingly biochemical changes through human emotional involvement. You literally have changed his chemistry by being his friend." -- Steve Lopez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131855-it-s-more-interesting-to-be-out-in-the-world-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 14:48:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Steve Lopez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131855-it-s-more-interesting-to-be-out-in-the-world-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's more interesting to be out in the world. than to see it reflected in the mirror." -- Steve Lopez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146533-the-american-really-loves-nothing-but-his-automobile-not-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 00:51:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146533-the-american-really-loves-nothing-but-his-automobile-not-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The American really loves nothing but his automobile: not his wife his child nor his country nor even his bank-account first (in fact he doesn't really love that bank-account nearly as much as foreigners like to think because he will spend almost any or all of it for almost anything provided it is valueless enough) but his motor-car. Because the automobile has become our national sex symbol. We cannot really enjoy anything unless we can go up an alley for it. Yet our whole background and raising and training forbids the sub rosa and surreptitious. So we have to divorce our wife today in order to remove from our mistress the odium of mistress in order to divorce our wife tomorrow in order to remove from our mistress and so on. As a result of which the American woman has become cold and and undersexed; she has projected her libido on to the automobile not only because its glitter and gadgets and mobility pander to her vanity and incapacity (because of the dress decreed upon her by the national retailers association) to walk but because it will not maul her and tousle her, get her all sweaty and disarranged. So in order to capture and master anything at all of her anymore the American man has got to make that car his own. Which is why let him live in a rented rathole though he must he will not only own one but renew it each year in pristine virginity, lending it to no one, letting no other hand ever know the last secret forever chaste forever wanton intimacy of its pedals and levers, having nowhere to go in it himself and even if he did he would not go where scratch or blemish might deface it, spending all Sunday morning washing and polishing and waxing it because in doing that he is caressing the body of the woman who has long since now denied him her bed." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153685-let-me-tell-you-about-love-that-silly-word-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2009 18:06:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153685-let-me-tell-you-about-love-that-silly-word-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me tell you about love, that silly word you believe is about whether you like somebody or whether somebody likes you or whether you can put up with somebody in order to get something or someplace you want or you believe it has to do with how your body responds to another body like robins or bison or maybe you believe love is how forces or nature or luck is benign to you in particular not maiming or killing you but if so doing it for your own good. Love is none of that. There is nothing in nature like it. Not in robins or bison or in the banging tails of your hunting dogs and not in blossoms or suckling foal. Love is divine only and difficult always. If you think it is easy you are a fool. If you think it is natural you are blind. It is a learned application without reason or motive except that it is God. You do not deserve love regardless of the suffering you have endured. You do not deserve love because somebody did you wrong. You do not deserve love just because you want it. You can only earn - by practice and careful contemplations - the right to express it and you have to learn how to accept it. Which is to say you have to earn God. You have to practice God. You have to think God-carefully. And if you are a good and diligent student you may secure the right to show love. Love is not a gift. It is a diploma. A diploma conferring certain privileges: the privilege of expressing love and the privilege of receiving it. How do you know you have graduated? You don't. What you do know is that you are human and therefore educable, and therefore capable of learning how to learn, and therefore interesting to God, who is interested only in Himself which is to say He is interested only in love. Do you understand me? God is not interested in you. He is interested in love and the bliss it brings to those who understand and share the interest. Couples that enter the sacrament of marriage and are not prepared to go the distance or are not willing to get right with the real love of God cannot thrive. They may cleave together like robins or gulls or anything else that mates for life. But if they eschew this mighty course, at the moment when all are judged for the disposition of their eternal lives, their cleaving won't mean a thing. God bless the pure and holy. Amen." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1519-i-believe-that-imagination-is-stronger-than-knowledge-that-myth</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 05:48:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1519-i-believe-that-imagination-is-stronger-than-knowledge-that-myth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that imagination is stronger than knowledge. That myth is more potent than history. That dreams are more powerful than facts. That hope always triumphs over experience. That laughter is the only cure for grief. And I believe that love is stronger than death." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1508-a-thing-is-not-necessarily-true-because-a-man-dies</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 05:50:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1508-a-thing-is-not-necessarily-true-because-a-man-dies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A thing is not necessarily true because a man dies for it." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1668-there-is-neither-happiness-nor-misery-in-the-world-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 05:50:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1668-there-is-neither-happiness-nor-misery-in-the-world-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is neither happiness nor misery in the world; there is only the comparison of one state with another, nothing more. He who has felt the deepest grief is best able to experience supreme happiness. We must have felt what it is to die, Morrel, that we may appreciate the enjoyments of life. 
&quot; Live, then, and be happy, beloved children of my heart, and never forget, that until the day God will deign to reveal the future to man, all human wisdom is contained in these two words, 'Wait and Hope." -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 05:54:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13155-it-is-a-curious-thing-the-death-of-a-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 05:55:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13155-it-is-a-curious-thing-the-death-of-a-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a curious thing, the death of a loved one. We all know that our time in this world is limited, and that eventually all of us will end up underneath some sheet, never to wake up. And yet it is always a surprise when it happens to someone we know. It is like walking up the stairs to your bedroom in the dark, and thinking there is one more stair than there is. Your foot falls down, through the air, and there is a sickly moment of dark surprise as you try and readjust the way you thought of things." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161547-he-could-climb-to-it-if-he-climbed-alone-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2009 10:23:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161547-he-could-climb-to-it-if-he-climbed-alone-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["he could climb to it, if he climbed alone, and once there he could suck on the pap of life, gulp down the incomparable milk of wonder.  
...He knew that when he kissed this girl, and forever wed his unutterable visions to her perishable breath, his mind would never romp again like the mind of God." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51783-a-man-breaking-his-journey-between-one-place-and-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2009 16:26:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51783-a-man-breaking-his-journey-between-one-place-and-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man breaking his journey between one place and another at a third place of no name, character, population or significance, sees a unicorn cross his path and disappear. That in itself is startling, but there are precedents for mystical encounters of various kinds, or to be less extreme, a choice of persuasions to put it down to fancy; until--&quot;My God,&quot; says a second man, &quot;I must be dreaming, I thought I saw a unicorn.&quot; At which point, a dimension is added that makes the experience as alarming as it will ever be. A third witness, you understand, adds no further dimension but only spreads it thinner, and a fourth thinner still, and the more witnesses there are the thinner it gets and the more reasonable it becomes until it is as thin as reality, the name we give to the common experience... &quot;Look, look!&quot; recites the crowd. &quot;A horse with an arrow in its forehead! It must have been mistaken for a deer." -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167059-wheels-have-been-set-in-motion-and-they-have-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2009 16:31:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167059-wheels-have-been-set-in-motion-and-they-have-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wheels have been set in motion, and they have their own pace, to which we are...condemned. Each move is dictated by the previous one - that is the meaning of order. If we start being arbitrary it'll just be a shambles: at least, let us hope so. Because if we happened, just happened to discover, or even suspect, that our spontaneity was part of their order, we'd know that we were lost. A Chinaman of the T'ang Dynasty - and, by which definition, a philosopher - dreamed he was a butterfly, and from that moment he was never quite sure that he was not a butterfly dreaming it was a Chinese philosopher. Envy him; his two-fold security. " -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167061-there-we-were---demented-children-mincing-about-in-clothes</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2009 16:36:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167061-there-we-were---demented-children-mincing-about-in-clothes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There we were - demented children mincing about in clothes that no one ever wore, speaking as no man ever spoke, swearing love in wigs and rhymed couplets, killing each other with wooden swords, hollow protestations of faith hurled after empty promises of vengeance - and every gesture, every pose, vanishing into the thin unpopulated air. We ransomed our dignity to the clouds, and the uncomprehending birds listened. Don't you see?! We're actors - we're the opposite of people!" -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54-don-t-walk-behind-me-i-may-not-lead-don-t-walk</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2009 15:15:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54-don-t-walk-behind-me-i-may-not-lead-don-t-walk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't walk behind me; I may not lead. Don't walk in front of me; I may not follow. Just walk beside me and be my friend." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182139-he-had-been-bored-that-s-all-bored-like-most-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2009 15:18:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182139-he-had-been-bored-that-s-all-bored-like-most-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He had been bored, that's all, bored like most people. Hence he had made himself out of whole cloth a life full of complications and drama. Something must happen - and that explains most human commitments. Something must happen, even loveless slavery, even war or death. Hurray then for funerals!" -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182140-the-truth-is-that-every-intelligent-man-as-you-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2009 15:19:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182140-the-truth-is-that-every-intelligent-man-as-you-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is that every intelligent man, as you know, dreams of being a gangster and of ruling over society by force alone. As it is not so easy as the detective novels might lead one to believe, one generally relies on politics and joins the cruelest party.What does it matter, after all, if by humiliating one's mind one succeeds in dominating every one? I discovered in myself sweet dreams of oppression." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14471-many-people-need-desperately-to-receive-this-message-i-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2009 15:28:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14471-many-people-need-desperately-to-receive-this-message-i-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many people need desperately to receive this message: 'I feel and think much as you do, care about many of the things you care about, although most people do not care about them. You are not alone." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182146-books-were-devices-as-crassly-practical-for-storing-or-transmitting</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2009 15:30:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kalilah add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182146-books-were-devices-as-crassly-practical-for-storing-or-transmitting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Books] were devices as crassly practical for storing or transmitting language, as the latest Silicon Valley miracles. But by accident, not by cunning calculation, books, because of their weight and texture, and because of their sweetly token resistance to manipulation, involve our hands and eyes, and then our mind and souls, in a spiritual adventure." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
