<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/377104-kim]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/377104-kim" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 06:54:03 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28266-words-are-pale-shadows-of-forgotten-names-as-names-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 06:54:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28266-words-are-pale-shadows-of-forgotten-names-as-names-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Words are pale shadows of forgotten names. As names have power, words have power. Words can light fires in the minds of men. Words can wring tears from the hardest hearts." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156661-perhaps-the-greatest-faculty-our-minds-possess-is-the-ability</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 06:55:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156661-perhaps-the-greatest-faculty-our-minds-possess-is-the-ability]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps the greatest faculty our minds possess is the ability to cope with pain. Classic thinking teaches us of the four doors of the mind, which everyone moves through according to their need.

First is the door of sleep. Sleep offers us a retreat from the world and all its pain. Sleep marks passing time, giving us distance from the things that have hurt us. When a person is wounded they will often fall unconscious. Similarly, someone who hears traumatic news will often swoon or faint. This is the mind's way of protecting itself from pain by stepping through the first door.

Second is the door of forgetting. Some wounds are too deep to heal, or too deep to heal quickly. In addition, many memories are simply painful, and there is no healing to be done. The saying 'time heals all wounds' is false. Time heals most wounds. The rest are hidden behind this door.

Third is the door of madness. There are times when the mind is dealt such a blow it hides itself in insanity. While this may not seem beneficial, it is. There are times when reality is nothing but pain, and to escape that pain the mind must leave reality behind. 

Last is the door of death. The final resort. Nothing can hurt us after we are dead, or so we have been told." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/351709-it-s-the-questions-we-can-t-answer-that-teach-us-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 06:55:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/351709-it-s-the-questions-we-can-t-answer-that-teach-us-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's the questions we can't answer that teach us the most. They teach us how to think. If you give a man an answer, all he gains is a little fact. But give him a question and he'll look for his own answers." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350254-it-had-flaws-but-what-does-that-matter-when-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 06:56:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350254-it-had-flaws-but-what-does-that-matter-when-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It had flaws, but what does that matter when it comes to matters of the heart? We love what we love. Reason does not enter into it. In many ways, unwise love is the truest love. Anyone can love a thing &lt;i&gt;because&lt;/i&gt;. That's as easy as putting a penny in your pocket. But to love something &lt;i&gt;despite&lt;/i&gt;. To know the flaws and love them too. That is rare and pure and perfect." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
