<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/379761-steve]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/379761-steve" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 10:05:23 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176664-the-end-of-man-is-knowledge-but-there-is-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 10:05:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176664-the-end-of-man-is-knowledge-but-there-is-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The end of man is knowledge, but there is one thing he can't know. He can't know whether knowledge will save him or kill him. He will be killed, all right, but he can't know whether he is killed because of the knowledge which he has got or because of the knowledge which he hasn't got and which if he had it, would save him." -- Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52428-we-get-very-few-of-he-true-images-in-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 10:06:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52428-we-get-very-few-of-he-true-images-in-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We get very few of he true images in our heads of the kind I am talking about, the kind which become more and more vivid for us as if the passage of the years did not obscure their reality but, year by year, drew off another veil to expose a meaning which we had only dimly surmised at first. Very probably the last veil will not be removed, for there are not enough years, but the brightness of the image increases and our conviction increases that the brightness is meaning, or the legend of meaning, and without the image our lives would be nothing except an old piece of film rolled on a spool and thrown into a desk drawer of unanswered letters." -- Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728397-for-me-this-is-exactly-what-s-so-pernicious-about-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 19:37:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728397-for-me-this-is-exactly-what-s-so-pernicious-about-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For me, this is exactly what's so pernicious about the morality of debt: the way that financial imperatives constantly try to reduce us all, despite ourselves, to the equivalent of pillagers, eyeing the world simply for what can be turned into money -- and then tell us that it's only those who are willing to see the world as pillagers who deserve access to the resources required to pursue anything in life &lt;i&gt;other&lt;/i&gt; than money." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
