<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/380936-nesnesnes]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/380936-nesnesnes" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 11:41:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64506-the-heaviest-of-burdens-crushes-us-we-sink-beneath-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 11:41:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64506-the-heaviest-of-burdens-crushes-us-we-sink-beneath-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The heaviest of burdens crushes us, we sink beneath it, it pins us to the ground. But in love poetry of every age, the woman longs to be weighed down by the man's body.The heaviest of burdens is therefore simultaneously an image of life's most intense fulfillment. The heavier the burden, the closer our lives come to the earth, the more real and truthful they become. Conversely, the absolute absence of burden causes man to be lighter than air, to soar into heights, take leave of the earth and his earthly being, and become only half real, his movements as free as they are insignificant. What then shall we choose? Weight or lightness?" -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/535467-books-can-be-immensely-powerful-the-ideas-in-them-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 04:12:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by John Farndon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/535467-books-can-be-immensely-powerful-the-ideas-in-them-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books can be immensely powerful. The ideas in them can change the way people think. Yet it was the Nazis and Stalin's officers who committed terrible crimes, and not Mein Kampf or the Communist Manifesto - and of course, the Manifesto contained many key ideas that are still relevant and important today, long after Stalin has gone. There is a crucial distinction between the book and its effect - it's crucial because if you talk about a book being harmful rather than its effect you begin to legitimise censorship. Abhorrent ideas need to be challenged by better ones, not banned." -- John Farndon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/540361-perhaps-i-love-you-perhaps-i-love-you-very-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 11:28:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/540361-perhaps-i-love-you-perhaps-i-love-you-very-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps I love you. Perhaps I love you very much. But probably just for this reason it would be better if we remain as we are. I think a man and a woman love each other all the more when they don't live together and when they know about each other only that they exist, and when they are grateful to each other for the fact that they exist and that they know they exist. And that alone is enough for their happiness." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533337-flux-n-the-natural-state-our-moods-change-our-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 10:22:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by David Levithan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533337-flux-n-the-natural-state-our-moods-change-our-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;b&gt;flux&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;i&gt;n&lt;/i&gt;.

The natural state. Our moods change. Our lives change. Our feelings for each other change. Our bearings change. The song changes. The air changes. The temperature of the shower changes.
Accept this. We must accept this." -- David Levithan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/441764-wenn-ein-kind-lesen-gelernt-hat-und-gerne-liest-entdeckt</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2012 12:54:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by Erich Kästner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/441764-wenn-ein-kind-lesen-gelernt-hat-und-gerne-liest-entdeckt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wenn ein Kind lesen gelernt hat und gerne liest, entdeckt und erobert es eine zweite Welt, das Reich der Buchstaben. Das Land des Lesens ist ein geheimnisvoller, unendlicher Erdteil. Aus Druckerschwärze entstehen Dinge, Menschen, Geister und Götter, die man sonst nicht sehen könnte. Wer noch nicht lesen kann, sieht nur, was greifbar vor seiner Nase liegt oder steht (...) Wer lesen kann, sitzt über einem Buch und erblickt mit einem Male den Kilimandscharo oder Karl den Großen oder Huckleberry Finn im Gebüsch oder Zeus als Stier, und auf seinem Rücken reitet die schöne Europa. Wer lesen kann, hat ein zweites Paar Augen, und er muss nur aufpassen, dass er sich dabei das erste Paar nicht verdirbt." -- Erich Kästner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/549830-dresden-war-eine-wunderbare-stadt-voller-kunst-und-geschichte-und</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 09:31:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by Erich Kästner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/549830-dresden-war-eine-wunderbare-stadt-voller-kunst-und-geschichte-und]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dresden war eine wunderbare Stadt, voller Kunst und Geschichte und trotzdem kein von sechshundertfünfzigtausend Dresdnern zufällig bewohntes Museum. Die Vergangenheit und die Gegenwart lebten miteinander im Einklang. Eigentlich müßte es heißen: im Zweiklang. Und mit der Landschaft zusammen, mit der Elbe, den Brücken, den Hügelhängen, den Wäldern und mit den Gebirgen am Horizont, ergab sich sogar ein Dreiklang. Geschichte, Kunst und Natur schwebten über Stadt und Tal, vorn Meißner Dom bis zum Großsedlitzer Schloßpark, wie ein von seiner eignen Harmonie bezauberter Akkord." -- Erich Kästner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54797-he-was-still-too-young-to-know-that-the-heart-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 15:37:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54797-he-was-still-too-young-to-know-that-the-heart-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was still too young to know that the heart's memory eliminates the bad and magnifies the good, and that thanks to this artifice we manage to endure the burden of the past." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/592558-niemand-w-rde-glauben-wie-sch-n-prag-in-der-nacht-ist</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 23:10:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by Jan Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/592558-niemand-w-rde-glauben-wie-sch-n-prag-in-der-nacht-ist]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Niemand würde glauben, wie schön Prag in der Nacht ist, im Glanz des Mondes. Die Menschen schlummern, die Steine sind lebendig geworden, auch in die Standbilder auf der Karlsbrücke kommt Leben. Der Hradčin, schon am Tage majestätisch erhaben, ist bei Nacht noch erhabener. Umflort von der Farbe der Finsternis, erhebt er sich hoch in den endlosen Himmel, und sein Turm, steil aufragend, reicht bis an die funkelnden Sterne. Die Moldau rauscht hymnisch, über ihrem Tal steht der Mond, der sich so manchmal von dem herrlichen Anblick nicht trennen kann; er schaut und schaut, bis ihn die eifersüchtige Sonne verscheucht." -- Jan Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/602795-l-hat-mir-einmal-aber-das-ist-lange-her-gesagt</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 17:08:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by David Wagner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/602795-l-hat-mir-einmal-aber-das-ist-lange-her-gesagt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["L. hat mir einmal, aber das ist lange her, gesagt, wenn Küsse eine Farbe hätten, müssten sie die Farbe von Himbeeren haben. Sie meinte auch, dass es Erdbeerküsse gebe und solche, die nach Himbeeren schmeckten. Ich konnte darauf nur erwidern, dass jeder Kuss auf ihren Lippen ein klein wenig anders schmecke, aber das sei bei den wilden Himbeeren, die man im Wald pflücke, ja auch so. Und ich fügte hinzu, dass im Mund jede Himbeere die Erinnerung an den Geschmack der davor auslösche, und genauso lasse jeder ihrer Küsse den vorhergehenden vergessen. Küsse aber, denke ich jetzt, lassen sich nicht einfrieren, das unterscheidet sie von Himbeeren." -- David Wagner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/695574-on-the-job-people-feel-skillful-and-challenged-and-therefore</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 10:09:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/695574-on-the-job-people-feel-skillful-and-challenged-and-therefore]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the job people feel skillful and challenged, and therefore feel more happy, strong, creative, and satisfied. In their free time people feel that there is generally not much to do and their skills are not being used, and therefore they tend to feel more sad, weak, dull, and dissatisfied. Yet they would like to work less and spend more time in leisure.

What does this contradictory pattern mean? There are several possible explanations, but one conclusion seems inevitable: when it comes to work, people do not heed the evidence of their senses. They disregard the quality of immediate experience, and base their motivation instead on the strongly rooted cultural stereotype of what work is supposed to be like. They think of it as an imposition, a constraint, an infringement of their freedom, and therefore something to be avoided as much as possible." -- Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111772-there-s-a-reason-we-refer-to-leaps-of-faith--</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 10:35:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111772-there-s-a-reason-we-refer-to-leaps-of-faith--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's a reason we refer to &quot;leaps of faith&quot; - because the decision to consent to any notion of divinity is a mighty jump from the rational over to the unknowable, and I don't care how diligently scholars of every religion will try to sit you down with their stacks of books and prove to you through scripture that their faith is indeed rational; it isn't.  If faith were rational, it wouldn't be - by definition - faith.  Faith is belief in what you cannot see or prove or touch.  Faith is walking face-first and full-speed into the dark.  If we truly knew all the answers in advance as to the meaning of life and the nature of God and the destiny of our souls, our belief would not be a leap of faith and it would not be a courageous act of humanity; it would just be... a prudent insurance policy." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/697770-contrary-to-what-we-usually-believe-moments-like-these-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 02:31:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/697770-contrary-to-what-we-usually-believe-moments-like-these-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Contrary to what we usually believe, moments like these, the best moments in our lives, are not the passive, receptive, relaxing times—although such experiences can also be enjoyable, if we have worked hard to attain them. The best moments usually occur when a person’s body or mind is stretched to its limits in a voluntary effort to accomplish something difficult and worthwhile. Optimal experience is thus something that we
make happen. For a child, it could be placing with trembling fingers the last blockon a tower she has built, higher than any she has built so far; for a swimmer, it could be trying to beat his own record; for a violinist, mastering an intricate musical passage. For each person there are thousands of opportunities, challenges to expand ourselves." -- Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487195-what-a-slut-time-is-she-screws-everybody</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 12:33:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487195-what-a-slut-time-is-she-screws-everybody]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a slut time is. She screws everybody." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/807795-du-kannst-nicht-viel-von-deiner-mutter-lernen-aber-das</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 03:18:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by Wolfgang Herrndorf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/807795-du-kannst-nicht-viel-von-deiner-mutter-lernen-aber-das]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Du kannst nicht viel von deiner Mutter lernen. Aber das kannst du von deiner Mutter lernen. Erstens, man kann über alles reden. Und zweitens, was die Leute denken, ist scheißegal." -- Wolfgang Herrndorf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1396-isn-t-it-enough-to-see-that-a-garden-is-beautiful</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2013 10:50:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1396-isn-t-it-enough-to-see-that-a-garden-is-beautiful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't it enough to see that a garden is beautiful without having to believe that there are fairies at the bottom of it too?" -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16160-but-who-can-say-what-s-best-that-s-why-you-need</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 12:55:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16160-but-who-can-say-what-s-best-that-s-why-you-need]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But who can say what's best? That's why you need to grab whatever chance you have of happiness where you find it, and not worry about other people too much. My experience tells me that we get no more than two or three such chances in a life time, and if we let them go, we regret it for the rest of our lives." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/975017-im-nachhinein-ist-jedes-leben-gegl-ckt</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 09:00:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by Thomas Hürlimann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/975017-im-nachhinein-ist-jedes-leben-gegl-ckt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Im Nachhinein ist jedes Leben geglückt." -- Thomas Hürlimann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1021830-it-is-a-place-that-grows-upon-you-every-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 12:12:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1021830-it-is-a-place-that-grows-upon-you-every-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a place that 'grows upon you' every day. There seems to be always something to find out in it. There are the most extraordinary alleys and by-ways to walk about in. You can lose your way (what a comfort that is, when you are idle!) twenty times a day, if you like; and turn up again, under the most unexpected and surprising difficulties. It abounds in the strangest contrasts; things that are picturesque, ugly, mean, magnificent, delightful, and offensive, break upon the view at every turn." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1120608-happiness-we-re-tearing-our-hair-out-to-try-to-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 15:39:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by François Lelord]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1120608-happiness-we-re-tearing-our-hair-out-to-try-to-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness. We're tearing our hair out to try to find a definition of it, for heaven's sake. Is it joy? People will tell you that it isn't, that joy is a fleeting emotion, a moment of happiness, which is always welcome, mind you. And then what about pleasure, huh? Oh, yes, that's easy, everybody knows what that is, but there again it doesn't last. But is happiness not the sum total of lots of small joys and pleasures, huh?" -- François Lelord]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189740-they-agreed-that-it-was-neither-possible-nor-necessary-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2014 23:51:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nesnesnes add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189740-they-agreed-that-it-was-neither-possible-nor-necessary-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[They] agreed that it was neither possible nor necessary to educate people who never questioned anything." -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
