<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/381029-lisa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/381029-lisa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 19:05:18 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 19:05:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 19:06:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that everything happens for a reason. People change so that you can learn to let go, things go wrong so that you appreciate them when they're right, you believe lies so you eventually learn to trust no one but yourself, and sometimes good things fall apart so better things can fall together." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2351-though-much-is-taken-much-abides-and-though-we-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 19:06:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2351-though-much-is-taken-much-abides-and-though-we-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Though much is taken, much abides; and though
We are not now that strength which in old days
Moved earth and heaven, that which we are, we are;
One equal temper of heroic hearts,
Made weak by time and fate, but strong in will
To strive, to seek, to find, and not to yield." -- Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59743-the-lights-begin-to-twinkle-from-the-rocks-the-long</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 19:06:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Alfred, Lord Tennyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59743-the-lights-begin-to-twinkle-from-the-rocks-the-long]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The lights begin to twinkle from the rocks;
The long day wanes; the slow moon climbs; the deep
Moans round with many voices. Come, my friends.
'T is not too late to seek a newer world.
Push off, and sitting well in order smite
The sounding furrows; for my purpose holds
To sail beyond the sunset, and the baths
Of all the western stars, until I die.
It may be that the gulfs will wash us down;
It may be we shall touch the Happy Isles,
And see the great Achilles, whom we knew.
Tho' much is taken, much abides; and tho'
We are not now that strength which in old days
Moved earth and heaven, that which we are, we are,--
One equal temper of heroic hearts,
Made weak by time and fate, but strong in will
To strive, to seek, to find, and not to yield." -- Alfred, Lord Tennyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230027-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 19:07:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230027-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look again at that dot. That's here. That's home. That's us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every &quot;superstar,&quot; every &quot;supreme leader,&quot; every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there-on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam.

The Earth is a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena.  Think of the endless cruelties visited by the inhabitants of one corner of this pixel on the scarcely distinguishable inhabitants of some other corner, how frequent their misunderstandings, how eager they are to kill one another, how fervent their hatreds.  Think of the rivers of blood spilled by all those generals and emperors so that, in glory and triumph, they could become the momentary masters of a fraction of a dot.

Our posturings, our imagined self-importance, the delusion that we have some privileged position in the Universe, are challenged by this point of pale light. Our planet is a lonely speck in the great enveloping cosmic dark. In our obscurity, in all this vastness, there is no hint that help will come from elsewhere to save us from ourselves.

The Earth is the only world known so far to harbor life. There is nowhere else, at least in the near future, to which our species could migrate. Visit, yes. Settle, not yet.  Like it or not, for the moment the Earth is where we make our stand.

It has been said that astronomy is a humbling and character-building experience. There is perhaps no better demonstration of the folly of human conceits than this distant image of our tiny world. To me, it underscores our responsibility to deal more kindly with one another, and to preserve and cherish the pale blue dot, the only home we've ever known." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8385-in-science-it-often-happens-that-scientists-say-you-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 19:08:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8385-in-science-it-often-happens-that-scientists-say-you-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In science it often happens that scientists say, 'You know that's a really good argument; my position is mistaken,' and then they would actually change their minds and you never hear that old view from them again. They really do it. It doesn't happen as often as it should, because scientists are human and change is sometimes painful. But it happens every day. I cannot recall the last time something like that happened in politics or religion." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38963-the-earth-is-a-very-small-stage-in-a-vast</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 19:21:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38963-the-earth-is-a-very-small-stage-in-a-vast]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The earth is a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena. Think of the rivers of blood spilled by all those generals and emperors so that in glory and in triumph they could become the momentary masters of a fraction of a dot. Think of the endless cruelties visited by the inhabitants of one corner of the dot on scarcely distinguishable inhabitants of some other corner of the dot. How frequent their misunderstandings, how eager they are to kill one another, how fervent their hatreds. Our posturings, our imagined self-importance, the delusion that we have some privileged position in the universe, are challenged by this point of pale light. Our planet is a lonely speck in the great enveloping cosmic dark. In our obscurity -- in all this vastness -- there is no hint that help will come from elsewhere to save us from ourselves. It is up to us. It's been said that astronomy is a humbling, and I might add, a character-building experience. To my mind, there is perhaps no better demonstration of the folly of human conceits than this distant image of our tiny world. To me, it underscores our responsibility to deal more kindly and compassionately with one another and to preserve and cherish that pale blue dot, the only home we've ever known." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27993-author-frederick-douglass-18943-taught-that-literacy-is-the-path-from-slavery</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 19:21:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27993-author-frederick-douglass-18943-taught-that-literacy-is-the-path-from-slavery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[author:Frederick Douglass|18943] taught that literacy is the path from slavery to freedom. There are many kinds of slavery and many kinds of freedom, but reading is still the path." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/660430-knowing-how-to-think-empowers-you-far-beyond-those-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 19:21:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Neil deGrasse Tyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/660430-knowing-how-to-think-empowers-you-far-beyond-those-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Knowing how to think empowers you far beyond those who know only what to think." -- Neil deGrasse Tyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
