<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/381380-brandon]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/381380-brandon" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 03:54:25 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 03:54:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't see things as they are, we see them as we are." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140964-the-right-thinks-that-the-breakdown-of-the-family-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 03:54:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by John D. Caputo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140964-the-right-thinks-that-the-breakdown-of-the-family-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Right thinks that the breakdown of the family is the source of crime and poverty, and this they very insightfully blame on the homosexuals, which would be amusing were it not so tragic.  Families and 'family values' are crushed by grinding poverty, which also makes violent crime and drugs attractive alternatives to desperate young men and sends young women into prostitution.  Family values are no less corrupted by the corrosive effects of individualism, consumerism, and the accumulation of wealth.  Instead of shouting this from the mountain tops, the get-me-to-heaven-and-the-rest-be-damned Christianity the Christian Right preaches is itself a version of selfish spiritual capitalism aimed at netting major and eternal dividends, and it fits hand in glove with American materialism and greed." -- John D. Caputo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140966-whether-new-protestant-church-movements-place-their-emphasis-on-new</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 03:54:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Michael Frost &amp; Alan Hirsch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140966-whether-new-protestant-church-movements-place-their-emphasis-on-new]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whether [new Protestant church movements] place their emphasis on new worship styles, expressions of the Holy Spirit’s power, evangelism to seekers, or Bible teaching, these so-called new movements still operate out of the fallacious assumption that the church belongs firmly in the town square, that is, at the heart of Western culture.  And if they begin with this mistaken belief about their position in Western society, all their church planting, all their reproduction will simply mirror this misapprehension." -- Michael Frost &amp; Alan Hirsch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141464-orthodoxy-is-idolatry-if-it-means-holding-the-correct-opinions</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 03:54:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by John D. Caputo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141464-orthodoxy-is-idolatry-if-it-means-holding-the-correct-opinions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Orthodoxy is idolatry if it means holding the 'correct opinions about God' - 'fundamentalism' is the most extreme and salient example of such idolatry - but not if it means holding faith in the right way, that is, not holding it at all but being held by God, in love and service.  Theology is idolatry if it means what we say about God instead of letting ourselves be addressed by what God has to say to us.  Faith is idolatrous if it is rigidly self-certain but not if it is softened in the waters of 'doubt." -- John D. Caputo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141466-what-was-true-of-an-ancient-community-of-christian-believers</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 03:54:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Brian J. Walsh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141466-what-was-true-of-an-ancient-community-of-christian-believers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What was true of an ancient community of Christian believers struggling with a powerful and appealing philosophy is also true for Christians in a postmodern context.  Arguments that deconstruct the regimes of truth at work in the late modern culture of global capitalism are indispensable.  So also is a deeper understanding of the counterideological force of the biblical tradition.  But such arguments are no guarantee that the biblical metanarrative will not be co-opted for ideological purposes of violent exclusion, nor do arguments prove the truth of the gospel.  Only the nonideological, embracing, forgiving and shalom-filled life of a dynamic Christian community formed by the story of Jesus will prove the gospel to be true and render the idolatrous alternatives fundamentally implausible." -- Brian J. Walsh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141470-a-corollary-of-this-has-been-that-christians-have-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 03:54:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Steve Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141470-a-corollary-of-this-has-been-that-christians-have-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A corollary of this has been that Christians have thought that they should only create art with a Pollyanna quality to it: paintings of birds and kittens, movies that extol family life and end happily, songs that are positive and uplifting – in short, works of art that show a world that is almost unfallen where no one experiences conflict and where sin is naughty rather than wicked." -- Steve Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141471-the-arts-can-sharpen-the-vision-quicken-the-intellect-preserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 03:54:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Steve Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141471-the-arts-can-sharpen-the-vision-quicken-the-intellect-preserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The arts can sharpen the vision, quicken the intellect, preserve the memory, activate the conscience, enhance the understanding and refresh the language." -- Steve Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198-i-am-so-clever-that-sometimes-i-don-t-understand-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 03:54:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198-i-am-so-clever-that-sometimes-i-don-t-understand-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am so clever that sometimes I don't understand a single word of what I am saying." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 03:53:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298-a-day-without-sunshine-is-like-you-know-night</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 03:53:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298-a-day-without-sunshine-is-like-you-know-night]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A day without sunshine is like, you know, night." -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 03:53:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25-we-are-all-in-the-gutter-but-some-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 03:53:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25-we-are-all-in-the-gutter-but-some-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all in the gutter, but some of us are looking at the stars." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3356-i-like-nonsense-it-wakes-up-the-brain-cells-fantasy</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 03:53:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3356-i-like-nonsense-it-wakes-up-the-brain-cells-fantasy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like nonsense, it wakes up the brain cells. Fantasy is a necessary ingredient in living." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 15:39:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363-it-is-better-to-remain-silent-at-the-risk-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 15:40:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Maurice Switzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363-it-is-better-to-remain-silent-at-the-risk-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to remain silent at the risk of being thought a fool, than to talk and remove all doubt of it." -- Maurice Switzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145661-it-may-actually-be-more-healthy-to-be-disturbed-confused</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 18:26:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Mark Scandrette]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145661-it-may-actually-be-more-healthy-to-be-disturbed-confused]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It may actually be more healthy to be disturbed, confused, or searching than confident, certain, and secure." -- Mark Scandrette]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145664-at-the-tattoo-parlor-my-friend-worked-with-needle-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 18:32:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Mark Scandrette]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145664-at-the-tattoo-parlor-my-friend-worked-with-needle-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the tattoo parlor, my friend worked with needle and ink applying a design to the skin on his client's back, as the three of us sat discussing our spiritual desires and ambivalence about religion.  In the midst of our conversation, the man under the needle turned and said, 'Jesus is cool, it's just that they have f***ed with Jesus.  I mean, Christianity was at its best when it was secret and hidden and you could die for it.'  This profound, if crass, statement recognizes that the power of the gospel lay in its ability to be a counter-cultural and revolutionary force - not only a story to believe, but a distinctive way of life.  The man's comment prompted me to consider the questions:  Am I in some measure complicit in the domestication of Jesus?" -- Mark Scandrette]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145666-i-believe-we-are-more-ready-to-embrace-our-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 18:36:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Mark Scandrette]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145666-i-believe-we-are-more-ready-to-embrace-our-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe we are more ready to embrace our lives in the here and now when we are able to recognize the continuity between the immanence of God in our world and eternity.  Rather than simply waiting to be liberated to another time or place, we are being invited to collaborate in the healing and redemption of our world." -- Mark Scandrette]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150404-for-better-of-for-worse-the-church-in-the-west</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 20:56:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Tim Keel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150404-for-better-of-for-worse-the-church-in-the-west]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For better of for worse the church in the West bought modernity's claims.  We were baptized in its story (even though it said it did not have one) and accepted its categories and definitions.  But somewhere along the way we also began to believe that the ways in which we accessed knowledge about God or Jesus or the Spirit or Christianity were those things themselves." -- Tim Keel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150406-i-realized-with-a-growing-and-startling</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 21:00:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Tim Keel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150406-i-realized-with-a-growing-and-startling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[". . . I realized with a growing and startling sense of clarity that the seminary was educating and training me for a world that no longer existed.  Moreover, the posture of this particular brand of Christianity toward the surrounding culture was one of enormous suspicion and at times hostility.  It seemed that part of this evolving designation involved a posture of entrenchment and argument toward culture.  But I loved culture.  I loved the freedom to engage with people for the purpose of friendship and dialogue, not simply evangelism." -- Tim Keel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150407-we-live-in-a-culture-of-reductionism-or-better-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 21:07:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Tim Keel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150407-we-live-in-a-culture-of-reductionism-or-better-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We live in a culture of reductionism.  Or better, we are living in the aftermath of a culture of reductionism, and I believe we have reduced the complexity and diversity of the Scriptures to systematic theologies that insist on ideological conformity, even when such conformity flattens the diversity of the Scriptural witness.  We have reduced our conception of gospel to four simple steps that short-circuit biblical narratives and notions of the kingdom of God on earth as it is in heaven in favor of a simplified means of entrance to heaven.  Our preaching is often wed to our materialistic, consumerist cultural assumptions, and sermons are subsequently reduced to delivering messages that reinforce the worst of what American culture produces: self-centered end users who believe that God is a resource that helps an individual secure what amounts to an anemic and culturally bound understanding of the 'abundant life." -- Tim Keel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150409-the-loss-of-connection-between-churches-and-neighborhoods-creates-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 21:21:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Tim Keel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150409-the-loss-of-connection-between-churches-and-neighborhoods-creates-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The loss of connection between churches and neighborhoods creates a corresponding loss of localized imagination and creates an addictive-like dependence on &lt;i&gt;a&lt;/i&gt;contextual experts who scan the physical and spiritual horizon for 'success." -- Tim Keel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150923-further-in-the-modern-story-reality-is-that-which-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2009 22:35:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Tim Keel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150923-further-in-the-modern-story-reality-is-that-which-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Further, in the modern story, reality is that which is observable, measurable, and repeatable - the kinds of phenomena available, accessible, and verifiable to the five senses.  Thus, reality comes to equal the scientific method.  It should come as no surprise that in such a world the life of the spirit is ignored or marginalized (as well as a great many other nonmaterial things.)  This view of life subsequently birthed in human beings a ravenous materialism as matters of the soul were ignored or reinterpreted within this tightly controlled version of reality.  When the life of the spirit is ignored, people will seek to feed the hunger of a neglected soul with the only nourishment  available: in our context, the consumptive acquisition of material goods." -- Tim Keel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150925-if-we-submit-everything-to-reason-our-religion-will-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2009 22:39:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Blaise Pascal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150925-if-we-submit-everything-to-reason-our-religion-will-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we submit everything to reason our religion will be left with nothing mysterious or supernatural.  If we offend the principles of reason our religion will be absurd and ridiculous . . . There are two equally dangerous extremes: to exclude reason, to admit nothing but reason." -- Blaise Pascal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41662-a-true-revolution-of-values-will-soon-cause-us-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2009 22:40:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41662-a-true-revolution-of-values-will-soon-cause-us-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A true revolution of values will soon cause us to question the fairness and justice of many of our past and present policies. ... A true revolution of values will soon look uneasily on the glaring contrast of poverty and wealth. With righteous indignation, it will look across the seas and see individual capitalists of the West investing huge sums of money in Asia, Africa, and South America, only to take the profits out with no concern for the social betterment of the countries, and say, &quot;This is not just.&quot; It will look at our alliance with the landed gentry of South America and say, &quot;This is not just.&quot; The Western arrogance of feeling that it has everything to teach others and nothing to learn from them is not just." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151759-in-post-christendom-the-church-is-that-community-of-people-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2009 17:19:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Tim Keel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151759-in-post-christendom-the-church-is-that-community-of-people-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In post-Christendom, the church is that community of people who look to discover what God is actively doing in the world around them and then join themselves to that work.  The church is that community of people gathered around Jesus Christ in order to participate in his life and incarnate it into the context where he has placed them." -- Tim Keel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151993-we-imagine-that-our-theological-conceptual-systems-are-the-means-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 17:14:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Tim Keel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151993-we-imagine-that-our-theological-conceptual-systems-are-the-means-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We imagine that our theological/conceptual systems are the means by which we know God as God is.  I truly believe that such postures and perspectives put us in danger of conceptual idolatry, worshiping our ideas of and frameworks for God." -- Tim Keel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156904-jesus-s-use-of-the-phrasing-a-new-commandment-is-frequently</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 17:28:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Carl Raschke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156904-jesus-s-use-of-the-phrasing-a-new-commandment-is-frequently]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jesus’s use of the phrasing “a new commandment” is frequently scanted in light of its implicit ramifications.  Because Jesus at the Last Supper has executed the “new covenant” with his disciples, the Great Commandment itself now acquires an unprecedented meaning.  Its new meaning belongs to this sudden revelation not merely about who God is but also about what love is.  Previously the Great Commandment bade us to love God and our neighbor.  Now this love can be comprehended only in an incarnational situation.  Its incarnate presence is the activation of profound rhizomic relations that explode from the center toward the ends of the earth.  We are commanded to be incarnational in relation to one another just as God at the cross was incarnational in Christ. . . . We are no longer simply Christ’s “followers&quot; - the pre-Easter form of relation to a master-and-teacher that is conventionally called “disciple” - but also perpetual Christ incarnators . . ." -- Carl Raschke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2009 13:08:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212715-the-latin-words-humus-soil-earth-and-homo-human-being-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2009 14:06:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon add a quote by Eugene Peterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212715-the-latin-words-humus-soil-earth-and-homo-human-being-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Latin words &lt;i&gt;humus&lt;/i&gt;, soil/earth, and &lt;i&gt;homo&lt;/i&gt;, human being, have a common derivation, from which we also get our word 'humble.'  This is the Genesis origin of who we are: dust - dust that the Lord God used to make us a human being.  If we cultivate a lively sense of our origin and nurture a sense of continuity with it, who knows, we may also acquire humility." -- Eugene Peterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
