<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/382392-beverly]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/382392-beverly" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2012 09:20:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141645-heard-joke-once-man-goes-to-doctor-says-he-s-depressed</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2012 09:20:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141645-heard-joke-once-man-goes-to-doctor-says-he-s-depressed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Heard joke once: Man goes to doctor. Says he's depressed. Says life seems harsh and cruel. Says he feels all alone in a threatening world where what lies ahead is vague and uncertain. Doctor says, &quot;Treatment is simple. Great clown Pagliacci is in town tonight. Go and see him. That should pick you up.&quot; Man bursts into tears. Says, &quot;But doctor...I am Pagliacci." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169577---nothing-else-has-any-efficacy-i-might-as-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2009 09:34:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Junot Diaz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169577---nothing-else-has-any-efficacy-i-might-as-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["- Nothing else has any efficacy, I might as well be myself.
- But your yourself sucks!
- It is, lamentably, all I have." -- Junot Diaz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/546183-independent-women-must-expect-more-of-themselves-since-neither-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2012 10:46:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by A.S. Byatt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/546183-independent-women-must-expect-more-of-themselves-since-neither-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Independent women must expect more of themselves, since neither men nor other more conventionally domesticated women will hope for anything, or expect any result other than utter failure." -- A.S. Byatt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 08:46:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always imagined that Paradise will be a kind of library." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399629-we-need-to-make-books-cool-again-if-you-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 12:15:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by John Waters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399629-we-need-to-make-books-cool-again-if-you-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We need to make books cool again. If you go home with somebody and they don't have books, don't fuck them." -- John Waters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153144-so-many-vows-they-make-you-swear-and-swear-defend</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 08:55:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153144-so-many-vows-they-make-you-swear-and-swear-defend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many vows... they make you swear and swear. Defend the king. Obey the king. Keep his secrets. Do his bidding. Your life for his. But obey your father. Love your sister. Protect the innocent. Defend the weak. Respect the gods. Obey the laws. It’s too much. No matter what you do, you’re forsaking one vow or the other." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53062-nothing-more-exhilarating-than-saving-yourself-by-the-simple</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 07:17:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Junot Díaz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53062-nothing-more-exhilarating-than-saving-yourself-by-the-simple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing more exhilarating ... than saving yourself by the simple act of waking." -- Junot Díaz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1981-my-experience-of-life-is-that-it-is-not-divided</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2012 17:20:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1981-my-experience-of-life-is-that-it-is-not-divided]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My experience of life is that it is not divided up into genres; it’s a horrifying, romantic, tragic, comical, science-fiction cowboy detective novel. You know, with a bit of pornography if you're lucky." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42152-if-before-every-action-we-were-to-begin-by-weighing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 07:07:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by José Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42152-if-before-every-action-we-were-to-begin-by-weighing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If, before every action, we were to begin by weighing up the consequences, thinking about them in earnest, first the immediate consequences, then the probable, then the possible, then the imaginable ones, we should never move beyond the point where our first thought brought us to a halt. The good and evil resulting from our words and deeds go on apportioning themselves, one assumes in a reasonably uniform and balanced way, throughout all the days to follow, including those endless days, when we shall not be here to find out, to congratulate ourselves or ask for pardon, indeed there are those who claim that this is the much talked of immortality." -- José Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52065-we-can-only-feel-sorry-for-ourselves-when-our-misfortunes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2013 18:33:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Marjane Satrapi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52065-we-can-only-feel-sorry-for-ourselves-when-our-misfortunes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can only feel sorry for ourselves when our misfortunes are still supportable. Once this limit is crossed, the only way to bear the unbearable is to laugh at it." -- Marjane Satrapi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72160-if-you-only-read-the-books-that-everyone-else-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 05:07:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72160-if-you-only-read-the-books-that-everyone-else-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you only read the books that everyone else is reading, you can only think what everyone else is thinking." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315361-and-once-the-storm-is-over-you-won-t-remember-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 05:08:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by haruki murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315361-and-once-the-storm-is-over-you-won-t-remember-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And once the storm is over, you won’t remember how you made it through, how you managed to survive. You won’t even be sure, whether the storm is really over. But one thing is certain. When you come out of the storm, you won’t be the same person who walked in. That’s what this storm’s all about." -- haruki murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31793-love-is-never-any-better-than-the-lover</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 09:18:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31793-love-is-never-any-better-than-the-lover]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is never any better than the lover. " -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61926-thermodynamic-miracles-events-with-odds-against-so-astronomical-they-re-effectively</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2009 09:35:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61926-thermodynamic-miracles-events-with-odds-against-so-astronomical-they-re-effectively]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thermodynamic miracles... events with odds against so astronomical they're effectively impossible, like oxygen spontaneously becoming gold. I long to observe such a thing.
And yet, in each human coupling, a thousand million sperm vie for a single egg. Multiply those odds by countless generations, against the odds of your ancestors being alive; meeting; siring this precise son; that exact daughter... Until your mother loves a man she has every reason to hate, and of that union, of the thousand million children competing for fertilization, it was you, only you, that emerged. To distill so specific a form from that chaos of improbability, like turning air to gold... that is the crowning unlikelihood. The thermodynamic miracle.

But...if me, my birth, if that's a thermodynamic miracle... I mean, you could say that about anybody in the world!.

Yes. Anybody in the world. ..But the world is so full of people, so crowded with these miracles that they become commonplace and we forget... I forget. We gaze continually at the world and it grows dull in our perceptions. Yet seen from the another's vantage point. As if new, it may still take our breath away. Come...dry your eyes. For you are life, rarer than a quark and unpredictable beyond the dreams of Heisenberg; the clay in which the forces that shape all things leave their fingerprints most clearly. Dry your eyes... and let's go home." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/963713-we-are-other-than-what-we-would-have-been-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 17:57:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/963713-we-are-other-than-what-we-would-have-been-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are other than what we would have been if we had crossed the oceans, if or mothers and fathers had not crossed the skies in search of work and dignity and a better life for their children. We have been made again: but I say that we shall also be the ones to remake this society, to shape it from the bottom to the top." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
