<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/382953-ben-hobden]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/382953-ben-hobden" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 21:10:51 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 21:10:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are bored and disgusted by politics and don't bother to vote, you are in effect voting for the entrenched Establishments of the two major parties, who please rest assured are not dumb, and who are keenly aware that it is in their interests to keep you disgusted and bored and cynical and to give you every possible reason to stay at home doing one-hitters and watching MTV on primary day.  By all means stay home if you want, but don't bullshit yourself that you're not voting.  In reality, there is &lt;i&gt;no such thing as not voting:&lt;/i&gt; you either vote by voting, or you vote by staying home and tacitly doubling the value of some Diehard's vote." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237758-when-they-were-introduced-he-made-a-witticism-hoping-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 04:46:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237758-when-they-were-introduced-he-made-a-witticism-hoping-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When they were introduced, he made a witticism, hoping to be liked. She laughed extremely hard, hoping to be liked. Then each drove home alone, staring straight ahead, with the very same twist to their faces.

The man who'd introduced them didn't much like either of them, though he acted as if he did, anxious as he was to preserve good relations at all times. One never knew, after all, now did one now did one now did one." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456687-there-is-a-cult-of-ignorance-in-the-united-states</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 09:05:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Issac Asimov ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456687-there-is-a-cult-of-ignorance-in-the-united-states]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a cult of ignorance in the United States, and there has always been. The strain of anti-intellectualism has been a constant thread winding its way through our political and cultural life, nurtured by the false notion that  democracy means that 'my ignorance is just as good as your knowledge." -- Issac Asimov ]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
