<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/383650-barbara]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/383650-barbara" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 21:06:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46108-no-matter-what-your-past-has-been-your-future-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 21:06:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Hugh B. Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46108-no-matter-what-your-past-has-been-your-future-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No matter what your past has been, your future is spotless." -- Hugh B. Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58394-reader-i-married-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 20:44:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58394-reader-i-married-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reader, I married him." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140214-mothers-are-the-first-professors-in-the-school-of-character</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 21:06:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Hugh B. Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140214-mothers-are-the-first-professors-in-the-school-of-character]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mothers are the first professors in the school of character." -- Hugh B. Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105372-while-life-lasts-one-must-look-upon-each-new-achievement</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 21:06:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Hugh B. Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105372-while-life-lasts-one-must-look-upon-each-new-achievement]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["While life lasts, one must look upon each new achievement as a challenge and a beginning.  Mile posts marking the way were not intended for camping grounds.
The gospel is a challenge to finish the course, not simply to begin it.  All the fine accomplishments of a worth-while life may be defeated by a poor ending." -- Hugh B. Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63558-even-water-carves-monuments-of-stone-so-do-our-thoughts</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 21:06:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Hugh B. Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63558-even-water-carves-monuments-of-stone-so-do-our-thoughts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even water carves monuments of stone, so do our thoughts shape our character." -- Hugh B. Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197766-life-is-not-a-journey-to-the-grave-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 11:32:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197766-life-is-not-a-journey-to-the-grave-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is not a journey to the grave with the intention of arriving safely in a well preserved body, but rather to skid in broadside, thoroughly used up, totally worn out, and loudly proclaiming, “Wow what a ride!" -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51827-how-did-a-nice-girl-like-me-get-into-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 11:32:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51827-how-did-a-nice-girl-like-me-get-into-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How did a nice girl like me get into a mess like this?" -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/343687-everything-you-are-learning-is-preparing-you-for-something-else</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 11:33:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/343687-everything-you-are-learning-is-preparing-you-for-something-else]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything you are learning is preparing you for something else." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357565-owning-our-story-can-be-hard-but-not-nearly-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 13:14:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Brene Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357565-owning-our-story-can-be-hard-but-not-nearly-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Owning our story can be hard but not nearly as difficult as spending our lives running from it. Embracing our vulnerabilities is risky but not nearly as dangerous as giving up on love and belonging and joy—the experiences that make us the most vulnerable. Only when we are brave enough to explore the darkness will we discover the infinite power of our light." -- Brene Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383047-shame-corrodes-the-very-part-of-us-that-believes-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 13:15:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Brene Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383047-shame-corrodes-the-very-part-of-us-that-believes-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Shame corrodes the very part of us that believes we are capable of change." -- Brene Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/544057-we-cannot-selectively-numb-emotions-when-we-numb-the-painful</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 13:15:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Brené Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/544057-we-cannot-selectively-numb-emotions-when-we-numb-the-painful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We cannot selectively numb emotions, when we numb the painful emotions, we also numb the positive emotions." -- Brené Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/642405-nostalgia-is-also-a-dangerous-form-of-comparison-think-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 13:15:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Brene Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/642405-nostalgia-is-also-a-dangerous-form-of-comparison-think-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nostalgia is also a dangerous form of comparison. Think about how often we compare our lives to a memory that nostalgia has so completely edited that it never really existed." -- Brene Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20606-the-homemaker-has-the-ultimate-career-all-other-careers-exist</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 11:46:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20606-the-homemaker-has-the-ultimate-career-all-other-careers-exist]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The homemaker has the ultimate career.  All other careers exist for one purpose only - and that is to support the ultimate career.  " -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62266-what-can-you-do-to-promote-world-peace-go-home</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 11:47:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62266-what-can-you-do-to-promote-world-peace-go-home]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What can you do to promote world peace? Go home and love your family." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24015-you-do-not-have-to-be-good-you-do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 11:47:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24015-you-do-not-have-to-be-good-you-do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You do not have to be good.
You do not have to walk on your knees
for a hundred miles through the desert, repenting.
You only have to let the soft animal of your body 
love what it loves.
Tell me about despair, yours, and I will tell you mine.
Meanwhile the world goes on.
Meanwhile the sun and the clear pebbles of the rain
are moving across the landscapes,
over the prairies and the deep trees,
the mountains and the rivers.
Meanwhile the wild geese, high in the clean blue air,
are heading home again.
Whoever you are, no matter how lonely,
the world offers itself to your imagination,
calls to you like the wild geese, harsh and exciting –
over and over announcing your place
in the family of things." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193095-when-god-created-mothers-when-the-good-lord-was-creating</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 11:48:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Erma Bombeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193095-when-god-created-mothers-when-the-good-lord-was-creating]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When God Created Mothers&quot;
  
When the Good Lord was creating mothers, He was into His sixth day of &quot;overtime&quot; when the angel appeared and said. &quot;You're doing a lot of fiddling around on this one.&quot; 

And God said, &quot;Have you read the specs on this order?&quot; She has to be completely washable, but not plastic. Have 180 moveable parts...all replaceable. Run on black coffee and leftovers. Have a lap that disappears when she stands up. A kiss that can cure anything from a broken leg to a disappointed love affair. And six pairs of hands.&quot; 

The angel shook her head slowly and said. &quot;Six pairs of hands.... no way.&quot; 

It's not the hands that are causing me problems,&quot; God remarked, &quot;it's the three pairs of eyes that mothers have to have.&quot; 

That's on the standard model?&quot; asked the angel. God nodded. 

One pair that sees through closed doors when she asks, 'What are you kids doing in there?' when she already knows. Another here in the back of her head that sees what she shouldn't but what she has to know, and of course the ones here in front that can look at a child when he goofs up and say. 'I understand and I love you' without so much as uttering a word.&quot; 

God,&quot; said the angel touching his sleeve gently, &quot;Get some rest tomorrow....&quot; 

I can't,&quot; said God, &quot;I'm so close to creating something so close to myself. Already I have one who heals herself when she is sick...can feed a family of six on one pound of hamburger...and can get a nine year old to stand under a shower.&quot; 

The angel circled the model of a mother very slowly. &quot;It's too soft,&quot; she sighed. 

But tough!&quot; said God excitedly. &quot;You can imagine what this mother can do or endure.&quot; 

Can it think?&quot; 

Not only can it think, but it can reason and compromise,&quot; said the Creator. 

Finally, the angel bent over and ran her finger across the cheek. 

There's a leak,&quot; she pronounced. &quot;I told You that You were trying to put too much into this model.&quot; 

It's not a leak,&quot; said the Lord, &quot;It's a tear.&quot; 

What's it for?&quot; 

It's for joy, sadness, disappointment, pain, loneliness, and pride.&quot; 

You are a genius, &quot; said the angel. 

Somberly, God said, &quot;I didn't put it there." -- Erma Bombeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206045-there-is-no-point-treating-a-depressed-person-as-though</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 11:49:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206045-there-is-no-point-treating-a-depressed-person-as-though]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no point treating a depressed person as though she were just feeling sad, saying, 'There now, hang on, you'll get over it.' Sadness is more or less like a head cold- with patience, it passes. Depression is like cancer." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292415-that-s-what-people-do-who-love-you-they-put-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 11:49:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Deb Caletti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292415-that-s-what-people-do-who-love-you-they-put-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's what people do who love you. They put their arms around you and love you when you're not so lovable." -- Deb Caletti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17691-when-your-mother-asks-do-you-want-a-piece-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 11:50:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Erma Bombeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17691-when-your-mother-asks-do-you-want-a-piece-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When your mother asks, &quot;Do you want a piece of advice?&quot; it's a mere formality. It doesn't matter if you answer yes or no. You're going to get it anyway." -- Erma Bombeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74445-as-you-grow-older-you-ll-see-white-men-cheat-black</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 11:50:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74445-as-you-grow-older-you-ll-see-white-men-cheat-black]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As you grow older, you'll see white men cheat black men every day of your life, but let me tell you something and don't you forget it - whenever a white man does that to a black man, no matter who he is, how rich he is, or how fine a family he comes from, he is trash." -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23510-i-sustain-myself-with-the-love-of-family</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 11:50:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23510-i-sustain-myself-with-the-love-of-family]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I sustain myself with the love of family." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54056-peace-is-the-gift-of-god-do-you-want-peace</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 11:51:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by John Taylor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54056-peace-is-the-gift-of-god-do-you-want-peace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Peace is the gift of God. Do you want peace? Go to God. Do you want peace in your families? Go to God. Do you want peace to brood over your families? If you do, live your religion, and the very peace of God will dwell and abide with you, for that is where peace comes from, and it doesn't dwell anywhere else. . . .
Some in speaking of war and troubles, will say are you not afraid? No, I am a servant of God, and this is enough, for Father is at the helm. It is for me to be as clay in the hands of the potter, to be pliable and walk in the light of the countenance of the Spirit of the Lord, and then no matter what comes. Let the lightnings flash and the earthquakes bellow, God is at the helm, and I feel like saying but little, for the Lord God Omnipotent reigneth and will continue his work until he has put all enemies under his feet, and his kingdom extends from the rivers to the ends of the earth." -- John Taylor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518846-when-our-children-were-very-small-i-started-to-write</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 11:51:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Henry B. Eyring]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518846-when-our-children-were-very-small-i-started-to-write]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When our children were very small, I started to write down a few things about what happened every day….I wrote down a few lines every day for years. I never missed a day no matter how tired I was or how early I would have to start the next day. Before I would write, I would ponder this question: “Have I seen the hand of God reaching out to touch us or our children or our family today?” As I kept at it, something began to happen. As I would cast my mind over the day, I would see evidence of what God had done for one of us that I had not recognized in the busy moments of the day.'
 
I would suggest that you keep a paper and pencil you your side as you read this book, particularly the stories and examples shared here. I am confident that as you read the stories of others, you will be reminded of times in your life when the Lord has given you special blessings. Or perhaps thoughts will come that will teach you what to do to have your own tender mercies. Write them down, and, if appropriate, share them with your families." -- Henry B. Eyring]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 11:52:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We accept the love we think we deserve." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 11:52:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opposite of love is not hate, it's indifference. The opposite of art is not ugliness, it's indifference. The opposite of faith is not heresy, it's indifference. And the opposite of life is not death, it's indifference." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/778-it-is-not-a-lack-of-love-but-a-lack</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 11:52:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/778-it-is-not-a-lack-of-love-but-a-lack]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not a lack of love, but a lack of friendship that makes unhappy marriages." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282642-w-hen-you-realize-you-want-to-spend-the-rest-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2014 21:59:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Barbara add a quote by Nora Ephron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282642-w-hen-you-realize-you-want-to-spend-the-rest-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[W]hen you realize you want to spend the rest of your life with somebody, you want the rest of your life to start as soon as possible." -- Nora Ephron]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
