<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/383682-rinabeana]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/383682-rinabeana" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 04:52:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11664-my-candle-burns-at-both-ends-it-will-not-last</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 04:52:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Edna St. Vincent Millay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11664-my-candle-burns-at-both-ends-it-will-not-last]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My candle burns at both ends;
It will not last the night;
But ah, my foes, and oh, my friends—
It gives a lovely light!" -- Edna St. Vincent Millay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 04:52:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She is too fond of books, and it has turned her brain." -- Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9927-i-ask-you-to-pass-through-life-at-my-side-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 04:52:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9927-i-ask-you-to-pass-through-life-at-my-side-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I ask you to pass through life at my side—to be my second self, and best earthly companion." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2119-he-was-born-with-a-gift-of-laughter-and-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 04:52:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Rafael Sabatini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2119-he-was-born-with-a-gift-of-laughter-and-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was born with a gift of laughter and a sense that the world was mad." -- Rafael Sabatini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46272-ink-runs-from-the-corners-of-my-mouth-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 04:52:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Mark Strand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46272-ink-runs-from-the-corners-of-my-mouth-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ink runs from the corners of my mouth.
There is no happiness like mine.
I have been eating poetry." -- Mark Strand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9926-thank-you-mr-rochester-for-your-great-kindness-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 05:19:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9926-thank-you-mr-rochester-for-your-great-kindness-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thank you, Mr. Rochester, for your great kindness. I am strangely glad to get back again to you: and wherever you are is my home—my only home." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21101-do-you-think-i-am-an-automaton-a-machine</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 05:20:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21101-do-you-think-i-am-an-automaton-a-machine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you think I am an automaton? — a machine without feelings? and can bear to have my morsel of bread snatched from my lips, and my drop of living water dashed from my cup? Do you think, because I am poor, obscure, plain, and little, I am soulless and heartless? You think wrong! — I have as much soul as you — and full as much heart! And if God had gifted me with some beauty and much wealth, I should have made it as hard for you to leave me, as it is now for me to leave you. I am not talking to you now through the medium of custom, conventionalities, nor even of mortal flesh: it is my spirit that addresses your spirit; just as if both had passed through the grave, and we stood at God's feet, equal — as we are!" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9930-either-you-go-to-america-with-mrs-van-hopper-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 05:22:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Daphne du Maurier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9930-either-you-go-to-america-with-mrs-van-hopper-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Either you go to America with Mrs. Van Hopper or you come home to Manderley with me.&quot;
&quot;Do you mean you want a secretary or something?&quot;
&quot;No, I'm asking you to marry me, you little fool." -- Daphne du Maurier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9931-he-belonged-to-a-walled-city-of-the-fifteenth-century</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 05:23:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Daphne Du Maurier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9931-he-belonged-to-a-walled-city-of-the-fifteenth-century]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He belonged to a walled city of the fifteenth century, a city of narrow, cobbled streets, and thin spires, where the inhabitants wore pointed shoes and worsted hose. His face was arresting, sensitive, medieval in some strange inexplicable way, and I was reminded of a portrait seen in a gallery I had forgotten where, of a certain Gentleman Unknown. Could one but rob him of his English tweeds, and put him in black, with lace at his throat and wrists, he would stare down at us in our new world from a long distant past—a past where men walked cloaked at night, and stood in the shadow of old doorways, a past of narrow stairways and dim dungeons, a past of whispers in the dark, of shimmering rapier blades, of silent, exquisite courtesy." -- Daphne Du Maurier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9932-the-bright-dawn-flooded-the-room-and-swept-the-fantastic</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 05:25:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9932-the-bright-dawn-flooded-the-room-and-swept-the-fantastic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The bright dawn flooded the room, and swept the fantastic shadows into dusky corners, where they lay shuddering." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9933-the-sound-of-distant-breakers-made-her-heart-ache-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 05:26:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Baroness Emmuska Orczy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9933-the-sound-of-distant-breakers-made-her-heart-ache-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sound of distant breakers made her heart ache with melancholy. She was in the mood when the sea has a saddening effect upon the nerves. It is only when we are very happy that we can bear to gaze merrily upon the vast and limitless expanse of water, rolling on and on with such persistent, irritating monotony to the accompaniment of our thoughts, whether grave or gay. When they are gay, the waves echo their gaiety; but when they are sad, then every breaker, as it rolls, seems to bring additional sadness and to speak to us of hopelessness and of the pettiness of all our joys." -- Baroness Emmuska Orczy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9934-as-she-chattered-and-laughed-and-cast-quick-glances-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 05:27:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9934-as-she-chattered-and-laughed-and-cast-quick-glances-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As she chattered and laughed and cast quick glances into the house and the yard, her eyes fell on a stranger, standing alone in the hall, staring at her in a cool impertinent way that brought her up sharply with a mingled feeling of feminine pleasure that she had attracted a man and an embarrassed sensation that her dress was too low in the bosom. He looked quite old, at least thirty-five. He was a tall man and powerfully built. Scarlett thought she had never seen such a man with such wide shoulders, so heavy with muscles, almost too heavy for gentility. When her eye caught his, he smiled, showing animal-white teeth below a close-clipped black mustache. He was dark of face, swarthy as a pirate, and his eyes were as bold and black as any pirate's appraising a galleon to be scuttled or a maiden to be ravished. There was a cool recklessness in his face and a cynical humor in his mouth as he smiled at her, and Scarlett caught her breath. She felt that she should be insulted by such a look as was annoyed with herself because she did not feel insulted. She did not know who he could be, but there was undeniably a look of good blood in his dark face. It showed in the thin hawk nose over the full red lips, and high forehead and the wide-set eyes." -- Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9935-forgive-me-for-startling-you-with-the-impetuosity-of-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 05:28:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9935-forgive-me-for-startling-you-with-the-impetuosity-of-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Forgive me for startling you with the impetuosity of my sentiments, my dear Scarlett—I mean, my dear Mrs. Kennedy. It cannot have escaped your notice that for some time past the friendship I have had in my heart for you has ripened into a deeper feeling, a feeling more beautiful, more pure, more sacred. Dare I name it you? Ah! It is love which makes me so bold!" -- Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10012-i-like-trees-because-they-seem-more-resigned-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:32:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Willa Cather]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10012-i-like-trees-because-they-seem-more-resigned-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like trees because they seem more resigned to the way they have to live than other things do. I feel as if this tree knows everything I ever think of when I sit here. When I come back to it, I never have to remind it of anything; I begin just where I left off." -- Willa Cather]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10013-and-now-the-old-story-has-begun-to-write-itself</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:33:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Willa Cather]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10013-and-now-the-old-story-has-begun-to-write-itself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And now the old story has begun to write itself over there,&quot; said Carl softly. &quot;Isn’t it queer: there are only two or three human stories, and they go on repeating themselves as fiercely as if they had never happened before; like the larks in this country, that have been singing the same five notes for thousands of years." -- Willa Cather]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10014-it-came-to-mr-blood-as-he-trudged-forward-under</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:34:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Rafael Sabatini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10014-it-came-to-mr-blood-as-he-trudged-forward-under]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It came to Mr. Blood, as he trudged forward under the laden apple-trees on that fragrant, delicious July morning, that man—as he had long suspected—was the vilest work of God, and that only a fool would set himself up as a healer of a species that was best exterminated." -- Rafael Sabatini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10016-a-year-or-two-younger-than-his-eminently-practical-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:36:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10016-a-year-or-two-younger-than-his-eminently-practical-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A year or two younger than his eminently practical friend, Mr. Bounderby looked older; his seven or eight and forty might have had the seven or eight added to it again, without surprising anybody.  He had not much hair.  One might have fancied he had talked it off; and that what was left, all standing up in disorder, was in that condition from being constantly blown about by his windy boastfulness." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10017-from-the-beginning-she-had-sat-looking-at-him-fixedly</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:37:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10017-from-the-beginning-she-had-sat-looking-at-him-fixedly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From the beginning, she had sat looking at him fixedly.  As he now leaned back in his chair, and bent his deep-set eyes upon her in his turn, perhaps he might have seen one wavering moment in her, when she was impelled to throw herself upon his breast, and give him the pent-up confidences of her heart.  But, to see it, he must have overleaped at a bound the artificial barriers he had for many years been erecting, between himself and all those subtle essences of humanity which will elude the utmost cunning of algebra until the last trumpet ever to be sounded shall blow even algebra to wreck.  The barriers were too many and too high for such a leap.  With his unbending, utilitarian, matter-of-fact face, he hardened her again; and the moment shot away into the plumbless depths of the past, to mingle with all the lost opportunities that are drowned there." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76029-a-safe-still-night-too-serene-for-the-companionship-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:39:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76029-a-safe-still-night-too-serene-for-the-companionship-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A safe, still night; too serene for the companionship of fear. We know that God is everywhere; but certainly we feel His presence most when His works are on the grandest scale spread before us: and it is in the unclouded night sky, where His worlds wheel their silent course, that we read clearest His infinitude, His omnipotence, His Omnipresence." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10019-we-do-not-always-remember-the-things-that-do-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:39:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10019-we-do-not-always-remember-the-things-that-do-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We do not always remember the things that do no credit to us. We justify them, cover them in bright lies or with the thick dust of forgetfulness. All of the things that Shadow had done in his life of which he was not proud, all the things he wished he had done otherwise or left undone, came at him then in a swirling storm of guilt and regret and shame, and he had nowhere to hide from them. He was as naked and as open as a corpse on a table, and dark Anubis the jackal god was his prosector and his prosecutor and his persecutor." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10021-actually-loneliness-has-a-kind-of-fascination-it-s-a-state</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:40:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Arturo Pérez-Reverte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10021-actually-loneliness-has-a-kind-of-fascination-it-s-a-state]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Actually loneliness has a kind of fascination; it's a state of egotistical, inner grace that you can achieve only by standing guard on old, forgotten roads that no one travels anymore." -- Arturo Pérez-Reverte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10022-you-don-t-choose-your-friends-they-choose-you-and-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:41:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Arturo Pérez-Reverte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10022-you-don-t-choose-your-friends-they-choose-you-and-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't choose your friends, they choose you, and you either reject them or you accept them without reservations." -- Arturo Pérez-Reverte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10023-when-a-man-who-is-drinking-neat-gin-starts-talking</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:41:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by C.S. Forester]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10023-when-a-man-who-is-drinking-neat-gin-starts-talking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a man who is drinking neat gin starts talking about his mother he is past all argument." -- C.S. Forester]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10024-once-in-my-father-s-bookshop-i-heard-a-regular-customer</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:42:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Carlos Ruiz Zafon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10024-once-in-my-father-s-bookshop-i-heard-a-regular-customer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once, in my father's bookshop, I heard a regular customer say that few things leave a deeper mark on a reader than the first book that finds its way into his heart.  Those first images, the echo of words we think we have left behind, accompany us throughout our lives and sculpt a palace in our memory to which, sooner or later—no matter how many books we read, how many worlds we discover, or how much we learn or forget—we will return." -- Carlos Ruiz Zafon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10025-he-domesticated-and-developed-the-native-wild-flowers-he-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:43:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Willa Cather]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10025-he-domesticated-and-developed-the-native-wild-flowers-he-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He domesticated and developed the native wild flowers.  He had one hill-side solidly clad with that low-growing purple verbena which mats over the hills of New Mexico.  It was like a great violet velvet mantle thrown down in the sun; all the shades that the dyers and weavers of Italy and France strove for through centuries, the violet that is full of rose colour and is yet not lavender; the blue that becomes almost pink and then retreats again into sea-dark purple—the true Episcopal colour and countless variations of it." -- Willa Cather]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10026-his-life-was-absurd-he-went-all-over-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:44:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by E.L. Doctorow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10026-his-life-was-absurd-he-went-all-over-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His life was absurd. He went all over the world accepting all kinds of bondage and escaping. He was roped to a chair. He escaped. He was chained to a ladder. He escaped. He was handcuffed, his legs were put in irons, he was tied up in a strait jacket and put in a locked cabinet.  He escaped. He escaped from bank vaults, nailed-up barrels, sewn mailbags; he escaped from a zinc-lined Knabe piano case, a giant football, a galvanized iron boiler, a rolltop desk, a sausage skin. His escapes were mystifying because he never damaged or appeared to unlock what he escaped from. The screen was pulled away and there he stood disheveled but triumphant beside the inviolate container that was supposed to have contained him. He waved to the crowd. He escaped from a sealed milk can filled with water. He escaped from a Siberian exile van. From a Chinese torture crucifix. From a Hamburg penitentiary. From an English prison ship. From a Boston jail. He was chained to automobile tires, water wheels, cannon, and he escaped. He dove manacled from a bridge into the Mississippi, the Seine, the Mersey, and came up waving. He hung upside down and strait-jacketed from cranes, biplanes and the tops of buildings. He was dropped into the ocean padlocked in a diving suit fully weighted and not connected to an air supply, and he escaped. He was buried alive in a grave and could not escape, and had to be rescued. Hurriedly, they dug him out. The earth is too heavy, he said gasping. His nails bled. Soil fell from his eyes. He was drained of color and couldn't stand. His assistant threw up. Houdini wheezed and sputtered. He coughed blood. They cleaned him off and took him back to the hotel. Today, nearly fifty years since his death, the audience for escapes is even larger." -- E.L. Doctorow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10027-it-was-evident-to-him-that-the-world-composed-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:44:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by E.L. Doctorow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10027-it-was-evident-to-him-that-the-world-composed-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was evident to him that the world composed and recomposed itself constantly in an endless process of dissatisfaction." -- E.L. Doctorow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10029-misery-in-cold-truth-is-a-weight-less-upon-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:46:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Kenneth Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10029-misery-in-cold-truth-is-a-weight-less-upon-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Misery, in cold truth, is a weight less upon those who undergo it than upon the minds of those who see it; for he who is cold and starving is so busy in his efforts to obtain warmth and food that he has little time for self-pity, and endures his unhappy condition better than those who take it upon themselves to suffer for him." -- Kenneth Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10030-take-my-love-one-day-share-my-life-be-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:49:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10030-take-my-love-one-day-share-my-life-be-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Take my love. One day share my life. Be my dearest, first on earth." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10031-god-surely-did-not-create-us-and-cause-us-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 10:51:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[rinabeana add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10031-god-surely-did-not-create-us-and-cause-us-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God surely did not create us, and cause us to live, with the sole end of wishing always to die. I believe, in my heart, we were intended to prize life and enjoy it, so long as we retain it. Existence never was originally meant to be that useless, blank, pale, slow-trailing thing it often becomes to many, and is becoming to me, among the rest." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
