<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/384807-caleb]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/384807-caleb" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 01:30:40 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5323-but-it-gradually-seemed-to-me-that-i-d-made-myself</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 01:30:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caleb add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5323-but-it-gradually-seemed-to-me-that-i-d-made-myself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...But it gradually seemed to me that I'd made myself believe something that wasn't true. I'd made myself believe that I was fine and happy and fulfilled on my own without the love of anyone else. Being in love was like China: you knew it was there, and no doubt it was very interesting, and some people went there, but I never would. I'd spend all my life without ever going to China, but it wouldn't matter, because there was all the rest of the world to visit... And I thought: am I really going to spend the rest of my life without feeling that again? I thought: I &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to go to China. It's full of treasures and strangeness and mysteries and joy." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53836-when-he-was-little-she-d-stay-late-in-his-room</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 00:26:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caleb add a quote by Dana Adam Shapiro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53836-when-he-was-little-she-d-stay-late-in-his-room]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When he was little, she'd stay late in his room, drawing pictures of him as he slept. She had fat pads filled with closeup sketches of his growing muscles, hands, and teeth, roughly rendered in black ink and charcoal. She wasn't trained or ambitious when it came to art; she was simply fascinated by her creation—not the drawings, the person. &quot;This is mine,&quot; she'd say, checking Henry's pulse, looking into his nostrils, &quot;This is me.&quot; She once counted his eyelashes with a magnifying glass and drew each one to scale." -- Dana Adam Shapiro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65323-people-who-have-only-good-experiences-aren-t-very-interesting-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 01:38:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caleb add a quote by Peter Cameron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65323-people-who-have-only-good-experiences-aren-t-very-interesting-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People who have only good experiences aren't very interesting. They may be content, and happy after a fashion, but they aren't very deep. It may seem a misfortune now, and it makes things difficult, but well--it's easy to feel all the happy, simple stuff. Not that happiness is necessarily simple. But I don't think you're going to have a life like that, and I think you'll be the better for it. The difficult thing is to not be overwhelmed by the bad patches. You must not let them defeat you. You must see them as a gift--a cruel gift, but a gift nonetheless." -- Peter Cameron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202485-it-s-kind-of-like-this-decker-said-you-wake-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 21:16:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caleb add a quote by Ethan Hawke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202485-it-s-kind-of-like-this-decker-said-you-wake-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's kind of like this,&quot; Decker said: &quot;You wake up in the middle of the night and you're dying for a glass of milk. So you stumble out of bed, stub your toe in the darkness, scream with pain, and limp your way to the refrigerator. You open it up and the light is brilliant. You're saved. Then you fold back the paper container, open up the milk, take a deep breath, and put it to your lips. Only --- yhrch! --- the milk is spoiled. Sure, you're bummed. You fold the thing close and put it back in the fridge. It's dark again. But as you're making your way to your lonely old bed, you think to yourself, Wait a minute, maybe that milk wasn't so bad. And I am still thirsty? So you do an about-face and go back to the fridge. The light warms you up again. You take a sip and yup, it's still spoiled. That, to me, is the fitting metaphor for most every relationship I've ever been in." -- Ethan Hawke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202486-look-i-have-no-idea-what-s-going-on-i-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 21:21:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caleb add a quote by Ethan Hawke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202486-look-i-have-no-idea-what-s-going-on-i-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look, I have no idea what's going on,&quot; I said, catching my breath. &quot;I don't like myself either. I don't know what's happening to me. I don't want to tell you to fuck off. But you gotta understand, everything in my life feels different. I just want so badly to know if you like me. And I know how asinine that sounds. If you want me to leave you alone, I will, but sometimes... sometimes you meet somebody and you know that whatever you did before, whatever your life was before, it must have been right... nothing could've been too bad or gone too far wrong because it led you to this person. You're that person. Do you want me to go away?" -- Ethan Hawke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202488-i-was-touched-that-he-d-brought-me-here-i-didn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 21:26:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caleb add a quote by Nick Burd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202488-i-was-touched-that-he-d-brought-me-here-i-didn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was touched that he'd brought me here. I didn't know what to say. Up until then there was a part of me that wondered if maybe there was nothing more to him than an aura of danger and a disposable charm that he used to keep himself from getting into too much trouble. I was beginning to realize that like everyone else, he was searching for something, and like everyone else, he had no idea where he could find it.
Thanks for bringing me here,&quot; I said. &quot; It really means a lot me.&quot;
Does it?&quot; he asked. He seemed genuinely surprised by this. &quot;I'm glad. I wasn't sure if you'd get it. I thought maybe you'd think it was creepy.&quot;
No,&quot; I said quickly. &quot;Not at all. I like that there's these different parts to you.&quot;
Good,&quot; he said, smiling. &quot;It's hard to show people everything, you know? You never know what they'll do with it once they have it." -- Nick Burd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239690-trust-is-like-a-mirror-you-can-fix-it-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 19:46:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caleb add a quote by Lady Gaga]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239690-trust-is-like-a-mirror-you-can-fix-it-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Trust is like a mirror, you can fix it if it's broken, but you can still see the crack in that mother fucker's reflection." -- Lady Gaga]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18490-we-must-always-take-sides-neutrality-helps-the-oppressor-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 15:32:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Caleb add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18490-we-must-always-take-sides-neutrality-helps-the-oppressor-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must always take sides.  Neutrality helps the oppressor, never the victim.  Silence encourages the tormentor, never the tormented." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
