<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/385021-elizabeth]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/385021-elizabeth" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 20:17:18 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14888-often-it-s-not-about-becoming-a-new-person-but-becoming</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 20:17:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Heath L. Buckmaster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14888-often-it-s-not-about-becoming-a-new-person-but-becoming]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Often, it’s not about becoming a new person, but becoming the person you were meant to be, and already are, but don’t know how to be." -- Heath L. Buckmaster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34708-she-was-still-hugging-the-cat-poor-slob-she-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 23:24:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Truman Capote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34708-she-was-still-hugging-the-cat-poor-slob-she-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was still hugging the cat. &quot;Poor slob,&quot; she said, tickling his head, &quot;poor slob without a name. It's a little inconvenient, his not having a name. But I haven't any right to give him one: he'll have to wait until he belongs to somebody. We just sort of took up by the river one day, we don't belong to each other: he's an independent, and so am I. I don't want to own anything until I know I've found the place where me and things belong together. I'm not quite sure where that is just yet. But I know what it's like.&quot; She smiled, and let the cat drop to the floor. &quot;It's like Tiffany's,&quot; she said.

[...]

It calms me down right away, the quietness and the proud look of it; nothing very bad could happen to you there, not with those kind men in their nice suits, and that lovely smell of silver and alligator wallets. If I could find a real-life place that made me feel like Tiffany's, then I'd buy some furniture and give the cat a name." -- Truman Capote]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
