<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/386257-homa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/386257-homa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 15:18:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48385-but-the-biggest-mistake-i-made-is-the-one-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 15:18:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Homa add a quote by Anna Quindlen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48385-but-the-biggest-mistake-i-made-is-the-one-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["but the biggest mistake I made is the one that most of us make while doing this. I did not live in the moment enough. This is particularly clear now that the moment is gone, captured only in photographs. There is one picture of the three on them sitting in the grass on a quilt in the shadow of the swing set on a summer day, ages 6, 4, and 1. And I wish I could remember what we ate, and what we talked about, and how they sounded, and how they looked when they slept that night. I wish I had not been in a hurry to get on to the next things: dinner, bath, book, bed. I wish I had treasured the doing a little more and the getting it done a little less." -- Anna Quindlen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66133-how-is-it-that-a-full-two-centuries-after-jane</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 15:19:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Homa add a quote by Anna Quindlen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66133-how-is-it-that-a-full-two-centuries-after-jane]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How is it that, a full two centuries after Jane Austen finished her manuscript, we come to the world of Pride and Prejudice and find ourselves transcending customs, strictures, time, mores, to arrive at a place that educates, amuses, and enthralls us? It is a miracle. We read in bed because reading is halfway between life and dreaming, our own consciousness in someone else's mind." -- Anna Quindlen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
