<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/388417-cara]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/388417-cara" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 17:37:18 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125477-in-the-moment-of-surrender-i-let-go-of-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 17:37:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cara add a quote by Anne Rice]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125477-in-the-moment-of-surrender-i-let-go-of-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the moment of surrender, I let go of all the theological or social questions which had kept me from Him for countless years. I simply let them go. There was the sense, profound and wordless, that if He knew everything I did not have to know everything, and that, in seeking to know everything, I'd been, all of my life, missing the entire point. No social paradox, no historic disaster, no hideous record of injustice or misery should keep me from Him. No question of Scriptural integrity, no torment over the fate of this or that atheist or gay friend, no worry for those condemned and ostracized by my church or any other church should stand between me and Him….I didn't have to know how He was going to save the unlettered and the unbaptized, or how He would redeem the conscientious heathen who had never spoken His name. I didn't have to know how my gay friends would find their way to Redemption or how my hardworking secular humanist friends could or would receive the power of His Saving Grace. I didn't have to know why good people suffered agony or died in pain. He knew. And it was his knowing that overwhelmed me…" -- Anne Rice]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69032-reading-one-book-is-like-eating-one-potato-chip</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 09:18:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cara add a quote by Diane Duane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69032-reading-one-book-is-like-eating-one-potato-chip]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reading one book is like eating one potato chip." -- Diane Duane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275905-it-is-better-i-think-to-grab-at-the-stars</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 14:58:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cara add a quote by R.A. Salvatore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275905-it-is-better-i-think-to-grab-at-the-stars]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better, I think, to grab at the stars than to sit flustered because you know you cannot reach them." -- R.A. Salvatore]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
