<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/38856-sylas]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/38856-sylas" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 22:00:59 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55159-how-easily-we-abandon-those-who-have-suffered-the-same</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 22:00:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Larissa Lai]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55159-how-easily-we-abandon-those-who-have-suffered-the-same]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How easily we abandon those who have suffered the same persecutions as we have.  How quickly we grow impatient with their inability to transcend the conditions of our lives.  " -- Larissa Lai]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58842-there-is-no-death-daughter-people-die-only-when-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 19:34:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Isabel Allende]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58842-there-is-no-death-daughter-people-die-only-when-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no death, daughter.  People die only when we forget them,' my mother explained shortly before she left me.  'If you can remember me, I will be with you always." -- Isabel Allende]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71153-i-wondered-why-i-was-acting-so-calm-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2008 16:18:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Goldberry Long]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71153-i-wondered-why-i-was-acting-so-calm-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[...] I wondered why I was acting so calm.  I wondered why I didn't writhe against being inside my own body.  If I could rip off my skin, I'd leave it in a bloody, shapeless heap on the floor beside the toilet, like so much dirty laundry.  I'd beat my head against the wall until there was nothing left of my face, if it would get me outside of myself." -- Goldberry Long]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71155-it-came-to-me-that-i-was-crying-a-steady</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2008 16:20:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Goldberry Long]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71155-it-came-to-me-that-i-was-crying-a-steady]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It came to me that I was crying, a steady runoff, a bodily function like anything else the body does on its own, a beating heart, a breath[...]" -- Goldberry Long]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71156-empathy-is-just-another-way-to-talk-about-yourself</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2008 16:21:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Goldberry Long]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71156-empathy-is-just-another-way-to-talk-about-yourself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Empathy is just another way to talk about yourself." -- Goldberry Long]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171951-or-perhaps-is-is-that-time-doesn-t-heal-wounds-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 09:29:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Thrity Umrigar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171951-or-perhaps-is-is-that-time-doesn-t-heal-wounds-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Or perhaps is is that time doesn't heal wounds at all, perhaps that is the biggest lie of them all, and instead what happens is that each wound penetrates the body deeper and deeper until one day you find that the sheer geography of your bones - the angle of your hips, the sharpness of your shoulders, as well as the luster of your eyes, the texture of your skin, the openness of your smile - has collapsed under the weight of your griefs." -- Thrity Umrigar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58841-you-ve-got-to-give-kids-really-beautiful-children-s-books-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 09:31:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Tony Millionaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58841-you-ve-got-to-give-kids-really-beautiful-children-s-books-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've got to give kids really beautiful children's books in order to turn them into revolutionaries. Because if they see these beautiful things when they're young, when they grow up they'll see the real world and say, 'Why is the world so ugly?! I remember when the world was beautiful.' And then they'll fight, and they'll have a revolution. They'll fight against all of our corruption in the world, they'll fight to try to make the world more beautiful. That's the job of a good children's book illustrator." -- Tony Millionaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52179-but-you-can-t-spend-your-whole-life-hoping-people-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 09:32:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Elizabeth McCracken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52179-but-you-can-t-spend-your-whole-life-hoping-people-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["but you can't spend your whole life hoping people will ask you the right questions. you must learn to love and answer the questions they already ask." -- Elizabeth McCracken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73855-perhaps-the-body-has-its-own-memory-system-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 15:05:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Thrity Umrigar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73855-perhaps-the-body-has-its-own-memory-system-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["  Perhaps the body has its own memory system, like the invisible meridian lines those Chinese acupuncturists always talk about.  Perhaps the body is unforgiving, perhaps every cell, every muscle and fragment of bone remembers each and every assault and attack.  Maybe the pain of memory is encoded into our bone marrow and each remembered grievance swims in our bloodstream like a hard, black pebble.  After all, the body, like God, moves in mysterious ways.

  From the time she was in her teens, Sera has been fascinated by this paradox - how a body that we occupy, that we have worn like a coat from the moment of our birth - from before birth, even - is still a stranger to us.  After all, almost everything we do in our lives is for the well-being of the body: we bathe daily, polish our teeth, groom our hair and fingernails; we work miserable jobs in order to feed and clothe it; we go to great lengths to protect it from pain and violence and harm.  And yet the body remains a mystery, a book that we have never read.  Sera plays with this irony, toys with it as if it were a puzzle: How, despite our lifelong preoccupation with our bodies, we have never met face-to-face with our kidneys, how we wouldn't recognize our own liver in a row of livers, how we have never seen our own heart or brain.  We know more about the depths of the ocean, are more acquainted with the far corners of outer space than with our own organs and muscles and bones.  So perhaps there are no phantom pains after all; perhaps all pain is real; perhaps each long ago blow lives on into eternity in some different permutation and shape; perhaps the body is this hypersensitive, revengeful entity, a ledger book, a warehouse of remembered slights and cruelties.

  But if this is true, surely the body also remembers each kindness, each kiss, each act of compassion?  Surely this is our salvation, our only hope - that joy and love are also woven into the fabric of the body, into each sinewy muscle, into the core of each pulsating cell?" -- Thrity Umrigar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2008 13:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be patient toward all that is unsolved in your heart and try to love the questions themselves, like locked rooms and like books that are now written in a very foreign tongue. Do not now seek the answers, which cannot be given you because you would not be able to live them. And the point is, to live everything. Live the questions now. Perhaps you will then gradually, without noticing it, live along some distant day into the answer." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 09:56:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think your pain and your heartbreak are unprecedented in the history of the world, but then you read. It was books that taught me that the things that tormented me most were the very things that connected me with all the people who were alive, or who had ever been alive." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94731-truthfully-this-is-the-fabric-of-all-my-fantasies-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2009 13:24:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Elizabeth McCracken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94731-truthfully-this-is-the-fabric-of-all-my-fantasies-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["truthfully, this is the fabric of all my fantasies: love shown not by a kiss or a wild look or a careful hand but by a willingness for research. i don’t dream of someone who understands me immediately, who seems to have known me my entire life, who says, i know me too. i want someone keen to learn my own strange organization, amazed at what’s revealed; someone who asks, and then what, and then what?" -- Elizabeth McCracken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151629-looking-back-it-is-also-the-smallest-moments-that-seem</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 22:18:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Evelyn Lau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151629-looking-back-it-is-also-the-smallest-moments-that-seem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Looking back, it is also the smallest moments that seem to radiate the most pain.  The moments when you realize you loved these people, helplessly, that you were given no choice in this matter of loving them, and that they will always be part of you no matter how you try to carve them out of your flesh.  That you are tied to them with bonds you could never sever, that they will live on inside you no matter how many effigies of them you hang and burn, no matter how often their reflections appear in the eyes of other men and women, men and women who then unwittingly play the roles of father and mother, with whom you act out the drama again and again." -- Evelyn Lau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151632-where-did-feelings-go-when-they-disappeared-did-they-leave</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 22:20:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Evelyn Lau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151632-where-did-feelings-go-when-they-disappeared-did-they-leave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where did feelings go when they disappeared?  Did they leave a chemical trace somewhere in our minds, so that if we could look inside ourselves we would see via the patterns of neurons some of the important things that had happened to us in our lifetimes?" -- Evelyn Lau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154350-the-horror-of-knowing-someone-and-living-with-them-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2009 15:39:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Michelle Tea]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154350-the-horror-of-knowing-someone-and-living-with-them-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The horror of knowing someone and living with them and even thinking you're lucky and then wham and now you know that every person is really two people and how can you ever know what the other half is up to." -- Michelle Tea]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180364-resist-the-temptation-to-think-what-afflicts-you-is-peculiar</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2009 11:47:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180364-resist-the-temptation-to-think-what-afflicts-you-is-peculiar]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Resist the temptation to think what afflicts you is peculiar to you.  Have faith that what is in your consciousness can be communicated to the consciousness of all.  And is, in many cases, already there." -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180366-i-m-mad-about-the-waste-that-happens-when-people-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2009 11:49:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180366-i-m-mad-about-the-waste-that-happens-when-people-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm mad about the waste that happens when people who love each other can't even bring themselves to talk." -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181890-it-is-important-to-always-remember-that-at-any-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2009 09:24:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Peter Rock]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181890-it-is-important-to-always-remember-that-at-any-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is important to always remember that at any time you think of it there are people being kept in buildings when they want to go outside." -- Peter Rock]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183491-time-wastes-too-fast-every-letter-i-trace-tells</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 13:49:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Tristram Shandy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183491-time-wastes-too-fast-every-letter-i-trace-tells]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time wastes too fast : every letter I trace tells me with what rapidity Life follows my pen ; the days and hours of it, more precious, my dear Jenny! than the rubies about thy neck, are flying over our heads like light clouds of a windy day, never to return more -- every thing presses on -- whilst thou are twisting that lock, -- see! it grows grey ; and every time I kiss thy hand to bid adieu, and every absence which follows it, are preludes to that eternal separation which we are shortly to make!" -- Tristram Shandy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192985-i-really-can-t-think-about-kissing-when-i-ve-got-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2009 21:44:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192985-i-really-can-t-think-about-kissing-when-i-ve-got-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I really can't think about kissing when I've got a rebellion to incite. " -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1219-delia-picked-at-the-raw-sores-of-her-conscience-drunk-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 10:27:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Dorothy Allison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1219-delia-picked-at-the-raw-sores-of-her-conscience-drunk-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Delia picked at the raw sores of her conscience...Drunk or sober, Delia lived in the small town in her heart, ignoring the world in which all her love had turned to grief." -- Dorothy Allison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221968-you-re-in-a-car-with-a-beautiful-boy-and-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2010 23:20:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by richard siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221968-you-re-in-a-car-with-a-beautiful-boy-and-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You’re in a car with a beautiful boy, and he won’t tell you that he loves you, but he loves you. And you feel like you’ve done something terrible, like robbed a liquor store, or swallowed pills, or shoveled yourself a grave in the dirt, and you’re tired. You’re in a car with a beautiful boy, and you’re trying not to tell him that you love him, and you’re trying to choke down the feeling, and you’re trembling, but he reaches over and he touches you, like a prayer for which no words exist, and you feel your heart taking root in your body, like you’ve discovered something you didn’t even have a name for." -- richard siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261503-i-m-battling-monsters-i-m-pulling-you-out-of-the-burning</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2010 23:22:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Richard Siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261503-i-m-battling-monsters-i-m-pulling-you-out-of-the-burning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm battling monsters, I'm pulling you out of the burning buildings/ and you say &lt;i&gt;I'll give you anything&lt;/i&gt; but you never come through." -- Richard Siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268241-he-woke-one-morning-tantalized-by-an-idea-if-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 21:50:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by David Wroblewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268241-he-woke-one-morning-tantalized-by-an-idea-if-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He woke one morning tantalized by an idea: if he could catch the orchard trees motionless for one second -- for &lt;i&gt;half&lt;/i&gt; of one second -- then none of it would have happened.  The kitchen door would bang open and in his father would walk, red-faced and slapping his hands and exclaiming about some newly whelped pup.  Childish, Edgar knew, but he didn't care.  The trick was to not focus on any single part of any tree, but to look through them all toward a point in the air.  But how insidious a bargain he'd made.  Even in the quietest moment some small thing quivered and the tableau was destroyed.

How many afternoons slipped away like that?  How many midnights standing in the spare room, watching the trees shiver in the moonlight?  Still he watched, transfixed.  Then, blushing because it was futile and silly, he forced himself to walk away.

When he blinked, an afterimage of perfect stillness.

To think it might happen when he wasn't watching.

He turned back before he reached the door.  Through the window glass, a dozen trees strummed by the winter wind, skeletons dancing pair-wise, fingers raised to heaven.

Stop it, he told himself.  Just stop.

And watched some more." -- David Wroblewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314174-the-point-for-me-is-to-create-relationships-based-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 11:55:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Dean Spade]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314174-the-point-for-me-is-to-create-relationships-based-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The point for me is to create relationships based on deeper and more real notions of trust. So that love becomes defined not by sexual exclusivity, but by actual respect, concern, commitment to act with kind intentions, accountability for our actions, and a desire for mutual growth." -- Dean Spade]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173799-as-long-as-i-kept-moving-my-grief-streamed-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 10:21:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173799-as-long-as-i-kept-moving-my-grief-streamed-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As long as I kept moving, my grief streamed out behind me like a swimmer's long hair in water.  I knew the weight was there but it didn't touch me.  Only when I stopped did the slick, dark stuff of it come floating around my face, catching my arms and throat till I began to drown.  So I just didn't stop." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165570-there-are-so-few-people-given-us-to-love-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 15:54:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Anne Enright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165570-there-are-so-few-people-given-us-to-love-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are so few people given us to love. I want to tell my daughters this, that each time you fall in love it is important, even at nineteen. Especially at nineteen. And if you can, at nineteen, count the people you love on one hand, you will not, at forty, have run out of fingers on the other. There are so few people given us to love and they all stick." -- Anne Enright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101458-everybody-is-a-genius-but-if-you-judge-a-fish</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 11:15:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101458-everybody-is-a-genius-but-if-you-judge-a-fish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody is a genius.  But if you judge a fish by its ability to climb a tree, it will live its whole life believing that it is stupid." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346181-nobody-heard-her-tears-the-heart-is-a-fountain-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 15:25:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Edward Dahlberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346181-nobody-heard-her-tears-the-heart-is-a-fountain-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody heard her tears; the heart is a fountain of weeping water which makes no noise in the world." -- Edward Dahlberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293323-solidarity-is-not-a-matter-of-altruism-solidarity-comes-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 09:23:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[sylas add a quote by Aurora Levins Morales]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293323-solidarity-is-not-a-matter-of-altruism-solidarity-comes-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Solidarity is not a matter of altruism. Solidarity comes from the inability to tolerate the affront to our own integrity of passive or active collaboration in the oppression of others, and from the deep recognition that, like it or not, our liberation is bound up with that of every other being on the planet, and that politically, spiritually, in our heart of hearts we know anything else is unaffordable. 
(Aurora Levins Morales, Medicine Stories: History, Culture and the Politics of Integrity)" -- Aurora Levins Morales]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
