<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/388830-charles-puskas]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/388830-charles-puskas" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 11:38:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/755577-for-it-was-the-one-that-i-would-have-chosen</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 11:38:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/755577-for-it-was-the-one-that-i-would-have-chosen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For it was the one that I would have chosen above all others, convinced as I was, with a botanist’s satisfaction, that it was not possible to find gathered together rarer specimens than these young flowers that at this moment before my eyes were breaking the line of the sea with their slender heads, like a bower of Pennsylvania roses adorned a Cliffside garden, between whose blooms is contained the whole tract of ocean crossed by some steamer, so slow in gliding along the blue, horizontal line that stretches from one stem to the next that an idle butterfly, dawdling in the cup of a flower which the ship’s hull has long since passed, can wait, before flying off in time to arrive before it, until nothing by the tiniest chink of blue still separates the prow from the first petal of the flower towards which it is steering." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/767818-there-were-some-that-were-of-so-rare-a-beauty</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 11:39:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/767818-there-were-some-that-were-of-so-rare-a-beauty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There were some that were of so rare a beauty that my pleasure on catching sight of them was enhanced by surprise. By what privilege, on one morning rather than another, did the window on being uncurtained disclose to my wondering eyes the nymph Glauconome, whose lazy beauty, gently breathing, had the transparence of a vaporous emerald beneath whose surface I could see teeming the ponderable elements that coloured it? She made the sun join in her play, with a smile rendered languorous by an invisible haze which was nought but a space kept vacant about her translucent surface, which, thus curtailed, became more appealing, like those goddesses whom the sculptor carves in relief upon a block of marble, the rest of which he leaves unchiselled. So, in her matchless colour, she invited us out over those rough terrestrial roads, from which, seated beside Mme. de Villeparisis in her barouche, we should see, all day long and without ever reaching it, the coolness of her gentle palpitation." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834844-while-elstir-at-my-request-went-on-painting-i-wandered</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 11:40:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834844-while-elstir-at-my-request-went-on-painting-i-wandered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["While Elstir, at my request, went on painting, I wandered about in the half-light, stopping to examine first one picture, then another.

Most of those that covered the walls were not what I should chiefly have liked to see of his work, paintings in what an English art journal which lay about on the reading-room table in the Grand Hotel called his first and second manners, the mythological manner and the manner in which he shewed signs of Japanese influence, both admirably exemplified, the article said, in the collection of Mme. de Guermantes. Naturally enough, what he had in his studio were almost all seascapes done here, at Balbec. But I was able to discern from these that the charm of each of them lay in a sort of metamorphosis of the things represented in it, analogous to what in poetry we call metaphor, and that, if God the Father had created things by naming them, it was by taking away their names or giving them other names that Elstir created them anew." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/458952-had-i-been-less-firmly-resolved-upon-settling-down-definitively</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 11:42:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/458952-had-i-been-less-firmly-resolved-upon-settling-down-definitively]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Had I been less firmly resolved upon settling down definitively to work, I should perhaps have made an effort to begin at once. But since my resolution was explicit, since within twenty-four hours, in the empty frame of the following day where everything was so well-arranged because I myself was not yet in it, my good intention would be realized without difficulty, it was better not to start on an evening when I felt ill-prepared. The following days were not, alas, to prove more propitious. But I was reasonable. It would have been puerile, on the part of one who had waited now for years, not to put up with a postponement of two or three days. Confident that by the day after tomorrow I should have written several pages, I said not a word more to my parents of my decision; I preferred to remain patient and then to bring to a convinced and comforted grandmother a sample of work that was already under way. Unfortunately the next day was not that vast, extraneous expanse of time to which I had feverishly looked forward. When it drew to a close, my laziness and my painful struggle to overcome certain internal obstacles had simply lasted twenty-four hours longer. And at the end of several days, my plans not having matured, I had no longer the same hope that they would be realized at once, and hence no longer the heart to subordinate everything else to their realization: I began once again to keep late hours..." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17931-if-you-want-to-really-hurt-you-parents-and-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 12:19:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charles add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17931-if-you-want-to-really-hurt-you-parents-and-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to really hurt you parents, and you don't have the nerve to be gay, the least you can do is go into the arts. I'm not kidding. The arts are not a way to make a living. They are a very human way of making life more bearable. Practicing an art, no matter how well or badly, is a way to make your soul grow, for heaven's sake. Sing in the shower. Dance to the radio. Tell stories. Write a poem to a friend, even a lousy poem. Do it as well as you possible can. You will get an enormous reward. You will have created something." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
