<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/389323-phil-smith]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/389323-phil-smith" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 21:25:51 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3880-the-cause-of-america-is-in-great-measure-the-cause</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 21:25:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Thomas Paine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3880-the-cause-of-america-is-in-great-measure-the-cause]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The cause of America is in great measure the cause of all mankind." -- Thomas Paine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3882-for-me-it-is-far-better-to-grasp-the-universe</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 21:29:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3882-for-me-it-is-far-better-to-grasp-the-universe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For me, it is far better to grasp the Universe as it really is than to persist in delusion, however satisfying and reassuring." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3883-the-painter-has-the-universe-in-his-mind-and-hands</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 21:30:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Leonardo da Vinci]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3883-the-painter-has-the-universe-in-his-mind-and-hands]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The painter has the Universe in his mind and hands." -- Leonardo da Vinci]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3884-i-would-call-that-man-a-born-artist-whose-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 21:30:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Hans von Marées]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3884-i-would-call-that-man-a-born-artist-whose-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would call that man a born artist whose soul nature has from the very beginning endowed with an ideal, and for whom this ideal replaces the truth; he believes in it without reservation, and his life's task will be to realize it completely for himself, and to set it forth for the contemplation of others." -- Hans von Marées]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3885-we-look-back-through-countless-millions-of-years-and-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 21:31:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by H. G. Wells]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3885-we-look-back-through-countless-millions-of-years-and-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We look back through countless millions of years and see the great will to live struggling out of the intertidal slime, struggling from shape to shape and from power to power, crawling and then walking confidently upon the land, struggling generation after generation to master the air, creeping down the darkness of the deep; we see it turn upon itself in rage and hunger and reshape itself anew, we watch it draw nearer and more akin to us, expanding, elaborating itself, pursuing its relentless inconceivable purpose, until at last it reaches us and its being beats through our brains and arteries...It is possible to believe that all the past is but the beginning of a beginning, and that all that is and has been is but the twilight of the dawn. It is possible to believe that all that the human mind has accomplished is but the dream before the awakening; out of our lineage, minds will spring that will reach back to us in our littleness to know us better than we know ourselves. A day will come, one day in the unending succession of days, when beings, beings who are now latent in our thoughts and hidden in our loins, shall stand upon this earth as one stands upon a footstool, and shall laugh and reach out their hands amidst the stars." -- H. G. Wells]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3886-the-permanent-establishment-of-terrestrial-life-in-space-is-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 21:38:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Phil Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3886-the-permanent-establishment-of-terrestrial-life-in-space-is-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The permanent establishment of terrestrial life in space is as profound an event as the emergence of life itself." -- Phil Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
