<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/394041-madhavi-anant-jha]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/394041-madhavi-anant-jha" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 18:12:10 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155596-awake-shake-dreams-from-your-hair-my-pretty-child-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 18:12:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by The Doors]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155596-awake-shake-dreams-from-your-hair-my-pretty-child-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Awake

Shake

Dreams from your hair 

My pretty child, my sweet one.

Choose the day and choose the sign of your day

The days divinity

First thing you see." -- The Doors]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155597-when-the-first-living-thing-existed-i-was-there-waiting</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 18:21:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155597-when-the-first-living-thing-existed-i-was-there-waiting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the first living thing existed, I was there waiting. When the last living thing dies, my job will be finished. I'll put the chairs on the tables, turn out the lights and lock the universe behind me when I leave." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8150-as-gregor-samsa-awoke-one-morning-from-uneasy-dreams-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 22:25:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8150-as-gregor-samsa-awoke-one-morning-from-uneasy-dreams-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As Gregor Samsa awoke one morning from uneasy dreams he found himself transformed in his bed into a gigantic insect." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/879-only-that-day-dawns-to-which-we-are-awake-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 22:26:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/879-only-that-day-dawns-to-which-we-are-awake-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only that day dawns to which we are awake. There is more day to dawn. The sun is but a morning star." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36496-she-was-lo-plain-lo-in-the-morning-standing-four</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 22:34:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36496-she-was-lo-plain-lo-in-the-morning-standing-four]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was Lo, plain Lo, in the morning, standing four feet ten in one sock. She was Lola in slacks. She was Dolly at school. She was Dolores on the dotted line. But in my arms she was always Lolita." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38362-i-find-suggestion-a-hell-of-a-lot-more-provocative</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 22:34:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Joan Crawford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38362-i-find-suggestion-a-hell-of-a-lot-more-provocative]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I find suggestion a hell of  a lot more provocative than explicit detail. You didn't see Clark[Gable] and Vivien[leigh] rolling around in bed in Gone With The Wind, but you saw that shit eating grin on her face the next morning and you knew damned well she'd gotten properly laid." -- Joan Crawford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28963-i-sit-beside-the-fire-and-think-of-all-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 22:35:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28963-i-sit-beside-the-fire-and-think-of-all-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I sit beside the fire and think 
Of all that I have seen
Of meadow flowers and butterflies
In summers that have been

Of yellow leaves and gossamer
In autumns that there were
With morning mist and silver sun
And wind upon my hair

I sit beside the fire and think
Of how the world will be
When winter comes without a spring 
That I shall ever see

For still there are so many things
That I have never seen
In every wood in every spring
There is a different green

I sit beside the fire and think
Of people long ago
And people that will see a world
That I shall never know

But all the while I sit and think
Of times there were before
I listen for returning feet 
And voices at the door" -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107091-birds-scream-at-the-top-of-their-lungs-in-horrified</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 22:36:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Kurt Cobain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107091-birds-scream-at-the-top-of-their-lungs-in-horrified]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Birds scream at the top of their lungs in horrified hellish rage every morning at daybreak to warn us all of the truth, but sadly we don't speak bird." -- Kurt Cobain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25764-i-slept-with-faith-and-found-a-corpse-in-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 22:36:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Aleister Crowley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25764-i-slept-with-faith-and-found-a-corpse-in-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I slept with faith and found a corpse in my arms on awakening; I drank and danced all night with doubt and found her a virgin in the morning." -- Aleister Crowley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17360-here-i-came-to-the-very-edge-where-nothing-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 22:40:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17360-here-i-came-to-the-very-edge-where-nothing-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here I came to the very edge where nothing at all needs saying...and every day on the balcony of the sea wings open fire is born and everything is blue again like morning." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134199-all-around-me-darkness-gathers-fading-is-the-sun-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 22:42:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134199-all-around-me-darkness-gathers-fading-is-the-sun-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All around me darkness gathers, 
Fading is the sun that shone, 
We must speak of other matters, 
You can be me when I'm gone

Flowers gathered in the morning,
Afternoon they blossom on,
Still are withered in the evening,
You can be me when I'm gone." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23190-good-morning-starshine-the-earth-says-hello</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 22:43:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Tim Burton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23190-good-morning-starshine-the-earth-says-hello]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good morning starshine the earth says hello...." -- Tim Burton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2009 18:45:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lolita, light of my life, fire of my loins. My sin, my soul. Lo-lee-ta: the tip of the tongue taking a trip of three steps down the palate to tap, at three, on the teeth. Lo. Lee. Ta. She was Lo, plain Lo, in the morning, standing four feet ten in one sock. She was Lola in slacks. She was Dolly at school. She was Dolores on the dotted line. But in my arms she was always Lolita. Did she have a precursor? She did, indeed she did. In point of fact, there might have been no Lolita at all had I not loved, one summer, an initial girl-child. In a princedom by the sea. Oh when? About as many years before Lolita was born as my age was that summer. You can always count on a murderer for a fancy prose style. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, exhibit number one is what the seraphs, the misinformed, simple, noble-winged seraphs, envied. Look at this tangle of thorns." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24842-there-s-always-one-who-loves-and-one-who-lets-himself</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2009 08:34:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24842-there-s-always-one-who-loves-and-one-who-lets-himself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's always one who loves and one who lets himself be loved." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111248-i-could-have-forgiven-it-if-he-d-fallen-desperately-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2009 08:39:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111248-i-could-have-forgiven-it-if-he-d-fallen-desperately-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I could have forgiven it if he'd fallen desperately in love with someone and gone off with her. I should have thought that natural. I shouldn't really have blamed him. I should have thought he was led away. Men are so weak, and women are so unscrupulous." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59631-i-want-to-do-with-you-what-spring-does-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 09:05:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59631-i-want-to-do-with-you-what-spring-does-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want
To do with you what spring does with the cherry trees." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 09:18:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98270-mad-girl-s-love-song-i-shut-my-eyes-and-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 09:20:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98270-mad-girl-s-love-song-i-shut-my-eyes-and-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mad Girl's Love Song

I shut my eyes and all the world drops dead;
I lift my lids and all is born again.
(I think I made you up inside my head.)

The stars go waltzing out in blue and red,
And arbitrary blackness gallops in:
I shut my eyes and all the world drops dead.

I dreamed that you bewitched me into bed
And sung me moon-struck, kissed me quite insane.
(I think I made you up inside my head.)

God topples from the sky, hell's fires fade:
Exit seraphim and Satan's men:
I shut my eyes and all the world drops dead.

I fancied you'd return the way you said,
But I grow old and I forget your name.
(I think I made you up inside my head.)

I should have loved a thunderbird instead;
At least when spring comes they roar back again.
I shut my eyes and all the world drops dead.
(I think I made you up inside my head.)" -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12900-the-stars-are-not-wanted-now-put-out-every-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 09:23:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by W. H. Auden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12900-the-stars-are-not-wanted-now-put-out-every-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The stars are not wanted now: put out every one;
Pack up the moon and dismantle the sun;
Pour away the ocean and sweep up the wood.
For nothing now can ever come to any good." -- W. H. Auden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1250-if-i-knew-that-today-would-be-the-last-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 09:37:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1250-if-i-knew-that-today-would-be-the-last-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I knew that today would be the last time I’d see you, I would hug you tight and pray the Lord be the keeper of your soul. If I knew that this would be the last time you pass through this door, I’d embrace you, kiss you, and call you back for one more. If I knew that this would be the last time I would hear your voice, I’d take hold of each word to be able to hear it over and over again. If I knew this is the last time I see you, I’d tell you I love you, and would not just assume foolishly you know it already." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232537-i-ve-changed-my-ways-a-little-i-cannot-now-run</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 07:49:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Robinson Jeffers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232537-i-ve-changed-my-ways-a-little-i-cannot-now-run]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've changed my ways a little, I cannot now
Run with you in the evenings along the shore,
Except in a kind of dream, and you, if you dream a moment,
You see me there." -- Robinson Jeffers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15935-if-you-are-a-dreamer-come-in-if-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 22:02:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Shel Silverstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15935-if-you-are-a-dreamer-come-in-if-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are a dreamer come in
If you are a dreamer a wisher a liar
A hoper a pray-er a magic-bean-buyer
If youre a pretender com sit by my fire
For we have some flax golden tales to spin
Come in! 
Come in!" -- Shel Silverstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132753-somewhere-i-have-never-travelled-gladly-beyond-any-experience-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 22:09:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by E.E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132753-somewhere-i-have-never-travelled-gladly-beyond-any-experience-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["somewhere i have never travelled, gladly beyond
any experience, your eyes have their silence:
in your most frail gesture are things which enclose me,
or which i cannot touch because they are too near

your slightest look easily will unclose me
though i have closed myself as fingers,
you open always petal by petal myself as Spring opens
(touching skilfully, mysteriously) her first rose

or if your wish be to close me, i and
my life will shut very beautifully, suddenly,
as when the heart of this flower imagines
the snow carefully everywhere descending;

nothing which we are to perceive in this world equals
the power of your intense fragility: whose texture
compels me with the colour of its countries,
rendering death and forever with each breathing

(i do not know what it is about you that closes
and opens; only something in me understands
the voice of your eyes is deeper than all roses)
nobody, not even the rain, has such small hands" -- E.E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84061-it-isn-t-possible-to-love-and-part-you-will-wish</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 22:10:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84061-it-isn-t-possible-to-love-and-part-you-will-wish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It isn't possible to love and part.  You will wish that it was.  You can transmute love, ignore it, muddle it, but you can never pull it out of you. I know by experience that the poets are right:  love is eternal." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19648-sometimes-things-become-possible-if-we-want-them-bad-enough</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 22:10:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19648-sometimes-things-become-possible-if-we-want-them-bad-enough]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes things become possible if we want them bad enough." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24973-i-wish-you-could-have-been-there-for-the-sun</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 22:22:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Brian Andreas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24973-i-wish-you-could-have-been-there-for-the-sun]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish you could have been there for the sun &amp; the rain &amp; the long, hard hills. For the sound of a thousand conversations scattered along the road. For the people laughing &amp; crying &amp; remembering at the end. But, mainly, I wish you could have been there." -- Brian Andreas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34357-she-fit-her-head-under-his-chin-and-he-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 22:48:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Charles Frazier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34357-she-fit-her-head-under-his-chin-and-he-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She fit her head under his chin, and he could feel her weight settle into him. He held her tight and words spilled out of him without prior composition. And this time he made no effort to clamp them off. He told her about the first time he had looked on the back of her neck as she sat in the church pew. Of the feeling that had never let go of him since. He talked to her of the great waste of years between then and now. A long time gone. And it was pointless, he said, to think how those years could have been put to better use, for he could hardly have put them to worse. There was no recovering them now. You could grieve endlessly for the loss of time and the damage done therein. For the dead, and for your own lost self. But what the wisdom of the ages says is that we do well not to grieve on and on. And those old ones knew a thing or two and had some truth to tell, Inman said, for you can grieve your heart out and in the end you are still where you are. All your grief hasn't changed a thing. What you have lost will not be returned to you. It will always be lost. You're left with only your scars to mark the void. All you can choose to do is go on or not. But if you go on, it's knowing you carry your scars with you. Nevertheless, over all those wasted years, he had held in his mind the wish to kiss her on the back of her neck, and now he had done it. There was a redemption of some kind, he believed, in such complete fulfillment of a desire so long deferred." -- Charles Frazier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83887-i-always-wished-that-i-could-find-someone-as-beautiful</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 23:33:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Madonna]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83887-i-always-wished-that-i-could-find-someone-as-beautiful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I always wished that I could find someone as beautiful as you, but in the process I forgot that I was special too. " -- Madonna]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97111-we-dance-for-laughter-we-dance-for-tears-we-dance</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 00:00:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97111-we-dance-for-laughter-we-dance-for-tears-we-dance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We dance for laughter, we dance for tears, we dance for madness, we dance for fears, we dance for hopes, we dance for screams, we are the dancers, we create the dreams." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132670-i-hope-you-will-have-a-wonderful-year-that-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 00:01:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madhavi Anant add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132670-i-hope-you-will-have-a-wonderful-year-that-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hope you will have a wonderful year, that you'll dream dangerously and outrageously, that you'll make something that didn't exist before you made it, that you will be loved and that you will be liked, and that you will have people to love and to like in return. And, most importantly (because I think there should be more kindness and more wisdom in the world right now), that you will, when you need to be, be wise, and that you will always be kind." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
