<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/39443-christy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/39443-christy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 05:27:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 05:27:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64745-i-ve-never-been-lost-but-i-was-mighty-turned-around</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2008 08:47:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Daniel Boone]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64745-i-ve-never-been-lost-but-i-was-mighty-turned-around]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've never been lost, but I was mighty turned around for three days once." -- Daniel Boone]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 08:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161067-encouragement-requires-empathy-and-seeing-the-world-from-your-spouse-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 09:45:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Gary Chapman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161067-encouragement-requires-empathy-and-seeing-the-world-from-your-spouse-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Encouragement requires empathy and seeing the world from your spouse's perspective. We must first learn what is important to our spouse. Only then can we give encouragement. With verbal encouragement, we are trying to communicate, &quot;I know. I care. I am with you. How can I help?&quot; We are trying to show that we believe in him and in his abilities. We are giving credit and praise." -- Gary Chapman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 12:49:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 12:49:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 12:50:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't interest me what you do for a living. I want to know what you ache for, and if you dare to dream of meeting your heart's longing.
It doesn't interest me how old you are. I want to know if you will risk looking like a fool for love, for your dream, for the adventure of being alive. 
It doesn't interest me what planets are squaring your moon. I want to know if you have touched the center of your own sorrow, if you have been opened by life's betrayals or have become shriveled and closed from fear of further pain!I want to know if you can sit with pain, mine or your own, without moving to hide it or fade it, or fix it. 
I want to know if you can be with joy, mine or your own, if you can dance with wildness and let the ecstasy fill you to the tips of your fingers and toes without cautioning us to be careful, to be realistic, to remember the limitations of being human. 
It doesn't interest me if the story you are telling me is true. I want to know if you can disappoint another to be true to yourself; if you can bear the accusation of betrayal and not betray your own soul; if you can be faithlessand therefore trustworthy. 
I want to know if you can see beauty even when it's not pretty, every day,and if you can source your own life from its presence. 
I want to know if you can live with failure, yours and mine, and still stand on the edge of the lake and shout to the silver of the full moon, “Yes!”
It doesn't interest me to know where you live or how much money you have. I want to know if you can get up, after the night of grief and despair, weary and bruised to the bone, and do what needs to be done to feed the children. 
It doesn't interest me who you know or how you came to be here. I want to know if you will stand in the center of the fire with me and not shrink back. 
It doesn't interest me where or what or with whom you have studied. I want to know what sustains you, from the inside, when all else falls away. 
I want to know if you can be alone with yourself and if you truly like the company you keep in the empty moments." -- Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329177-if-you-weren-t-driving-i-d-kiss-you-senseless-i-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 12:33:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329177-if-you-weren-t-driving-i-d-kiss-you-senseless-i-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you weren't driving, I'd kiss you senseless,&quot; I tell him.
He swerves to the side of the road and stops the car abruptly.
&quot;Not driving any more." -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/981712-espresso-now-there-s-a-pointless-substance-anything-served-in-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 18:46:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Paul J. Newell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/981712-espresso-now-there-s-a-pointless-substance-anything-served-in-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Espresso, now there’s a pointless substance. Anything served in a thimble I do not class as a beverage." -- Paul J. Newell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/981797-call-me-a-prude-but-i-m-a-stickler-for-furnishings</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 19:49:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Paul J. Newell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/981797-call-me-a-prude-but-i-m-a-stickler-for-furnishings]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Call me a prude but I’m a stickler for furnishings in my household not doing things without my say so. If there’s one thing that bugs me it’s being second-guessed by my décor." -- Paul J. Newell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/982929-and-in-the-end-that-s-what-does-it-for-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 18:50:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Paul J. Newell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/982929-and-in-the-end-that-s-what-does-it-for-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And in the end that’s what does it for you. Not that they excite you, but that you can excite them. That’s the drug that draws you in, pulls you back. It gives meaning to your existence, solidifies your purpose." -- Paul J. Newell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/602841-off-topic-but-what-a-slut-time-is-she-screws</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 19:30:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/602841-off-topic-but-what-a-slut-time-is-she-screws]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["(Off topic, but: What a slut time is. She screws everybody.)" -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/975570-the-fault-dear-brutus-is-not-in-our-stars</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 19:31:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/975570-the-fault-dear-brutus-is-not-in-our-stars]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fault, dear Brutus, is not in our stars / But in ourselves.” Easy enough to say when you’re a Roman nobleman (or Shakespeare!), but there is no shortage of fault to be found amid our stars." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1022099-i-am-he-said-he-was-staring-at-me-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 18:34:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1022099-i-am-he-said-he-was-staring-at-me-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am,” he said. He was staring at me, and I could see the corners of his eyes crinkling. “I’m in love with you, and I’m not in the business of denying myself the simple pleasure of saying true things. I’m in love with you, and I know that love is just a shout into the void, and that oblivion is inevitable, and that we’re all doomed and that there will come a day when all our labor has been returned to dust, and I know the sun will swallow the only earth we’ll ever have, and I am in love with you." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1022104-they-looked-for-all-the-world-like-miniaturized-rose-petals</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 18:44:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1022104-they-looked-for-all-the-world-like-miniaturized-rose-petals]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They looked for all the world like miniaturized rose petals drained of their color. These pale petals were gathering in the wind like flocking birds—thousands of them, like a spring snowstorm." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/971120-do-you-know-he-asked-in-a-delicious-accent-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 18:49:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/971120-do-you-know-he-asked-in-a-delicious-accent-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you know,” he asked in a delicious accent, “what Dom Pérignon said after inventing champagne?” “No?” I said. “He called out to his fellow monks, ‘Come quickly: I am tasting the stars." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1023403-my-dad-was-waiting-for-us-in-baggage-claim-standing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 19:56:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1023403-my-dad-was-waiting-for-us-in-baggage-claim-standing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My dad was waiting for us in baggage claim, standing amid all the limo drivers in suits holding signs printed with the last names of their passengers: JOHNSON, BARRINGTON, CARMICHAEL. Dad had a sign of his own. MY BEAUTIFUL FAMILY, it read, and then underneath that (AND GUS)." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1035850-when-you-have-a-ceo-who-is-so-ingrained-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 19:03:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by James M. Kouzes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1035850-when-you-have-a-ceo-who-is-so-ingrained-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["when you have a CEO who is so ingrained in the agency, staff, and each and every one of the clients, you only want to push yourself further.” Because Barby is so transparent about her values and vision for the organization, “There’s no question,” according to Alison, “that people want to follow her." -- James M. Kouzes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1035862-exemplary-leaders-know-that-if-they-want-to-gain-commitment</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 19:19:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by James M. Kouzes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1035862-exemplary-leaders-know-that-if-they-want-to-gain-commitment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Exemplary leaders know that if they want to gain commitment and achieve the highest standards, they must be models of the behavior they expect of others." -- James M. Kouzes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1081213-although-deep-down-i-think-i-had-known-this-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 19:18:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Paul J. Newell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1081213-although-deep-down-i-think-i-had-known-this-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Although, deep down, I think I had known this all along. I was not aware of the mechanism, but I had always felt that through my learning I was reawakening an ancient skill. The fact is that before humans developed spoken language we had communicated for millennia by other means; by body language and facial expressions and scent. I had found the key to turn this skill back on. The pertinent question was why it was ever switched off." -- Paul J. Newell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1085259-it-made-me-realise-just-how-desperate-the-world-is-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 19:07:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Paul J. Newell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1085259-it-made-me-realise-just-how-desperate-the-world-is-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It made me realise just how desperate the world is for a superhero. I don’t just mean those of the comic books. For there is an inexhaustible supply of would-be superheroes throughout history and across the globe. From the legends of King Arthur and Robin Hood, to the Gods of a thousand religions. From Santa Claus to Peter Pan to a myriad other folklore characters. Monsters from the Lochs. Spirits from the other side. Aliens from distant planets. The world longs for something ... something else. Something powerful and exciting. A little bit of magic." -- Paul J. Newell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1172136-she-thrust-herself-into-your-life-pulling-you-into-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 19:45:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by P.T. Michelle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1172136-she-thrust-herself-into-your-life-pulling-you-into-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She thrust herself into your life, pulling you into a tight hug before you even had a chance to say, “Welcome to my personal space." -- P.T. Michelle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1219532-it-gives-me-such-a-twist-of-pleasure-to-watch</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 18:17:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Rae Carson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1219532-it-gives-me-such-a-twist-of-pleasure-to-watch]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["it gives me such a twist of pleasure to watch her react to praise from someone she despises. The Scriptura Sancta calls it “the fire of kindness." -- Rae Carson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
