<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/395791-erik]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/395791-erik" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 23:41:31 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512501-to-allow-the-market-mechanism-to-be-sole-director-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 23:41:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Karl Polanyi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512501-to-allow-the-market-mechanism-to-be-sole-director-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...To allow the market mechanism to be sole director of the fate of human beings and their natural environment, indeed, even of the amount and use of purchasing power, would result in the demolition of society. For the alleged commodity, &quot;labor power&quot; cannot be shoved about, used indiscriminately, or even left unused, without affecting the human individual who happens to be the bearer of this peculiar commodity. In disposing of a man's labor power the system would, incidentally, dispose of the physical, psychological, and moral entity of &quot;man&quot; attached to the tag. Robbed of the protective covering of cultural institutions, human beings would perish from the the effects of social exposure; they would die as the victims of acute social dislocation through vice, perversion, crime, and starvation. Nature would be reduced to its elements, neighborhoods and landscapes defiled, rovers polluted, military safety jeopardized, the power to produce food and raw materials destroyed..." -- Karl Polanyi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512504-at-that-time-macondo-was-a-village-of-twenty-adobe</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 23:42:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512504-at-that-time-macondo-was-a-village-of-twenty-adobe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At that time Macondo was a village of twenty adobe houses, built on the bank of a river of clear water that ran along a bed of polished stones, which were white and enormous, like prehistoric eggs. The world was so recent that many things lacked names, and in order to indicate them it was necessary to point..." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512510-the-silence-of-a-place-where-there-were-once-horses</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 23:52:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by W.S. Merwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512510-the-silence-of-a-place-where-there-were-once-horses]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...The silence of a place where there were once horses
is a mountain

and I have seen by lightning that ever mountain
once fell from the air
ringing
like the chime of an iron shoe..." -- W.S. Merwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
