<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/395772-wendy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/395772-wendy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 11:04:59 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56756-prayer-is-a-relationship-half-the-job-is-mine-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 11:04:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56756-prayer-is-a-relationship-half-the-job-is-mine-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Prayer is a relationship; half the job is mine.  If I want transformation, but can't even be bothered to articulate what, exactly, I'm aiming for, how will it ever occur?  Half the benefit of prayer is in the asking itself, in the offering of a clearly posed and well-considered intention.  If you don't have this, all your pleas and desires are boneless, floppy, inert; they swirl at your feet in a cold fog and never lift." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111769-as-i-focus-on-diligent-joy-i-also-keep-remembering</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 11:11:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111769-as-i-focus-on-diligent-joy-i-also-keep-remembering]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As I focus on diligent joy, I also keep remembering a simple idea my friend Darcey told me once -- that all the sorrow and trouble of this world is caused by unhappy people.  Not only in the big global Hitler-'n'-Stalin picture, but also on the smallest personal level.  Even in my own life, I can see exactly where my episodes of unhappiness have brought suffering or distress or (at the very least) inconvenience to those around me.  The search for contentment is, therefore, not merely a self-preserving and self-benefiting act, but also a generous gift to the world.  Clearing out all your misery gets you out of the way.  You cease being an obstacle, not only to yourself but to anyone else.  Only then are you free to serve and enjoy other people." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111772-there-s-a-reason-we-refer-to-leaps-of-faith--</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 11:16:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111772-there-s-a-reason-we-refer-to-leaps-of-faith--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's a reason we refer to &quot;leaps of faith&quot; - because the decision to consent to any notion of divinity is a mighty jump from the rational over to the unknowable, and I don't care how diligently scholars of every religion will try to sit you down with their stacks of books and prove to you through scripture that their faith is indeed rational; it isn't.  If faith were rational, it wouldn't be - by definition - faith.  Faith is belief in what you cannot see or prove or touch.  Faith is walking face-first and full-speed into the dark.  If we truly knew all the answers in advance as to the meaning of life and the nature of God and the destiny of our souls, our belief would not be a leap of faith and it would not be a courageous act of humanity; it would just be... a prudent insurance policy." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/597685-i-don-t-believe-in-twisting-yourself-into-knots-of-excuses</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 07:47:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendy add a quote by Julia Child]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/597685-i-don-t-believe-in-twisting-yourself-into-knots-of-excuses]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't believe in twisting yourself into knots of excuses and explanations over the food you make.  When one's hostess starts in with self-deprecations such as &quot;Oh, I don't know how to cook...,&quot; or &quot;Poor little me...,&quot; or &quot;This may taste awful...,&quot; it is so dreadful to have to reassure her that everything is delicious and fine, whether it is or not.  Besides, such admissions only draw attention to one's shortcomings (or self-perceived shortcomings), and make the other person think, &quot;Yes, you're right, this really is an awful meal!&quot; Maybe the cat has fallen into the stew, or the lettuce has frozen, or the cake has collapsed -- eh bien, tant pis!  Usually one's cooking is better than one thinks it is.  And if the food is truly vile, as my ersatz eggs Florentine surely were, then the cook must simply grit her teeth and bear it with a smile -- and learn from her mistakes." -- Julia Child]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706131-in-other-words-to-live-eternal-life-in-the-full</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 18:01:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendy add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706131-in-other-words-to-live-eternal-life-in-the-full]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In other words to live Eternal Life in the full and final sense is to be with God as Christ is with him, and with each other as Christ is with us." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
