<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/398225-natalia]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/398225-natalia" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 23:24:48 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224609-i-m-just-tired-of-hearing-about-god-all-the-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 23:24:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by Lorraine Hansberry ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224609-i-m-just-tired-of-hearing-about-god-all-the-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm just tired of hearing about God all the time. What has He got to do with anything?... I'm not going to be immoral or commit crimes because I don't believe. I don't even think about that. I just get so tired of Him getting the credit for things the human race achieves through its own effort. Now, there simply is no God. There's only man. And it's he who makes miracles." -- Lorraine Hansberry ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119224-i-close-my-eyes-and-i-let-my-body-shut</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 22:17:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by James Frey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119224-i-close-my-eyes-and-i-let-my-body-shut]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I close my eyes and I let my body shut itself down and I let my mind wander.  It wanders to a familiar place.  A place I don’t talk about or acknowledge exists.  A place where there is only me.  A place that I hate.  I am alone.  Alone here and alone in the world.  Alone in my heart and alone in my mind.  Alone everywhere, all the time, for as long as I can remember.  Alone with my Family, alone with my friends, alone in a Room full of People.  Alone when I wake, alone through each awful day, alone when I finally meet the blackness.  I am alone in my horror.  Alone in my horror.  I don’t want to be alone.  I have never wanted to be alone.  I fucking hate it.  I hate that I have no one to talk to, I hate that I have no one to call, I hate that I have no one to hold my hand, hug me, tell me everything is going to be all right.  I hate that I have no one to share my hopes and dreams with, I hate that I no longer have any hopes or dreams, I hate that I have no one to tell me to hold on, that I can find them again.   I hate that when I scream, and I scream bloody murder, that I am screaming into emptiness.  I hate that there is no one to hear my scream and that there is no one to help me learn how to stop screaming. . .  More than anything, all I have ever wanted is to be close to someone.  More than anything, all I have ever wanted is to feel as if I wasn’t alone." -- James Frey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132325-let-us-learn-to-show-our-friendship-for-a-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 15:05:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalia add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132325-let-us-learn-to-show-our-friendship-for-a-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let us learn to show our friendship for a man when he is alive and not after he is dead." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
