<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/399090-walter]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/399090-walter" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 15:26:59 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18410-i-think-we-are-well-advised-to-keep-on-nodding</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 15:26:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18410-i-think-we-are-well-advised-to-keep-on-nodding]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think we are well advised to keep on nodding terms with the  people we used to be, whether we find them attractive company or not.  Otherwise they turn up unannounced and surprise us, come hammering on the mind's door at 4 a.m. of a bad night and demand to know who deserted them, who betrayed them, who is going to make amends." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22079-gradually-it-was-disclosed-to-me-that-the-line-separating</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 14:26:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22079-gradually-it-was-disclosed-to-me-that-the-line-separating]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Gradually it was disclosed to me that the line separating good and evil passes not through states, nor between classes, nor between political parties either -- but right through every human heart -- and through all human hearts. This line shifts. Inside us, it oscillates with the years. And even within hearts overwhelmed by evil, one small bridgehead of good is retained. And even in the best of all hearts, there remains ... an unuprooted small corner of evil. 

Since then I have come to understand the truth of all the religions of the world: They struggle with the &lt;i&gt;evil inside a human being&lt;/i&gt; (inside every human being). It is impossible to expel evil from the world in its entirety, but it is possible to constrict it within each person." -- Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150847-there-s-always-time-for-one-more-pint---chief-inspector</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 10:06:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Colin Dexter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150847-there-s-always-time-for-one-more-pint---chief-inspector]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's always time for one more pint. - Chief Inspector Morse" -- Colin Dexter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1-the-story-so-far-in-the-beginning-the-universe-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2013 20:25:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1-the-story-so-far-in-the-beginning-the-universe-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The story so far:
In the beginning the Universe was created.
This has made a lot of people very angry and been widely regarded as a bad move." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/811-for-instance-on-the-planet-earth-man-had-always-assumed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2013 20:25:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/811-for-instance-on-the-planet-earth-man-had-always-assumed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For instance, on the planet Earth, man had always assumed that he was more intelligent than dolphins because he had achieved so much&amp;mdash;the wheel, New York, wars and so on&amp;mdash;whilst all the dolphins had ever done was muck about in the water having a good time. But conversely, the dolphins had always believed that they were far more intelligent than man&amp;mdash;for precisely the same reasons." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3047-don-t-panic</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2013 20:25:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3047-don-t-panic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't Panic." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6344-time-is-an-illusion-lunchtime-doubly-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2013 20:25:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6344-time-is-an-illusion-lunchtime-doubly-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time is an illusion. Lunchtime doubly so." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14434-space-is-big-you-just-won-t-believe-how-vastly-hugely</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2013 20:26:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14434-space-is-big-you-just-won-t-believe-how-vastly-hugely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Space is big. You just won't believe how vastly, hugely, mind-bogglingly big it is. I mean, you may think it's a long way down the road to the chemist's, but that's just peanuts to space." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3066-let-s-think-the-unthinkable-let-s-do-the-undoable-let-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2013 20:26:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3066-let-s-think-the-unthinkable-let-s-do-the-undoable-let-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let's think the unthinkable, let's do the undoable. Let us prepare to grapple with the ineffable itself, and see if we may not eff it after all." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69255-so-this-is-it-said-arthur-we-are-going-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2013 20:27:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69255-so-this-is-it-said-arthur-we-are-going-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So this is it,&quot; said Arthur, &quot;We are going to die.&quot;
&quot;Yes,&quot; said Ford, &quot;except... no! Wait a minute!&quot; He suddenly lunged across the chamber at something behind Arthur's line of vision. &quot;What's this switch?&quot; he cried.
&quot;What? Where?&quot; cried Arthur, twisting round.
&quot;No, I was only fooling,&quot; said Ford, &quot;we are going to die after all." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11056-it-is-a-mistake-to-think-you-can-solve-any</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2013 20:29:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11056-it-is-a-mistake-to-think-you-can-solve-any]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a mistake to think you can solve any major problems just with potatoes." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135260-in-the-great-debate-that-has-raged-for-centuries-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 09:10:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135260-in-the-great-debate-that-has-raged-for-centuries-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the great debate that has raged for centuries about what, if anything, happens to you after death, be it heaven, hell, purgatory or extinction, one thing has never been in doubt - that you would at least know the answer when you were dead." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/327077-religion-has-certain-ideas-at-the-heart-of-it-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 09:14:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/327077-religion-has-certain-ideas-at-the-heart-of-it-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Religion... has certain ideas at the heart of it which we call sacred or holy or whatever... If someone votes for a party that you don't agree with, you're free to argue about it as much as you like; everybody will have an argument but nobody feels aggrieved by it. If somebody thinks taxes should go up or down you are free to have an argument about it. But on the other hand if somebody says 'I must [not] move a light switch on a Saturday', you say, 'I respect that'... Yet when you look at it rationally there is no reason why those ideas shouldn't be as open to debate as any other, except that we have agreed somehow between us that they shouldn't be." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/683-i-don-t-accept-the-currently-fashionable-assertion-that-any-view</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 13:51:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/683-i-don-t-accept-the-currently-fashionable-assertion-that-any-view]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't accept the currently fashionable assertion that any view is automatically as worthy of respect as any equal and opposite view. My view is that the moon is made of rock. If someone says to me 'Well, you haven't been there, have you? You haven't seen it for yourself, so my view that it is made of Norwegian Beaver Cheese is equally valid' - then I can't even be bothered to argue. There is such a thing as the burden of proof, and in the case of god, as in the case of the composition of the moon, this has shifted radically. God used to be the best explanation we'd got, and we've now got vastly better ones. God is no longer an explanation of anything, but has instead become something that would itself need an insurmountable amount of explaining. So I don't think that being convinced that there is no god is as irrational or arrogant a point of view as belief that there is. I don't think the matter calls for even-handedness at all." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52534-when-we-find-ourselves-in-a-midlife-depression-suddenly-hate</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 21:02:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Robert A Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52534-when-we-find-ourselves-in-a-midlife-depression-suddenly-hate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we find ourselves in a midlife depression, suddenly hate our spouse, our jobs, our lives – we can be sure that the unlived life is seeking our attention. When we feel restless, bored, or empty despite an outer life filled with riches, the unlived life is asking for us to engage. To not do this work will leave us depleted and despondent, with a nagging sense of ennui or failure. As you may have already discovered, doing or acquiring more does not quell your unease or dissatisfaction. Neither will “meditating on the light” or attempting to rise above the sufferings of earthly existence. Only awareness of your shadow qualities can help you to find an appropriate place for your unredeemed darkness and thereby create a more satisfying experience. To not do this work is to remain trapped in the loneliness, anxiety, and dualistic limits of the ego instead of awakening to your higher calling." -- Robert A Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160611-a-man-needs-a-little-madness-or-else-he-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 16:04:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Nikos Kazantzakis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160611-a-man-needs-a-little-madness-or-else-he-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man needs a little madness, or else... he never dares cut the rope and be free." -- Nikos Kazantzakis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11263-this-is-true-happiness-to-have-no-ambition-and-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 16:08:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Nikos Kazantzakis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11263-this-is-true-happiness-to-have-no-ambition-and-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is true happiness:  to have no ambition and to work like a horse as if you had every ambition.  To live far from men, not to need them and yet to love them.  To have the stars above, the land to your left and the sea to your right and to realize of a sudden that in your heart, life has accomplished its final miracle:  it has become a fairy tale." -- Nikos Kazantzakis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/734813-i-felt-once-more-how-simple-and-frugal-a-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 16:08:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Nikos Kazantzakis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/734813-i-felt-once-more-how-simple-and-frugal-a-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I felt once more how simple and frugal a thing is happiness: a glass of wine, a roast chestnut, a wretched little brazier, the sound of the sea. Nothing else." -- Nikos Kazantzakis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220397-look-one-day-i-had-gone-to-a-little-village</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 16:09:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walter add a quote by Nikos Kazantzakis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220397-look-one-day-i-had-gone-to-a-little-village]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look, one day I had gone to a little village.  An old grandfather of ninety was busy planting an almond tree.  ‘What, grandfather!’ I exclaimed.  ‘Planting an almond tree?’  And he, bent as he was, turned around and said: ‘My son, I carry on as if I should never die.’  I replied: ‘And I carry on as if I was going to die any minute.’ 

Which of us was right, boss?" -- Nikos Kazantzakis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
