<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/40158-jennifer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/40158-jennifer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 12:59:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308860-i-have-traveled-widely-i-have-seen-this-country-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 12:59:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jennifer add a quote by Peter Carey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308860-i-have-traveled-widely-i-have-seen-this-country-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have traveled widely. I have seen this country in its infancy. I tell you what it will become. The public squares will be occupied by an uneducated class who will not be able to quote a line of Shakespeare." -- Peter Carey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27147-you-never-have-to-change-anything-you-got-up-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 12:53:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jennifer add a quote by Saul Bellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27147-you-never-have-to-change-anything-you-got-up-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You never have to change anything you got up in the middle of the night to write." -- Saul Bellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19249-it-s-usually-the-selfish-people-who-are-loved-the-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 15:44:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jennifer add a quote by Saul Bellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19249-it-s-usually-the-selfish-people-who-are-loved-the-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's usually the selfish people who are loved the most. They do what you deny yourself, and you love them for it. You give them your heart." -- Saul Bellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177590-every-one-suspects-himself-of-at-least-one-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 15:45:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jennifer add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177590-every-one-suspects-himself-of-at-least-one-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every one suspects himself of at least one of the cardinal virtues, and this is mine: I am one of the few honest people that I have ever known." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114988-curiosity-is-insubordination-in-its-purest-form</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 15:52:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jennifer add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114988-curiosity-is-insubordination-in-its-purest-form]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Curiosity is insubordination in its purest form." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85163-the-disappearance-of-a-sense-of-responsibility-is-the-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 22:14:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jennifer add a quote by Stanley Milgram]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85163-the-disappearance-of-a-sense-of-responsibility-is-the-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The disappearance of a sense of responsibility is the most far-reaching consequence of submission to authority." -- Stanley Milgram]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245873-what-happened-between-us-both-happened-and-didn-t-happen-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 14:24:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jennifer add a quote by Javier Marías]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245873-what-happened-between-us-both-happened-and-didn-t-happen-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What happened between us both happened and didn't happen, it's the same with everything, why do or not do something, why say &quot;yes&quot; or &quot;no,&quot; why worry yourself with a &quot;perhaps&quot; or a &quot;maybe,&quot; why speak, why remain silent, why refuse, why know anything if nothing of what happens happens, because nothing happens without interruption, nothing lasts or endures or is ceaselessly remembered, what takes place is identical to what doesn't take place, what we dismiss or allow to slip by us is identical to what we accept and seize, what we experience identical to what we never try; we pour all our intelligence and out feelings and our enthusiasm into the task of discriminating between things that will all be made equal, if they haven't already been, and that's why we're so full of regrets and lost opportunities, of confirmations and reaffirmations and opportunities grasped, when the truth is that nothing is affirmed and everything is constantly in the process of being lost. Or perhaps there never was anything." -- Javier Marías]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51063-i-wonder-which-is-preferable-to-walk-around-all-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 22:27:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jennifer add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51063-i-wonder-which-is-preferable-to-walk-around-all-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wonder which is preferable, to walk around all your life swollen up with your own secrets until you burst from the pressure of them, or to have them sucked out of you, every paragraph, every sentence, every word of them, so at the end you're depleted of all that was once as precious to you as hoarded gold, as close to you as your skin - everything that was of the deepest importance to you, everything that made you cringe and wish to conceal, everything that belonged to you alone - and must spend the rest of your days like an empty sack flapping in the wind, an empty sack branded with a bright fluorescent label so that everyone will know what sort of secrets used to be inside you?" -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
