<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/40204-theresa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/40204-theresa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2009 10:31:15 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2009 10:31:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lolita, light of my life, fire of my loins. My sin, my soul. Lo-lee-ta: the tip of the tongue taking a trip of three steps down the palate to tap, at three, on the teeth. Lo. Lee. Ta. She was Lo, plain Lo, in the morning, standing four feet ten in one sock. She was Lola in slacks. She was Dolly at school. She was Dolores on the dotted line. But in my arms she was always Lolita. Did she have a precursor? She did, indeed she did. In point of fact, there might have been no Lolita at all had I not loved, one summer, an initial girl-child. In a princedom by the sea. Oh when? About as many years before Lolita was born as my age was that summer. You can always count on a murderer for a fancy prose style. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, exhibit number one is what the seraphs, the misinformed, simple, noble-winged seraphs, envied. Look at this tangle of thorns." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47882-to-crave-and-to-have-are-as-like-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2009 10:32:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47882-to-crave-and-to-have-are-as-like-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To crave and to have are as like as a thing and its shadow. For when does a berry break upon the tongue as sweetly as when one longs to taste it, and when is the taste refracted into so many hues and savors of ripeness and earth, and when do our senses know any thing so utterly as when we lack it? And here again is a foreshadowing -- the world will be made whole. For to wish for a hand on one's hair is all but to feel it. So whatever we may lose, very craving gives it back to us again." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53417-a-man-can-know-his-father-or-his-son-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 13:08:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53417-a-man-can-know-his-father-or-his-son-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man can know his father, or his son, and there might still be nothing between them but loyalty and love and mutual incomprehension." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113320-grace-has-a-grand-laughter-in-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 13:08:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113320-grace-has-a-grand-laughter-in-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Grace has a grand laughter in it." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/349991-there-s-so-much-to-be-grateful-for-words-are-poor</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 13:09:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/349991-there-s-so-much-to-be-grateful-for-words-are-poor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's so much to be grateful for, words are poor things." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125911-a-story-has-no-beginning-or-end-arbitrarily-one-chooses</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 13:17:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125911-a-story-has-no-beginning-or-end-arbitrarily-one-chooses]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A story has no beginning or end: arbitrarily one chooses that moment of experience from which to look back or from which to look ahead." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122822-when-i-began-to-write-our-story-down-i-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 13:18:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122822-when-i-began-to-write-our-story-down-i-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I began to write our story down, I thought I was writing a record of hate, but somehow the hate has got mislaid and all I know is that in spite of her mistakes and her unreliability, she was better than most. It's just as well that one of us should believe in her: she never did in herself." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310990-i-ve-caught-belief-like-a-disease-i-ve-fallen-into-belief</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 13:21:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310990-i-ve-caught-belief-like-a-disease-i-ve-fallen-into-belief]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've caught belief like a disease.  I've fallen into belief like I fell in love." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240275-they-say-that-every-snowflake-is-different-if-that-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 13:27:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240275-they-say-that-every-snowflake-is-different-if-that-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They say that every snowflake is different. If that were true, how could the world go on? How could we ever get up off our knees? How could we ever recover from the wonder of it?

By forgetting. We cannot keep in mind too many things.
    There is only the present and nothing to remember." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119429-julia-s-vocabulary-was-chock-full-of-strangely-archaic-words---spiffing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 13:54:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Kate Atkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119429-julia-s-vocabulary-was-chock-full-of-strangely-archaic-words---spiffing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Julia's vocabulary was &quot;chock-full&quot; of strangely archaic words - &quot;spiffing,&quot; &quot;crumbs,&quot; &quot;jeepers&quot; - that seemed to have originated in some prewar girls' annual rather than in Julia's own life. For Jackson, words were functional, they helped you get to places and explain things. For Julia, they were freighted with inexplicable emotion." -- Kate Atkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392451-olivia-was-her-only-beautiful-child-julia-with-her-dark</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 13:57:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Kate Atkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392451-olivia-was-her-only-beautiful-child-julia-with-her-dark]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Olivia was her only beautiful child. Julia, with her dark curls and snub nose, was pretty but her character wasn't, Sylvia --- poor Sylvia, what could you say? And Amelia was somehow ...bland, but Olivia, Olivia was spun from light. It seemed impossible that she was Victor's child, although, unfortunately, there was no doubting the fact. Olivia was the only one she loved, although God knows she tried her best with the others. Everything was from duty, nothing from love. Duty killed you in the end." -- Kate Atkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/447369-i-will-love-you-as-a-drawer-loves-a-secret</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 17:29:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/447369-i-will-love-you-as-a-drawer-loves-a-secret]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will love you as a drawer loves a secret compartment, and as a secret compartment loves a secret, and as a secret loves to make a person gasp, and as a gasping person loves a glass of brandy to calm their nerves, and as a glass of brandy loves to shatter on the floor, and as the noise of glass shattering loves to make someone else gasp, and as someone else gasping loves a nearby desk to lean against, even if leaning against it presses a lever that loves to open a drawer and reveal a secret compartment. I will love you until all such compartments are discovered and opened, and until all the secrets have gone gasping into the world." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34449-strange-as-it-may-seem-i-still-hope-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 17:30:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34449-strange-as-it-may-seem-i-still-hope-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Strange as it may seem, I still hope for the best, even though the best, like an interesting piece of mail, so rarely arrives, and even when it does it can be lost so easily." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209357-we-star-crossed-lovers-of-district-12-who-suffered-so-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 15:00:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Theresa add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209357-we-star-crossed-lovers-of-district-12-who-suffered-so-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We star-crossed lovers of District 12, who suffered so much and enjoyed so little the rewards of our victory, do not seek our fans' favor, grace them with our smiles, or catch their kisses. We are unforgiving.
    And I love it. Getting to be myself at last." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
