<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/402005-amy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/402005-amy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 00:42:07 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334309-girls-are-taught-a-lot-of-stuff-growing-up-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 00:42:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Greg Behrendt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334309-girls-are-taught-a-lot-of-stuff-growing-up-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Girls are taught a lot of stuff growing up. If a guy punches you he likes you. Never try to trim your own bangs and someday you will meet a wonderful guy and get your very own happy ending. Every movie we see, Every story we're told implores us to wait for it, the third act twist, the unexpected declaration of love, the exception to the rule. But sometimes we're so focused on finding our happy ending we don't learn how to read the signs. How to tell from the ones who want us and the ones who don't, the ones who will stay and the ones who will leave. And maybe a happy ending doesn't include a guy, maybe... it's you, on your own, picking up the pieces and starting over, freeing yourself up for something better in the future. Maybe the happy ending is... just... moving on. Or maybe the happy ending is this, knowing after all the unreturned phone calls, broken-hearts, through the blunders and misread signals, through all the pain and embarrassment you never gave up hope." -- Greg Behrendt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278921-desiring-another-person-is-perhaps-the-most-risky-endeavor-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 21:47:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278921-desiring-another-person-is-perhaps-the-most-risky-endeavor-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Desiring another person is perhaps the most risky endeavor of all. As soon as you want somebody—really want him—it is as though you have taken a surgical needle and sutured your happiness to the skin of that person, so that any separation will now cause a lacerating injury." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274412-i-desire-to-be-with-you-i-miss-you-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 21:49:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Jack Llawayllynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274412-i-desire-to-be-with-you-i-miss-you-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I desire to be with you. I miss you. I feel lonely when I can't see you. I am obsessed with you, fascinated by you, infatuated with you. I hunger for your taste, your smell, the feel of your soul touching mine." -- Jack Llawayllynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
