<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/402362-nicole]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/402362-nicole" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 22:37:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27788-when-will-our-consciences-grow-so-tender-that-we-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 22:37:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27788-when-will-our-consciences-grow-so-tender-that-we-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When will our consciences grow so tender that we will act to prevent human misery rather than avenge it?" -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191747-i-will-find-you-he-whispered-in-my-ear-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 10:52:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Diana Gabaldon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191747-i-will-find-you-he-whispered-in-my-ear-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will find you,&quot; he whispered in my ear.  &quot;I promise.  If I must endure two hundred years of purgatory, two hundred years without you - then that is my punishment, which I have earned for my crimes.  For I have lied, and killed, and stolen; betrayed and broken trust.  But there is the one thing that shall lie in the balance.  When I shall stand before God, I shall have one thing to say, to weigh against the rest.&quot;

His voice dropped, nearly to a whisper, and his arms tightened around me.

Lord, ye gave me a rare woman, and God!  I loved her well." -- Diana Gabaldon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19986-i-talk-to-you-as-i-talk-to-my-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 10:53:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Diana Gabaldon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19986-i-talk-to-you-as-i-talk-to-my-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I talk to you as I talk to my own soul,&quot; he said, turning me to face him. He reached up and cupped my cheek, fingers light on my temple. &quot;And Sassenach,&quot; he whispered, &quot;Your face is my heart." -- Diana Gabaldon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/347523-any-piece-of-good-music-is-in-essence-a-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 10:54:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Diana Gabaldon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/347523-any-piece-of-good-music-is-in-essence-a-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any piece of good music is in essence a love song." -- Diana Gabaldon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28418-i-stood-still-vision-blurring-and-in-that-moment-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 10:56:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Diana Gabaldon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28418-i-stood-still-vision-blurring-and-in-that-moment-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I stood still, vision blurring, and in that moment, I heard my heart break.  It was a small, clean sound, like the snapping of a flower's stem." -- Diana Gabaldon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/478267-i-meant-it-claire-he-said-quietly-my-life-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 11:00:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Diana Gabaldon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/478267-i-meant-it-claire-he-said-quietly-my-life-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I meant it, Claire,' he said quietly. 'My life is yours. And it's yours to decide what we shall do, where we go next. To France, to Italy, even back to Scotland. My heart has been yours since first I saw ye, and you've held my soul and body between your two hands here, and kept them safe. We shall go as ye say." -- Diana Gabaldon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/573975-the-most-exhausting-thing-in-life-i-have-discovered-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 21:30:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/573975-the-most-exhausting-thing-in-life-i-have-discovered-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most exhausting thing in life, I have discovered, is being insincere." -- Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134614-security-in-a-relationship-lies-neither-in-looking-back-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 21:31:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134614-security-in-a-relationship-lies-neither-in-looking-back-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Security in a relationship lies neither in looking back to what it was in nostalgia, nor forward to what it might be in dread or anticipation, but living in the present relationship and accepting it as it is now." -- Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298323-one-writes-not-to-be-read-but-to-breathe-one-writes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 21:32:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298323-one-writes-not-to-be-read-but-to-breathe-one-writes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One writes not to be read but to breathe...one writes to think, to pray, to analyze. One writes to clear one's mind, to dissipate one's fears, to face one's doubts, to look at one's mistakes--in order to retrieve them. One writes to capture and crystallize one's joy, but also to disperse one's gloom. Like prayer--you go to it in sorrow more than joy, for help, a road back to 'grace'." -- Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371712-one-learns-to-accept-the-fact-that-no-permanent-return</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 21:34:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371712-one-learns-to-accept-the-fact-that-no-permanent-return]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One learns to accept the fact that no permanent return is possible to an old form of relationship; and, more deeply still, that there is no holding of a relationship to a single form.  This is not tragedy but part of the ever-recurrent miracle of life and growth." -- Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/332078-what-a-commentary-on-our-civilization-when-being-alone-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 21:34:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/332078-what-a-commentary-on-our-civilization-when-being-alone-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a commentary on our civilization, when being alone is considered suspect; when one has to apologize for it, make excuses, hide the fact that one practices it—like a secret vice!" -- Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308331-the-ragamuffin-who-sees-his-life-as-a-voyage-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 10:16:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Brennan Manning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308331-the-ragamuffin-who-sees-his-life-as-a-voyage-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The ragamuffin who sees his life as a voyage of discovery and runs the risk of failure has a better feel for faithfulness than the timid man who hides behind the law and never finds out who he is at all." -- Brennan Manning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/589574-how-i-treat-a-brother-or-sister-from-day-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 10:18:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Brennan Manning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/589574-how-i-treat-a-brother-or-sister-from-day-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How I treat a brother or sister from day to day, how I react to the sin-scarred wino on the street, how I respond to interruptions from people I dislike, how I deal with normal people in their normal confusion on a normal day may be a better indication of my reverence for life than the antiabortion sticker on the bumper of my car." -- Brennan Manning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/502415-aristotle-said-i-am-a-rational-animal-i-say-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 10:18:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Brennan Manning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/502415-aristotle-said-i-am-a-rational-animal-i-say-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...Aristotle said I am a rational animal; I say I am an angel with an incredible capacity for beer." -- Brennan Manning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3354-silence-is-sometimes-the-best-answer</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 23:24:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Dalai Lama XIV]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3354-silence-is-sometimes-the-best-answer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Silence is sometimes the best answer" -- Dalai Lama XIV]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286360-whether-one-is-rich-or-poor-educated-or-illiterate-religious</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 23:30:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Dalai Lama XIV]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286360-whether-one-is-rich-or-poor-educated-or-illiterate-religious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whether one is rich or poor, educated or illiterate, religious or nonbelieving, man or woman, black, white, or brown, we are all the same.  Physically, emotionally, and mentally, we are all equal.  We all share basic needs for food, shelter, safety, and love.  We all aspire to happiness and we all shun suffering.  Each of us has hopes, worries, fears, and dreams.  Each of us wants the best for our family and loved ones.  We all experience pain when we suffer loss and joy when we achieve what we seek.  On this fundamental level, religion, ethnicity, culture, and language make no difference." -- Dalai Lama XIV]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492486-an-open-heart-is-an-open-mind</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 23:38:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Dalai Lama XIV]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492486-an-open-heart-is-an-open-mind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An open heart is an open mind." -- Dalai Lama XIV]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204206-what-makes-a-genius-the-ability-to-see-to-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2013 21:36:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Brennan Manning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204206-what-makes-a-genius-the-ability-to-see-to-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What makes a genius?  The ability to see.  To see what?  The butterfly in a caterpillar, the eagle in an egg, the saint in a selfish person, life in death, unity in separation, 
God in the human and human in God and suffering as the form in which the incomprehensibility of God himself appears." -- Brennan Manning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2014 13:23:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
