<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/402431-kimberly]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/402431-kimberly" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 12:53:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201369-the-first-duty-of-wine-is-to-be-red-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 12:53:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Henry Murger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201369-the-first-duty-of-wine-is-to-be-red-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first duty of wine is to be red. Don't talk to me of your white wines." -- Henry Murger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127314-i-m-going-to-take-you-out-of-here-i-m</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 12:29:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127314-i-m-going-to-take-you-out-of-here-i-m]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm going to take you out of here ... I'm going to take you home, to the world where you belong, where cats with bent tails live, and there are little backyards, and alarm clocks ring in the morning." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43380-don-t-worry-about-your-originality-you-couldn-t-get-rid-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 12:29:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Robert Henri]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43380-don-t-worry-about-your-originality-you-couldn-t-get-rid-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't worry about your originality. You couldn't get rid of it even if you wanted to. It will stick with you and show up for better or worse in spite of all you or anyone else can do." -- Robert Henri]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 13:12:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opposite of love is not hate, it's indifference. The opposite of art is not ugliness, it's indifference. The opposite of faith is not heresy, it's indifference. And the opposite of life is not death, it's indifference." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57741-dumbledore-watched-her-fly-away-and-as-her-silvery-glow</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 12:29:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57741-dumbledore-watched-her-fly-away-and-as-her-silvery-glow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dumbledore watched her fly away, and as her silvery glow faded he turned back to Snape, and his eyes were full of tears.
&quot;After all this time?&quot;
&quot;Always,&quot; said Snape." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4122-only-dull-people-are-brilliant-at-breakfast</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 13:15:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4122-only-dull-people-are-brilliant-at-breakfast]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only dull people are brilliant at breakfast." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17533-i-carry-your-heart-with-me-i-carry-it-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 13:17:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by E.E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17533-i-carry-your-heart-with-me-i-carry-it-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I carry your heart with me (I carry it in my heart)I am never without it (anywhere
I go you go,my dear; and whatever is done by only me is your doing,my darling)
I fear no fate (for you are my fate,my sweet)I want no world (for beautiful you are my world,my true)
and it's you are whatever a moon has always meant and whatever a sun will always sing is you

here is the deepest secret nobody knows
(here is the root of the root and the bud of the bud and the sky of the sky of a tree called life; which grows
higher than the soul can hope or mind can hide)
and this is the wonder that's keeping the stars apart

I carry your heart (I carry it in my heart)" -- E.E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10722-i-love-you-as-certain-dark-things-are-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 06:38:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10722-i-love-you-as-certain-dark-things-are-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you as certain dark things are to be loved, 
in secret, between the shadow and the soul." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126301-so-i-wait-for-you-like-a-lonely-house-till</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 06:39:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126301-so-i-wait-for-you-like-a-lonely-house-till]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["so I wait for you like a lonely house
till you will see me again and live in me.
Till then my windows ache." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49138-es-tan-corto-el-amor-y-es-tan-largo-el</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 06:46:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49138-es-tan-corto-el-amor-y-es-tan-largo-el]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Es tan corto el amor, y es tan largo el olvido." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134645-lost-opportunities-lost-possibilities-feelings-we-can-never-get-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 11:34:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134645-lost-opportunities-lost-possibilities-feelings-we-can-never-get-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lost opportunities, lost possibilities, feelings we can never get back.  That's part of what it means to be alive.  But inside our heads - at least that's where I imagine it - there's a little room where we store those memories.  A room like the stacks in this library.  And to understand the workings of our own heart we have to keep on making new reference cards.  We have to dust things off every once in awhile, let in fresh air, change the water in the flower vases.  In other words, you'll live forever in your own private library." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34244-when-i-was-alive-i-believed-as-you-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 05:39:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34244-when-i-was-alive-i-believed-as-you-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was alive, I believed — as you do — that time was at least as real and solid as myself, and probably more so. I said 'one o'clock' as though I could see it, and 'Monday' as though I could find it on the map; and I let myself be hurried along from minute to minute, day to day, year to year, as though I were actually moving from one place to another. Like everyone else, I lived in a house bricked up with seconds and minutes, weekends and New Year's Days, and I never went outside until I died, because there was no other door. Now I know that I could have walked through the walls. (...) You can strike your own time, and start the count anywhere. When you understand that — then any time at all will be the right time for you." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24440-and-it-came-to-me-then-that-we-were-wonderful</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 07:56:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24440-and-it-came-to-me-then-that-we-were-wonderful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And it came to me then. That we were wonderful traveling companions but in the end no more than lonely lumps of metal in their own separate orbits.  From far off they look like beautiful shooting stars, but in reality they're nothing more than prisons, where each of us is locked up alone, going nowhere. When the orbits of these two satellites of ours happened to cross paths, we could be together. Maybe even open our hearts to each other. But that was only for the briefest moment. In the next instant we'd be in absolute solitude. Until we burned up and became nothing." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223690-i-must-be-in-love-with-this-woman-sumire-realized</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 07:58:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223690-i-must-be-in-love-with-this-woman-sumire-realized]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I must be in love with this woman, Sumire realized with a start.  No
mistake about it.  Ice is cold; roses are red; I'm in love.  And this
love is about to carry me off somewhere.  This current's too
overpowering; I don't have any choice.  It may very well be a special
place, some place I've never seen before.  Danger may be lurking
there, something that may end up wounding me deeply, fatally. I might
end up losing everything.  But there's no turning back.  I can only go
with the flow.  Even if it means I'll be burned up, gone forever." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296691-i-brought-her-flowers-one-dusky-tuesday-evening-when-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 06:02:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Peter Watts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296691-i-brought-her-flowers-one-dusky-tuesday-evening-when-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I brought her flowers one dusky Tuesday evening when the light was perfect. I pointed out the irony of that romantic old tradition— the severed genitalia of another species, offered as a precopulatory bribe—and then I recited my story just as we were about to fuck.

To this day, I still don't know what went wrong." -- Peter Watts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328188-i-will-love-you-with-no-regard-to-the-actions</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 06:05:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328188-i-will-love-you-with-no-regard-to-the-actions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will love you with no regard to the actions of our enemies or the jealousies of actors. I will love you with no regard to the outrage of certain parents or the boredom of certain friends. I will love you no matter what is served in the world’s cafeterias or what game is played at each and every recess. I will love you no matter how many fire drills we are all forced to endure, and no matter what is drawn upon the blackboard in blurry, boring chalk. I will love you no matter how many mistakes I make when trying to reduce fractions, and no matter how difficult it is to memorize the periodic table.
I will love you no matter what your locker combination was, or how you decided to spend your time during study hall. I will love you no matter how your soccer team performed in the tournament or how many stains I received on my cheerleading uniform. I will love you if I never see you again, and I will love you if I see you every Tuesday. I will love you if you cut your hair and I will love you if you cut the hair of others. I will love you if you abandon your baticeering, and I will love you if you if you retire from the theater to take up some other, less dangerous occupation. I will love you if you drop your raincoat on the floor instead of hanging it up and I will love you if you betray your father. I will love you even if you announce that the poetry of Edgar Guest is the best in the world and even if you announce that the work of Zilpha Keatley Snyder is unbearably tedious. I will love you if you abandon the theremin and take up the harmonica and I will love you if you donate your marmosets to the zoo and your tree frogs to M. I will love you as a starfish loves a coral reef and as a kudzu loves trees, even if the oceans turn to sawdust and the trees fall in the forest without anyone around to hear them. I will love you as the pesto loves the fettuccini and as the horseradish loves the miyagi, as the tempura loves the ikura and the pepperoni loves the pizza.
I will love you as the manatee loves the head of lettuce and as the dark spot loves the leopard, as the leech loves the ankle of a wader and as a corpse loves the beak of the vulture. I will love you as the doctor loves his sickest patient and a lake loves its thirstiest swimmer. I will love you as the beard loves the chin, and the crumbs love the beard, and the damp napkin loves the crumbs, and the precious document loves the dampness in the napkin, and the squinting eye of the reader loves the smudged print of the document, and the tears of sadness love the squinting eye as it misreads what is written. I will love you as the iceberg loves the ship, and the passengers love the lifeboat, and the lifeboat loves the teeth of the sperm whale, and the sperm whale loves the flavor of naval uniforms. i will love you as a child loves to overhear the conversations of its parents, and the parents love the sound of their own arguing voices, and as the pen loves to write down the words these voices utter in a notebook for safekeeping. I will love you as a shingle loves falling off a house on a windy day and striking a grumpy person across the chin, and as an oven loves malfunctioning in the middle of roasting a turkey.
I will love you as an airplane loves to fall from a clear blue sky and as an escalator loves to entangle expensive scarves in its mechanisms. I will love you as a wet paper towel loves to be crumpled into a ball and thrown at a bathroom ceiling and as an eraser loves to leave dust in the hairdos of people who talk too much. I will love you as a cufflink loves to drop from its shirt and explore the party for itself and as a pair of white gloves loves to slip delicately into the punchbowl. I will love you as the taxi loves the muddy splash of a puddle and as a library loves the patient tick of a clock." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18508-eat-food-not-too-much-mostly-plants</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 11:59:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Michael Pollan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18508-eat-food-not-too-much-mostly-plants]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eat food.  Not too much.  Mostly plants." -- Michael Pollan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33501-he-showed-the-words-chocolate-cake-to-a-group-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 12:00:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Michael Pollan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33501-he-showed-the-words-chocolate-cake-to-a-group-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He showed the words “chocolate cake” to a group of Americans and recorded their word associations. “Guilt” was the top response. If that strikes you as unexceptional, consider the response of French eaters to the same prompt: “celebration." -- Michael Pollan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/304617-i-am-not-sure-that-i-exist-actually-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 20:30:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/304617-i-am-not-sure-that-i-exist-actually-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am not sure that I exist, actually. I am all the writers that I have read, all the people that I have met, all the women that I have loved; all the cities I have visited." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58954-the-answer-is-dreams-dreaming-on-and-on-entering-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 10:31:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58954-the-answer-is-dreams-dreaming-on-and-on-entering-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The answer is dreams. Dreaming on and on. Entering the world of dreams and never coming out. Living in dreams for the rest of time." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12863-i-can-only-note-that-the-past-is-beautiful-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 06:12:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12863-i-can-only-note-that-the-past-is-beautiful-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can only note that the past is beautiful because one never realises an emotion at the time. It expands later, and thus we don't have complete emotions about the present, only about the past." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2203-it-is-what-you-read-when-you-don-t-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 06:13:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2203-it-is-what-you-read-when-you-don-t-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is what you read when you don't have to that determines what you will be when you can't help it." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19297-reader-s-bill-of-rights-1-the-right-to-not-read</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 07:44:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Daniel Pennac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19297-reader-s-bill-of-rights-1-the-right-to-not-read]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reader's Bill of Rights

1. The right to not read 

2. The right to skip pages 

3. The right to not finish 

4. The right to reread 

5. The right to read anything 

6. The right to escapism 

7. The right to read anywhere 

8. The right to browse 

9. The right to read out loud 

10. The right to not defend your tastes" -- Daniel Pennac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223385-i-made-no-resolutions-for-the-new-year-the-habit</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 07:46:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223385-i-made-no-resolutions-for-the-new-year-the-habit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I made no resolutions for the New Year.  The habit of making plans, of criticizing, sanctioning and molding my life, is too much of a daily event for me.  " -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6273-don-t-ask-what-the-world-needs-ask-what-makes-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 10:09:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Howard Thurman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6273-don-t-ask-what-the-world-needs-ask-what-makes-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don’t ask what the world needs. Ask what makes you come alive, and go do it. Because what the world needs is people who have come alive." -- Howard Thurman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384557-when-i-look-at-my-life-and-its-secret-colours</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 06:36:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384557-when-i-look-at-my-life-and-its-secret-colours]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I look at my life and its secret colours, I feel like bursting into tears." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43397-the-object-isn-t-to-make-art-it-s-to-be-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 11:15:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Robert Henri]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43397-the-object-isn-t-to-make-art-it-s-to-be-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The object isn't to make art, it's to be in that wonderful state which makes art inevitable." -- Robert Henri]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/635954-beauty-is-an-intangible-thing-can-not-be-fixed-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 11:17:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by Robert Henri]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/635954-beauty-is-an-intangible-thing-can-not-be-fixed-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beauty is an intangible thing; can not be fixed on the surface, and the wear and tear of old age on the body cannot defeat it. Nor will a &quot;pretty&quot; face make it, for &quot;pretty&quot; faces are often dull and empty, and beauty is never dull and it fills all spaces." -- Robert Henri]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/397334-i-ve-been-homesick-for-countries-i-ve-never-been-and-longed</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 06:24:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kimberly add a quote by John Cheever]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/397334-i-ve-been-homesick-for-countries-i-ve-never-been-and-longed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been homesick for countries I've never been, and longed to be where I couldn't be." -- John Cheever]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
