<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/402598-andrea-carolina]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/402598-andrea-carolina" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2008 09:02:04 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111959-le-a-mucho-pero-con-la-lectura-pasa-lo-mismo-ya</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2008 09:02:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Sandor Marai]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111959-le-a-mucho-pero-con-la-lectura-pasa-lo-mismo-ya]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Leía mucho. Pero con la lectura pasa lo mismo, ya sabes… sólo obtienes algo de los libros si eres capaz de poner algo tuyo en lo que estás leyendo. Quiero decir que sólo si te aproximas al libro con el ánimo dispuesto a herir y ser herido en el duelo de la lectura, a polemizar, a convencer y ser convencido, y luego, una vez enriquecido con lo que has aprendido, a emplearlo en construir algo en la vida o en el trabajo”

La mayor parte de la gente no puede dar ni recibir amor porque es cobarde y orgullosa, porque tiene miedo al fracaso”

… a veces las personas son buenas porque no tienen inhibiciones que les impiden actuar con maldad. … Y luego están los que son buenos porque son demasiado cobardes para ser malos”
El burgués tiene que estar toda la vida demostrando quién es. El aristócrata ya ha demostrado quién es en el momento de nacer”

No me gusta entregarme a los sentimientos…pero el sentimiento de la amistad es mucho más complicado y delicado que el del amor”

Ya ves lo ingenuos que somos. Tendemos a creer que los asuntos propios, los verdaderos, son acontecimientos de relevancia mundial”

No es cierto que el sufrimiento nos purifique y nos haga mejores, más sabios y comprensivos. Nos vuelve demasiado lúcidos, fríos e indiferentes”
Y entonces te das cuenta de que ésa es la verdadera venganza, la única, la perfecta: ya no quieres saber nada de él, no le deseas nada malo ni nada bueno, ya no puede hacerte sufrir" -- Sandor Marai]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3397-i-gestured-at-my-litre-of-fizzy-red-wine-want</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 06:54:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3397-i-gestured-at-my-litre-of-fizzy-red-wine-want]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I gestured at my litre of fizzy red wine. “Want a drop of this?” I asked him.
No thanks. I try not to drink at lunchtime.”
So do I. But I never quite make it.”
I feel like shit all day if I drink at lunchtime.”
Me too. But I feel like shit all lunchtime if I don’t.”
Yes, well it all comes down to choices, doesn’t it?” he said. “It’s the same in the evenings. Do you want to feel good at night or do you want to feel good in the morning? It’s the same with life. Do you want to feel good young or do you want to feel good old? One or the other, not both.”
Isn’t it a tragedy?" -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12075-perhaps-there-are-other-bits-of-my-life-that-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 06:26:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12075-perhaps-there-are-other-bits-of-my-life-that-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps there are other bits of my life that would take on content, take on shadow, if only I read more and thought less about money." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62629-your-purpose-when-driving-is-not-to-arrive-at-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 06:26:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62629-your-purpose-when-driving-is-not-to-arrive-at-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your purpose when driving is not to arrive at your destination safely or quickly. Your purpose when driving is...to impress your personality on the road." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62635-love-might-have-expanded-her-but-we-are-not-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 06:27:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62635-love-might-have-expanded-her-but-we-are-not-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love might have expanded her. But we are not all of us going to get loved. We are not all of us going to get expanded." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57206-the-children-of-the-nuclear-age-i-think-were-weakened</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 06:31:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57206-the-children-of-the-nuclear-age-i-think-were-weakened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The children of the nuclear age, I think, were weakened in their capacity to love. Hard to love, when you're bracing yourself for impact. Hard to love, when the loved one, and the lover, might at any instant become blood and flames, along with everybody else." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71539-you-can-kill-time-in-a-number-of-ways-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 06:35:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71539-you-can-kill-time-in-a-number-of-ways-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can kill time in a number of ways but it always depends on the kind of time you're fighting: some time is unkillable, immortal" -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72426-cities-at-night-i-feel-contain-men-who-cry-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 06:36:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72426-cities-at-night-i-feel-contain-men-who-cry-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cities at night, I feel, contain men who cry in their sleep and then say Nothing. It's nothing. Just sad dreams. Or something like that...Swing low in your weep ship, with your tear scans and sob probes, and you would mark them. Women--and they can be wives, lovers, gaunt muses, fat nurses, obsessions, devourers, exes, nemeses--will wake and turn to these men and ask, with female need-to-know, &quot;What is it?&quot; And the men will say, &quot;Nothing. No it isn't anything really. Just sad dreams." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113041-when-the-sky-is-as-grey-as-this---impeccably</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 06:38:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113041-when-the-sky-is-as-grey-as-this---impeccably]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["when the sky is as grey as this - impeccably grey, a denial, really of the very concept of colour - and the stooped millions lift their heads, it's hard to tell the air from the impurities in our human eyes, as if the sinking climbing paisley curlicues of grit were part of the element itself, rain, spores, tears, film, dirt. Perhaps, at such moments, the sky is no more then the sum of the dirt that lives in our human eyes." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5015-what-did-nabokov-and-joyce-have-in-common-apart-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 06:04:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5015-what-did-nabokov-and-joyce-have-in-common-apart-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What did Nabokov and Joyce have in common, apart from the poor teeth and the great prose? Exile, and decades of near pauperism. A compulsive tendency to overtip. An uxoriousness that their wives deservedly inspired. More than that, they both lived their lives 'beautifully'--not in any Jamesian sense (where, besides, ferocious solvency would have been a prerequisite), but in the droll fortitude of their perseverance. They got the work done, with style." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20727-love-is-an-abstract-noun-something-nebulous-and-yet-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 06:07:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20727-love-is-an-abstract-noun-something-nebulous-and-yet-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is an abstract noun, something nebulous. And yet love turns out to be the only part of us that is solid, as the world turns upside down and the screen goes black. We can't tell if it will survive us. But we can be sure that it's the last thing to go." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9094-life-is-made-of-fear-some-people-eat-fear-soup</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 06:07:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9094-life-is-made-of-fear-some-people-eat-fear-soup]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is made of fear.  Some people eat fear soup three times a day.  Some people eat fear soup all the meals there are.  I eat it sometimes.  When they bring me fear soup to eat, I try not to eat it, I try to send it back.  But sometimes I'm too afraid to and have to eat it anyway." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7688-es-curioso-c-mo-el-pensamiento-incurre-en-lo-inveros-mil-c-mo</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 06:22:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Javier Marías]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7688-es-curioso-c-mo-el-pensamiento-incurre-en-lo-inveros-mil-c-mo]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Es curioso cómo el pensamiento incurre en lo inverosímil, cómo se lo permite momentáneamente, cómo fantasea o se hace supersticioso para descansar un rato o encontrar alivio, cómo es capaz de negar los hechos y hacer que retroceda el tiempo, aunque sea un instante. Cómo se parece al sueño." -- Javier Marías]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117366-he-was-an-atheist-and-it-had-been-years-since</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 04:34:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117366-he-was-an-atheist-and-it-had-been-years-since]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was an atheist and it had been years since he read a book, despite the fact that he had amassed a more than decent library of works in his specialty, as well as volumes of philosophy and Mexican history and a novel or two. Sometimes he thought it was precisely because he was an atheist that he didn't read anymore. Not reading, it might be said, was the highest expression of atheism or at least of atheism as he conceived of it. If you don't believe in God, how do you believe in a fucking book? he asked himself." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127519-they-could-read-him-they-could-study-him-they-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 04:35:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127519-they-could-read-him-they-could-study-him-they-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They could read him, they could study him, they could pick him apart, but they couldn't laugh or be sad with him...." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140109-reading-is-like-thinking-like-praying-like-talking-to-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 04:38:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140109-reading-is-like-thinking-like-praying-like-talking-to-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reading is like thinking, like praying, like talking to a friend, like expressing your ideas, like listening to other people's ideas, like listening to music, like looking at the view, like taking a walk on the beach." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136183-for-a-while-criticism-travels-side-by-side-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 04:40:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136183-for-a-while-criticism-travels-side-by-side-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For a while, Criticism travels side by side with the Work, then Criticism vanishes and it's the Readers who keep pace. The journey may be long or short. Then the Readers die one by one and the Work continues on alone, although a new Criticism and new Readers gradually fall into step with it along its path. Then Criticism dies again and the Readers die again and the Work passes over a trail of bones on its journey toward solitude. To come near the work, to sail in her wake, is a sign of certain death, but new Criticism and new Readers approach her tirelessly and relentlessly and are devoured by time and speed. Finally the Work journeys irremediably alone in the Great Vastness. And one day the Work dies, as all things must die and come to an end: the Sun and the Earth and the Solar System and the Galaxy and the farthest reaches of man's memory. Everything that begins as comedy ends in tragedy." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140981-supe-entonces-con-humildad-con-perplejidad-en-un-arranque-de</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 04:45:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140981-supe-entonces-con-humildad-con-perplejidad-en-un-arranque-de]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Supe entonces, con humildad, con perplejidad, en un arranque de mexicanidad absoluta, que estábamos gobernados por el azar y que en esa tormenta todos nos ahogaríamos, y supe que sólo los más astutos, no yo ciertamente, iban a mantenerse a flote un poco más de tiempo." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140983-todo-pasaba-por-el-filtro-de-las-palabras-convenientemente-adecuado</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 04:54:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140983-todo-pasaba-por-el-filtro-de-las-palabras-convenientemente-adecuado]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Todo pasaba por el filtro de las palabras, convenientemente adecuado a nuestro miedo. ¿Qué hace un niño cuando tiene miedo? Cierra los ojos. ¿Qué hace un niño al que van a violar y luego matar? Cierra los ojos. Y también grita, pero primero cierra los ojos. Las palabras servían para ese fin. Y es curioso, pues todos los arquetipos de la locura y la crueldad humana no han sido inventados por los hombres de esta época sino por nuestros antepasados. Los griegos inventaron, por decirlo de alguna manera, el mal, vieron el mal que todos llevamos dentro, pero los testimonios o las pruebas de ese mal ya no nos conmueven, nos parecen futiles, ininteligibles[...]Durante la Comuna de 1871 murieron asesinadas miles de personas y nadie derramó una lágrima por ellas. Por esa misma fecha un afilador de cuchillos mató a una mujer y a su anciana madre (no a la madre de la mujer, sino a su propia madre, querido amigo) y luego fue abatido por la policía. La noticia no sólo recorrió los periódicos de Francia sino que también fue reseñada en otros periódicos de Europa" -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162799-ambos-siguieron-atentos-a-los-rumores-crecientes-sobre-la-gravedad</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 08:34:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162799-ambos-siguieron-atentos-a-los-rumores-crecientes-sobre-la-gravedad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ambos siguieron atentos a los rumores crecientes sobre la gravedad de la peste, y aun contra sus deseos tuvieron que conversar otra vez sobre asuntos que les eran comunes, como en los tiempos en que se odiaban menos. Para él era claro. Siempre creyó que amaba a la hija, pero el miedo al mal de rabia lo obligaba a confesarse que se engañaba a sí mismo por comodidad. Bernarda, en cambio, no se lo preguntó siquiera, pues tenía plena conciencia de no amarla ni de ser amada por ella, y ambas cosas le parecían justas. Mucho del odio que ambos sentían por la niña era por lo que ella tenía del uno y del otro. Sin embargo, Bernarda estaba dispuesta a hacer la farsa de las lágrimas y a guardar un luto de madre." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57418-you-wanted-to-look-at-life-for-yourself---but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 08:45:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57418-you-wanted-to-look-at-life-for-yourself---but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You wanted to look at life for yourself - but you were not allowed; you were punished for your wish. You were ground in the very mill of the conventional." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75330-she-envied-ralph-his-dying-for-if-one-were-thinking</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 08:49:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75330-she-envied-ralph-his-dying-for-if-one-were-thinking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She envied Ralph his dying, for if one were thinking of rest that was the most perfect of all. To cease utterly, to give it all up and not know anything more - this idea was as sweet as a vision of a cool bath in a marble tank, in a darkened chamber, in a hot land. ... but Isabel recognized, as it passed before her eyes, the quick vague shadow of a long future. She should never escape; she should last to the end." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32804-a-swift-carriage-of-a-dark-night-rattling-with-four</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 08:50:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32804-a-swift-carriage-of-a-dark-night-rattling-with-four]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A swift carriage, of a dark night, rattling with four horses over roads that one can’t see--that’s my idea of happiness." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112718-i-call-people-rich-when-they-re-able-to-meet-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 08:52:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112718-i-call-people-rich-when-they-re-able-to-meet-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I call people rich when they're able to meet the requirements of their imagination." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318700-to-live-only-to-suffer-only-to-feel-the-injury-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 08:56:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318700-to-live-only-to-suffer-only-to-feel-the-injury-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To live only to suffer—only to feel the injury of life repeated and enlarged—it seemed to her she was too valuable, too capable, for that. Then she wondered if it were vain and stupid to think so well of herself. When had it even been a guarantee to be valuable? Wasn't all history full of the destruction of precious things? Wasn't it much more probable that if one were fine one would suffer?" -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72412-i-m-yours-for-ever--for-ever-and-ever-here-i-stand</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 09:00:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72412-i-m-yours-for-ever--for-ever-and-ever-here-i-stand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm yours for ever--for ever and ever.  Here I stand; I'm as firm as a rock. If you'll only trust me, how little you'll be disappointed. Be mine as I am yours." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84244-when-a-man-conclusively-exalts-one-woman-and-one-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 18:10:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84244-when-a-man-conclusively-exalts-one-woman-and-one-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a man conclusively exalts one woman, and one woman only, “above all others,” you can be pretty sure you are dealing with a misogynist.  It frees him up for thinking the rest are shit." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84246-when-you-ve-lost-all-your-play-guess-what-love-becomes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 18:11:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84246-when-you-ve-lost-all-your-play-guess-what-love-becomes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you’ve lost all your play, guess what love becomes.  Work.  Work that gets harder every hour." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219227-don-t-i-ever-do-anything-else-but-take-soulful-walks</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 18:13:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219227-don-t-i-ever-do-anything-else-but-take-soulful-walks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't I ever do anything else but take soulful walks down the Bayswater Road, I thought, as I walked soulfully down the Baywater Road." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84243-venus-i-m-sorry-that-you-ve-gone-on-minding-that-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 18:20:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andrea Carolina add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84243-venus-i-m-sorry-that-you-ve-gone-on-minding-that-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Venus, I’m sorry that you’ve gone on minding that I didn’t let you drive me to O’Hare.  “That’s what we do,” you said: “We drive each other to and from the airport.”  Do you realize how rare that is?  No one does it anymore, not even newlyweds.  All right – it was selfish of me to decline.  I said it was because I didn’t want to say goodbye to you in a public place.  But I think it was the asymmetry of it that was really troubling me.  You and I, we drive each other to and from the airport.  And I didn’t want a to when I knew there wouldn’t be a from." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
