<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/405940-sarah-jo]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/405940-sarah-jo" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 11:02:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47580-it-exasperated-her-sometimes-the-way-men-could-be-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 11:02:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah Jo add a quote by Mark Haddon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47580-it-exasperated-her-sometimes-the-way-men-could-be-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It exasperated her sometimes. The way men could be so sure of themselves. They put words together like sheds or shelves and you could stand on them they were so solid. And those feelings which overwhelmed you in the small hours turned to smoke." -- Mark Haddon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47583-and-it-occurred-to-him-that-there-were-two-parts</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 11:05:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah Jo add a quote by Mark Haddon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47583-and-it-occurred-to-him-that-there-were-two-parts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And it occurred to him that there were two parts to being a better person. One part was thinking about other people. The other part was not giving a toss what other people thought." -- Mark Haddon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47586-closeness-can-lead-to-emotions-other-than-love-it-s-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 11:10:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah Jo add a quote by Daniel Mendelsohn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47586-closeness-can-lead-to-emotions-other-than-love-it-s-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Closeness can lead to emotions other than love. It's the ones who have been too intimate with you, lived in too close quarters, seen too much of your pain or envy or, perhaps more than anything, your shame, who, at the crucial moment, can be too easy to cut out, to exile, to expel, to kill off." -- Daniel Mendelsohn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49113-i-spent-my-life-learning-to-feel-less-every-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 18:39:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah Jo add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49113-i-spent-my-life-learning-to-feel-less-every-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I spent my life learning to feel less. Every day I felt less. Is that growing old? Or is it something worse? You cannot protect yourself from sadness without protecting yourself from happiness." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49116-when-i-looked-at-you-my-life-made-sense-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 18:41:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah Jo add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49116-when-i-looked-at-you-my-life-made-sense-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I looked at you, my life made sense. Even the bad things made sense. They were necessary to make you possible." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61350-as-many-have-discovered-it-is-entirely-possible-although-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2008 11:09:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah Jo add a quote by Gabrielle Zevin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61350-as-many-have-discovered-it-is-entirely-possible-although-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As many have discovered, it is entirely possible (although not particularly desirable) to love two people with all your heart. It is entirely possible to long for two lives, to feel that one life can't come close to containing it all." -- Gabrielle Zevin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160054-it-s-the-longing-that-ultimately-undoes-you-when-it-finds</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 08:49:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah Jo add a quote by Matthew Sturges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160054-it-s-the-longing-that-ultimately-undoes-you-when-it-finds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s the Longing that ultimately undoes you. When it finds you, it gnaws at your bones and tugs at your chest. It fills you up inside like rot and makes you dream dreams and it drowns you. The Longing keeps you in bed, clutching at your sheets while the world goes on outside. It smells like old leaves and cigarette smoke, mixed with the scent of far-off places you will hear of, but never see. It’s the gloss on a lover’s lips the moment you realize you will never kiss those lips again. It is the bittersweet, unrequited love of creation and it will break your heart again and again and again. If you know the Longing the way I do, then these words are redundant. We understand each other perfectly, you and I." -- Matthew Sturges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237445-and-then-she-frowned-and-shook-her-head-then-put</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 12:28:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah Jo add a quote by David Nicholls]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237445-and-then-she-frowned-and-shook-her-head-then-put]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And then she frowned, and shook her head, then put her arms around him once more, pressing her face into his shoulder, making a noise that sounded almost like rage.
'What's up?' he asked.
'Nothing. Oh, nothing. Just...' She looked up at him. 'I thought I'd finally got rid of you.'
'I don't think you can.' he said" -- David Nicholls]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237489-and-they-did-have-fun-though-it-was-of-different</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 16:07:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah Jo add a quote by David Nicholls]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237489-and-they-did-have-fun-though-it-was-of-different]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And they did have fun, though it was of different kind now. All that yearning and passion had been replaced by a steady pulse of pleasure and satisfaction and occasional irritation, and this seemed to be a happy exchange; if there had been moments in her life when she had been more elated, there had never been a time when things had been more constant." -- David Nicholls]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237494-she-sometimes-wondered-what-her-twenty-two-year-old-self-would-think-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 16:17:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah Jo add a quote by David Nicholls]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237494-she-sometimes-wondered-what-her-twenty-two-year-old-self-would-think-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She sometimes wondered what her twenty-two-year-old self would think of today's Emma Mayhew. Would she consider her self-centered? Compromised? A bourgeois sell-out, with her appetite for home ownership and foreign travel, clothes from Paris and expensive haircuts? Would she find her conventional, with her new surname and hopes for a family life? Maybe, but then the twenty-two-year-old Emma Morley wasn't such a paragon either: pretentious, petulant, lazy, speechifying, judgmental. Self-pitying, self-righteous, self-important, all of the selfs except self-confident, the quality that she always needed most." -- David Nicholls]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239050-the-more-he-asked-about-her-childhood-at-cloonhill-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 17:03:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah Jo add a quote by William Trevor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239050-the-more-he-asked-about-her-childhood-at-cloonhill-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The more he asked about her childhood at Cloonhill the more Ellie loved her interrogator. No matter how strange he still sometimes seemed, she felt as if all her life she had known him. The past he talked about himself became another part of her: The games he had played alone, the untidy rooms of the house he described, the parties given, the pictures painted. Being with him in the woods at Lyre, where the air was cold and the trees imposed a gloomy darkness, or walking among the monks' graves, or being with him anywhere, telling or listening, was for Ellie more than friendship, or living, had ever been before." -- William Trevor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/400204-god-damn-it-he-said-there-are-nice-things-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2011 11:56:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah Jo add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/400204-god-damn-it-he-said-there-are-nice-things-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God damn it,&quot; he said, &quot;there are nice things in the world- and I mean nice things. We're all such morons to get so sidetracked. Always, always referring every goddam thing that happens right back to our lousy little egos." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
