<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/406781-patricia]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/406781-patricia" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2011 08:37:28 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21101-do-you-think-i-am-an-automaton-a-machine</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2011 08:37:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21101-do-you-think-i-am-an-automaton-a-machine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you think I am an automaton? — a machine without feelings? and can bear to have my morsel of bread snatched from my lips, and my drop of living water dashed from my cup? Do you think, because I am poor, obscure, plain, and little, I am soulless and heartless? You think wrong! — I have as much soul as you — and full as much heart! And if God had gifted me with some beauty and much wealth, I should have made it as hard for you to leave me, as it is now for me to leave you. I am not talking to you now through the medium of custom, conventionalities, nor even of mortal flesh: it is my spirit that addresses your spirit; just as if both had passed through the grave, and we stood at God's feet, equal — as we are!" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360214-right-now-i-am-in-fallujah-i-am-in-darfur</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 20:02:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Stephen Adly Guirgis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360214-right-now-i-am-in-fallujah-i-am-in-darfur]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Right now, I am in Fallujah. I am in Darfur. I am on Sixty-third and Park having dinner with Ellen Barkin and Ron Perelman... Right now, I'm on Lafayette and Astor waiting to hit you up for change so I can get high. I'm taking a walk through the Rose Garden with George Bush. I'm helping Donald Rumsfeld get a good night's sleep...I was in that cave with Osama, and on that plane with Mohamed Atta...And what I want you to know is that your work has barely begun. And what I want you to trust is the efficacy of divine love if practiced consciously. And what I need you to believe is that if you hate who I love, you do not know me at all. And make no mistake, &quot;Who I Love&quot; is every last one. I am every last one. People ask of me: Where are you? Where are you?...Verily I ask of you to ask yourself: Where are you? Where are you?" -- Stephen Adly Guirgis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268540-maybe-there-s-something-you-re-afraid-to-say-or-someone-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 22:13:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268540-maybe-there-s-something-you-re-afraid-to-say-or-someone-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe there's something you're afraid to say, or someone you're afraid to love, or somewhere you're afraid to go. It's gonna hurt. It's gonna hurt because it matters." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
