<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/406701-nate-d]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/406701-nate-d" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 10:02:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369383-the-world-is-kept-alive-only-by-heretics-the-heretic</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 10:02:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate D add a quote by Yevgeny Zamyatin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369383-the-world-is-kept-alive-only-by-heretics-the-heretic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is kept alive only by heretics: the heretic Christ, the heretic Copernicus, the heretic Tolstoy. Our symbol of faith is heresy. (“Tomorrow”)" -- Yevgeny Zamyatin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60814-what-one-ought-to-capture-in-beauty-is-that-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2012 10:06:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate D add a quote by László Krasznahorkai]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60814-what-one-ought-to-capture-in-beauty-is-that-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...what one ought to capture in beauty is that which is treacherous and irresistible..." -- László Krasznahorkai]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/646343-i-said-that-i-have-finished-telling-my-story-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2012 09:17:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate D add a quote by Herbert Rosendorfer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/646343-i-said-that-i-have-finished-telling-my-story-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I said that I have finished telling my story, not that the story is finished. I said before that no story is ever really finished, each one is part of a longer story and consists of smaller stories, some of which are told, others passed over in silence. And whenever you tell any one of the stories, whether you intend it or not, you include the shadow of all the others. The result is that once you have told one story, once you have undone the meshes of the net at one point, you are trapped. You are compelled to go on with the story. And because we ourselves, like all life, are stories, we become the story of the stories." -- Herbert Rosendorfer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/691426-may-your-course-not-run-from-one-end-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2012 11:05:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate D add a quote by Marcel Schwob]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/691426-may-your-course-not-run-from-one-end-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May your course not run from one end to the other; for such a course does not exist; but may every step you take mark a redressed projection.
With your left foot you shall wipe out the footprint of your right foot." -- Marcel Schwob]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/751653-do-you-believe-she-went-on-that-the-past-dies</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 22:35:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate D add a quote by Leonora Carrington]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/751653-do-you-believe-she-went-on-that-the-past-dies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you believe, she went on, that the past dies?

Yes, said Margaret. Yes, if the present cuts its throat." -- Leonora Carrington]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60954-so-he-lent-her-books-after-all-one-of-life-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 12:49:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate D add a quote by William Vollmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60954-so-he-lent-her-books-after-all-one-of-life-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So he lent her books. After all, one of life's best pleasures is reading a book of perfect beauty; more pleasurable still is rereading that book; most pleasurable of all is lending it to the person one loves: Now she is reading or has just read the scene with the mirrors; she who is so lovely is drinking in that loveliness I've drunk." -- William Vollmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/833196-i-really-only-write-about-inner-landscapes-and-most-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 23:15:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate D add a quote by Thomas Bernhard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/833196-i-really-only-write-about-inner-landscapes-and-most-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I really only write about inner landscapes and most people don’t see them, because they see practically nothing within, because they think that because it’s inside, it’s dark, and so they don’t see anything. I don’t think I’ve ever yet, in any of my books, described a landscape. There's really nothing of the kind in any of them. I only ever write concepts.  And so I’m always referring to &quot;mountains&quot; or &quot;a city&quot; or &quot;streets.&quot;  But as to how they look: I've never produced a description of a landscape. That's never even interested me." -- Thomas Bernhard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/901702-when-we-think-of-the-masterpieces-that-nobody-praised-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 16:51:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate D add a quote by Randall Jarrell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/901702-when-we-think-of-the-masterpieces-that-nobody-praised-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we think of the masterpieces that nobody praised and nobody read, back there in the past, we feel an impatient superiority to the readers of the past. If we had been there, we can’t help feeling, we’d have known that Moby-Dick was a good book—-why, how could anyone help knowing?

But suppose someone says to us, “Well, you’re here now: what’s our own Moby-Dick? What’s the book that, a hundred years from now, everybody will look down on us for not having liked?” What do we say then?" -- Randall Jarrell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1229316-the-urge-to-leap-across-feminism-to-human-liberation-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2014 11:39:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate D add a quote by Adrienne Rich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1229316-the-urge-to-leap-across-feminism-to-human-liberation-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The urge to leap across feminism to &quot;human liberation&quot; is a tragic and dangerous mistake. It deflects us from our real sources of vision, recycles us back into old definitions and structures, and continues to serve the purposes of the patriarchy, which will use &quot;women's lib,&quot; as it contemptuously phrases it, only to buy more time for itself—as both capitalism and socialism are now doing. Feminism is a criticism and subversion of &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; patriarchal thought and institutions—not merely those currently seen as reactionary and tyrannical." -- Adrienne Rich]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
