<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/407662-cathy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/407662-cathy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2011 16:24:29 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4641-jane-be-still-don-t-struggle-so-like-a-wild-frantic</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2011 16:24:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4641-jane-be-still-don-t-struggle-so-like-a-wild-frantic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jane, be still; don't struggle so like a wild, frantic bird, that is rending its own plumage in its desperation.&quot;
&quot;I am no bird; and no net ensnares me; I am a free human being, with an independent will; which I now exert to leave you." -- Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89451-he-said-it-was-interesting-he-used-the-word-textured</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 14:49:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Jeannette Walls]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89451-he-said-it-was-interesting-he-used-the-word-textured]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["....he said it was interesting. He used the word 'textured'. He said 'smooth' is boring but 'textured' was interesting, and the scar meant that I was stronger than whatever had tried to hurt me." -- Jeannette Walls]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422-there-are-years-that-ask-questions-and-years-that-answer</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 13:57:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422-there-are-years-that-ask-questions-and-years-that-answer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are years that ask questions and years that answer." -- Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60090-i-m-not-going-to-change-the-way-i-look-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 20:56:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60090-i-m-not-going-to-change-the-way-i-look-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not going to change the way I look or the way I feel to conform to anything. I've always been a freak. So I've been a freak all my life and I have to live with that, you know. I'm one of those people." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74804-if-you-look-for-perfection-you-ll-never-be-content</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2012 23:24:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74804-if-you-look-for-perfection-you-ll-never-be-content]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you look for perfection, you'll never be content." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485442-as-he-read-i-fell-in-love-the-way-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 19:25:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485442-as-he-read-i-fell-in-love-the-way-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As he read, I fell in love the way you fall asleep: slowly, and then all at once." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432910-you-can-clutch-the-past-so-tightly-to-your-chest</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 17:56:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Jan Glidewell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432910-you-can-clutch-the-past-so-tightly-to-your-chest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["‎You can clutch the past so tightly to your chest that it leaves your arms too full to embrace the present." -- Jan Glidewell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584441-men-always-say-that-as-the-defining-compliment-don-t-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 17:58:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584441-men-always-say-that-as-the-defining-compliment-don-t-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men always say that as the defining compliment, don’t they? She’s a cool girl. Being the Cool Girl means I am a hot, brilliant, funny woman who adores football, poker, dirty jokes, and burping, who plays video games, drinks cheap beer, loves threesomes and anal sex, and jams hot dogs and hamburgers into her mouth like she’s hosting the world’s biggest culinary gang bang while somehow maintaining a size 2, because Cool Girls are above all hot. Hot and understanding. Cool Girls never get angry; they only smile in a chagrined, loving manner and let their men do whatever they want. Go ahead, shit on me, I don’t mind, I’m the Cool Girl.

Men actually think this girl exists. Maybe they’re fooled because so many women are willing to pretend to be this girl. For a long time Cool Girl offended me. I used to see men – friends, coworkers, strangers – giddy over these awful pretender women, and I’d want to sit these men down and calmly say: You are not dating a woman, you are dating a woman who has watched too many movies written by socially awkward men who’d like to believe that this kind of woman exists and might kiss them. I’d want to grab the poor guy by his lapels or messenger bag and say: The bitch doesn’t really love chili dogs that much – no one loves chili dogs that much! And the Cool Girls are even more pathetic: They’re not even pretending to be the woman they want to be, they’re pretending to be the woman a man wants them to be. Oh, and if you’re not a Cool Girl, I beg you not to believe that your man doesn’t want the Cool Girl. It may be a slightly different version – maybe he’s a vegetarian, so Cool Girl loves seitan and is great with dogs; or maybe he’s a hipster artist, so Cool Girl is a tattooed, bespectacled nerd who loves comics. There are variations to the window dressing, but believe me, he wants Cool Girl, who is basically the girl who likes every fucking thing he likes and doesn’t ever complain. (How do you know you’re not Cool Girl? Because he says things like: “I like strong women.” If he says that to you, he will at some point fuck someone else. Because “I like strong women” is code for “I hate strong women.”)" -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6452-i-wanna-hold-your-hand-first-single-fucking-brilliant-perhaps</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2013 21:17:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Rachel Cohn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6452-i-wanna-hold-your-hand-first-single-fucking-brilliant-perhaps]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I Wanna Hold Your Hand.’ First single. Fucking brilliant. Perhaps the most fucking brilliant song ever written. Because they nailed it. That’s what everyone wants. Not 24-7 hot wet sex. Not a marriage that lasts a hundred years. Not a Porsche or a blow job or a million-dollar crib. No. They wanna hold your hand. They have a feeling that they can’t hide." -- Rachel Cohn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280390-yet-she-likes-complications-she-wishes-she-could-turn-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 15:00:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Colum McCann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280390-yet-she-likes-complications-she-wishes-she-could-turn-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yet she likes complications. She wishes she could turn and say: I like people who unbalance me." -- Colum McCann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53726-we-turned-at-a-dozen-paces-for-love-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 17:26:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53726-we-turned-at-a-dozen-paces-for-love-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We turned at a dozen paces, for love is a duel, and looked at each other for the last time." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/502578-marylou-was-watching-dean-as-she-had-watched-him-clear</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2013 09:18:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/502578-marylou-was-watching-dean-as-she-had-watched-him-clear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Marylou was watching Dean as she had watched him clear across the country and back, out of the corner of her eye--with a sullen, sad air, as though she wanted to cut off his head and hide it in her closet, an envious and rueful love of him so amazingly himself, all raging and sniffy and crazy-wayed, a smile of tender dotage but also sinister envy that frightened me about her, a love she knew would never bear fruit because when she looked at his hangjawed bony face with its male self-containment and absentmindedness she knew he was too mad." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1981-my-experience-of-life-is-that-it-is-not-divided</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 19:53:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1981-my-experience-of-life-is-that-it-is-not-divided]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My experience of life is that it is not divided up into genres; it’s a horrifying, romantic, tragic, comical, science-fiction cowboy detective novel. You know, with a bit of pornography if you're lucky." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363962-you-can-t-get-a-suit-of-armour-and-a-rubber</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 04:46:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Michael Palin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363962-you-can-t-get-a-suit-of-armour-and-a-rubber]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can't get a suit of armour and a rubber chicken just like that.  You have to plan ahead." -- Michael Palin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124144-she-talks-with-a-broken-heart---her-voice-lutes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 10:33:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124144-she-talks-with-a-broken-heart---her-voice-lutes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She talks with a broken heart  - Her voice lutes brokenly like a heart lost, musically too, like in a lost grove, it's almost too much to bear sometimes like some fantastic futuristic Jerry Southern singer in a nightclub who steps up to the mike in the spotlight in Las Vegas but doesn't even have to sing, just talk, to make men sigh and women wonder I guess..." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250408-you-know-the-reason-the-beatles-made-it-so-big-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2013 15:03:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by David Levithan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250408-you-know-the-reason-the-beatles-made-it-so-big-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know the reason The Beatles made it so big?...'I Wanna Hold Your Hand.' First single. Fucking brilliant. Perhaps the most fucking brilliant song ever written. Because they nailed it. That's what everyone wants. Not 24/7 hot wet sex. Not a marriage that lasts a hundred years. Not a Porsche...or a million-dollar crib. No. They wanna hold your hand. They have such a feeling that they can't hide. Every single successful song of the past fifty years can be traced back to 'I Wanna Hold Your Hand.' And every single successful love story has those unbearable and unbearably exciting moments of hand-holding." -- David Levithan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59323-i-am-glad-that-i-paid-so-little-attention-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 21:32:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Edna St. Vincent Millay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59323-i-am-glad-that-i-paid-so-little-attention-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am glad that I paid so little attention to good advice; had I abided by it I might have been saved from some of my most valuable mistakes." -- Edna St. Vincent Millay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84036-well-i-have-lost-you-and-i-lost-you-fairly</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 21:32:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Edna St. Vincent Millay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84036-well-i-have-lost-you-and-i-lost-you-fairly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, I have lost you; and I lost you fairly;
In my own way, and with my full consent.
Say what you will, kings in a tumbrel rarely
Went to their deaths more proud than this one went.

Some nights of apprehension and hot weeping
I will confess; but that's permitted me;
Day dried my eyes; I was not one for keeping
Rubbed in a cage a wing that would be free.

If I had loved you less or played you slyly
I might have held you for a summer more,
But at the cost of words I value highly,
And no such summer as the one before.

Should I outlive this anguish, and men do,
I shall have only good to say of you." -- Edna St. Vincent Millay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/855853-you-never-knew-which-split-second-might-be-the-zigzag</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 10:56:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/855853-you-never-knew-which-split-second-might-be-the-zigzag]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You never knew which split second might be the zigzag bolt dividing all that went before from the everything that comes next." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1268722-in-recognizing-the-humanity-of-our-fellow-beings-we-pay</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 05:17:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Thurgood Marshall]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1268722-in-recognizing-the-humanity-of-our-fellow-beings-we-pay]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In recognizing the humanity of our fellow beings, we pay ourselves the highest tribute." -- Thurgood Marshall]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
