<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/409141-kami]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/409141-kami" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2009 11:24:36 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10111-we-don-t-need-a-list-of-rights-and-wrongs-tables</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2009 11:24:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kami add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10111-we-don-t-need-a-list-of-rights-and-wrongs-tables]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don’t need a list of rights and wrongs, tables of dos and don’ts: we need books, time, and silence. &lt;I&gt;Thou shalt not&lt;/I&gt; is soon forgotten, but &lt;I&gt;Once upon a time&lt;/I&gt; lasts forever." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20924-when-you-look-at-what-c-s-lewis-is-saying-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2009 11:24:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kami add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20924-when-you-look-at-what-c-s-lewis-is-saying-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you look at what C.S. Lewis is saying, his message is so anti-life, so cruel, so unjust. The view that the Narnia books have for the material world is one of almost undisguised contempt. At one point, the old professor says, ‘It’s all in Plato’ — meaning that the physical world we see around us is the crude, shabby, imperfect, second-rate copy of something much better. I want to emphasize the simple physical truth of things, the absolute primacy of the material life, rather than the spiritual or the afterlife.

[&lt;i&gt;The New York Times interview, 2000&lt;/i&gt;]" -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113274-why-do-people-who-are-good-at-families-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 17:59:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kami add a quote by Hanif Kureishi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113274-why-do-people-who-are-good-at-families-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why do people who are good at families have to be smug and assume it is the only way to live. … Why can’t they be blamed for being bad at promiscuity?" -- Hanif Kureishi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2010 13:32:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kami add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The really important kind of freedom involves attention, and awareness, and discipline, and effort, and being able truly to care about other people and to sacrifice for them, over and over, in myriad petty little unsexy ways, every day." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20112-when-adults-say-teenagers-think-they-are-invincible-with-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 14:38:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kami add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20112-when-adults-say-teenagers-think-they-are-invincible-with-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When adults say, &quot;Teenagers think they are invincible&quot; with that sly, stupid smile on their faces, they don't know how right they are. We need never be hopeless, because we can never be irreparably broken. We think that we are invincible because we are. We cannot be born, and we cannot die. Like all energy, we can only change shapes and sizes and manifestations. They forget that when they get old. They get scared of losing and failing. But that part of us greater than the sum of our parts cannot begin and cannot end, and so it cannot fail." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1288-i-don-t-know-about-you-but-i-m-kind-of-fed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 01:47:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kami add a quote by Audrey Niffenger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1288-i-don-t-know-about-you-but-i-m-kind-of-fed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know about you, but I'm kind of fed up with realism. After all, there's enough reality already; why make more of it? Why not leave realism for the memoirs of drug addicts, the histories of salt, the biographies of porn stars? Why must we continue to read about the travails of divorced people or mildly depressed Canadians when we could be contemplating the shopping habits of zombies, or the difficulties that ensue when living and dead people marry each other? We should be demanding more stories about faery handbags and pyjamas inscribed with the diaries of strange women. We should not rest until someone writes about a television show that features the Free People's World-Tree Library, with its elaborate waterfalls and Forbidden Books and Pirate-Magicians. We should be pining for a house haunted by rabbits." -- Audrey Niffenger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/503052-part-of-the-post-apocalyptic-dystopian-trend-is-that-it-seems</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 21:22:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kami add a quote by Julianna Baggott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/503052-part-of-the-post-apocalyptic-dystopian-trend-is-that-it-seems]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Part of the post-apocalyptic, dystopian trend is that it seems to go hand in hand with young adult novels. Maybe that's because it's not simply the adults who are aware of the current crisis. Teens are the ones who are being told, again and again, that their futures are in jeopardy. The teen years can feel dystopian even in the best of times. But I don't think we realize how much pressure and feeling of doom we're passing down to our teens." -- Julianna Baggott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14844-garcia-wondered-why-people-with-jesus-stickers-on-their-bumper</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 09:15:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kami add a quote by Carl Hiaasen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14844-garcia-wondered-why-people-with-jesus-stickers-on-their-bumper]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Garcia wondered why people with JESUS stickers on their bumper always drove twenty miles per hour under the speed limit.  If God was my co-pilot, he thought, I'd be doing a hundred and twenty." -- Carl Hiaasen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
