<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/409154-alban]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/409154-alban" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:35:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/304617-i-am-not-sure-that-i-exist-actually-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:35:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alban add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/304617-i-am-not-sure-that-i-exist-actually-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am not sure that I exist, actually. I am all the writers that I have read, all the people that I have met, all the women that I have loved; all the cities I have visited." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2869-the-tree-which-moves-some-to-tears-of-joy-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:35:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alban add a quote by William Blake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2869-the-tree-which-moves-some-to-tears-of-joy-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The tree which moves some to tears of joy is in the eyes of others only a green thing that stands in the way. Some see nature all ridicule and deformity... and some scarce see nature at all. But to the eyes of the man of imagination, nature is imagination itself." -- William Blake]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2956-the-things-that-the-novel-does-not-say-are-necessarily</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:35:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alban add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2956-the-things-that-the-novel-does-not-say-are-necessarily]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The things that the novel does not say are necessarily more numerous than those it does say and only a special halo around what is written can give the illusion that you are reading also what is not written." -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123110-we-are-born-like-this-into-this-into-these-carefully</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:35:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alban add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123110-we-are-born-like-this-into-this-into-these-carefully]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are
Born like this
Into this
Into these carefully mad wars
Into the sight of broken factory windows of emptiness
Into bars where people no longer speak to each other
Into fist fights that end as shootings and knifings
Born into this
Into hospitals which are so expensive that it’s cheaper to die
Into lawyers who charge so much it’s cheaper to plead guilty
Into a country where the jails are full and the madhouses closed
Into a place where the masses elevate fools into rich heroes" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2863-i-believe-all-sin-love-glory-are-this-when-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2007 18:42:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alban add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2863-i-believe-all-sin-love-glory-are-this-when-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe all sin, love, glory are this: when you slide down the knotted sheets, escaping from Gestapo headquarters, and she hugs you, there, suspended, and she whispers that she's always dreamed of you. The rest is just sex, copulation, the perpetuation of the vile species." -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2867-if-everyone-fought-for-their-own-convictions-there-would-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2007 18:47:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alban add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2867-if-everyone-fought-for-their-own-convictions-there-would-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If everyone fought for their own convictions there would be no war." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5238-i-have-claimed-that-escape-is-one-of-the-main</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2007 18:49:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alban add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5238-i-have-claimed-that-escape-is-one-of-the-main]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have claimed that Escape is one of the main functions of fairy-stories, and since I do not disapprove of them, it is plain that I do not accept the tone of scorn or pity with which 'Escape' is now so often used. Why should a man be scorned if, finding himself in prison, he tries to get out and go home? Or if he cannot do so, he thinks and talks about other topics than jailers and prison-walls?" -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2498-i-have-come-to-believe-that-the-whole-world-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 12:38:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alban add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2498-i-have-come-to-believe-that-the-whole-world-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have come to believe that the whole world is an enigma, a harmless enigma that is made terrible by our own mad attempt to interpret it as though it had an underlying truth." -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2448-to-live-is-the-rarest-thing-in-the-world-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 16:41:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alban add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2448-to-live-is-the-rarest-thing-in-the-world-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To live is the rarest thing in the world. Most people exist, that is all." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2787-we-write-to-taste-life-twice-in-the-moment-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 16:43:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alban add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2787-we-write-to-taste-life-twice-in-the-moment-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We write to taste life twice, in the moment and in retrospect." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162822-i-ve-lived-so-little-that-i-tend-to-imagine-i-m</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 11:53:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alban add a quote by Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162822-i-ve-lived-so-little-that-i-tend-to-imagine-i-m]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've lived so little that I tend to imagine I'm not going to die; it seems improbable
that human existence can be reduced to so little; one imagines, in spite of oneself,
that sooner or later something is bound to happen. A big mistake. A life can just as
well be both empty and short. The days slip by indifferently, leaving neither trace nor
memory; and then all of a sudden they stop." -- Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50676-for-some-reason-you-will-no-longer-be-the-person</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 11:54:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alban add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50676-for-some-reason-you-will-no-longer-be-the-person]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For some reason, you will no longer be the person you believed you once were. You'll detect slow and subtle shifts going on all around you, more importantly shifts in you. Worse, you'll realize it's always been shifting, like a shimmer of sorts, a vast shimmer, only dark like a room. But you won't understand why or how." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16731-it-s-been-a-prevalent-notion-fallen-sparks-fragments-of-vessels</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 11:55:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alban add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16731-it-s-been-a-prevalent-notion-fallen-sparks-fragments-of-vessels]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's been a prevalent notion. Fallen sparks. Fragments of vessels broken at the Creation. And someday, somehow, before the end, a gathering back to home. A messenger from the Kingdom, arriving at the last moment. But I tell you there is no such message, no such home -- only the millions of last moments . . . nothing more. Our history is an aggregate of last moments." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162817-the-problem-is-it-s-just-not-enough-to-live-according</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 17:15:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alban add a quote by Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162817-the-problem-is-it-s-just-not-enough-to-live-according]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem is, it's just not enough to live according to the rules. Sure, you manage to live according to the rules. Sometimes it's tight, extremely tight, but on the whole you manage it. Your tax papers are up to date. Your bills paid on time. You never go out without your identity card (and the special little wallet for your Visa!).
Yet you haven’t any friends.
The rules are complex, multiform. There’s the shopping that needs doing out of working hours, the automatic dispensers where money has to be got (and where you so often have to wait). Above all there are the different payments you must make to the organizations that run different aspects of your life. You can fall ill into the bargain, which involves costs, and more formalities.
Nevertheless, some free time remains. What’s to be done? How do you use your
time? In dedicating yourself to helping people? But basically other people don’t interest you. Listening to records? That used to be a solution, but as the years go by you have to say that music moves you less and less.
Taken in its widest sense, a spot of do-it-yourself can be a way out. But the fact is that nothing can halt the ever-increasing recurrence of those moments when your total isolation, the sensation of an all-consuming emptiness, the foreboding that your existence is nearing a painful and definitive end all combine to plunge you into a state of real suffering.
And yet you haven’t always wanted to die.
You have had a life. There have been moments when you were having a life. Of
course you don't remember too much about it; but there are photographs to prove it. This was probably happening round about the time of your adolescence, or just after. How great your appetite for life was, then! Existence seemed so rich in new possibilities. You might become a pop singer, go off to Venezuela.
More surprising still, you have had a childhood. Observe, now, a child of seven, playing with his little soldiers on the living room carpet. I want you to observe him closely. Since the divorce he no longer has a father. Only rarely does he see his mother, who occupies an important post in a cosmetics firm. And yet he plays with his little soldiers and the interest he takes in these representations of the world and of war seems very keen. He already lacks a bit of affection, that's for sure, but what an air he has of being interested in the world!
You too, you took an interest in the world. That was long ago. I want you to cast your mind back to then. The domain of the rules was no longer enough for you; you were unable to live any longer in the domain of the rules; so you had to enter into the domain of the struggle. I ask you to go back to that precise moment. It was long ago, no? Cast your mind back: the water was cold." -- Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
