<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/409615-teri-harman]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/409615-teri-harman" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 09:26:21 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129399-a-person-is-a-fool-to-become-a-writer-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 09:26:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teri add a quote by Roald Dahl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129399-a-person-is-a-fool-to-become-a-writer-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A person is a fool to become a writer. His only compensation is absolute freedom.  He has no master except his own soul, and that, I am sure, is why he does it" -- Roald Dahl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/301050-and-now-these-books-this-he-touched-physiognomonie-the-secrets</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 13:33:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teri add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/301050-and-now-these-books-this-he-touched-physiognomonie-the-secrets]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And now, these books. This. He touched PHYSIOGNOMONIE. The secrets of the individual's character as found on his face. Were Jim and Will, then, featured all angelic, pure, half-innocent, peering up through the sidewalk at marching terror? Did the boys represent the ideal for your Woman, Man, or Child of Excellent Bearing, Color, Balance, and Summer Disposition?
Converserly...Charles Halloway turned a page...did the scurrying freaks, the Illustrated Marvel, bear the foreheads of the Irascible, the Cruel, the Covetous, the mouths of the Lewd and Untruthful? the teeth of the Crafty, the Unstable, the Audacious, the Vainglorious, and your Marvelous Beast?
No. The book slipped shut. If faces were judged, the freaks were no worse than many he'd been slipping from the liberty late nights in his long career.
There was only one thing sure.
Two lines of Shakespeare said it. He should write them in the middle of the clock of books, to fix the heart of his apprehension:
By the pricking of my thumbs,
Something wicked this way comes.
So vague yet so immense.
He did not want to live with it.
Yet he knew that, during this night, unless he lived with it very well, he might have to live with it for all the rest of his life.
At the window he looked out and thought Jim, Will, are you coming? will you get here?
Waiting, his flesh took paleness from his bones." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66649-there-is-no-exquisite-beauty-without-some-strangeness-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 14:49:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teri add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66649-there-is-no-exquisite-beauty-without-some-strangeness-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no exquisite beauty… without some strangeness in the proportion." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408225-it-is-true-that-novelists-are-shameless-and-obey-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 08:46:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teri add a quote by Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408225-it-is-true-that-novelists-are-shameless-and-obey-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is true that novelists are shameless and obey no decent law, and they are not to be trusted on any account, but some Mysteries even they must honor." -- Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
