<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/410028-stephen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/410028-stephen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:23:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238373-behold-the-fool-saith-put-not-all-thine-eggs-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:23:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephen add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238373-behold-the-fool-saith-put-not-all-thine-eggs-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Behold, the fool saith, &quot;Put not all thine eggs in the one basket&quot; - which is but a matter of saying, &quot;Scatter your money and your attention&quot;; but the wise man saith, &quot;Pull all your eggs in the one basket and - WATCH THAT BASKET.&quot; - Pudd'nhead Wilson's Calendar" -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182534-this-is-what-i-find-most-encouraging-about-the-writing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:28:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephen add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut Jr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182534-this-is-what-i-find-most-encouraging-about-the-writing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what I find most encouraging about the writing trades: They allow mediocre people who are patient and industrious to revise their stupidity, to edit themselves into something like intelligence. They also allow lunatics to seem saner than sane." -- Kurt Vonnegut Jr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154267-though-i-speak-with-the-tongues-of-men-and-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 18:58:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephen add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154267-though-i-speak-with-the-tongues-of-men-and-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Though I speak with the tongues of men and of angels, and have not 
money, I am become as a sounding brass, or a tinkling cymbal. And 
though I have the gift of prophecy, and understand all mysteries, 
and all knowledge; and though I have all faith, so that I could 
remove mountains, and have not money, I am nothing. And though I 
bestow all my goods to feed the poor, and though I give my body to 
be burned, and have not money, it profiteth me nothing. Money 
suffereth long, and is kind; money envieth not; money vaunteth not 
itself, is not puffed up, doth not behave unseemly, seeketh not her 
own, is not easily provoked, thinketh no evil; rejoiceth not in 
iniquity, but rejoiceth in the truth; beareth all things, believeth 
all things, hopeth all things, endureth all things. . . . And now 
abideth faith, hope, money, these three; but the greatest of these 
is money. 

I Corinthians xiii (adapted) " -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
