<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/411691-joseph]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/411691-joseph" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 06:20:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62272-man-is-a-religious-animal-he-is-the-only-religious</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 06:20:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62272-man-is-a-religious-animal-he-is-the-only-religious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man is a Religious Animal. He is the only Religious Animal. He is the only animal that has the True Religion--several of them. He is the only animal that loves his neighbor as himself and cuts his throat if his theology isn't straight. He has made a graveyard of the globe in trying his honest best to smooth his brother's path to happiness and heaven....The higher animals have no religion. And we are told that they are going to be left out in the Hereafter. I wonder why? It seems questionable taste." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69213-o-ho-are-you-there-with-me-no-eyes-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 08:38:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69213-o-ho-are-you-there-with-me-no-eyes-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["O, ho, are you there with me?  No eyes in your head, nor no money in  your purse? Your eyes are in a heavy case, your purse in a light: yet  you see how this world goes.
Ear; of Gloster, “I see it feelingly.”
Lear, “What, art mad? A man may see how this world goes with no eyes. Look with thine ears: see how  yond justice rails upon yond simple thief. Hark, in thine ear: change places; and handy-dandy, which is the justice, which is the thief? - Thou hast seen a farmer’s dog bark at a begger?
Earl of Gloster, ‘Ay, sir.
Lear, “And the creature run from the cur? There thou mightst behold the great image of authority: a dog’s obey’d in office. - Thou rascal beadle, hold thy bloody hand! Why dost though lash that whore? Strip thine own back; Thou hotly lusts to use her in that kind For which thou whipst her. The usurer hangs the cozener. Through tattere’d clothes small vices to appear; Robes and furr’d gowns hide all. Plate sin with gold, And the strong lance of justice hurtless breaks; Arm it in rags, a pygmy’s straw does pierce it. None does offend, none, - I say, none; I’ll able ‘em to seal the accuser’s lips.  Get thee glass eyes; To see the things thou dost not. - Now, now, now, now: Pull off my boots: - harder, harder: - so.
Edgar (aside), “O, matter and impertinency mixt! Reason in madness!" -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69214-as-flies-to-wanton-boys-are-we-to-the-gods</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 08:40:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69214-as-flies-to-wanton-boys-are-we-to-the-gods]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As flies to wanton boys are we to the gods.
They kill us for their sport." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41840-this-is-the-excellent-foppery-of-the-world-that-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 08:41:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41840-this-is-the-excellent-foppery-of-the-world-that-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is the excellent foppery of the world, that,
when we are sick in fortune,--often the surfeit
of our own behavior,--we make guilty of our
disasters the sun, the moon, and the stars: as
if we were villains by necessity; fools by
heavenly compulsion; knaves, thieves, and
treachers, by spherical predominance; drunkards,
liars, and adulterers, by an enforced obedience of
planetary influence; and all that we are evil in,
by a divine thrusting on: an admirable evasion
of whoremaster man, to lay his goatish
disposition to the charge of a star." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69216-second-in-the-series-from-king-henry-the-fourth-part</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 08:43:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69216-second-in-the-series-from-king-henry-the-fourth-part]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Second in the series: From “King Henry the Fourth,  Part I, Act 5, Scene I where Prince Henry is speaking of honor in battle and Falstaff responds, “… honour pricks me on. Yea, but how if honour prick me off when I come on? How then? Can honour set a leg? No: or a arm? No: or take away the grief of a wound? No. Honour hath no skill in surgery then? No. What is honour? A word. What is that then? Air. A trim reckoning! - Who hath it? He that died o‘ Wednesday? Doth he feel it? No. Doth he hear it? No. ‘Tis insensible, then? Yea, to the dead. But will it not live with the living? No. Why? Detraction will not suffer it. Therefore I‘ll have none of it: honour is a mere scutcheon: - and so ends my catechism." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2458-i-am-a-jew-hath-not-a-jew-eyes-hath</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 08:44:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2458-i-am-a-jew-hath-not-a-jew-eyes-hath]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am a Jew. Hath not a Jew eyes? Hath not a Jew hands, organs, dimensions, senses, affections, passions; fed with the same food, hurt with the same weapons, subject to the same diseases, 
heal'd by the same means, warm'd and cool'd by the same winter and summer, as a Christian is? 

If you prick us, do we not bleed? If 
you tickle us, do we not laugh? If you poison us, do we not die? 

And if you wrong us, do we not revenge? If we are like you in the rest, we will resemble you in that." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48483-my-country-right-or-wrong-is-a-thing-that-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 08:51:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48483-my-country-right-or-wrong-is-a-thing-that-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My country, right or wrong,” is a thing that no patriot would think of saying except in a desperate case. It is like saying, “My mother, drunk or sober." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71368-wealth-consists-not-in-having-great-possessions-but-in-having</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 09:26:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by Epictetus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71368-wealth-consists-not-in-having-great-possessions-but-in-having]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wealth consists not in having great possessions, but in having few wants." -- Epictetus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71690-ecology-teaches-us-that-the-total-economy-of-the-planet</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 14:06:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by Kenneth Burke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71690-ecology-teaches-us-that-the-total-economy-of-the-planet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ecology teaches us “that the total economy of the planet cannot be guided by an efficient rationale of exploitation alone,” wrote Burke more than 70 years ago, “but that the exploiting part must eventually suffer if it too greatly disturbs the balance of the whole." -- Kenneth Burke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28449-i-believe-that-when-i-die-i-shall-rot-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2010 13:32:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28449-i-believe-that-when-i-die-i-shall-rot-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that when I die I shall rot, and nothing of my ego will survive. I am not young and I love life. But I should scorn to shiver with terror at the thought of annihilation. Happiness is nonetheless true happiness because it must come to an end, nor do thought and love lose their value because they are not everlasting. Many a man has borne himself proudly on the scaffold; surely the same pride should teach us to think truly about man's place in the world. Even if the open windows of science at first make us shiver after the cosy indoor warmth of traditional humanizing myths, in the end the fresh air brings vigour, and the great spaces have a splendour of their own." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
