<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/41181-linda]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/41181-linda" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2012 18:54:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22971-the-real-things-haven-t-changed-it-is-still-best-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2012 18:54:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Laura Ingalls Wilder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22971-the-real-things-haven-t-changed-it-is-still-best-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The real things haven't changed.  It is still best to be honest and truthful; to make the most of what we have; to be happy with simple pleasures; and have courage when things go wrong." -- Laura Ingalls Wilder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/651-all-that-we-see-or-seem-is-but-a-dream</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 08:58:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/651-all-that-we-see-or-seem-is-but-a-dream]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that we see or seem is but a dream within a dream." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1034124-no-his-mind-is-not-for-rent-to-any-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 17:59:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Rush]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1034124-no-his-mind-is-not-for-rent-to-any-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No, his mind is not for rent
To any god or government
Always hopeful, yet discontent
He knows changes aren't permanent
But change is" -- Rush]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21101-do-you-think-i-am-an-automaton-a-machine</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 20:13:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21101-do-you-think-i-am-an-automaton-a-machine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you think I am an automaton? — a machine without feelings? and can bear to have my morsel of bread snatched from my lips, and my drop of living water dashed from my cup? Do you think, because I am poor, obscure, plain, and little, I am soulless and heartless? You think wrong! — I have as much soul as you — and full as much heart! And if God had gifted me with some beauty and much wealth, I should have made it as hard for you to leave me, as it is now for me to leave you. I am not talking to you now through the medium of custom, conventionalities, nor even of mortal flesh: it is my spirit that addresses your spirit; just as if both had passed through the grave, and we stood at God's feet, equal — as we are!" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/323209-sometimes-ms-lane-he-said-one-must-break-with-one-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 20:26:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Karen Marie Moning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/323209-sometimes-ms-lane-he-said-one-must-break-with-one-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, Ms. Lane,&quot; he said, &quot;one must break with one's past to embrace one's future. It is never an easy thing to do. It is one of the distinguishing characteristics between survivors and victims. Letting go of what was, to survive what is." -- Karen Marie Moning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131460-for-the-first-twenty-years-of-my-life-i-rocked</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 20:28:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131460-for-the-first-twenty-years-of-my-life-i-rocked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the first twenty years of my life, I rocked myself to sleep.  It was a harmless enough hobby, but eventually, I had to give it up.  Throughout the next twenty-two years I lay still and discovered that after a few minutes I could drop off with no problem.  Follow seven beers with a couple of scotches and a thimble of good marijuana, and it’s funny how sleep just sort of comes on its own.  Often I never even made it to the bed.  I’d squat down to pet the cat and wake up on the floor eight hours later, having lost a perfectly good excuse to change my clothes.  I’m now told that this is not called “going to sleep” but rather “passing out,” a phrase that carries a distinct hint of judgment." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214560-you-know-i-do-believe-in-magic-i-was-born</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 20:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Robert R. McCammon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214560-you-know-i-do-believe-in-magic-i-was-born]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know, I do believe in magic. I was born and raised in a magic time, in a magic town, among magicians. Oh, most everybody else didn’t realize we lived in that web of magic, connected by silver filaments of chance and circumstance. But I knew it all along. When I was twelve years old, the world was my magic lantern, and by its green spirit glow I saw the past, the present and into the future. You probably did too; you just don’t recall it. See, this is my opinion: we all start out knowing magic. We are born with whirlwinds, forest fires, and comets inside us. We are born able to sing to birds and read the clouds and see our destiny in grains of sand. But then we get the magic educated right out of our souls. We get it churched out, spanked out, washed out, and combed out. We get put on the straight and narrow and told to be responsible. Told to act our age. Told to grow up, for God’s sake. And you know why we were told that? Because the people doing the telling were afraid of our wildness and youth, and because the magic we knew made them ashamed and sad of what they’d allowed to wither in themselves.

After you go so far away from it, though, you can’t really get it back. You can have seconds of it. Just seconds of knowing and remembering. When people get weepy at movies, it’s because in that dark theater the golden pool of magic is touched, just briefly. Then they come out into the hard sun of logic and reason again and it dries up, and they’re left feeling a little heartsad and not knowing why. When a song stirs a memory, when motes of dust turning in a shaft of light takes your attention from the world, when you listen to a train passing on a track at night in the distance and wonder where it might be going, you step beyond who you are and where you are. For the briefest of instants, you have stepped into the magic realm.

That’s what I believe.

The truth of life is that every year we get farther away from the essence that is born within us. We get shouldered with burdens, some of them good, some of them not so good. Things happen to us. Loved ones die. People get in wrecks and get crippled. People lose their way, for one reason or another. It’s not hard to do, in this world of crazy mazes. Life itself does its best to take that memory of magic away from us. You don’t know it’s happening until one day you feel you’ve lost something but you’re not sure what it is. It’s like smiling at a pretty girl and she calls you “sir.” It just happens.

These memories of who I was and where I lived are important to me. They make up a large part of who I’m going to be when my journey winds down. I need the memory of magic if I am ever going to conjure magic again. I need to know and remember, and I want to tell you." -- Robert R. McCammon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411641-i-had-always-wondered-what-reverend-lovoy-meant-when-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 20:30:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Robert McCammon (Author)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411641-i-had-always-wondered-what-reverend-lovoy-meant-when-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had always wondered what Reverend Lovoy meant when he talked about &quot;grace.&quot;  I understood it now.  It was being able to give up something that it broke your heart to lose, and be happy about it." -- Robert McCammon (Author)]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
