<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/412899-krista]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/412899-krista" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 23:45:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51851-perhaps-the-greatest-charity-comes-when-we-are-kind-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 23:45:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Marvin J. Ashton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51851-perhaps-the-greatest-charity-comes-when-we-are-kind-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps the greatest charity comes when we are kind to each other, when we don’t judge or categorize someone else, when we simply give each other the benefit of the doubt or remain quiet. Charity is accepting someone’s differences, weaknesses, and shortcomings; having patience with someone who has let us down; or resisting the impulse to become offended when someone doesn’t handle something the way we might have hoped. Charity is refusing to take advantage of another’s weakness and being willing to forgive someone who has hurt us. Charity is expecting the best of each other" -- Marvin J. Ashton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252628-perhaps-the-greatest-charity-comes-when-we-are-kind-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 23:45:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Marvin J. Ashton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252628-perhaps-the-greatest-charity-comes-when-we-are-kind-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps the greatest charity comes when we are kind to each other, when we don't judge or categorize someone else, when we simply give each other the benefit of the doubt or remain quiet. Charity is accepting someone's differences, weaknesses, and shortcomings; having patience with someone who has let us down; or resisting the impulse to become offended when someone doesn't handle something the way we might have hoped. Charity is refusing to take advantage of another's weakness and being willing to forgive someone who has hurt us. Charity is expecting the best of each other.

None of us need one more person bashing or pointing out where we have failed or fallen short. Most of us are already well aware of the areas in which we are weak. What each of us does need is family, friends, employers, and brothers and sisters who support us, who have the patience to teach us, who believe in us, and who believe we're trying to do the best we can, in spite of our weaknesses. What ever happened to giving each other the benefit of the doubt? What ever happened to hoping that another person would succeed or achieve? What ever happened to rooting for each other?" -- Marvin J. Ashton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106128-some-blessings-come-soon-some-come-late-and-some-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 15:13:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106128-some-blessings-come-soon-some-come-late-and-some-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some blessings come soon, some come late, and some don't come until heaven; but for those who embrace the gospel of Jesus Christ, they come." -- Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/354763-don-t-you-quit-you-keep-walking-you-keep-trying-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 15:14:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/354763-don-t-you-quit-you-keep-walking-you-keep-trying-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't you quit. You keep walking, you keep trying, there is help and happiness ahead. Some blessings come soon. Some come late. Some don't come until heaven. But for those who embrace the gospel of Jesus Christ, they come. It will be alright in the end. Trust God and believe in Good Things to Come." -- Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27602-cultivate-an-attitude-of-happiness-cultivate-a-spirit-of-optimism</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 12:27:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27602-cultivate-an-attitude-of-happiness-cultivate-a-spirit-of-optimism]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cultivate an attitude of happiness. Cultivate a spirit of optimism. Walk with faith, rejoicing in the beauties of nature, in the goodness of those you love, in the testimony which you carry in your heart concerning things divine." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27605-each-of-us-will-have-our-own-fridays-those-days-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 12:28:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Joseph B. Wirthlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27605-each-of-us-will-have-our-own-fridays-those-days-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each of us will have our own Fridays—those days when the universe itself seems shattered and the shards of our world lie littered about us in pieces. We all will experience those broken times when it seems we can never be put together again. We will all have our Fridays. But I testify to you in the name of the One who conquered death—Sunday will come. In the darkness of our sorrow, Sunday will come. No matter our desperation, no matter our grief, Sunday will come. In this life or the next, Sunday will come." -- Joseph B. Wirthlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27601-patience-is-tied-very-closely-to-faith-in-our-heavenly</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 12:29:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27601-patience-is-tied-very-closely-to-faith-in-our-heavenly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Patience is tied very closely to faith in our Heavenly Father. Actually, when we are unduly impatient, we are suggesting that we know what is best—better than does God. Or, at least, we are asserting that our timetable is better than His. We can grow in faith only if we are willing to wait patiently for God's purposes and patterns to unfold in our lives, on His timetable." -- Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36605-jesus-said-several-times-come-follow-me-his-was-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 12:32:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Spencer W. Kimball]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36605-jesus-said-several-times-come-follow-me-his-was-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jesus said several times, “Come, follow me.” His was a program of “do what I do,” rather than “do what I say.” His innate brilliance would have permitted him to put on a dazzling display, but that would have left his followers far behind. He walked and worked with those he was to serve. His was not a long-distance leadership. He was not afraid of close friendships; he was not afraid that proximity to him would disappoint his followers. The leaven of true leadership cannot lift others unless we are with and serve those to be led." -- Spencer W. Kimball]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62463-do-not-allow-yourselves-to-be-made-to-feel-inadequate</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 12:33:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Marvin. J. Ashton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62463-do-not-allow-yourselves-to-be-made-to-feel-inadequate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not allow yourselves to be made to feel inadequate or frustrated because you cannot do everything others seem to be accomplishing.  Only you and your Father in Heaven know your needs, strengths, and desires.  Around this knowledge your personal course must be charted and your chioces made." -- Marvin. J. Ashton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27604-perseverance-means-to-continue-in-a-given-course-until-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 12:35:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Joseph B. Wirthlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27604-perseverance-means-to-continue-in-a-given-course-until-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perseverance means to continue in a given course until we have reached a goal or objective, regardless of obstacles, opposition, and other counterinfluences...Perseverance is a positive, active characteristic...It gives us hope by helping us realize that the righteous suffer no failure except in giving up and no longer trying." -- Joseph B. Wirthlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95243-any-task-in-life-is-easier-if-we-approach-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 12:37:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Richard L. Evans]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95243-any-task-in-life-is-easier-if-we-approach-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any task in life is easier if we approach it with the one at a time attitude. ... To cite a whimsical saying; 'If you chase two rabbits, both of them will escape.' No one is adequate to do everything all at once. We have to select what is important, what is possible, and begin where we are, with what we have. And if we beginand if we keep going the weight, the worry, the doubt, the depression will begin to lift .... We can't do everything always, but we can do something now, and doing something will help to lift the weight and lessen the worry, 'The beginning,' said Plato, 'is the most important part." -- Richard L. Evans]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118529-in-the-things-that-really-matter--our-covenants-the-commandments-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 12:41:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Sheri L. Dew]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118529-in-the-things-that-really-matter--our-covenants-the-commandments-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the things that really matter--our covenants, the commandments, and following the prophet--we need to be completely united.  In the non-essentials, we have our agency to handle things as we see fit.  But, in all things, regardless of whether we make the same choices or not, we are to treat each other with dignity and respect, both of which are evidences of charity in our hearts and lives." -- Sheri L. Dew]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431932-you-are-good-but-it-is-not-enough-just-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 12:44:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431932-you-are-good-but-it-is-not-enough-just-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are good. But it is not enough just to be good. You must be good for something. You must contribute good to the world. The world must be a better place for your presence. And the good that is in you must be spread to others… In this world so filled with problems, so constantly threatened by dark and evil challenges, you can and must rise above mediocrity, above indifference. You can become involved and speak with a strong voice for that which is right." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 12:56:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Kent M. Keith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Paradoxical Commandments

People are illogical, unreasonable, and self-centered.
Love them anyway.

If you do good, people will accuse you of selfish ulterior motives.
Do good anyway.

If you are successful, you will win false friends and true enemies.
Succeed anyway.

The good you do today will be forgotten tomorrow.
Do good anyway.

Honesty and frankness make you vulnerable.
Be honest and frank anyway.

The biggest men and women with the biggest ideas can be shot down by the smallest men and women with the smallest minds.
Think big anyway.

People favor underdogs but follow only top dogs.
Fight for a few underdogs anyway.

What you spend years building may be destroyed overnight.
Build anyway.

People really need help but may attack you if you do help them.
Help people anyway.

Give the world the best you have and you'll get kicked in the teeth.
Give the world the best you have anyway." -- Kent M. Keith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128964-our-testimonies-our-closeness-to-our-father-in-heaven-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 13:03:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Kristen McMain Oaks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128964-our-testimonies-our-closeness-to-our-father-in-heaven-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our testimonies, our closeness to our Father in Heaven, and our ability to serve and love and laugh and enjoy life do not depend on whether we are married or single. If we look to Christ for answers, He will give them. It also follows that with our increased devotion and understanding of Him, the happier and more complete we will become and the more we will comprehend our true worth in the sight of God." -- Kristen McMain Oaks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274536-and-now-i-moroni-would-speaksomewhatconcerning-these-things-i-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 13:07:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274536-and-now-i-moroni-would-speaksomewhatconcerning-these-things-i-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And now, I, Moroni would speaksomewhatconcerning these things; I would show unto the world that faith is things which are hoped for and not seen; wherefore, dispute not because ye seenot, for ye recieve no witness until after the trial of your faith.
For it was by Faith that Christ showed himself unto our fathers after he had risen from the dead; and he showed not himself unto them until after they had fiath in him; wherefore, it must needs be that some had faith in hime, for he showed himself not unto the world." -- The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518935-christ-walked-the-path-every-mortal-is-called-to-walk</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 13:13:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518935-christ-walked-the-path-every-mortal-is-called-to-walk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Christ walked the path every mortal is called to walk so that he would know how to succor and strengthen us in our most difficult times.  He knows the deepest and most personal burdens we carry.  He knows the most public and poignant pains we bear.  He descended below al such grief in order that he might lift us above it.  There is no anguish or sorrow or sadness in life that he has not suffered in our behalf and borne away upon his own valiant and compassionate shoulders." -- Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518908-the-saints-should-always-remember-that-god-sees-not-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 13:17:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by George Q. Cannon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518908-the-saints-should-always-remember-that-god-sees-not-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The saints should always remember that God sees not as man sees; that he does not willingly afflict his children, and that if he requires them to endure present privation and trial, it is that they may escape greater tribulations which would otherwise inevitably overtake them. If He deprives them of any present blessing, it is that he may bestow upon them greater and more glorious ones by-and by." -- George Q. Cannon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518919-in-the-heroic-effort-of-the-handcart-pioneers-we-learn</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 13:19:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by James E. Faust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518919-in-the-heroic-effort-of-the-handcart-pioneers-we-learn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the heroic effort of the handcart pioneers, we learn a great truth. All must pass through a refiner’s fire, and the insignificant and unimportant in our lives can melt away like dross and make our faith bright, intact, and strong. There seems to be a full measure of anguish, sorrow, and often heartbreak for everyone, including those who earnestly seek to do right and be faithful. Yet this is part of the purging to become acquainted with God." -- James E. Faust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522099-now-the-atonement-of-christ-is-the-most-basic-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 13:21:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Bruce R. McConkie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522099-now-the-atonement-of-christ-is-the-most-basic-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now, the atonement of Christ is the most basic and fundamental doctrine of the gospel, and it is the least understood of all our revealed truths.

Many of us have a superficial knowledge and rely upon the Lord and his goodness to see us through the trials and perils of life.

But if we are to have faith like Enoch and Elijah we must believe what they believed, know what they knew, and live as they lived.

May I invite you to join with me in gaining a sound and sure knowledge of the Atonement.

We must cast aside the philosophies of men and the wisdom of the wise and hearken to that Spirit which is given to us to guide us into all truth.

We must search the scriptures, accepting them as the mind and will and voice of the Lord and the very power of God unto salvation.

As we read, ponder, and pray, there will come into our minds a view of the three gardens of God—the Garden of Eden, the Garden of Gethsemane, and the Garden of the Empty Tomb where Jesus appeared to Mary Magdalene." -- Bruce R. McConkie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160333-the-only-calibration-that-counts-is-how-much-heart-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 13:02:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Ted Hughes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160333-the-only-calibration-that-counts-is-how-much-heart-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only calibration that counts is how much heart people invest, how much they ignore their fears of being hurt or caught out or humiliated. And the only thing people regret is that they didn't live boldly enough, that they didn't invest enough heart, didn't love enough. Nothing else really counts at all." -- Ted Hughes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/631560-do-a-loony-goony-dance-cross-the-kitchen-floor-put-something</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 13:01:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Shel Silverstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/631560-do-a-loony-goony-dance-cross-the-kitchen-floor-put-something]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do a loony-goony dance 
'Cross the kitchen floor, 
Put something silly in the world 
That ain't been there before." -- Shel Silverstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218975-no-pain-that-we-suffer-no-trial-that-we-experience</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 12:44:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krista add a quote by Orson F. Whitney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218975-no-pain-that-we-suffer-no-trial-that-we-experience]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No pain that we suffer, no trial that we experience is wasted. It ministers to our education, to the development of such qualities as patience, faith, fortitude and humility. All that we suffer and all that we endure, especially when we endure it patiently, builds up our characters, purifies our hearts, expands our souls, and makes us more tender and charitable, more worthy to be called the children of God . . . and it is through sorrow and suffering, toil and tribulation, that we gain the education that we come here to acquire and which will make us more like our Father and Mother in heaven." -- Orson F. Whitney]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
