<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/412902-jon]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/412902-jon" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 22:31:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39670-no-live-organism-can-continue-for-long-to-exist-sanely</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 22:31:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Shirley Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39670-no-live-organism-can-continue-for-long-to-exist-sanely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No live organism can continue for long to exist sanely under conditions of absolute reality." -- Shirley Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45163-it-s-easier-to-floss-with-barbed-wire-than-admit-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 06:44:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45163-it-s-easier-to-floss-with-barbed-wire-than-admit-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's easier to floss with barbed wire than admit you like someone in middle school." -- Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30130-hell-is-empty-and-all-the-devils-are-here</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 17:38:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30130-hell-is-empty-and-all-the-devils-are-here]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hell is empty and all the devils are here." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212528-perhaps-the-difference-between-a-professor-and-a-bus-driver</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 17:58:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Les Back]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212528-perhaps-the-difference-between-a-professor-and-a-bus-driver]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps the difference between a professor and a bus driver is that the professor can say stupid things with complete authority while the bus driver is not authorized to make brilliant insights." -- Les Back]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212529-when-something-seems-the-most-obvious-thing-in-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 18:04:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Bertolt Brecht]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212529-when-something-seems-the-most-obvious-thing-in-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When something seems ‘the most obvious thing in the world’ it means that any attempt to understand the world has been given up." -- Bertolt Brecht]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212531-if-we-are-in-a-general-way-permitted-to-regard</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 18:12:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Georg Wilhelm Friedrich Hegel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212531-if-we-are-in-a-general-way-permitted-to-regard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we are in a general way permitted to regard human activity in the realm of the beautiful as a liberation of the soul, as a release from constraint and restriction, in short to consider that art does actually alleviate the most overpowering and tragic catastrophes by means of the creations it offers to our contemplation and enjoyment, it is the art of music which conducts us to the final summit of that ascent to freedom." -- Georg Wilhelm Friedrich Hegel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212532-there-is-a-common-tendency-to-turn-off-one-s-imagination</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 18:15:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by John Fraser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212532-there-is-a-common-tendency-to-turn-off-one-s-imagination]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a common tendency to turn off one's imagination at certain points and refuse to contemplate the possibility of having to do certain things and cope with the attendant moral problems.  The things simply get done by the social machine, and one can keep one's clear conscience and one's moral indignation unsullied." -- John Fraser]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212533-truth-be-told-i-m-not-an-easy-man-i-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 18:17:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Richard Russo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212533-truth-be-told-i-m-not-an-easy-man-i-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Truth be told, I'm not an easy man.  I can be an entertaining one, though it's been my experience that most people don't want to be entertained.  They want to be comforted.  And, of course, my idea of entertaining might not be yours.  I'm in complete agreement with all those people who say, regarding movies, 'I just want to be entertained.'  This populist position is much derided by my academic colleagues as simpleminded and unsophisticated, evidence of questionable analytical and critical acuity.  But I agree with the premise, and I too just want to be entertained.  That I am almost never entertained by what entertains other people who just want to be entertained doesn't make us philosophically incompatible.  It just means that we shouldn't go to movies together." -- Richard Russo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212537-we-don-t-live-in-a-world-that-suffers-from-doubt</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 18:20:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Les Back]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212537-we-don-t-live-in-a-world-that-suffers-from-doubt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don’t live in a world that suffers from doubt, but one that suffers from certainty, false certainties that compensate for the well of worldly anxieties and worries." -- Les Back]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212540-i-have-often-wondered-sir-to-observe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 18:26:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Henry Fielding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212540-i-have-often-wondered-sir-to-observe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have often wondered, Sir, [. . .] to observe so few Instances of Charity among Mankind; for tho' the Goodness of a Man's Heart did not incline him to relieve the Distresses of his Fellow-Creatures, methinks the Desire of Honour should move him to it. What inspires a Man to build fine Houses, to purchase fine Furniture, Pictures, Clothes, and other things at a great Expence, but an Ambition to be respected more than other People? Now would not one great Act of Charity, one Instance of redeeming a poor Family from all the Miseries of Poverty, restoring an unfortunate Tradesman by a Sum of Money to the means of procuring a Livelihood by his Industry, discharging an undone Debtor from his Debts or a Goal, or any such Example of Goodness, create a Man more Honour and Respect than he could acquire by the finest House, Furniture, Pictures or Clothes that were ever beheld? For not only the Object himself who was thus relieved, but all who heard the Name of such a Person must, I imagine, reverence him infinitely more than the Possessor of all those other things: which when we so admire, we rather praise the Builder, the Workman, the Painter, the Laceman, the Taylor, and the rest, by whose Ingenuity they are produced, than the Person who by his Money makes them his own." -- Henry Fielding]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216422-we-take-off-into-the-cosmos-ready-for-anything-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 21:01:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Stanisław Lem]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216422-we-take-off-into-the-cosmos-ready-for-anything-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We take off into the cosmos, ready for anything: for solitude, for hardship, for exhaustion, death. Modesty forbids us to say so, but there are times when we think pretty well of ourselves. And yet, if we examine it more closely, our enthusiasm turns out to be all a sham. We don't want to conquer the cosmos, we simply want to extend the boundaries of Earth to the frontiers of the cosmos. For us, such and such a planet is as arid as the Sahara, another as frozen as the North Pole, yet another as lush as the Amazon basin. We are humanitarian and chivalrous; we don't want to enslave other races, we simply want to bequeath them our values and take over their heritage in exchange. We think of ourselves as the Knights of the Holy Contact. This is another lie. We are only seeking Man. We have no need of other worlds. A single world, our own, suffices us; but we can't accept it for what it is. We are searching for an ideal image of our own world: we go in quest of a planet, a civilization superior to our own but developed on the basis of a prototype of our primeval past. At the same time, there is something inside us which we don't like to face up to, from which we try to protect ourselves, but which nevertheless remains, since we don't leave Earth in a state of primal innocence. We arrive here as we are in reality, and when the page is turned and that reality is revealed to us - that part of our reality which we would prefer to pass over in silence - then we don't like it anymore." -- Stanisław Lem]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219735-any-capitalist-who-had-made-sixty-thousand</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 18:37:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219735-any-capitalist-who-had-made-sixty-thousand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any capitalist . . . who had made sixty thousand pounds out of sixpence, always professed to wonder why the sixty thousand nearest Hands didn't each make sixty thousand pounds out of sixpence, and more or less reproached them every one for not accomplishing the little feat. What I did you can do. Why don't you go and do it?" -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235327-anything-that-doesn-t-take-years-of-your-life-and-drive</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 22:21:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235327-anything-that-doesn-t-take-years-of-your-life-and-drive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anything that doesn't take years of your life and drive you to suicide hardly seems worth doing." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267864-today-everybody-is-talking-about-the-fact-that-we-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 01:33:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267864-today-everybody-is-talking-about-the-fact-that-we-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today everybody is talking about the fact that we live in one world; because of globalization, we are all part of the same planet. They talk that way, but do they mean it? We should remind them that the words of the Declaration [of Independence] apply not only to people in this country, but also to people all over the world. People everywhere have the same right to life, liberty, and the pursuit of happiness. When the government becomes destructive of that, then it is patriotic to dissent and to criticize - to do what we always praise and call heroic when we look upon the dissenters and critics in totalitarian countries who dare to speak out." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267866-a-society-without-the-authentic-and-vibrant-influence-of-women</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 01:41:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Stephen Catanzarite]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267866-a-society-without-the-authentic-and-vibrant-influence-of-women]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A society without the authentic and vibrant influence of women is a society that is not fully alive. A culture lacking the vital creativity of women is disadvantaged. Without the bearing of women on world affairs, humanity's already tenuous grip on peace is made even less sure. When women are barred, whether by law, cultural prejudice, or political ideology, from developing their full potential and offering their unique gifts, it is an injustice to women themselves and to humanity as a whole." -- Stephen Catanzarite]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269956-if-something-is-going-to-happen-to-me-i-want</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 16:52:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269956-if-something-is-going-to-happen-to-me-i-want]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If something is going to happen to me, I want to be there." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277002-as-usual-in-every-scheme-that-worsens-the-position-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 00:03:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Vandana Shiva]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277002-as-usual-in-every-scheme-that-worsens-the-position-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As usual, in every scheme that worsens the position of the poor, it is the poor who are invoked as beneficiaries." -- Vandana Shiva]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277003-gordon-edgley-s-sudden-death-came-as-a-shock-to-everyone</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 00:10:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Derek Landy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277003-gordon-edgley-s-sudden-death-came-as-a-shock-to-everyone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Gordon Edgley's sudden death came as a shock to everyone - not least himself. One moment he was in his study, seven words into the twenty-fifth sentence of the final chapter of his new book, &lt;i&gt;And the Darkness Rained upon Them&lt;/i&gt;, and the next he was dead. &lt;i&gt;A tragic loss&lt;/i&gt;, his mind echoed numbly as he slipped away." -- Derek Landy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278899-people-ask-themselves-what-is-suitable-for-my-position-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 21:54:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by John Stuart Mill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278899-people-ask-themselves-what-is-suitable-for-my-position-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[People] ask themselves, what is suitable for my position? What is usually done by persons of my station and percuniary circumstances? Or (worse still) what is usually done by persons of a station and circumstances superior to mine? I do not mean that they choose what is customary in preference to what suits their own inclinations. It does not occur to them to have any inclination, except for what is customary. Thus the mind itself is bowed to the yoke: even in what people do for pleasure, conformity is the first thing thought of; they like in crowds; they exercise choice only among things that are commonly done: peculiarity of taste, eccentricity of conduct, are shunned equally with crimes: until by dint of not following their own nature they have no nature to follow: their human capacities are withered and starved: they become incapable of any strong wishes or native pleasures, and are generally without either opinions or feelings of home growth, or properly their own." -- John Stuart Mill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279280-right-now-in-every-big-city-ghetto-tens-of-thousands</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 21:34:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Malcolm X]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279280-right-now-in-every-big-city-ghetto-tens-of-thousands]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Right now, in every big city ghetto, tens of thousands of yesterday's and today's school dropouts are keeping body and soul together by some form of hustling in the same way I did." -- Malcolm X]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/281531-i-don-t-think-that-god-says-go-to-church-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 16:48:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Elvia Alvarado]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/281531-i-don-t-think-that-god-says-go-to-church-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't think that God says, &quot;Go to church and pray all day and everything will be fine.&quot; No. For me God says, &quot;Go out and make the changes that need to be made, and I'll be there to help you." -- Elvia Alvarado]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290506-america-is-subsidizing-what-is-left-of-the-prestige-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 09:18:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Malcolm X]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290506-america-is-subsidizing-what-is-left-of-the-prestige-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["America is subsidizing what is left of the prestige and strength of the once mighty Britain. The sun has set forever on that monocled, pith-helmeted resident colonialist, sipping tea with his delicate lady in the non-white colonies being systematically robbed of every valuable resource. Britain's superfluous royalty and nobility now exist by charging tourists to inspect the once baronial castles, and by selling memoirs, perfumes, autographs, titles, and even themselves." -- Malcolm X]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290512-i-have-seen-many-cases-like-n-during-the-five</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 09:28:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290512-i-have-seen-many-cases-like-n-during-the-five]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have seen many cases like N. during the five years I've been in practice. I sometimes picture these unfortunates as men and women being pecked to death by predatory birds. The birds are invisible - at least until a psychiatrist who is good, or lucky, or both, sprays them with his version of Luminol and shines the right light on them - but they are nevertheless very real. The wonder is that so many OCDs manage to live productive lives, just the same. They work, they eat (often not enough or too much, it's true), they go to movies, they make love to their girlfriends and boyfriends, their wives and husbands . . . and all the time those birds are there, clinging to them and pecking away little bits of flesh." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295079-i-feel-ill-howl-announced-i-m-going-to-bed-where</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 18:27:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Diana Wynne Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295079-i-feel-ill-howl-announced-i-m-going-to-bed-where]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I feel ill,&quot; [Howl] announced. &quot;I'm going to bed, where I may die." -- Diana Wynne Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302372-i-do-not-know-if-all-cops-are-poets-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 20:46:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Ralph Ellison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302372-i-do-not-know-if-all-cops-are-poets-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not know if all cops are poets, but I know that all cops carry guns with triggers." -- Ralph Ellison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321105-if-hitting-an-unexpected-speed-bump-with-your-car-equates</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2010 10:25:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Ellen Phillips]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321105-if-hitting-an-unexpected-speed-bump-with-your-car-equates]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If hitting an unexpected speed bump with your car equates to the best sex you've had lately, you know your hormones are sending you a signal." -- Ellen Phillips]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321106-as-an-artist-you-look-into-yourself-to-understand-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2010 10:33:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by David Cronenberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321106-as-an-artist-you-look-into-yourself-to-understand-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As an artist you look into yourself to understand the human potential to be all kinds of things that are not necessarily pleasant but are real - a criminal, a murderer, a sadist, a rapist; to be all of these things that many people are. You can't allow yourself to say, 'I'm a different species from those people.' Because you aren't.

The criminal as monster is kind of common. That's very convenient because you can then say, 'Of course I'm not a monster, therefore I'm not a criminal therefore I have no potential in tern of criminality.' And that lets you off the hook. That gives you a nice wall between yourself and them." -- David Cronenberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352627-it-comes-down-to-this-we-re-pieces-of-equipment-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 23:37:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Rolando Hinojosa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352627-it-comes-down-to-this-we-re-pieces-of-equipment-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It comes down to this: we're pieces of equipment
To be counted and signed for.
     On occasion some of us break down,
And those parts which can't be salvaged
Are replaced with other GI parts, that's all." -- Rolando Hinojosa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/387512-our-nation-was-born-in-genocide-when-it-embraced-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 08:44:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Dr. Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/387512-our-nation-was-born-in-genocide-when-it-embraced-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our nation was born in genocide when it embraced the doctrine that the original American, the Indian, was an inferior race. Even before there were large numbers of Negroes on our shore, the scar of racial hatred had already disfigured colonial society. From the sixteenth century forward, blood flowed in battles over racial supremacy. We are perhaps the only nation which tried as a matter of national policy to wipe out its indigenous population. Moreover, we elevated that tragic experience into a noble crusade. Indeed, even today we have not permitted ourselves to reject or feel remorse for this shameful episode. Our literature, our films, our drama, our folklore all exalt it. Our children are still taught to respect the violence which reduced a red-skinned people of an earlier culture into a few fragmented groups herded into impoverished reservations." -- Dr. Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/389103-single-parents---both-women-and-men---can-play</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 00:22:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jon add a quote by Michael Kimmel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/389103-single-parents---both-women-and-men---can-play]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Single parents - both women and men - can play as critical a role as the traditional two-parent family, and gay and lesbian parents can, and do, raise happy, resilient children. When it comes to family life, form is not merely as important as content. Feeling loved and supported, nurtured and safe, is far more critical than the 'package' it comes in." -- Michael Kimmel]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
