<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/413569-michelle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/413569-michelle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2008 08:44:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31829-you-are-doing-god-s-work-you-are-doing-it-wonderfully</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2008 08:44:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31829-you-are-doing-god-s-work-you-are-doing-it-wonderfully]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are doing God's work. You are doing it wonderfully well. He is blessing you, and He will bless you, --even--no, -especially--when your days and your nights may be most challenging. Like the woman who anonymously, meekly, perhaps even with hesitation and some embarrassment, fought her way through the crowd just to touch the hem of the Master's garment, so Christ will say to the women who worry and wonder and weep over their responsibility as mothers, `Daughter, be of good comfort; thy faith hath made thee whole.' And it will make your children whole as well." -- Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65579-god-expects-you-to-have-enough-faith-and-determination-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2008 08:45:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65579-god-expects-you-to-have-enough-faith-and-determination-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God expects you to have enough faith and determination and enough trust in Him to keep moving, keep living, keep rejoicing. In fact, He expects you not simply to face the future (that sounds pretty grim and stoic); He expects you to embrace and shape the future--to love it and rejoice in it and delight in your opportunities.

God is anxiously waiting for the chance to answer your prayers and fulfill your dreams, just as He always has. But He can't if you don't pray, and He can't if you don't dream. In short, He can't if you don't believe." -- Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
