<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/4147-robert]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/4147-robert" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 06:39:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115309-your-head-s-like-mine-like-all-our-heads-big-enough</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 06:39:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Grant Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115309-your-head-s-like-mine-like-all-our-heads-big-enough]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your head's like mine, like all our heads; big enough to contain every god and devil there ever was. Big enough to hold the weight of oceans and the turning stars. Whole universes fit in there! But what do we choose to keep in this miraculous cabinet? Little broken things, sad trinkets that we play with over and over. The world turns our key and we play the same little tune again and again and we think that tune's all we are." -- Grant Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153062-one-thought-alone-preoccupies-the-submerged-mind-of-empire-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 06:39:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153062-one-thought-alone-preoccupies-the-submerged-mind-of-empire-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One thought alone preoccupies the submerged mind of Empire: how not to end, how not to die, how to prolong its era. By day it pursues its enemies. It is cunning and ruthless, it sends its bloodhounds everywhere. By night it feeds on images of disaster: the sack of cities, the rape of populations, pyramids of bones, acres of desolation." -- J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154774-to-the-last-we-have-learned-nothing-in-all-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 06:39:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154774-to-the-last-we-have-learned-nothing-in-all-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To the last we have learned nothing. In all of us, deep down, there seems to be something granite and unteachable. No one truly believes, despite the hysteria in the streets that the world of tranquil certainties we were born into is about to be extinguished." -- J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47261-generally-speaking-i-think-it-is-fair-to-say-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 06:39:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by John Hodgman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47261-generally-speaking-i-think-it-is-fair-to-say-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Generally speaking, I think it is fair to say that I am a friend to the creatures of the Earth when I am not busy eating them or wearing them." -- John Hodgman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43565-he-walked-out-in-the-gray-light-and-stood-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 06:39:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43565-he-walked-out-in-the-gray-light-and-stood-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He walked out in the gray light and stood and he saw for a brief moment the absolute truth of the world. The cold relentless circling of the intestate earth. Darkness implacable. The blind dogs of the sun in their running. The crushing black vacuum of the universe. And somewhere two hunted animals trembling like ground-foxes in their cover. Borrowed time and borrowed world and borrowed eyes with which to sorrow it." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23141-deep-in-each-man-is-the-knowledge-that-something-knows</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2009 09:02:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23141-deep-in-each-man-is-the-knowledge-that-something-knows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Deep in each man is the knowledge that something knows of his existence. Something knows, and cannot be fled nor hid from." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221447-snowflake-you-catch-the-snowflake-but-when-you-look-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 06:57:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221447-snowflake-you-catch-the-snowflake-but-when-you-look-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Snowflake. You catch the snowflake but when you look in your hand you don’t have it no more. Maybe you see this dechado. But before you see it it is gone. If you want to see it you have to see it on its own ground. If you catch it you lose it. And where it goes there is no coming back from. Not even God can bring it back." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241281-he-sat-a-long-time-and-he-thought-about-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 06:40:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241281-he-sat-a-long-time-and-he-thought-about-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He sat a long time and he thought about his life and how little of it he could ever have foreseen and he wondered for all his will and all his intent how much of it was his doing." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268415-one-would-think-a-writer-would-be-happy-here---</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 10:36:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Raymond Chandler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268415-one-would-think-a-writer-would-be-happy-here---]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One would think a writer would be happy here -- if a writer is every happy anywhere." -- Raymond Chandler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275981-you-talk-too-damn-much-and-too-damn-much-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 17:25:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Raymond Chandler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275981-you-talk-too-damn-much-and-too-damn-much-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You talk too damn much and too damn much of it is about you." -- Raymond Chandler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59786-all-reality-is-a-game-physics-at-its-most-fundamental</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 05:52:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Iain M. Banks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59786-all-reality-is-a-game-physics-at-its-most-fundamental]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All reality is a game. Physics at its most fundamental, the very fabric of our universe, results directly from the interaction of certain fairly simple rules, and chance; the same description may be applied to the best, most elefant and both intellectually and aesthetically satisfying games. By being unknowable, by resulting from events which, at the sub-atomic level, cannot be fully predicted, the future remains makkeable, and retains the possibility of change, the hope of coming to prevail; victory, to use an unfashionable word. In this, the future is a game; time is one of the rules. Generally, all the best mechanistic games - those which can be played in any sense &quot;perfectly&quot;, such as a grid, Prallian scope, 'nkraytle, chess, Farnic dimensions - can be traced to civilisations lacking a realistic view of the universe (let alone the reality). They are also, I might add, invariably pre-machine-sentience societies.

    The very first-rank games acknowledge the element of chance, even if they rightly restrict raw luck. To attempt to construct a game on any other lines, no matter how complicated and subtle the rules are, and regardless of the scale and differentiation of the playing volume and the variety of the powers and attibutes of the pieces, is inevitably to schackle oneself to a conspectus which is not merely socially but techno-philosophically lagging several ages behind our own. As a historical exercise it might have some value, As a work of the intellect, it's just a waste of time. If you want to make something old-fashioned, why not build a wooden sailing boat, or a steam engine? They're just as complicated and demanding as a mechanistic game, and you'll keep fit at the same time." -- Iain M. Banks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303824-cats-were-the-gangsters-of-the-animal-world-living-outside</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 07:08:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303824-cats-were-the-gangsters-of-the-animal-world-living-outside]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cats were the gangsters of the animal world, living outside the law and often dying there. There were a great many of them who never grew old by the fire." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277342-the-soil-of-a-man-s-heart-is-stonier-a-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 07:14:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277342-the-soil-of-a-man-s-heart-is-stonier-a-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The soil of a man’s heart is stonier; a man grows what he can and tends it." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/355082-what-could-a-child-know-of-the-darkness-of-god-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 07:59:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/355082-what-could-a-child-know-of-the-darkness-of-god-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What could a child know of the darkness of God's plan? Or how flesh is so frail it is hardly more than a dream" -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23134-so-everything-is-necessary-every-least-thing-this-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 13:07:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23134-so-everything-is-necessary-every-least-thing-this-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So everything is necessary. Every least thing. This is the hard lesson. Nothing can be dispensed with. Nothing despised. Because the seams are hid from us, you see. The joinery. The way in which the world is made. We have no way to know what could be taken away. What omitted. We have no way to tell what might stand and what might fall." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339274-music-expresses-feeling-that-is-to-say-gives-shape-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2011 05:29:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339274-music-expresses-feeling-that-is-to-say-gives-shape-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Music expresses feeling, that is to say, gives shape and habitation to feeling, not in space but in time. To the extent that music has a history that is more than a history of its formal evolution, our feelings must have a history too. Perhaps certain qualities of feeling that found expression in music can be recorded by being notated on paper, have become so remote that we can no longer inhabit them as feelings, can get a grasp of them only after long training in the history and philosophy of music, the philosophical history of music, the history of music as a history of the feeling soul." -- J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249420-i-had-two-dreams-about-him-after-he-died-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2011 05:43:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249420-i-had-two-dreams-about-him-after-he-died-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had two dreams about him after he died.  I dont remember the first one all that well but it was about meetin him in town somewheres and he give me some money and I think I lost it.  But the second one it was like we was both back in older times and I was on horseback goin through the mountains of a night.  Goin through this pass in the mountains.  It was cold and there was snow on the ground and he rode past me and kept on goin.  Never said nothin.  He just rode on past and he had this blanket wrapped around him and he had his head down and when he rode past I seen he was carryin fire in a horn the way people used to do and I could see the horn from the light inside of it.  About the color of the moon.  And in the dream I knew that he was goin on ahead and that he was fixin to make a fire somewhere out there in all that dark and all that cold and I knew that whenever I got there he would be there.  And then I woke up." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110589-no-soul-moves-alone-through-the-world-leweth-our-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 06:17:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by R. Scott Bakker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110589-no-soul-moves-alone-through-the-world-leweth-our-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No soul moves alone through the world, Leweth. Our every thought stems from the thoughts of others. Our every word is but a repetition of world spoken before. Every time we listen, we allow the movements of another should to carry our own...NO one's soul moves alone, Leweth. When one love dies, on must learn to love another." -- R. Scott Bakker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240957-the-thoughts-of-all-men-arise-from-the-darkness-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 06:17:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by R. Scott Bakker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240957-the-thoughts-of-all-men-arise-from-the-darkness-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The thoughts of all men arise from the darkness. If you are the movement of your soul, and the cause of that movement precedes you, then how could you ever call your thoughts your own? How could you be anything other than a slave to the darkness that comes before?" -- R. Scott Bakker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/376257-gods-are-but-greater-demons-the-cishaurim-said-hungers-across</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 05:47:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by R. Scott Bakker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/376257-gods-are-but-greater-demons-the-cishaurim-said-hungers-across]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Gods are but greater demons,&quot; the Cishaurim said, &quot;hungers across the surface of eternity, wanting only to taste the clarity of our souls. Can you not see this?" -- R. Scott Bakker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112183-there-is-for-a-man-two-things-in-life-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 05:06:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112183-there-is-for-a-man-two-things-in-life-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is for a man two things in life that are very important, head and shoulders above everything else. Find work you like, and find someone to live with you like. Very few people get both." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1954-we-believe-that-we-invent-symbols-the-truth-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 05:48:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Gene Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1954-we-believe-that-we-invent-symbols-the-truth-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We believe that we invent symbols. The truth is that they invent us; we are their creatures, shaped by their hard, defining edges. When soldiers take their oath they are given a coin, an asimi stamped with the profile of the Autarch. Their acceptance of that coin is their acceptance of the special duties and burdens of military life&amp;mdash;they are soldiers from that moment, though they may know nothing of the management of arms. I did not know that then, but it is a profound mistake to believe that we must know of such things to be influenced by them, and in fact to believe so is to believe in the most debased and superstitious kind of magic. The would-be sorcerer alone has faith in the efficacy of pure knowledge; rational people know that things act of themselves or not at all." -- Gene Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
