<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/415449-jenny]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/415449-jenny" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 16:16:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8160-the-essential-matrimonial-facts-that-to-be-happy-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 16:16:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8160-the-essential-matrimonial-facts-that-to-be-happy-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The essential matrimonial facts: that to be happy you have to find variety in repetition; that to go forward you have to come back to where you begin." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43665-love-is-like-the-sea-it-s-a-moving-thing-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2010 14:45:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43665-love-is-like-the-sea-it-s-a-moving-thing-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is like the sea. It's a moving thing, but still and all, it takes its shape from the shore it meets, and it's different with every shore." -- Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173532-she-had-an-inside-and-an-outside-now-and-suddenly</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2010 14:45:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173532-she-had-an-inside-and-an-outside-now-and-suddenly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had an inside and an outside now and suddenly she knew how not to mix them." -- Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250213-the-spirit-of-the-marriage-left-the-bedroom-and-took</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2010 14:47:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250213-the-spirit-of-the-marriage-left-the-bedroom-and-took]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The spirit of the marriage left the bedroom and took to living in the parlor." -- Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258046-she-often-spoke-to-falling-seeds-and-said-ah-hope</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2010 14:48:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258046-she-often-spoke-to-falling-seeds-and-said-ah-hope]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She often spoke to falling seeds and said, &quot;Ah hope you fall on soft ground,&quot; because she had heard seeds saying that to each other as they passed. The familiar people and things had failed her so she hung over the gate and looked up the road towards way off. She knew now that marriage did not make love. Janie's first dream was dead, so she became a woman." -- Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422-there-are-years-that-ask-questions-and-years-that-answer</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2010 14:48:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422-there-are-years-that-ask-questions-and-years-that-answer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are years that ask questions and years that answer." -- Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/987-there-are-only-two-ways-to-live-your-life-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2010 14:51:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/987-there-are-only-two-ways-to-live-your-life-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are only two ways to live your life. One is as though nothing is a miracle. The other is as though everything is a miracle." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8206-do-i-contradict-myself-very-well-then-i-contradict-myself</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 13:11:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8206-do-i-contradict-myself-very-well-then-i-contradict-myself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do I contradict myself? Very well, then, I contradict myself; I am large -- I contain multitudes." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10775-and-your-very-flesh-shall-be-a-great-poem</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 13:11:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10775-and-your-very-flesh-shall-be-a-great-poem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And your very flesh shall be a great poem." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7511-i-saw-my-life-branching-out-before-me-like-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 13:14:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7511-i-saw-my-life-branching-out-before-me-like-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I saw my life branching out before me like the green fig tree in the story. From the tip of every branch, like a fat purple fig, a wonderful future beckoned and winked. One fig was a husband and a happy home and children, and another fig was a famous poet and another fig was a brilliant professor, and another fig was Ee Gee, the amazing editor, and another fig was Europe and Africa and South America, and another fig was Constantin and Socrates and Attila and a pack of other lovers with queer names and offbeat professions, and another fig was an Olympic lady crew champion, and beyond and above these figs were many more figs I couldn't quite make out. I saw myself sitting in the crotch of this fig tree, starving to death, just because I couldn't make up my mind which of the figs I would choose. I wanted each and every one of them, but choosing one meant losing all the rest, and, as I sat there, unable to decide, the figs began to wrinkle and go black, and, one by one, they plopped to the ground at my feet." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44671-there-is-nothing-like-puking-with-somebody-to-make-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 13:13:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44671-there-is-nothing-like-puking-with-somebody-to-make-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing like puking with somebody to make you into old friends." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23327-that-s-one-of-the-reasons-i-never-wanted-to-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 13:13:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23327-that-s-one-of-the-reasons-i-never-wanted-to-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That’s one of the reasons I never wanted to get married. The last thing I wanted was infinite security and to be the place an arrow shoots off from. I wanted change and excitement and to shoot off in all directions myself, like the colored arrows from a Fourth of July rocket." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17521-it-s-so-hard-to-forget-pain-but-it-s-even-harder</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 13:16:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17521-it-s-so-hard-to-forget-pain-but-it-s-even-harder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's so hard to forget pain, but it's even harder to remember sweetness.  We have no scar to show for happiness. We learn so little from peace." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137748-the-best-love-is-the-kind-that-awakens-the-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 13:14:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137748-the-best-love-is-the-kind-that-awakens-the-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best love is the kind that awakens the soul and makes us reach for more, that plants a fire in our hearts and brings peace to our minds. And that's what you've given me. That's what I'd hoped to give you forever" -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34503-don-t-gain-the-world-lose-your-soul-wisdom-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 13:15:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34503-don-t-gain-the-world-lose-your-soul-wisdom-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't Gain The World &amp; Lose Your Soul, Wisdom Is Better Than Silver Or Gold." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3583-passion-makes-a-person-stop-eating-sleeping-working-feeling-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 13:18:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3583-passion-makes-a-person-stop-eating-sleeping-working-feeling-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Passion makes a person stop eating, sleeping, working, feeling at peace. A lot of people are frightened because, when it appears, it demolishes all the old things it finds in its path. 

No one wants their life thrown into chaos. That is why a lot of people keep that threat under control, and are somehow capable of sustaining a house or a structure that is already rotten. They are the engineers of the superseded. 

Other people think exactly the opposite: they surrender themselves without a second thought, hoping to find in passion the solutions to all their problems. They make the other person responsible for their happiness and blame them for their possible unhappiness. They are either euphoric because something marvelous has happened or depressed because something unexpected has just ruined everything. 

Keeping passion at bay or surrendering blindly to it - which of these two attitudes is the least destructive? 

I don't know." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15849-make-a-radical-change-in-your-lifestyle-and-begin-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 13:20:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15849-make-a-radical-change-in-your-lifestyle-and-begin-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["make a radical change in your lifestyle and begin to boldly do things which you may previously never have thought of doing, or been too hesitant to attempt. So many people live within unhappy circumstances and yet will not take the initiative to change their situation because they are conditioned to a life of security, conformity, and conservation, all of which may appear to give one peace of mind, but in reality nothing is more damaging to the adventurous spirit within a man than a secure future. The very basic core of a man's living spirit is his passion for adventure. The joy of life comes from our encounters with new experiences, and hence there is no greater joy than to have an endlessly changing horizon, for each day to have a new and different sun. If you want to get more out of life, you must lose your inclination for monotonous security and adopt a helter-skelter style of life that will at first appear to you to be crazy. But once you become accustomed to such a life you will see its full meaning and its incredible beauty." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30038-go-placidly-amid-the-noise-and-the-haste-and-remember</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 13:22:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Max Ehrmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30038-go-placidly-amid-the-noise-and-the-haste-and-remember]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Go placidly amid the noise and the haste, and remember what peace there may be in silence. As far as possible without surrender, be on good terms with all persons. Speak your truth quietly and clearly, and listen to others, even the dull and ignorant; they too have their story. Be yourself. Especially do not feign affection. Neither be cynical about love – for in the face of all aridity and disenchantment is it perennial as the grass. Take kindly the counsel of the years, gracefully surrendering the things of youth. Nurture strength of spirit to shield you from misfortune. But do not distress yourself with imaginings. Many fears are born of fatigue and loneliness. Beyond a wholesome discipline, be gentle with yourself. You are a child of the universe no less than the trees and the stars; you have a right to be here. And whether or not it is clear to you, no doubt the universe is unfolding as it should. Therefore be at peace with God, whatever you conceive Him to be, and whatever your labours and aspirations, in the noisy confusion of life keep peace with your soul. With all its sham, drudgery and broken dreams, it is still a beautiful world." -- Max Ehrmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13235-rose-of-all-roses-rose-of-all-the-world-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 14:03:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by William Butler Yeats]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13235-rose-of-all-roses-rose-of-all-the-world-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["ROSE of all Roses, Rose of all the World!	
The tall thought-woven sails, that flap unfurled	
Above the tide of hours, trouble the air,	
And God’s bell buoyed to be the water’s care;	
While hushed from fear, or loud with hope, a band	        
With blown, spray-dabbled hair gather at hand.	
Turn if you may from battles never done,	
I call, as they go by me one by one,	
Danger no refuge holds, and war no peace,	
For him who hears love sing and never cease,	       
Beside her clean-swept hearth, her quiet shade:	
But gather all for whom no love hath made	
A woven silence, or but came to cast	
A song into the air, and singing past	
To smile on the pale dawn; and gather you	       
Who have sought more than is in rain or dew	
Or in the sun and moon, or on the earth,	
Or sighs amid the wandering starry mirth,	
Or comes in laughter from the sea’s sad lips;	
And wage God’s battles in the long grey ships.	       
The sad, the lonely, the insatiable,	
To these Old Night shall all her mystery tell;	
God’s bell has claimed them by the little cry	
Of their sad hearts, that may not live nor die.	
 
Rose of all Roses, Rose of all the World!	     
You, too, have come where the dim tides are hurled	
Upon the wharves of sorrow, and heard ring	
The bell that calls us on; the sweet far thing.	
Beauty grown sad with its eternity	
Made you of us, and of the dim grey sea.	
Our long ships loose thought-woven sails and wait,	
For God has bid them share an equal fate;	
And when at last defeated in His wars,	
They have gone down under the same white stars,	
We shall no longer hear the little cry	       
Of our sad hearts, that may not live nor die.

The Sweet Far Thing" -- William Butler Yeats]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172527-for-things-to-reveal-themselves-to-us-we-need-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 14:20:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172527-for-things-to-reveal-themselves-to-us-we-need-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For things to reveal themselves to us, we need to be ready to abandon our views about them." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/443825-your-breathing-should-flow-gracefully-like-a-river-like-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 14:24:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/443825-your-breathing-should-flow-gracefully-like-a-river-like-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your breathing should flow gracefully,
like a river, like a watersnake crossing
the water, and not like a chain of rugged mountains or the gallop of a horse. To master our breath is to be in control of our bodies and minds. Each time we find ourselves dispersed and find it difficult to gain control of ourselves by different means, the method of watching the breath should always be used." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/466355-you-must-love-in-such-a-way-that-the-person</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 14:26:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/466355-you-must-love-in-such-a-way-that-the-person]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must love in such a way that the person you love feels free." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11602-the-privilege-of-a-lifetime-is-being-who-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 14:37:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11602-the-privilege-of-a-lifetime-is-being-who-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The privilege of a lifetime is being who you are." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10442-people-say-that-what-we-re-all-seeking-is-a-meaning</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 14:41:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10442-people-say-that-what-we-re-all-seeking-is-a-meaning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People say that what we’re all seeking is a meaning for life. I don’t think that’s what we’re really seeking. I think that what we’re seeking is an experience of being alive, so that our life experiences on the purely physical plane will have resonances with our own innermost being and reality, so that we actually feel the rapture of being alive." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41441-half-the-people-in-the-world-think-that-the-metaphors</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 14:40:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41441-half-the-people-in-the-world-think-that-the-metaphors]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Half the people in the world think that the metaphors of their religious traditions, for example, are facts. And the other half contends that they are not facts at all. As a result we have people who consider themselves believers because they accept metaphors as facts, and we have others who classify themselves as atheists because they think religious metaphors are lies." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37475-furthermore-we-have-not-even-to-risk-the-adventure-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 14:42:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37475-furthermore-we-have-not-even-to-risk-the-adventure-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Furthermore, we have not even to risk the adventure alone; for the heroes of all time have gone before us, the labyrinth is fully known; we have only to follow the thread of the hero-path.  And where we had thought to find an abomination, we shall find a god; where we had thought to slay another, we shall slay ourselves; where we had thought to travel outward, we shall come to the center of our own existence; where we had thought to be alone, we shall be with all the world." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175745-the-big-question-is-whether-you-are-going-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 14:44:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175745-the-big-question-is-whether-you-are-going-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The big question is whether you are going to be able to say a hearty yes to your adventure " -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22965-for-we-have-not-even-to-risk-the-adventure-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 14:45:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22965-for-we-have-not-even-to-risk-the-adventure-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For we have not even to risk the adventure alone, for the heros of all time have gone before us..." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4864-to-the-well-organized-mind-death-is-but-the-next-great</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2012 16:53:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4864-to-the-well-organized-mind-death-is-but-the-next-great]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To the well-organized mind, death is but the next great adventure." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5785-the-fear-of-death-follows-from-the-fear-of-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2012 16:53:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenny add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5785-the-fear-of-death-follows-from-the-fear-of-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fear of death follows from the fear of life. A man who lives fully is prepared to die at any time." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
