<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/415415-cheryl-lee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/415415-cheryl-lee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 22:23:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16593-responsibility-to-yourself-means-refusing-to-let-others-do-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 22:23:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cheryl Lee add a quote by Adrienne Rich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16593-responsibility-to-yourself-means-refusing-to-let-others-do-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Responsibility to yourself means refusing to let others do your thinking, talking, and naming for you...it means that you do not treat your body as a commodity with which to purchase superficial intimacy or economic security; for our bodies to be treated as objects, our minds are in mortal danger. It means insisting that those to whom you give your friendship and love are able to respect your mind. It means being able to say, with Charlotte Bronte's Jane Eyre: &quot;I have an inward treasure born with me, which can keep me alive if all the extraneous delights should be withheld or offered only at a price I cannot afford to give.

Responsibility to yourself means that you don't fall for shallow and easy solutions--predigested books and ideas...marrying early as an escape from real decisions, getting pregnant as an evasion of already existing problems. It means that you refuse to sell your talents and aspirations short...and this, in turn, means resisting the forces in society which say that women should be nice, play safe, have low professional expectations, drown in love and forget about work, live through others, and stay in the places assigned to us. It means that we insist on a life of meaningful work, insist that work be as meaningful as love and friendship in our lives. It means, therefore, the courage to be &quot;different&quot;...The difference between a life lived actively, and a life of passive drifting and dispersal of energies, is an immense difference. Once we begin to feel committed to our lives, responsible to ourselves, we can never again be satisfied with the old, passive way." -- Adrienne Rich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44367-that-s-why-i-want-to-speak-to-you-now-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 22:24:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cheryl Lee add a quote by Adrienne Rich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44367-that-s-why-i-want-to-speak-to-you-now-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's why I want to speak to you now.

To say: no person, trying to take responsibility for her or his identity, should have to be so alone. There must be those among whom we can sit down and weep, and still be counted as warriors. (I make up this strange, angry packet for you, threaded with love.)

I think you thought there was no such place for you, and perhaps there was none then, and perhaps there is none now; but we will have to make it, we who want an end to suffering, who want to change the laws of history, if we are not to give ourselves away." -- Adrienne Rich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214603-unless-it-comes-out-of-your-soul-like-a-rocket</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 01:25:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cheryl Lee add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214603-unless-it-comes-out-of-your-soul-like-a-rocket]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["unless it comes out of
your soul like a rocket,
unless being still would
drive you to madness or
suicide or murder,
don't do it.
unless the sun inside you is
burning your gut,
don't do it.

when it is truly time,
and if you have been chosen,
it will do it by
itself and it will keep on doing it
until you die or it dies in you.

there is no other way.

and there never was." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82437-you-ll-get-over-it-it-s-the-clich-s-that-cause-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2012 16:55:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cheryl Lee add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82437-you-ll-get-over-it-it-s-the-clich-s-that-cause-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You’ll get over it…” It’s the clichés that cause the trouble. To lose someone you love is to alter your life for ever. You don’t get over it because ‘it” is the person you loved. The pain stops, there are new people, but the gap never closes. How could it? The particularness of someone who mattered enough to grieve over is not made anodyne by death. This hole in my heart is in the shape of you and no-one else can fit it. Why would I want them to?" -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
