<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/4155-connor]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/4155-connor" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 14:38:06 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8526-memories-warm-you-up-from-the-inside-but-they-also</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 14:38:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[connor add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8526-memories-warm-you-up-from-the-inside-but-they-also]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Memories warm you up from the inside. But they also tear you apart." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42499-light-thinks-it-travels-faster-than-anything-but-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 10:03:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[connor add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42499-light-thinks-it-travels-faster-than-anything-but-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Light thinks it travels faster than anything but it is wrong. No matter how fast light travels, it finds the darkness has always got there first, and is waiting for it." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1820-the-gross-and-net-result-of-it-is-that-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 14:16:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[connor add a quote by Flann O'Brien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1820-the-gross-and-net-result-of-it-is-that-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The gross and net result of it is that people who spent most of their natural lives riding iron bicycles over the rocky roadsteads of this parish get their personalities mixed up with the personalities of their bicycle as a result of the interchanging of the atoms of each of them and you would be surprised at the number of people in these parts who are nearly half people and half bicycles...when a man lets things go so far that he is more than half a bicycle, you will not see him so much because he spends a lot of his time leaning with one elbow on walls or standing propped by one foot at kerbstones." -- Flann O'Brien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/347496-i-would-not-hurt-you-little-man-he-said-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 14:19:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[connor add a quote by Flann O'Brien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/347496-i-would-not-hurt-you-little-man-he-said-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would not hurt you, little man,' he said.

'I think that I got the disorder in Mullingar,' I explained. I knew that I had gained his confidence and that the danger of violence was now passed. He then did something which took me by surprise. He pulled up his own ragged trouser and showed me his own left leg. It was smooth, shapely and fairly fat but it was made of wood also.

'That is a funny coincidence,' I said. I now perceived the reason for his sudden change of attitude.

'You are a sweet man,' he responded, 'and I would not lay a finger on your personality. I am the captain of all the one-legged men in the country. I knew them all up to now except one—your own self—and that one is now also my friend into the same bargain. If any man looks at you sideways, I will rip his belly.'

'That is very friendly talk,' I said.

'Wide open,' he said, making a wide movement with his hands. 'If you are ever troubled, send for me and I will save you from the woman.'

'Women I have no interest in at all,' I said smiling. 'A fiddle is a better thing for diversion.'

'It does not matter. If your perplexity is an army or a dog, I will come with all the one-leggèd men and rip the bellies. My real name is Martin Finnucane.'

'It is a reasonable name,' I assented.

'Martin Finnucane,' he repeated, listening to his own voice as if he were listening to the sweetest music in the world." -- Flann O'Brien]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
