<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/417418-wendi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/417418-wendi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 08:26:05 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 08:26:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendi add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the world were merely seductive, that would be easy. If it were merely challenging, that would be no problem. But I arise in the morning torn between a desire to improve the world and a desire to enjoy the world. This makes it hard to plan the day." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 08:27:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendi add a quote by Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not the critic who counts; not the man who points out how the strong man stumbles, or where the doer of deeds could have done them better. The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the arena, whose face is marred by dust and sweat and blood; who strives valiantly; who errs, who comes short again and again, because there is no effort without error and shortcoming; but who does actually strive to do the deeds; who knows great enthusiasms, the great devotions; who spends himself in a worthy cause; who at the best knows in the end the triumph of high achievement, and who at the worst, if he fails, at least fails while daring greatly, so that his place shall never be with those cold and timid souls who neither know victory nor defeat." -- Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 08:31:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendi add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3823-you-gain-strength-courage-and-confidence-by-every-experience-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 08:31:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendi add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3823-you-gain-strength-courage-and-confidence-by-every-experience-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You gain strength, courage and confidence by every experience in which you really stop to look fear in the face. You are able to say to yourself, 'I have lived through this horror. I can take the next thing that comes along.' You must do the thing you think you cannot do." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54-don-t-walk-behind-me-i-may-not-lead-don-t-walk</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 08:39:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendi add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54-don-t-walk-behind-me-i-may-not-lead-don-t-walk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't walk behind me; I may not lead. Don't walk in front of me; I may not follow. Just walk beside me and be my friend." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6130-a-woman-should-have-enough-money-within-her-control</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 09:07:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendi add a quote by Pamela Redmond Satran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6130-a-woman-should-have-enough-money-within-her-control]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  enough money within her control to move out
  and rent a place of her own even if she never wants
  to or needs to...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  something perfect to wear if the employer or date of her
  dreams wants to see her in an hour...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ...
  a youth she's content to leave behind....
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a past juicy enough that she's looking forward to
  retelling it in her old age....
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE .....
  a set of screwdrivers, a cordless drill, and a black
  lace bra...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  one friend who always makes her laugh... and one who
  lets her cry...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a good piece of furniture not previously owned by anyone
  else in her family...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  eight matching plates, wine glasses with stems, and a
  recipe for a meal that will make her guests feel honored...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a feeling of control over her destiny...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  how to fall in love without losing herself..
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  HOW TO QUIT A JOB,
  BREAK UP WITH A LOVER,
  AND CONFRONT A FRIEND WITHOUT RUINING THE FRIENDSHIP...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  when to try harder... and WHEN TO WALK AWAY...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  that she can't change the length of her calves,
  the width of her hips, or the nature of her parents..
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  that her childhood may not have been perfect...but it's over...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  what she would and wouldn't do for love or more...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  how to live alone... even if she doesn't like it...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  whom she can trust,
  whom she can't,
  and why she shouldn't
  take it personally...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  where to go...
  be it to her best friend's kitchen table...
  or a charming inn in the woods...
  when her soul needs soothing...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  what she can and can't accomplish in a day...
  a month...and a year..." -- Pamela Redmond Satran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1280-you-can-go-through-life-and-make-new-friends-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 09:09:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendi add a quote by Alexander McCall Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1280-you-can-go-through-life-and-make-new-friends-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can go through life and make new friends every year - every month practically - but there was never any substitute for those friendships of childhood that survive into adult years. Those are the ones in which we are bound to one another with hoops of steel." -- Alexander McCall Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1930-think-of-all-the-beauty-still-left-around-you-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 09:09:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendi add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1930-think-of-all-the-beauty-still-left-around-you-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Think of all the beauty still left around you and be happy." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17411-think-left-and-think-right-and-think-low-and-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2008 22:48:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendi add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17411-think-left-and-think-right-and-think-low-and-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Think left and think right and think low and think high. Oh, the thinks you can think up if only you try!" -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2008 16:33:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendi add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 09:17:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendi add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18502-every-closed-eye-is-not-sleeping-and-every-open-eye</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 09:30:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wendi add a quote by Bill Cosby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18502-every-closed-eye-is-not-sleeping-and-every-open-eye]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every closed eye is not sleeping, and every open eye is not seeing." -- Bill Cosby]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
