<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/417703-jena-garcia]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/417703-jena-garcia" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 12:18:23 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108208-i-hope-you-have-not-been-leading-a-double-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 12:18:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108208-i-hope-you-have-not-been-leading-a-double-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hope you have not been leading a double life, pretending to be wicked and being good all the time. That would be hypocrisy." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178186-it-s-discouraging-to-think-how-many-people-are-shocked-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 12:20:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Noël Coward]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178186-it-s-discouraging-to-think-how-many-people-are-shocked-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's discouraging to think how many people are shocked by honesty and how few by deceit." -- Noël Coward]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231424-scriptures-n-the-sacred-books-of-our-holy-religion-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 12:21:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231424-scriptures-n-the-sacred-books-of-our-holy-religion-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;b&gt;Scriptures, n.&lt;/b&gt; The sacred books of our holy religion, as distinguished from the false and profane writings on which all other faiths are based." -- Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230617-and-nothing-inspires-as-much-shame-as-being-a-parent</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 12:23:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230617-and-nothing-inspires-as-much-shame-as-being-a-parent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And nothing inspires as much shame as being a parent. Children confront us with our paradoxes and hypocrisies, and we are exposed. You need to find an answer for every why — Why do we do this? Why don’t we do that? — and often there isn’t a good one. So you say, simply, because. Or you tell a story that you know isn’t true. And whether or not your face reddens, you blush. The shame of parenthood — which is a good shame — is that we want our children to be more whole than we are, to have satisfactory answers." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/435078-i-am-tired-of-hiding-tired-of-misspent-and-knotted</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 12:31:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Kay Redfield Jamison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/435078-i-am-tired-of-hiding-tired-of-misspent-and-knotted]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am tired of hiding, tired of misspent and knotted energies, tired of the hypocrisy, and tired of acting as though I have something to hide." -- Kay Redfield Jamison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44274-people-speak-sometimes-about-the-bestial-cruelty-of-man-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 12:35:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky  ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44274-people-speak-sometimes-about-the-bestial-cruelty-of-man-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People speak sometimes about the &quot;bestial&quot; cruelty of man, but that is terribly unjust and offensive to beasts, no animal could ever be so cruel as a man, so artfully, so artistically cruel." -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky  ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 12:36:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Kent M. Keith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Paradoxical Commandments

People are illogical, unreasonable, and self-centered.
Love them anyway.

If you do good, people will accuse you of selfish ulterior motives.
Do good anyway.

If you are successful, you will win false friends and true enemies.
Succeed anyway.

The good you do today will be forgotten tomorrow.
Do good anyway.

Honesty and frankness make you vulnerable.
Be honest and frank anyway.

The biggest men and women with the biggest ideas can be shot down by the smallest men and women with the smallest minds.
Think big anyway.

People favor underdogs but follow only top dogs.
Fight for a few underdogs anyway.

What you spend years building may be destroyed overnight.
Build anyway.

People really need help but may attack you if you do help them.
Help people anyway.

Give the world the best you have and you'll get kicked in the teeth.
Give the world the best you have anyway." -- Kent M. Keith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11741-the-weak-can-never-forgive-forgiveness-is-the-attribute-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 12:36:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11741-the-weak-can-never-forgive-forgiveness-is-the-attribute-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The weak can never forgive. Forgiveness is the attribute of the strong." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13146-never-trust-anyone-who-has-not-brought-a-book-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 12:43:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13146-never-trust-anyone-who-has-not-brought-a-book-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never trust anyone who has not brought a book with them." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184013-i-don-t-trust-people-who-don-t-love-themselves-and-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 12:44:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184013-i-don-t-trust-people-who-don-t-love-themselves-and-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't trust people who don't love themselves and tell me, 'I love you.' ... There is an African saying which is: Be careful when a naked person offers you a shirt." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27688-for-me-trees-have-always-been-the-most-penetrating-preachers</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 12:46:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Herman Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27688-for-me-trees-have-always-been-the-most-penetrating-preachers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For me, trees have always been the most penetrating preachers. I revere them when they live in tribes and families, in forests and groves. And even more I revere them when they stand alone. They are like lonely persons. Not like hermits who have stolen away out of some weakness, but like great, solitary men, like Beethoven and Nietzsche. In their highest boughs the world rustles, their roots rest in infinity; but they do not lose themselves there, they struggle with all the force of their lives for one thing only: to fulfil themselves according to their own laws, to build up their own form, to represent themselves. Nothing is holier, nothing is more exemplary than a beautiful, strong tree. When a tree is cut down and reveals its naked death-wound to the sun, one can read its whole history in the luminous, inscribed disk of its trunk: in the rings of its years, its scars, all the struggle, all the suffering, all the sickness, all the happiness and prosperity stand truly written, the narrow years and the luxurious years, the attacks withstood, the storms endured. And every young farmboy knows that the hardest and noblest wood has the narrowest rings, that high on the mountains and in continuing danger the most indestructible, the strongest, the ideal trees grow.

     Trees are sanctuaries. Whoever knows how to speak to them, whoever knows how to listen to them, can learn the truth. They do not preach learning and precepts, they preach, undeterred by particulars, the ancient law of life.

     A tree says: A kernel is hidden in me, a spark, a thought, I am life from eternal life. The attempt and the risk that the eternal mother took with me is unique, unique the form and veins of my skin, unique the smallest play of leaves in my branches and the smallest scar on my bark. I was made to form and reveal the eternal in my smallest special detail.

     A tree says: My strength is trust. I know nothing about my fathers, I know nothing about the thousand children that every year spring out of me. I live out the secret of my seed to the very end, and I care for nothing else. I trust that God is in me. I trust that my labor is holy. Out of this trust I live.

     When we are stricken and cannot bear our lives any longer, then a tree has something to say to us: Be still! Be still! Look at me! Life is not easy, life is not difficult. Those are childish thoughts. Let God speak within you, and your thoughts will grow silent. You are anxious because your path leads away from mother and home. But every step and every day lead you back again to the mother. Home is neither here nor there. Home is within you, or home is nowhere at all.

     A longing to wander tears my heart when I hear trees rustling in the wind at evening. If one listens to them silently for a long time, this longing reveals its kernel, its meaning. It is not so much a matter of escaping from one's suffering, though it may seem to be so. It is a longing for home, for a memory of the mother, for new metaphors for life. It leads home. Every path leads homeward, every step is birth, every step is death, every grave is mother.

     So the tree rustles in the evening, when we stand uneasy before our own childish thoughts: Trees have long thoughts, long-breathing and restful, just as they have longer lives than ours. They are wiser than we are, as long as we do not listen to them. But when we have learned how to listen to trees, then the brevity and the quickness and the childlike hastiness of our thoughts achieve an incomparable joy. Whoever has learned how to listen to trees no longer wants to be a tree. He wants to be nothing except what he is. That is home. That is happiness." -- Herman Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2876-self-pity-becomes-your-oxygen-but-you-learned-to-breathe</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 10:16:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Paul Monette]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2876-self-pity-becomes-your-oxygen-but-you-learned-to-breathe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Self pity becomes your oxygen. But you learned to breathe it without a gasp. So, nobody even notices you're hurting." -- Paul Monette]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174561-grief-and-disappointment-are-like-hate-they-make-men-ugly</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 10:18:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174561-grief-and-disappointment-are-like-hate-they-make-men-ugly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Grief and disappointment are like hate: they make men ugly with self-pity and bitterness. And how selfish they make us too." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51043-what-we-do-see-depends-mainly-on-what-we-look</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 10:28:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by John Lubbock]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51043-what-we-do-see-depends-mainly-on-what-we-look]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What we do see depends mainly on what we look for. ... In the same field the farmer will notice the crop, the geologists the fossils, botanists the flowers, artists the colouring, sportmen the cover for the game. Though we may all look at the same things, it does not all follow that we should see them." -- John Lubbock]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41988-some-changes-look-negative-on-the-surface-but-you-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 22:28:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41988-some-changes-look-negative-on-the-surface-but-you-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some changes look negative on the surface but you will soon realize that space is being created in your life for something new to emerge." -- Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19563-from-the-backstabbing-co-worker-to-the-meddling-sister-in-law-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 22:28:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19563-from-the-backstabbing-co-worker-to-the-meddling-sister-in-law-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From the backstabbing co-worker to the meddling sister-in-law, you are in charge of how you react to the people and events in your life. You can either give negativity power over your life or you can choose happiness instead. Take control and choose to focus on what is important in your life. Those who cannot live fully often become destroyers of life." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6621-i-love-science-and-it-pains-me-to-think-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 12:22:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Robert Sapolsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6621-i-love-science-and-it-pains-me-to-think-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love science, and it pains me to think that so many are terrified of the subject or feel that choosing science means you cannot also choose compassion, or the arts, or be awed by nature.  Science is not meant to cure us of mystery, but to reinvent and reinvigorate it." -- Robert Sapolsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41698-be-compassionate-morrie-whispered-and-take-responsibility-for-each-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 19:31:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41698-be-compassionate-morrie-whispered-and-take-responsibility-for-each-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be compassionate,&quot; Morrie whispered. And take responsibility for each other. If we only learned those lessons, this world would be so much better a place.&quot;

He took a breath, then added his mantra: &quot;Love each other or die." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158840-optimism-is-a-strategy-for-making-a-better-future-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 19:31:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Noam Chomsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158840-optimism-is-a-strategy-for-making-a-better-future-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Optimism is a strategy for making a better future. Because unless you believe that the future can be better, you are unlikely to step up and take responsibility for making it so." -- Noam Chomsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114802-i-don-t-like-ass-kissers-flag-wavers-or-team-players</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 19:34:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114802-i-don-t-like-ass-kissers-flag-wavers-or-team-players]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't like ass kissers, flag wavers or team players. I like people who buck the system. Individualists. I often warn people: &quot;Somewhere along the way, someone is going to tell you, 'There is no &quot;I&quot; in team.' What you should tell them is, 'Maybe not. But there is an &quot;I&quot; in independence, individuality and integrity.'&quot; Avoid teams at all cost. Keep your circle small. Never join a group that has a name. If they say, &quot;We're the So-and-Sos,&quot; take a walk. And if, somehow, you must join, if it's unavoidable, such as a union or a trade association, go ahead and join. But don't participate; it will be your death. And if they tell you you're not a team player, congratulate them on being observant." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32526-whoever-is-careless-with-the-truth-in-small-matters-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 19:34:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32526-whoever-is-careless-with-the-truth-in-small-matters-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whoever is careless with the truth in small matters cannot be trusted with important matters" -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78272-imagine-life-is-a-game-in-which-you-are-juggling</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 19:35:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by James Patterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78272-imagine-life-is-a-game-in-which-you-are-juggling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine life is a game in which you are juggling five balls. The balls are called work, family, health, friends, and integrity. And you're keeping all of them in the air. But one day you finally come to understand that work is a rubber ball. If you drop it, it will bounce back. The other four balls...are made of glass. If you drop one of these, it will be irrevocably scuffed, nicked, perhaps even shattered." -- James Patterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6946-not-all-of-us-can-do-great-things-but-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 13:45:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6946-not-all-of-us-can-do-great-things-but-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not all of us can do great things. But we can do small things with great love." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49502-i-alone-cannot-change-the-world-but-i-can-cast</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 13:46:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49502-i-alone-cannot-change-the-world-but-i-can-cast]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I alone cannot change the world, but I can cast a stone across the waters to create many ripples." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/472915-i-am-convinced-that-human-life-is-filled-with-many</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 14:40:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jena add a quote by Osamu Dazai]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/472915-i-am-convinced-that-human-life-is-filled-with-many]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am convinced that human life is filled with many pure, happy, serene examples of insincerity, truly splendid of their kind-of people deceiving one another without (strangely enough) any wounds being inflicted, of people who seem unaware even that they are deceiving one another." -- Osamu Dazai]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
