<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/419239-ayrdaomei]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/419239-ayrdaomei" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2007 17:58:47 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8775-let-me-just-say-that-i-am-not-often-lonely</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2007 17:58:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Nuala O'Faolain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8775-let-me-just-say-that-i-am-not-often-lonely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me just say that I am not often lonely in country places.  In cities I am, like the writers of the letters.  Nature doesn't break your heart: other people do.  Yet, we cannot live apart from each other in bowers feeding on nectar.  We're in this together, this getting through our lives, as the fact that we are word-users shows." -- Nuala O'Faolain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8777-i-think-men-get-nervous-when-women-start-counting-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2007 18:00:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Dahlia Lithwick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8777-i-think-men-get-nervous-when-women-start-counting-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think men get nervous when women start counting the number of female senators, and whites become edgy when they hear the next Supreme Court seat will probably go to a Latino. This isn't always because they object to sharing the spoils, by the way; it just reminds us that the melting pot may not be working, and we haven't yet achieved the ambiguous national dream of becoming a nation of indistinguishable beige atheists." -- Dahlia Lithwick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8778-it-is-rare-indeed-that-people-give-most-people-guard</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2007 18:00:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8778-it-is-rare-indeed-that-people-give-most-people-guard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is rare indeed that people give. Most people guard and keep; they suppose that it is they themselves and what they identify with themselves that they are guarding and keeping, whereas what they are actually guarding and keeping is their system of reality and what they assume themselves to be." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8780-it-was-books-that-taught-me-that-the-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2007 18:01:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8780-it-was-books-that-taught-me-that-the-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was books that taught me that the things that tormented me most were the very things that connected me with all the people who were alive, or who had ever been alive." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9406-chronic-remorse-as-all-the-moralists-are-agreed-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2007 18:02:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9406-chronic-remorse-as-all-the-moralists-are-agreed-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chronic remorse, as all the moralists are agreed, is a most undesirable sentiment. If you have behaved badly, repent, make what amends you can and address yourself to the task of behaving better next time. On no account brood over your wrongdoing. Rolling in the muck is not the best way of getting clean." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112327-states-rights-as-our-forefathers-conceived-it-was-a-protection</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 17:48:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Robert Kennedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112327-states-rights-as-our-forefathers-conceived-it-was-a-protection]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["States' rights, as our forefathers conceived it, was a protection of the right of the individual citizen.  Those who preach most frequently about states' rights today are not seeking the protection of the individual citizen, but his exploitation. . . . The time is long past - if indeed it ever existed - when we should permit the noble concept of States' rights to be betrayed and corrupted into a slogan to hide the bald denial of American rights, of civil rights, and of human rights." -- Robert Kennedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 20:10:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2011 05:57:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I can hear my bones straining under the weight of all the lives I'm not living." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2528-keep-away-from-people-who-try-to-belittle-your-ambitions</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2011 05:58:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2528-keep-away-from-people-who-try-to-belittle-your-ambitions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Keep away from people who try to belittle your ambitions. Small people always do that, but the really great make you feel that you, too, can become great." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1716-travel-is-fatal-to-prejudice-bigotry-and-narrow-mindedness-and-many</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2011 05:59:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1716-travel-is-fatal-to-prejudice-bigotry-and-narrow-mindedness-and-many]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Travel is fatal to prejudice, bigotry, and narrow-mindedness, and many of our people need it sorely on these accounts. Broad, wholesome, charitable views of men and things cannot be acquired by vegetating in one little corner of the earth all one's lifetime." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6193-the-world-is-a-book-and-those-who-do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2011 06:00:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by St. Augustine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6193-the-world-is-a-book-and-those-who-do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is a book and those who do not travel read only one page." -- St. Augustine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7096-listen-to-the-mustn-ts-child-listen-to-the-don-ts-listen</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2011 01:15:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Shel Silverstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7096-listen-to-the-mustn-ts-child-listen-to-the-don-ts-listen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen to the mustn'ts, child. Listen to the don'ts. Listen to the shouldn'ts, the impossibles, the won'ts. Listen to the never haves, then listen close to me... Anything can happen, child. Anything can be." -- Shel Silverstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57214-saying-i-notice-you-re-a-nerd-is-like-saying-hey</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 02:49:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57214-saying-i-notice-you-re-a-nerd-is-like-saying-hey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Saying 'I notice you're a nerd' is like saying, 'Hey, I notice that you'd rather be intelligent than be stupid, that you'd rather be thoughtful than be vapid, that you believe that there are things that matter more than the arrest record of Lindsay Lohan. Why is that?' In fact, it seems to me that most contemporary insults are pretty lame. Even 'lame' is kind of lame. Saying 'You're lame' is like saying 'You walk with a limp.' Yeah, whatever, so does 50 Cent, and he's done all right for himself." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185805-because-nerds-like-us-are-allowed-to-be-unironically-enthusiastic</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 02:57:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185805-because-nerds-like-us-are-allowed-to-be-unironically-enthusiastic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…because nerds like us are allowed to be unironically enthusiastic about stuff… Nerds are allowed to love stuff, like jump-up-and-down-in-the-chair-can’t-control-yourself love it. Hank, when people call people nerds, mostly what they’re saying is ‘you like stuff.’ Which is just not a good insult at all. Like, ‘you are too enthusiastic about the miracle of human consciousness’." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473959-he-waits-for-the-kid-to-decide-whether-to-pull</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 07:19:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Malcolm Gladwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473959-he-waits-for-the-kid-to-decide-whether-to-pull]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["he waits for the kid to decide whether to pull the gun up or simply to drop it - and all the while, even as he tracks the progress of the gun, he is also watching the kid's face, to see whether he is dangerous or simply frightened. is there a more beautiful example of a snap judgment? this is the gift of training and expertise - the ability to extract an enormous amount of meaningful information from the very thinnest slice of experience." -- Malcolm Gladwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70498-what-she-was-finding-also-was-how-one-book-led</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 05:50:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Alan Bennett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70498-what-she-was-finding-also-was-how-one-book-led]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What she was finding also was how one book led to another, doors kept opening wherever she turned and the days weren't long enough for the reading she wanted to do." -- Alan Bennett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/536961-the-reasonable-man-adapts-himself-to-the-world-the-unreasonable</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 06:08:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/536961-the-reasonable-man-adapts-himself-to-the-world-the-unreasonable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The reasonable man adapts himself to the world: the unreasonable one persists in trying to adapt the world to himself. Therefore all progress depends on the unreasonable man." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367428-my-life-was-my-life-i-would-have-to-stare</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 00:28:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Paula McLain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367428-my-life-was-my-life-i-would-have-to-stare]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My life was my life; I would have to stare it down, somehow, and make it work for me." -- Paula McLain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464577-to-marry-was-to-say-you-believed-in-the-future</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 00:28:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Paula McLain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464577-to-marry-was-to-say-you-believed-in-the-future]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To marry was to say you believed in the future and in the past, too-that history and tradition and hope could stay knit together to hold you up." -- Paula McLain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/486071-i-miss-good-old-fashioned-honorable-people-just-trying-to-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 00:29:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Paula McLain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/486071-i-miss-good-old-fashioned-honorable-people-just-trying-to-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I miss good old-fashioned honorable people just trying to make something of life. Simply, without hurting anyone else.  I know that makes me a sap." -- Paula McLain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422893-this-was-my-one-brush-with-love-was-it-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 00:29:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Paula McLain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422893-this-was-my-one-brush-with-love-was-it-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This was my one brush with love. Was it love? It felt awful enough. I spent another two years crawling around in the skin of it, smoking too much and growing too thin and having stray thoughts of jumping from my balcony like a tortured heroine in a Russian novel." -- Paula McLain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584320-more-and-more-i-find-myself-at-a-loss-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 00:30:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Paula McLain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584320-more-and-more-i-find-myself-at-a-loss-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["More and more I find myself at a loss for words and didn't want to hear other people talking either. Their conversations seemed false and empty. I preferred to look at the sea, which said nothing and never made you feel alone." -- Paula McLain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/534619-there-was-no-back-home-any-more-not-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 00:32:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Paula McLain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/534619-there-was-no-back-home-any-more-not-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was no back home any more, not in the essential way, and that was part of Paris too. Why we couldn't stop drinking or talking or kissing the wrong people no matter what it ruined. Some of us had looked into the faces of the dead and tried not to remember anything in particular. Ernest was one of these. He often said he'd died in the war, just for a moment; that his soul had left his body like a silk handkerchief, slipping out and levitating over his chest. It had returned without being called back, and I often wondered if writing for him was a way of knowing his soul was there after all, back in its place. Of saying to himself, if not to anyone else, that he had seen what he'd seen and felt those terrible things and lived anyway. That he had died but wasn't dead any more." -- Paula McLain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/621169-the-marriage-of-a-jewish-son-is-a-bittersweet-prospect</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2012 18:49:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Francesca Segal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/621169-the-marriage-of-a-jewish-son-is-a-bittersweet-prospect]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The marriage of a Jewish son is a bittersweet prospect. There is relief, always, that he has navigated the tantalizing and plentiful assemblies of non-Jewish women to whom the children of the Diaspora are inevitably exposed: from the moment he enters secondary school there is the constant anxiety that a blue-eyed Christina or Mary will lure him away from the tribe. Jewish men are widely known to be uxorious in all the most advantageous ways. And so each mother fears that, whether he be short and myopic, boorish or stupid or prone to discuss his lactose intolerance with strangers, whether he be blessed with a beard rising almost to meet his hairline, he is still within the danger zone. Somewhere out there is a &lt;i&gt;shiksa&lt;/i&gt; with designs on her son. Jewish men make good husbands. It is the Jewish woman's blessing as a wife, and her curse as a mother." -- Francesca Segal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41291-the-sense-of-unhappiness-is-so-much-easier-to-convey</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 16:43:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41291-the-sense-of-unhappiness-is-so-much-easier-to-convey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sense of unhappiness is so much easier to convey than that of happiness. In misery we seem aware of our own existence, even though it may be in the form of a monstrous egotism: this pain of mine is individual, this nerve that winces belongs to me and to no other. But happiness annihilates  us: we lose our identity." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114116-i-want-men-to-admire-me-but-that-s-a-trick</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 16:44:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114116-i-want-men-to-admire-me-but-that-s-a-trick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want men to admire me, but that's a trick you learn at school--a movement of the eyes, a tone of voice, a touch of the hand on the shoulder or the head. If they think you admire them, they will admire you because of your good taste, and when they admire you, you have an illusion for a moment that there's something to admire." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/580983-life-is-a-shipwreck-but-we-must-not-forget-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 06:56:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Voltaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/580983-life-is-a-shipwreck-but-we-must-not-forget-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["‎Life is a shipwreck, but we must not forget to sing in the lifeboats." -- Voltaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9292-it-isn-t-what-you-have-or-who-you-are-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 06:01:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Dale Carnegie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9292-it-isn-t-what-you-have-or-who-you-are-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It isn't what you have or who you are or where you are or what you are doing that makes you happy or unhappy. It is what you think about it." -- Dale Carnegie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10837-happiness-is-the-consequence-of-personal-effort-you-fight-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 11:03:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10837-happiness-is-the-consequence-of-personal-effort-you-fight-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is the consequence of personal effort.  You fight for it, strive for it, insist upon it, and sometimes even travel around the world looking for it.  You have to participate relentlessly in the manifestations of your own blessings.  And once you have achieved a state of happiness, you must never become lax about maintaining it.  You must make a mighty effort to keep swimming upward into that happiness forever, to stay afloat on top of it." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228577-you-need-to-learn-how-to-select-your-thoughts-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 11:03:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[ayrdaomei add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228577-you-need-to-learn-how-to-select-your-thoughts-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You need to learn how to select your thoughts just the same way you select your clothes every day.  This is a power you can cultivate.  If you want to control things in your life so bad, work on the mind.  That's the only thing you should be trying to control." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
