<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/419333-brad]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/419333-brad" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 09:10:04 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/977344-in-preindustrial-times-according-to-one-study-inequality-in-landed</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 09:10:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brad add a quote by John Alexander Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/977344-in-preindustrial-times-according-to-one-study-inequality-in-landed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In preindustrial times, according to one study, inequality in landed property was greater in the Appalachian backcountry than anywhere else in America," -- John Alexander Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980527-how-pathetic-it-is-that-such-products-now-appeal-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 22:39:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brad add a quote by Susan Jacoby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980527-how-pathetic-it-is-that-such-products-now-appeal-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How pathetic it is that such products now appeal to a huge market of people who do not understand that the way to introduce children to music is by playing good music, uninterrupted by video clowns, at home; the way to introduce poetry is by reciting or reading it at bedtime; and the way to instill an appreciation of beauty is not to bombard a toddler with screen images of Monet’s Giverny but to introduce her to the real sights and scents of a garden. It is a fine thing for tired parents to gain a quiet hour for themselves by mesmerizing small children with videos—who would be stuffy enough to suggest that the occasional hour in front of animals dancing to Tchaikovsky can do a baby any real harm?—but let us not delude ourselves that education is what is going on." -- Susan Jacoby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1025604-what-i-have-written-is-drawn-from-experience-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 15:04:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brad add a quote by Harry M. Caudill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1025604-what-i-have-written-is-drawn-from-experience-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I have written is drawn from experience — from seeing, hearing and working with mountaineers. In a land with few books and pens many tales are transmitted from father and mother to son and daughter." -- Harry M. Caudill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1025868-however-it-is-doubtless-true-that-in-a-vague-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 20:23:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brad add a quote by Harry M. Caudill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1025868-however-it-is-doubtless-true-that-in-a-vague-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["However, it is doubtless true that in a vague way some of these poorer mountaineers, fiercely independent as they were, found something abhorrent in the ownership of one person by another." -- Harry M. Caudill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1025886-here-the-mountains-were-like-the-walls-of-a-great</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 20:45:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brad add a quote by Harry M. Caudill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1025886-here-the-mountains-were-like-the-walls-of-a-great]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here the mountains were like the walls of a great jail which shut in the combatants. After Appomattox it was as though mortal enemies had been locked in the same prison without taking away the deadly weapons they knew so well how to use. Perhaps in no other region of the United States except the Southern mountains were the lives and property of a great number of pro-Union civilians lost in the war. In Pennsylvania, Kansas and a few other border areas the people were subjected to occasional Confederate forays, but those areas were comparatively rich and the losses were soon restored. But in the highlands much of the modest and slowly-built-up accumulations of three generations were destroyed, impoverishing virtually the entire population." -- Harry M. Caudill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1025893-kentucky-as-a-whole-has-lagged-behind-the-rest-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 20:52:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brad add a quote by Harry M. Caudill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1025893-kentucky-as-a-whole-has-lagged-behind-the-rest-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kentucky as a whole has lagged behind the rest of the nation in almost every field of government and public service, primarily because the fiercely independent and uncooperative mentality of the frontier hunter-farmer has remained so deeply and tenaciously embedded in the mass psyche." -- Harry M. Caudill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1033551-this-is-indeed-only-a-game-but-it-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2014 21:17:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brad add a quote by David M. Ewalt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1033551-this-is-indeed-only-a-game-but-it-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is indeed only a game, but it is a game of life and death!” the Reverend John Hollidge of Gold Hill Baptist Church in Buckinghamshire said in a letter to parents." -- David M. Ewalt]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
