<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/420656-josabeth-comandante]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/420656-josabeth-comandante" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 01:26:56 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61962-make-sure-it-is-god-s-trumpet-you-are-blowing--if</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 01:26:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by W. Ian Thomas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61962-make-sure-it-is-god-s-trumpet-you-are-blowing--if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Make sure it is God's trumpet you are blowing- 
if it is only yours it won't wake the dead, 
it will simply disturb the neighbours." -- W. Ian Thomas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121465-a-leader-should-set-an-example-of-a-big-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2008 19:14:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Pres. Ramon Magsaysay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121465-a-leader-should-set-an-example-of-a-big-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A leader should set an example of a big heart, an honest mind, sound instincts, the virtue of healthy impatience and an abiding love for the common man." -- Pres. Ramon Magsaysay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21343-i-think-people-are-very-brave-and-often-are-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 18:22:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Brenda Peterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21343-i-think-people-are-very-brave-and-often-are-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think people are very brave and often are a lot more frightened than they're allowed to admit.  Life is much harder to live for most people than we want to admit.  And so many things take a summoning up of courage.  It makes one's own life a little bit easier when you can acknowledge that.
-Ursula LeGuin, interviewed by" -- Brenda Peterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303823-odd-she-thought-how-intensely-you-knew-a-person-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 00:14:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Anita Shreve]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303823-odd-she-thought-how-intensely-you-knew-a-person-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Odd, she thought, how intensely you knew a person, or thought you did, when you were in love - soaked, drenched in love - only to discover later that perhaps you didn't know that person quite as well as you had imagined. Or weren't quite as well known as you had hoped to be. In the beginning, a lover drank in every word and gesture and then tried to hold on to that intensity for as long as possible. But inevitable, if two people were together long enough, that intensity had to wane." -- Anita Shreve]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280109-is-imagination-dependent-upon-experience-or-is-experience-influenced-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 00:19:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Anita Shreve]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280109-is-imagination-dependent-upon-experience-or-is-experience-influenced-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is imagination dependent upon experience, or is experience influenced by imagination?" -- Anita Shreve]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209682-the-greater-intellect-one-has-the-more-originality-one-finds</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 00:27:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Blaise Pascal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209682-the-greater-intellect-one-has-the-more-originality-one-finds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greater intellect one has, the more originality one finds in men. Ordinary persons find no difference between men." -- Blaise Pascal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105921-i-feel-too-much-that-s-what-s-going-on-do-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 19:33:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105921-i-feel-too-much-that-s-what-s-going-on-do-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I feel too much.  That's what's going on.'  'Do you think one can feel too much?  Or just feel in the wrong ways?'  'My insides don't match up with my outsides.'  'Do anyone's insides and outsides match up?'  'I don't know.  I'm only me.'  'Maybe that's what a person's personality is: the difference between the inside and outside.'  'But it's worse for me.'  'I wonder if everyone thinks it's worse for him.'  'Probably.  But it really is worse for me." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414001-all-i-ever-wanted-was-to-reach-out-and-touch</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 19:35:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Tahereh Mafi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414001-all-i-ever-wanted-was-to-reach-out-and-touch]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All I ever wanted was to reach out and touch another human being not just with my hands but with my heart." -- Tahereh Mafi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292212-when-someone-loves-you-the-way-they-say-your-name</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 21:01:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Jess C. Scott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292212-when-someone-loves-you-the-way-they-say-your-name]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When someone loves you, the way they say your name is different. You know that your name is safe in their mouth." -- Jess C. Scott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7915-each-friend-represents-a-world-in-us-a-world-possibly</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 21:02:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7915-each-friend-represents-a-world-in-us-a-world-possibly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each friend represents a world in us, a world possibly not born until they arrive, and it is only by this meeting that a new world is born." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526863-there-are-moments-when-i-wish-i-could-roll-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 18:06:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526863-there-are-moments-when-i-wish-i-could-roll-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are moments when I wish I could roll back the clock and take all the sadness away, but I have the feeling that if I did, the joy would be gone as well." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 18:38:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405557-for-everything-in-this-journey-of-life-we-are-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 01:04:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405557-for-everything-in-this-journey-of-life-we-are-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For everything in this journey of life we are on, there is a right wing and a left wing: for the wing of love there is anger; for the wing of destiny there is fear; for the wing of pain there is healing; for the wing of hurt there is forgiveness; for the wing of pride there is humility; for the wing of giving there is taking; for the wing of tears there is joy; for the wing of rejection there is acceptance; for the wing of judgment there is grace; for the wing of honor there is shame; for the wing of letting go there is the wing of keeping. We can only fly with two wings and two wings can only stay in the air if there is a balance. Two beautiful wings is perfection. There is a generation of people who idealize perfection as the existence of only one of these wings every time. But I see that a bird with one wing is imperfect. An angel with one wing is imperfect. A butterfly with one wing is dead. So this generation of people strive to always cut off the other wing in the hopes of embodying their ideal of perfection, and in doing so, have created a crippled race." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150233-i-told-you-you-don-t-love-someone-because-of-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 00:34:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by L.J. Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150233-i-told-you-you-don-t-love-someone-because-of-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I told you. You don't love someone because of their looks or their clothes or their car. You love them because they sing a song only your heart can understand." -- L.J. Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1958-whenever-i-feel-the-need-to-exercise-i-lie-down</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 00:38:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Paul   Terry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1958-whenever-i-feel-the-need-to-exercise-i-lie-down]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever I feel the need to exercise, I lie down until it goes away." -- Paul   Terry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder-and-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 00:38:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Miss Piggy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder-and-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beauty is in the eye of the beholder and it may be necessary from time to time to give a stupid or misinformed beholder a black eye." -- Miss Piggy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3312-women-and-cats-will-do-as-they-please-and-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 00:38:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3312-women-and-cats-will-do-as-they-please-and-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Women and cats will do as they please, and men and dogs should relax and get used to the idea." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6708-the-statistics-on-sanity-are-that-one-out-of-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 00:39:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Rita Mae Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6708-the-statistics-on-sanity-are-that-one-out-of-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The statistics on sanity are that one out of every four people is suffering from a mental illness. Look at your 3 best friends. If they're ok, then it's you." -- Rita Mae Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584819-when-i-walk-down-the-beach-and-smell-the-salt</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 01:15:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Wendy Joubert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584819-when-i-walk-down-the-beach-and-smell-the-salt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I walk down the beach and smell the salt water, hear the waves crashing against the shoreline, and feel the granular sand under my feet, I can't help but realize why I'm here on this green earth" -- Wendy Joubert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/562468-nostalgia-is-like-a-grammar-lesson-you-find-the-present</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 23:51:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Owens Lee Pomeroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/562468-nostalgia-is-like-a-grammar-lesson-you-find-the-present]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nostalgia is like a grammar lesson: you find the present tense, and the past perfect!" -- Owens Lee Pomeroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/598188-each-night-i-lie-down-in-a-graveyard-of-memories</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 23:53:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Jerry Spinelli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/598188-each-night-i-lie-down-in-a-graveyard-of-memories]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each night I lie down in a graveyard of memories." -- Jerry Spinelli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7924-the-reason-i-talk-to-myself-is-because-i-m-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 23:56:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7924-the-reason-i-talk-to-myself-is-because-i-m-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The reason I talk to myself is because I’m the only one whose answers I accept." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11689-a-poem-needs-disguises-it-needs-secrets-it-thrives-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 23:05:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by J.D. McClatchy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11689-a-poem-needs-disguises-it-needs-secrets-it-thrives-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A poem needs disguises. It needs secrets. It thrives on the tension between what is said and not said; it prefers the oblique, the implied, the ironic, the suggestive; when it speaks, it wants you to lean forward a little to overhear; it wants you to understand things only years later." -- J.D. McClatchy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339882-criticism-of-others-is-thus-an-oblique-form-of-self-commendation</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 23:06:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Fulton J. Sheen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339882-criticism-of-others-is-thus-an-oblique-form-of-self-commendation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Criticism of others is thus an oblique form of self-commendation. We think we make the picture hang straight on our wall by telling our neighbors that all his pictures are crooked." -- Fulton J. Sheen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295293-creative-minds-are-uneven-and-the-best-of-fabrics-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 00:21:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295293-creative-minds-are-uneven-and-the-best-of-fabrics-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Creative minds are uneven, and the best of fabrics have their dull spots." -- H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419447-the-true-runner-is-a-very-fortunate-person-he-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2012 01:18:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by George Sheehan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419447-the-true-runner-is-a-very-fortunate-person-he-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The true runner is a very fortunate person. He has found something in him that is just perfect." -- George Sheehan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419441-as-every-runner-knows-running-is-about-more-than-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2012 01:18:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Joan Benoit Samuelson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419441-as-every-runner-knows-running-is-about-more-than-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As every runner knows, running is about more than just putting one foot in front of the other; it is about our lifestyle and who we are." -- Joan Benoit Samuelson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225877-there-s-nothing-more-dangerous-than-a-boy-with-charm</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2012 01:23:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Christina Aguilera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225877-there-s-nothing-more-dangerous-than-a-boy-with-charm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There’s nothing more dangerous than a boy with charm." -- Christina Aguilera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163282-the-insane-on-occasion-are-not-without-their-charms</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2012 01:24:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163282-the-insane-on-occasion-are-not-without-their-charms]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The insane, on occasion, are not without their charms." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/388506-rafe-didn-t-just-flirt-he-charmed-girls-right-up-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2012 01:25:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josabeth  add a quote by Kelley Armstrong]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/388506-rafe-didn-t-just-flirt-he-charmed-girls-right-up-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Rafe didn't just flirt-he charmed girls right up to the point where they fell for him, then he changed his mind.I called him a player with attention deficit disorder." -- Kelley Armstrong]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
