<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/42305-andreas]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/42305-andreas" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 22:02:22 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47167-but-that-night-as-i-drove-back-to-montreal-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 22:02:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andreas add a quote by Hugh MacLennan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47167-but-that-night-as-i-drove-back-to-montreal-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But that night as I drove back to Montreal, I at least discovered this: that there is no simple explanation for anything important any of us do, and that the human tragedy, or the human irony, consists in the necessity of living with the consequences of actions performed under the pressure of compulsions so obscure we do not and cannot understand them." -- Hugh MacLennan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47168-not-a-breath-not-a-sound-except-at-intervals-the-muffled</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 22:06:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andreas add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47168-not-a-breath-not-a-sound-except-at-intervals-the-muffled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not a breath, not a sound—except at intervals the muffled crackling of stones that the cold was reducing to sand—disturbed the solitude and silence surrounding Janine. After a moment, however, it seemed to her that the sky above her was moving in a sort of slow gyration. In the vast reaches of the dry, cold night, thousands of stars were constantly appearing, and their sparkling icicles, loosened at once, began to slip gradually towards the horizon. Janine could not tear herself away from contemplating those drifting flares. She was turning with them, and the apparently stationary progress little by little identified her with the core of her being, where cold and desire were now vying with each other. Before her the stars were falling one by one and being snuffed out among the stones of the desert, and each time Janine opened a little more to the night. Breathing deeply, she forgot the cold, the dead weight of others, the craziness or stuffiness of life, the long anguish of living and dying. After so many years of mad, aimless fleeing from fear, she had come to a stop at last. At the same time, she seemed to recover her roots and the sap again rose in her body, which had ceased trembling. Her whole belly pressed against the parapet as she strained towards the moving sky; she was merely waiting for her fluttering heart to calm down and establish silence within her. The last stars of the constellations dropped their clusters a little lower on the desert horizon and became still. Then, with unbearable gentleness, the water of night began to fill Janine, drowned the cold, rose gradually from the hidden core of her being and overflowed in wave after wave, rising up even to her mouth full of moans. The next moment, the whole sky stretched out over her, fallen on her back on the cold earth." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47170-only-a-rich-cunt-can-save-me-now-he-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 22:10:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andreas add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47170-only-a-rich-cunt-can-save-me-now-he-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only a rich cunt can save me now,' he says with an air of utmost weariness. 'One gets tired of chasing after new cunts all the time. It gets mechanical. The trouble is, you see, I can't fall in love. I'm too much of an egoist. Women only help me to dream, that's all. It's a vice, like drink or opium. I've got to have a new one every day; if I don't I get morbid. I think too much. Sometimes I'm amazed at myself, how quick I pull it off — and how little it really means. I do it automatically like. Sometimes I'm not thinking about a woman at all, but suddenly I notice a woman looking at me and then, bango! it starts all over again. Before I know what I'm doing I've got her up to the room. I don't even remember what I say to them. I bring them up to the room, give them a pat on the ass, and before I know what it's all about it's over. It's like a dream.... Do you know what I mean?" -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467589-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-if-this-isn-t-a-guidebook-what-is-it-a-book</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 21:50:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andreas add a quote by Harvey Manning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467589-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-if-this-isn-t-a-guidebook-what-is-it-a-book]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If this isn't a guidebook, what is it? A book of sermons, perhaps.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I preach that air travel be scaled back, as a start, to the level of twenty years ago, further reductions to be considered after all the Boeing engineers have been retrained as turkey ranchers.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The state Game Department should establish a season on helicopters — fifty-two weeks a year, twenty-four hours a day, no bag limit.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Passenger trains must be restored, as a start, to the service of forty years ago and then improved from there.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The Gypsy Bus System must not be regularized (the government would regulate it to death) but publicized cautiously through the underground.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I would discourage, if not ban, trekking to Everest base camp and flying over the Greenland Icecap. Generally, people should stay home. Forget gaining a little knowledge about a lot and strive to learn about a little." -- Harvey Manning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470216-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-in-the-static-mode-an-observer-may-unify-the-pieces</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 13:35:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Andreas add a quote by Harvey Manning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470216-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-nbsp-in-the-static-mode-an-observer-may-unify-the-pieces]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;In the static mode an observer may unify the pieces of a puzzle, but only as a blueprint—kinetics add the third dimention of depth, and the fourth of history. The motion, however, must be on the human scale, which happens also to be that of birds, waves, and clouds. Were a bullet to be made sentient, it still would see or hear or smell or feel nothing in land or water or air except its target. So, too, with a passenger in any machine that goes faster than a Model A. As speed increases, reality thins and becomes at the pace of a jet airplane no more substantial than a computer readout.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Running suits a person who seeks to look inward, through a fugue of pain, to study the dark self. A person afraid of the dark had better walk—strenuous enough for the rhythm of the feet to pace those of heart and lungs, relaxed enough to let him look outward, through joy, to a bright creation." -- Harvey Manning]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
