<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/423272-allison]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/423272-allison" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 19:30:21 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134585-now-death-is-uncool-old-fashioned-to-my-mind-the-defining</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 19:30:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Tana French]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134585-now-death-is-uncool-old-fashioned-to-my-mind-the-defining]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now death is uncool, old-fashioned. To my mind the defining characteristic of our era is spin, everything tailored to vanishing point by market research, brands and bands manufactured to precise specifications; we are so used to things transmuting into whatever we would like them to be that it comes as a profound outrage to encounter death, stubbornly unspinnable, only and immutably itself." -- Tana French]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/799530-at-the-kitchen-table-she-examined-the-glass-of-ice</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 09:38:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allison add a quote by Anthony Marra]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/799530-at-the-kitchen-table-she-examined-the-glass-of-ice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the kitchen table she examined the glass of ice. Each cube was rounded by room temperature, dissolving in its own remains, and belatedly she understood that this was how a loved one disappeared. Despite the shock wave of walking into an empty flat, the absence isn’t immediate, more a fade from the present tense you shared, a melting into the mast, not an erasure but a conversion in form, from presence to memory, from solid to liquid, and the person you once touched runs over your skin, now in sheets down your back, and you may bathe, may sink, may drown in the memory, but your fingers cannot hold it." -- Anthony Marra]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
