<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/424765-maggie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/424765-maggie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 09:12:59 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440-who-knows-how-to-make-love-stay-1-tell-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 09:12:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maggie add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440-who-knows-how-to-make-love-stay-1-tell-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who knows how to make love stay?

1. Tell love you are going to Junior's Deli on Flatbush Avenue in Brooklyn to pick up a cheesecake, and if loves stays, it can have half. It will stay.

2. Tell love you want a momento of it and obtain a lock of its hair. Burn the hair in a dime-store incense burner with yin/yang symbols on three sides. Face southwest. Talk fast over the burning hair in a convincingly exotic language. Remove the ashes of the burnt hair and use them to paint a moustache on your face. Find love. Tell it you are someone new. It will stay.

3. Wake love up in the middle of the night. Tell it the world is on fire. Dash to the bedroom window and pee out of it. Casually return to bed and assure love that everything is going to be all right. Fall asleep. Love will be there in the morning." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121820-maybe-that-s-what-we-look-for-in-the-people-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2009 19:34:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maggie add a quote by Tom Perrotta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121820-maybe-that-s-what-we-look-for-in-the-people-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe that's what we look for in the people we love, the spark of unhappiness we think we know how to extinguish." -- Tom Perrotta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29973-it-seems-to-me-now-that-the-plain-state-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2009 19:34:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maggie add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29973-it-seems-to-me-now-that-the-plain-state-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seems to me now that the plain state of being human is dramatic enough for anyone; you don't need to be a heroin addict or a performance poet to experience extremity. You just have to love someone." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189412-i-miss-him-like-one-might-miss-a-scar-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2009 19:39:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maggie add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189412-i-miss-him-like-one-might-miss-a-scar-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I miss him like one might miss a scar, or wooden leg, something disfiguring but characteristic." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11769-conversation-between-a-princess-and-an-outlaw-if-i-stand</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 09:08:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maggie add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11769-conversation-between-a-princess-and-an-outlaw-if-i-stand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Conversation between a princess and an outlaw: 
&quot;If I stand for fairy-tale balls and dragon bait--dragon bait--what do you stand for?&quot;
&quot;Me? I stand for uncertainty, insecurity, bad taste, fun, and things that go boom in the night.&quot;
&quot;Franky, it seems to me that you've turned yourself into a stereotype.&quot;
&quot;You may be right. I don't care. As any car freak will tell you, the old models are the most beautiful, even if they aren't the most efficient. People who sacrifice beauty for efficiency get what they deserve.&quot;
&quot;Well, you may get off on being a beautiful stereotype, regardless of the social consequences, but my conscience won't allow it.&quot; 
&quot;And I goddamn refuse to be dragon bait. I'm as capable of rescuing you as you are of rescuing me.&quot;
&quot;I'm an outlaw, not a hero. I never intended to rescue you. We're our own dragons as well as our own heroes, and we have to rescue ourselves from ourselves." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
