<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/42473-dana]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/42473-dana" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 22:21:17 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430913-george-was-an-atheist-and-so-am-i-but-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 22:21:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Justin Spring, quoting Samuel Steward]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430913-george-was-an-atheist-and-so-am-i-but-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["George was an atheist, and so am I. But how I long now for an afterlife - a world of light or of deep dazzling darkness, where he and the others we've lost reside, unscathed, forever accessible - to have tea with, to talk nonsense with, to reinvent the world with" -- Justin Spring, quoting Samuel Steward]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13848-here-s-to-the-few-who-forgive-what-you-do-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 22:21:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Leonard Cohen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13848-here-s-to-the-few-who-forgive-what-you-do-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the few who forgive what you do, and the fewer who don't even care" -- Leonard Cohen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/595436-that-s-what-being-shy-feels-like-like-my-skin-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 10:14:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Carol Rifka Brunt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/595436-that-s-what-being-shy-feels-like-like-my-skin-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's what being shy feels like. Like my skin is too thin, the light too bright. Like the best place I could possibly be is in a tunnel far under the cool, dark earth. Someone asks me a question and I stare at them, empty-faced, my brain jammed up with how hard I'm trying to find something interesting to say. And in the end, all I can do is nod or shrug, because the light of their eyes looking at me, waiting for me, is just too much to take. And then it's over and there's one more person in the world who thinks I'm a complete and total waste of space. 
The worst thing is the stupid hopefulness. Every new party, every new bunch of people, and I start thinking that maybe this is my chance. That I'm going to be normal this time. A new leaf. A fresh start. But then I find myself at the party, thinking, Oh, yeah. This again. 
So I stand on the edge of things, crossing my fingers, praying nobody will try to look me in the eye. And the good thing is, they usually don't." -- Carol Rifka Brunt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/650928-howard-s-eyes-were-open-and-very-clear-i-d-forgotten-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 10:27:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Gore Vidal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/650928-howard-s-eyes-were-open-and-very-clear-i-d-forgotten-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Howard's] eyes were open and very clear. I'd forgotten what a beautiful gray they were--illness and medicine had regularly glazed them over; now they were bright and attentive, and he was watching me, consciously, through long lashes. Lungs, heart may have stopped but the optic nerves were still sending messages to a brain which, those who should know tell us, does not immediately shut down. So we stared at each other at the end... 'Can you hear me?' I asked him. 'I know you can see me.' Although there was no breath for speech, he now had a sort of wry wiseguy from the Bronx expression on his face which said clearly to me who knew all his expressions, 'So this is the big fucking deal everyone goes on about." -- Gore Vidal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/337721-kizzy-wanted-it-all-so-bad-her-soul-leaned-half</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 12:25:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Laini Taylor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/337721-kizzy-wanted-it-all-so-bad-her-soul-leaned-half]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kizzy wanted it all so bad her soul leaned half out of her body hungering after it, and that was what drove the goblins wild, her soul hanging out there like an untucked shirt." -- Laini Taylor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39926-in-great-deeds-something-abides-on-great-fields-something-stays</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 21:27:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Joshua Lawrence Chamberlain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39926-in-great-deeds-something-abides-on-great-fields-something-stays]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In great deeds, something abides. On great fields, something stays. Forms change and pass; bodies disappear; but spirits linger, to consecrate ground for the vision-place of souls… generations that know us not and that we know not of, heart-drawn to see where and by whom great things were suffered and done for them, shall come to this deathless field, to ponder and dream; and lo! the shadow of a mighty presence shall wrap them in its bosom, and the power of the vision pass into their souls." -- Joshua Lawrence Chamberlain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/450576-when-the-sun-has-set-no-candle-can-replace-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 11:31:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/450576-when-the-sun-has-set-no-candle-can-replace-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the sun has set, no candle can replace it." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756346-for-the-girls-with-messy-hair-and-thirsty-hearts</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2013 16:30:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Jodi Lynn Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756346-for-the-girls-with-messy-hair-and-thirsty-hearts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the girls with messy hair and thirsty hearts." -- Jodi Lynn Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/805193-i-wondered-what-that-was-like-to-hold-someone-s-hand</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:58:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Benjamin Alire Sáenz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/805193-i-wondered-what-that-was-like-to-hold-someone-s-hand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wondered what that was like, to hold someone’s hand.  I bet you could sometimes find all of the mysteries of the universe in someone’s hand." -- Benjamin Alire Sáenz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/615777-to-be-careful-with-people-and-with-words-was-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 13:30:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Benjamin Alire Sáenz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/615777-to-be-careful-with-people-and-with-words-was-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be careful with people and with words was a rare and beautiful thing." -- Benjamin Alire Sáenz]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
