<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/425987-amy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/425987-amy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 08:01:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40902-i-mean-i-don-t-know-how-the-world-broke-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 08:01:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Rachel Cohn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40902-i-mean-i-don-t-know-how-the-world-broke-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I mean, I don’t know how the world broke. And I don’t know if there’s a God who can help us fix it. But the fact that the world is broken - I absolutely believe that. Just look around us. Every minute - every single second - there are a million things you could be thinking about. A million things you could be worrying about. Our world - don’t you just feel we’re becoming more fragmented? I used to think that when I got older, the world would make so much more sense. But you know what? The older I get, the more confusing it is to me. The more complicated it is. Harder. You’d think we’d be getting better at it. But there’s just more and more chaos. The pieces - they’re everywhere. And nobody knows what to do about it. I find myself grasping, Nick. You know that feeling? That feeling when you just want the right thing to fall into the right place, not only because it’s right, but because it would mean that such a thing is still possible? I want to believe that." -- Rachel Cohn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111906-i-am-the-spirit-that-negates-and-rightly-so-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 08:02:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111906-i-am-the-spirit-that-negates-and-rightly-so-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the spirit that negates.
And rightly so, for all that comes to be
Deserves to perish wretchedly;
'Twere better nothing would begin.
Thus everything that that your terms, sin,
Destruction, evil represent—
That is my proper element." -- Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252682-entropy-shakes-its-angry-fist-at-you-for-being-clever</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 08:02:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252682-entropy-shakes-its-angry-fist-at-you-for-being-clever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Entropy shakes its angry fist at you for being clever enough to organize the world. (p 2)" -- Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476130-time-goes-forward-because-energy-itself-is-always-moving-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 08:04:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Jeremy Rifkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476130-time-goes-forward-because-energy-itself-is-always-moving-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time goes forward because energy itself is always moving from an available to an unavailable state. Our consciousness is continually recording the entropy change in the world around us. We watch our friends get old and die. We sit next to a fire and watch it's red-hot embers turn slowly into cold white ashes. We experience the world always changing around us, and that experience is the unfolding of the second law. It is the irreversible process of dissipation of energy in the world. What does it mean to say, 'The world is running out of time'? Simply this: we experience the passage of time by the succession of one event after another. And every time an event occurs anywhere in this world energy is expended and the overall entropy is increased. To say the world is running out of time then, to say the world is running out of usable energy. In the words of Sir Arthur Eddington, 'Entropy is time's arrow'." -- Jeremy Rifkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377395-information-defined-intuitively-and-informally-might-be-something-like-uncertainty-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 08:05:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Brian Christian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377395-information-defined-intuitively-and-informally-might-be-something-like-uncertainty-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Information, defined intuitively and informally, might be something like 'uncertainty's antidote.' This turns out also to be the formal definition- the amount of information comes from the amount by which something reduces uncertainty...The higher the [information] entropy, the more information there is. It turns out to be a value capable of measuring a startling array of things- from the flip of a coin to a telephone call, to a Joyce novel, to a first date, to last words, to a Turing test...Entropy suggests that we gain the most insight on a question when we take it to the friend, colleague, or mentor of whose reaction and response we're least certain. And it suggests, perhaps, reversing the equation, that if we want to gain the most insight into a person, we should ask the question of qhose answer we're least certain... Pleasantries are low entropy, biased so far that they stop being an earnest inquiry and become ritual. Ritual has its virtues, of course, and I don't quibble with them in the slightest. But if we really want to start fathoming someone, we need to get them speaking in sentences we can't finish." -- Brian Christian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/517530-we-all-behave-like-maxwell-s-demon-organisms-organize-in-everyday</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 08:06:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by James Gleick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/517530-we-all-behave-like-maxwell-s-demon-organisms-organize-in-everyday]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all behave like Maxwell’s demon. Organisms organize. In everyday experience lies the reason sober physicists across two centuries kept this cartoon fantasy alive. We sort the mail, build sand castles, solve jigsaw puzzles, separate wheat from chaff, rearrange chess pieces, collect stamps, alphabetize books, create symmetry, compose sonnets and sonatas, and put our rooms in order, and all this we do requires no great energy, as long as we can apply intelligence. We propagate structure (not just we humans but we who are alive). We disturb the tendency toward equilibrium. It would be absurd to attempt a thermodynamic accounting for such processes, but it is not absurd to say we are reducing entropy, piece by piece. Bit by bit. The original demon, discerning one molecules at a time, distinguishing fast from slow, and operating his little gateway, is sometimes described as “superintelligent,” but compared to a real organism it is an idiot savant. Not only do living things lessen the disorder in their environments; they are in themselves, their skeletons and their flesh, vesicles and membranes, shells and carapaces, leaves and blossoms, circulatory systems and metabolic pathways - miracles of pattern and structure. It sometimes seems as if curbing entropy is our quixotic purpose in the universe." -- James Gleick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227430-nor-public-flame-nor-private-dares-to-shine-nor-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 08:17:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Alexander Pope]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227430-nor-public-flame-nor-private-dares-to-shine-nor-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nor public flame, nor private, dares to shine;
Nor human spark is left, nor glimpse divine!
Lo! thy dread empire, Chaos! is restored;
Light dies before thy uncreating word:
Thy hand, great Anarch! lets the curtain fall;
And universal darkness buries all." -- Alexander Pope]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235289-eventually-everything-connects---people-ideas-objects-the-quality-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 02:37:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Charles Eames]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235289-eventually-everything-connects---people-ideas-objects-the-quality-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eventually everything connects - people, ideas, objects. The quality of the connections is the key to quality per se." -- Charles Eames]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/562216-i-like-women-who-haven-t-lived-with-too-many-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 02:20:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/562216-i-like-women-who-haven-t-lived-with-too-many-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like women who haven’t lived with too many men.
I don’t expect virginity but I simply prefer women
who haven’t been rubbed raw by experience.
There is a quality about women who choose
men sparingly;
it appears in their walk
in their eyes
in their laughter and in their
gentle hearts.
Women who have had too many men
seem to choose the next one
out of revenge rather than with
feeling.
When you play the field selfishly everything
works against you:
one can’t insist on love or
demand affection.
You’re finally left with whatever
you have been willing to give
which often is:
nothing." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37223-tyger-tyger-burning-bright-in-the-forests-of-the-night</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 08:36:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by William Blake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37223-tyger-tyger-burning-bright-in-the-forests-of-the-night]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tyger! Tyger! burning bright 
In the forests of the night, 
What immortal hand or eye 
Could frame thy fearful symmetry?" -- William Blake]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/944659-the-future-has-an-ancient-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 08:36:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Carlo Levi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/944659-the-future-has-an-ancient-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The future has an ancient heart." -- Carlo Levi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/994126-it-is-better-to-arm-and-strengthen-your-hero-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 00:46:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Anne Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/994126-it-is-better-to-arm-and-strengthen-your-hero-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to arm and strengthen your hero, than to disarm and enfeeble your foe." -- Anne Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1142054-stalin-scribbled-on-an-intelligence-report-predicting-that-hitler-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 23:29:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Ion Mihai Pacepa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1142054-stalin-scribbled-on-an-intelligence-report-predicting-that-hitler-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stalin scribbled on an intelligence report predicting that Hitler would attack the Soviet Union in June 1941: 'You can send your &quot;source&quot; to his f*cking mother. This is disinformation." -- Ion Mihai Pacepa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191180-do-we-really-want-to-travel-in-hermetically-sealed-popemobiles</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 23:29:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Anthony Bourdain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191180-do-we-really-want-to-travel-in-hermetically-sealed-popemobiles]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do we really want to travel in hermetically sealed popemobiles through the rural provinces of France, Mexico and the Far East, eating only in Hard Rock Cafes and McDonalds? Or do we want to eat without fear, tearing into the local stew, the humble taqueria's mystery meat, the sincerely offered gift of a lightly grilled fish head? I know what I want. I want it all. I want to try everything once." -- Anthony Bourdain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48673-no-one-understands-and-appreciates-the-american-dream-of-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 23:29:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Anthony Bourdain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48673-no-one-understands-and-appreciates-the-american-dream-of-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one understands and appreciates the American Dream of hard work leading to material rewards better than a non-American. " -- Anthony Bourdain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273355-we-know-for-instance-that-there-is-a-direct-inverse</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 23:31:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Anthony Bourdain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273355-we-know-for-instance-that-there-is-a-direct-inverse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We know, for instance, that there is a direct, inverse relationship between frequency of family meals and social problems. Bluntly stated, members of families who eat together regularly are statistically less likely to stick up liquor stores, blow up meth labs, give birth to crack babies, commit suicide, or make donkey porn. If Little Timmy had just had more meatloaf, he might not have grown up to fill chest freezers with Cub Scout parts." -- Anthony Bourdain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310463-peta-doesn-t-want-stressed-animals-to-be-cruelly-crowded-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 23:31:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Anthony Bourdain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310463-peta-doesn-t-want-stressed-animals-to-be-cruelly-crowded-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["PETA doesn't want stressed animals to be cruelly crowded into sheds, ankle-deep in their own crap, because they don't want any animals to die-ever-and basically think chickens should, in time, gain the right to vote. I don't want animals stressed or crowded or treated cruelly or inhumanely because that makes them probably less delicious." -- Anthony Bourdain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525717-skills-can-be-taught-character-you-either-have-or-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 23:32:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Anthony Bourdain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525717-skills-can-be-taught-character-you-either-have-or-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Skills can be taught.  Character you either have or you don't have." -- Anthony Bourdain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1195028-what-are-you-going-to-do-everything-is-my-guess</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 02:18:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Nora Ephron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1195028-what-are-you-going-to-do-everything-is-my-guess]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What are you going to do? Everything, is my guess. It will be a little messy, but embrace the mess. It will be complicated, but rejoice in the complications." -- Nora Ephron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150628-god-save-us-from-people-who-mean-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 08:37:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Vikram Seth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150628-god-save-us-from-people-who-mean-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God save us from people who mean well." -- Vikram Seth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533627-many-abused-children-cling-to-the-hope-that-growing-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 12:06:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Judith Lewis Herman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533627-many-abused-children-cling-to-the-hope-that-growing-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many abused children cling to the hope that growing up will bring escape and freedom. 

But the personality formed in the environment of coercive control is not well adapted to adult life. The survivor is left with fundamental problems in basic trust, autonomy, and initiative. She approaches the task of early adulthood――establishing independence and intimacy――burdened by major impairments in self-care, in cognition and in memory, in identity, and in the capacity to form stable relationships. 

She is still a prisoner of her childhood; attempting to create a new life, she reencounters the trauma." -- Judith Lewis Herman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
