<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/427051-lara]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/427051-lara" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 19:32:36 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19219-one-is-loved-because-one-is-loved-no-reason-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 19:32:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19219-one-is-loved-because-one-is-loved-no-reason-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One is loved because one is loved. No reason is needed for loving." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9616-everything-tells-me-that-i-am-about-to-make-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 19:33:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9616-everything-tells-me-that-i-am-about-to-make-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything tells me that I am about to make a wrong decision, but making mistakes is just part of life. What does the world want of me? Does it want me to take no risks, to go back to where I came from because I didn't have the courage to say &quot;yes&quot; to life?" -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16154-we-are-afraid-of-losing-what-we-have-whether-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 19:34:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16154-we-are-afraid-of-losing-what-we-have-whether-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are afraid of losing what we have, whether it's our life or our possessions and property. But this fear evaporates when we understand that our life stories and the history of the world were written by the same hand." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2489-if-there-hadn-t-been-a-sixth-day-man-would-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 19:34:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2489-if-there-hadn-t-been-a-sixth-day-man-would-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there hadn't been a sixth day, man would not exist; copper would always be copper; and lead just lead. It's true that everything has its Personal Legend, but one day that Personal Legend will be realized. So each thing has to transform itself into something better, and to acquire a new Personal Legend, until, someday, the Soul of the World becomes one thing only." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12405-tell-your-heart-that-the-fear-of-suffering-is-worse</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 19:34:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12405-tell-your-heart-that-the-fear-of-suffering-is-worse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tell your heart that the fear of suffering is worse than the suffering itself. And that no heart has ever suffered when it goes in search of its dreams, because every second of the search is a second's encounter with God and with eternity." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16152-what-s-the-world-s-greatest-lie-it-s-this-that-at-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 19:34:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16152-what-s-the-world-s-greatest-lie-it-s-this-that-at-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What's the world's greatest lie?... It's this: that at a certain point in our lives, we lose control of what's happening to us, and our lives become controlled by fate." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13208-you-fight-your-superficiality-your-shallowness-so-as-to-try</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 19:37:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13208-you-fight-your-superficiality-your-shallowness-so-as-to-try]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You fight your superficiality, your shallowness, so as to try to come at people without unreal expectations, without an overload of bias or hope or arrogance, as untanklike as you can be, sans cannon and machine guns and steel plating half a foot thick; you come at them unmenacingly on your own ten toes instead of tearing up the turf with your caterpillar treads, take them on with an open mind, as equals, man to man, as we used to say, and yet you never fail to get them wrong.  You might as well have the brain of a tank.  You get them wrong before you meet them, while you're anticipating meeting them; you get them wrong while you're with them; and then you go home to tell somebody else about the meeting and you get them all wrong again.  Since the same generally goes for them with you, the whole thing is really a dazzling illusion. ...  The fact remains that getting people right is not what living is all about anyway.  It's getting them wrong that is living, getting them wrong and wrong and wrong and then, on careful reconsideration, getting them wrong again.  That's how we know we're alive:  we're wrong.  Maybe the best thing would be to forget being right or wrong about people and just go along for the ride.  But if you can do that -- well, lucky you." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/869-benedicto-may-your-trails-be-crooked-winding-lonesome-dangerous-leading</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 19:38:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/869-benedicto-may-your-trails-be-crooked-winding-lonesome-dangerous-leading]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Benedicto: May your trails be crooked, winding, lonesome, dangerous, leading to the most amazing view. May your mountains rise into and above the clouds. May your rivers flow without end, meandering through pastoral valleys tinkling with bells, past temples and castles and poets towers into a dark primeval forest where tigers belch and monkeys howl, through miasmal and mysterious swamps and down into a desert of red rock, blue mesas, domes and pinnacles and grottos of endless stone, and down again into a deep vast ancient unknown chasm where bars of sunlight blaze on profiled cliffs, where deer walk across the white sand beaches, where storms come and go as lightning clangs upon the high crags, where something strange and more beautiful and more full of wonder than your deepest dreams waits  for you -- beyond that next turning of the canyon walls." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10471-wilderness-is-not-a-luxury-but-a-necessity-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 19:38:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10471-wilderness-is-not-a-luxury-but-a-necessity-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wilderness is not a luxury but a necessity of the human spirit, and as vital to our lives as water and good bread. A civilization which destroys what little remains of the wild, the spare, the original, is cutting itself off from its origins and betraying the principle of civilization itself." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5643-how-to-overthrow-the-system-brew-your-own-beer-kick</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 19:38:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5643-how-to-overthrow-the-system-brew-your-own-beer-kick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How to Overthrow the System: brew your own beer; kick in your Tee Vee; kill your own beef; build your own cabin and piss off the front porch whenever you bloody well feel like it." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21667-society-is-like-a-stew-if-you-don-t-stir-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 19:38:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21667-society-is-like-a-stew-if-you-don-t-stir-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Society is like a stew. If you don't stir it up every once in a while then a layer of scum floats to the top." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15390-resist-much-obey-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 19:38:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Edward Abbey/Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15390-resist-much-obey-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Resist much, obey little" -- Edward Abbey/Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21664-growth-for-the-sake-of-growth-is-the-ideology-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 19:39:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21664-growth-for-the-sake-of-growth-is-the-ideology-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Growth for the sake of growth is the ideology of the cancer cell." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10455-wilderness-and-motors-are-incompatible-and-the-former-can-best</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 19:39:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10455-wilderness-and-motors-are-incompatible-and-the-former-can-best]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wilderness and motors are incompatible and the former can best be experienced, understood and enjoyed when the machines are left behind where they belong -- on the superhighways and in the parking lots, on the reservoirs and in the marinas." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/871-if-people-persist-in-trespassing-upon-the-grizzlies-territory-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 19:39:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/871-if-people-persist-in-trespassing-upon-the-grizzlies-territory-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If people persist in trespassing upon the grizzlies' territory, we must accept the fact that the grizzlies, from time to time, will harvest a few trespassers." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4693-we-the-mortals-touch-the-metals-the-wind-the-ocean</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 07:41:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4693-we-the-mortals-touch-the-metals-the-wind-the-ocean]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We the mortals touch the metals,
the wind, the ocean shores, the stones,
knowing they will go on, inert or burning,
and I was discovering, naming all the these things:
it was my destiny to love and say goodbye." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48507-i-crave-your-mouth-your-voice-your-hair-silent-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 07:42:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48507-i-crave-your-mouth-your-voice-your-hair-silent-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I crave your mouth, your voice, your hair.
Silent and starving, I prowl through the streets. 
Bread does not nourish me, dawn disrupts me, all day 
I hunt for the liquid measure of your steps. 

I hunger for your sleek laugh, 
your hands the color of a savage harvest, 
hunger for the pale stones of your fingernails, 
I want to eat your skin like a whole almond. 

I want to eat the sunbeam flaring in your lovely body, 
the sovereign nose of your arrogant face, 
I want to eat the fleeting shade of your lashes, 

and I pace around hungry, sniffing the twilight, 
hunting for you, for your hot heart, 
Like a puma in the barrens of Quitratue." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5647-and-when-you-want-something-all-the-universe-conspires-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 07:43:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5647-and-when-you-want-something-all-the-universe-conspires-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And, when you want something, all the universe conspires in helping you to achieve it." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12948-life-always-waits-for-some-crisis-to-occur-before-revealing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 07:44:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12948-life-always-waits-for-some-crisis-to-occur-before-revealing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life always waits for some crisis to occur before revealing itself at its most brilliant." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15209-this-is-what-we-call-love-when-you-are-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 07:57:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15209-this-is-what-we-call-love-when-you-are-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what we call love. When you are loved, you can do anything in creation. When you are loved, there's no need at all to understand what's happening, because everything happens within you." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167015-it-would-be-incorrect-in-every-sense-to-say-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 10:04:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lara add a quote by Ann Patchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167015-it-would-be-incorrect-in-every-sense-to-say-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It would be incorrect in every sense to say that so near the end of his life he had lost his faith, when in fact 
God seemed more abundant to him in the Regina Cleri home than any place he had been before. God was in the folds of his bathrobe, the ache of his knees. God saturated the hallways in the form of a pale electrical light.  But now that his heart had become so shiftless and unreliable, now that he should be sensing the afterlife like a sweet scent drifting in from the garden, he had started to wonder if there was in fact no afterlife at all.  Look at all these true believers who wanted only to live, look at himself, cling onto this life like a squirrel scrambling up the icy pitch of a roof. In suggesting that there may be nothing ahead of them, he in no way meant to diminish the future; instead, Father Sullivan hoped to elevate the present to a state of the divine. It seemed from this moment of repose that God may well have been life itself.  God may have been the baseball games, the beautiful cigarette he smoked alone after checking to see that all the bats had been put back behind the closet door.  God could have been the masses in which he had told people how best to prepare for the glorious life everlasting, the one they couldn't see as opposed to the one they were living at that exact moment in the pews of the church hall, washed over in stained glass light.  How wrongheaded it seemed now to think that the thrill of heartbeat and breath were just a stepping stone to something greater.  What could be greater than the armchair, the window, the snow? Life itself had been holy. We had been brought forth from nothing to see the face of God and in his life Father Sullivan had seen it miraculously for eighty-eight years.  Why wouldn't it stand to reason that this had been the whole of existence and now he would retreat back to the nothingness he had come from in order to let someone else have their turn at the view. This was not the workings of disbelief. It was instead a final, joyful realization of all he had been given.  It would be possible to overlook just about anything if you were trained to constantly strain forward to see the power and the glory that was waiting up ahead.  What a shame it would have been to miss God while waiting for him. " -- Ann Patchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
