<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/430887-katherine-willis-pershey]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/430887-katherine-willis-pershey" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2008 22:08:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73418-when-i-am-with-you-we-stay-up-all-night</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2008 22:08:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73418-when-i-am-with-you-we-stay-up-all-night]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I am with you, we stay up all night.
When you're not here, I can't go to sleep.
Praise God for those two insomnias!
And the difference between them." -- Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109867-love-the-quick-profit-the-annual-raise-vacation-with-pay</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2008 13:21:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109867-love-the-quick-profit-the-annual-raise-vacation-with-pay]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love the quick profit, the annual raise,
vacation with pay. Want more
of everything ready-made. Be afraid
to know your neighbors and to die.

And you will have a window in your head.
Not even your future will be a mystery
any more. Your mind will be punched in a card
and shut away in a little drawer.

When they want you to buy something
they will call you. When they want you
to die for profit they will let you know.
So, friends, every day do something
that won’t compute. Love the Lord.
Love the world. Work for nothing.
Take all that you have and be poor.
Love someone who does not deserve it.

Denounce the government and embrace
the flag. Hope to live in that free
republic for which it stands.
Give your approval to all you cannot
understand. Praise ignorance, for what man
has not encountered he has not destroyed.

Ask the questions that have no answers.
Invest in the millenium. Plant sequoias.
Say that your main crop is the forest
that you did not plant,
that you will not live to harvest.

Say that the leaves are harvested
when they have rotted into the mold.
Call that profit. Prophesy such returns.
Put your faith in the two inches of humus
that will build under the trees
every thousand years.

Listen to carrion — put your ear
close, and hear the faint chattering
of the songs that are to come.
Expect the end of the world. Laugh.
Laughter is immeasurable. Be joyful
though you have considered all the facts.
So long as women do not go cheap
for power, please women more than men.

Ask yourself: Will this satisfy
a woman satisfied to bear a child?
Will this disturb the sleep
of a woman near to giving birth?

Go with your love to the fields.
Lie down in the shade. Rest your head
in her lap. Swear allegiance
to what is nighest your thoughts.

As soon as the generals and the politicos
can predict the motions of your mind,
lose it. Leave it as a sign
to mark the false trail, the way
you didn’t go.

Be like the fox
who makes more tracks than necessary,
some in the wrong direction.
Practice resurrection." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19265-as-it-has-been-said-love-and-a-cough-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 12:17:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Anne Sexton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19265-as-it-has-been-said-love-and-a-cough-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As it has been said:
Love and a cough
cannot be concealed.
Even a small cough.
Even a small love." -- Anne Sexton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126334-love-all-god-s-creation-both-the-whole-and-every-grain</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 13:26:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126334-love-all-god-s-creation-both-the-whole-and-every-grain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love all God’s creation, both the whole and every grain of sand. Love every leaf, every ray of light. Love the animals, love the plants, love each separate thing. If thou love each thing thou wilt perceive the mystery of God in all; and when once thou perceive this, thou wilt thenceforward grow every day to a fuller understanding of it: until thou come at last to love the whole world with a love that will then be all-embracing and universal." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8986-joy-is-the-infallible-sign-of-the-presence-of-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 10:10:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Pierre Teilhard de Chardin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8986-joy-is-the-infallible-sign-of-the-presence-of-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Joy is the infallible sign of the presence of God." -- Pierre Teilhard de Chardin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487129-i-shall-tell-you-what-i-believe-i-believe-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2012 12:03:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Sarah  Smith ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487129-i-shall-tell-you-what-i-believe-i-believe-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I shall tell you what I believe. I believe God is a librarian. I believe that literature is holy...it is that best part of our souls that we break off and give each other, and God has a special dispensation for it, angels to guard its making and its preservation." -- Sarah  Smith ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521133-marriage-is-foremost-a-vocation-two-people-are-called-together</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 20:08:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521133-marriage-is-foremost-a-vocation-two-people-are-called-together]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...marriage is foremost a vocation. Two people are called together to fulfill a mission that God has given them. Marriage is a spiritual reality. That is to say, a man and a woman come together for life, not just because they experience deep love for each other, but because they believe that God loves each of them with an infinite love and has called them to each other to be living witnesses of that love. To love is to embody God's infinite love in a faithful communion with another human being." -- Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261952-what-marriage-offers---and-what-fidelity-is-meant-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 10:04:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261952-what-marriage-offers---and-what-fidelity-is-meant-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What marriage offers - and what fidelity is meant to protect - is the possibility of moments when what we have chosen and what we desire are the same.  Such a convergence obviously cannot be continuous.  No relationship can continue very long at its highest emotional pitch.  But fidelity prepares us for the return of these moments, which give us the highest joy we can know; that of union, communion, atonement (in the root sense of at-one-ment)...
To forsake all others does not mean - because it cannot mean - to ignore or neglect all others, to hide or be hidden from all others, or to desire or love no others.  To live in marriage is a responsible way to live in sexuality, as to live in a household is a responsible way to live in the world.  One cannot enact or fulfill one's love for womankind or mankind, or even for all the women or men to whom one is attracted.  If one is to have the power and delight of one's sexuality, then the generality of instinct must be resolved in a responsible relationship to a particular person.  Similarly, one cannot live in the world; that is, one cannot become, in the easy, generalizing sense with which the phrase is commonly used, a &quot;world citizen.&quot;  There can be no such think as a &quot;global village.&quot;  No matter how much one may love the world as a whole, one can live fully in it only by living responsibly in some small part of it.  Where we live and who we live there with define the terms of our relationship to the world and to humanity.  We thus come again to the paradox that one can become whole only by the responsible acceptance of one's partiality.
(pg.117-118, &quot;The Body and the Earth&quot;)" -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10136-there-is-nothing-sweeter-in-this-sad-world-than-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 06:24:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katherine add a quote by Kate DiCamillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10136-there-is-nothing-sweeter-in-this-sad-world-than-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing sweeter in this sad world than the sound of someone you love calling your name." -- Kate DiCamillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
