<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/431480-jeremiah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/431480-jeremiah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 20:59:35 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 20:59:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremiah add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that is gold does not glitter,
Not all those who wander are lost;
The old that is strong does not wither,
Deep roots are not reached by the frost.

From the ashes a fire shall be woken,
A light from the shadows shall spring;
Renewed shall be blade that was broken,
The crownless again shall be king." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309485-nobody-tells-this-to-people-who-are-beginners-i-wish</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 18:06:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremiah add a quote by Ira Glass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309485-nobody-tells-this-to-people-who-are-beginners-i-wish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody tells this to people who are beginners, I wish someone told me. All of us who do creative work, we get into it because we have good taste. But there is this gap. For the first couple years you make stuff, it’s just not that good. It’s trying to be good, it has potential, but it’s not. But your taste, the thing that got you into the game, is still killer. And your taste is why your work disappoints you. A lot of people never get past this phase, they quit. Most people I know who do interesting, creative work went through years of this. We know our work doesn’t have this special thing that we want it to have. We all go through this. And if you are just starting out or you are still in this phase, you gotta know its normal and the most important thing you can do is do a lot of work. Put yourself on a deadline so that every week you will finish one story. It is only by going through a volume of work that you will close that gap, and your work will be as good as your ambitions. And I took longer to figure out how to do this than anyone I’ve ever met. It’s gonna take awhile. It’s normal to take awhile. You’ve just gotta fight your way through." -- Ira Glass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99392-no-man-knows-how-bad-he-is-till-he-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 16:22:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremiah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99392-no-man-knows-how-bad-he-is-till-he-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No man knows how bad he is till he has tried very hard to be good. A silly idea is current that good people do not know what temptation means. This is an obvious lie. Only those who try to resist temptation know how strong it is. After all, you find out the strength of the German army by fighting against it, not by giving in. You find out the strength of a wind by trying to walk against it, not by lying down. A man who gives in to temptation after five minutes simply does not know what it would have been like an hour later. That is why bad people, in one sense, know very little about badness — they have lived a sheltered life by always giving in. We never find out the strength of the evil impulse inside us until we try to fight it: and Christ, because He was the only man who never yielded to temptation, is also the only man who knows to the full what temptation means — the only complete realist." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
