<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/431447-katy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/431447-katy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 10:50:02 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31219-i-am-life-that-wants-to-live-in-the-midst</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 10:50:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Albert Schweitzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31219-i-am-life-that-wants-to-live-in-the-midst]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am life that wants to live, in the midst of life that wants to live." -- Albert Schweitzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 10:50:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be the change that you wish to see in the world." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 10:53:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what you shall do; Love the earth and sun and the animals, despise riches, give alms to every one that asks, stand up for the stupid and crazy, devote your income and labor to others, hate tyrants, argue not concerning God, have patience and indulgence toward the people, take off your hat to nothing known or unknown or to any man or number of men, go freely with powerful uneducated persons and with the young and with the mothers of families, read these leaves in the open air every season of every year of your life, re-examine all you have been told at school or church or in any book, dismiss whatever insults your own soul, and your very flesh shall be a great poem and have the richest fluency not only in its words but in the silent lines of its lips and face and between the lashes of your eyes and in every motion and joint of your body." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3407-the-only-escape-from-the-miseries-of-life-are-music</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 10:57:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Albert Schweitzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3407-the-only-escape-from-the-miseries-of-life-are-music]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only escape from the miseries of life are music and cats..." -- Albert Schweitzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1858-for-most-of-history-anonymous-was-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 11:04:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1858-for-most-of-history-anonymous-was-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For most of history, Anonymous was a woman." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9181-for-it-would-seem---her-case-proved-it--</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 11:05:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9181-for-it-would-seem---her-case-proved-it--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For it would seem - her case proved it - that we write, not with the fingers, but with the whole person. The nerve which controls the pen winds itself about every fibre of our being, threads the heart, pierces the liver." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5732-all-that-you-touch-you-change-all-that-you-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 11:07:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Octavia E. Butler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5732-all-that-you-touch-you-change-all-that-you-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that you touch
You Change.

All that you Change
Changes you.

The only lasting truth
is Change.

God
is Change." -- Octavia E. Butler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14425-only-if-we-understand-can-we-care-only-if-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 11:08:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Jane Goodall]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14425-only-if-we-understand-can-we-care-only-if-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only if we understand, can we care. Only if we care, we will help. Only if we help, we shall be saved." -- Jane Goodall]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241199-in-this-age-the-mere-example-of-non-conformity-the-mere</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 11:13:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by John Stuart Mill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241199-in-this-age-the-mere-example-of-non-conformity-the-mere]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In this age, the mere example of non-conformity, the mere refusal to bend the knee to custom, is itself a service. Precisely because the tyranny of opinion is such as to make eccentricity a reproach, it is desirable, in order to break through that tyranny, that people should be eccentric. Eccentricity has always abounded when and where strength of character has abounded; and the amount of eccentricity in a society has generally been proportional to the amount of genius, mental vigor, and moral courage which it contained. That so few now dare to be eccentric, marks the chief danger of the time." -- John Stuart Mill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26613-the-peculiar-evil-of-silencing-the-expression-of-an-opinion</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 11:14:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by John Stuart Mill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26613-the-peculiar-evil-of-silencing-the-expression-of-an-opinion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The peculiar evil of silencing the expression of an opinion is, that it is robbing the human race; posterity as well as the existing generation; those who dissent from the opinion, still more than those who hold it. If the opinion is right, they are deprived of the opportunity of exchanging error for truth: if wrong, they lose, what is almost as great a benefit, the clearer perception and livelier impression of truth, produced by its collision with error." -- John Stuart Mill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4976-a-person-may-cause-evil-to-others-not-only-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 11:14:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by John Stuart Mill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4976-a-person-may-cause-evil-to-others-not-only-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A person may cause evil to others not only by his actions but by his inaction, and in either case he is justly accountable to them for the injury." -- John Stuart Mill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346-there-may-be-times-when-we-are-powerless-to-prevent</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 09:15:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346-there-may-be-times-when-we-are-powerless-to-prevent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There may be times when we are powerless to prevent injustice, but there must never be a time when we fail to protest." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512-there-is-no-greater-agony-than-bearing-an-untold-story</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 09:18:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512-there-is-no-greater-agony-than-bearing-an-untold-story]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no greater agony than bearing an untold story inside you." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335611-the-object-of-this-essay-is-to-assert-one-very</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 15:24:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by John Stuart Mill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335611-the-object-of-this-essay-is-to-assert-one-very]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The object of this Essay is to assert one very simple principle, as entitled to govern absolutely the dealings of society with the individual in the way of compulsion and control, whether the means used be physical force in the form of legal penalties, or the moral coercion of public opinion. That principle is, that the sole end for which mankind are warranted, individually or collectively in interfering with the liberty of action of any of their number, is self-protection. That the only purpose for which power can be rightfully exercised over any member of a civilized community, against his will, is to prevent harm to others. His own good, either physical or moral, is not a sufficient warrant. He cannot rightfully be compelled to do or forbear because it will be better for him to do so, because it will make him happier, because, in the opinions of others, to do so would be wise, or even right. These are good reasons for remonstrating with him, or reasoning with him, or persuading him, or entreating him, but not for compelling him, or visiting him with any evil, in case he do otherwise. To justify that, the conduct from which it is desired to deter him must be calculated to produce evil to someone else. The only part of the conduct of any one, for which he is amenable to society, is that which concerns others. In the part which merely concerns himself, his independence is, of right, absolute. Over himself, over his own body and mind, the individual is sovereign." -- John Stuart Mill]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
