<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/431878-quee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/431878-quee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 20:46:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117226-true-literature-can-exist-only-where-it-is-created-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 20:46:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Quee add a quote by Yevgeny Zamyatin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117226-true-literature-can-exist-only-where-it-is-created-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["True literature can exist only where it is created, not by diligent and trustworthy functionaries, but by madmen, hermits, heretics, dreamers, rebels, and skeptics." -- Yevgeny Zamyatin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66640-we-may-insist-as-often-as-we-like-that-man-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 20:48:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Quee add a quote by Sigmund Freud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66640-we-may-insist-as-often-as-we-like-that-man-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We may insist as often as we like that man's intellect is powerless in comparison to his instinctual life, and we may be right in this. Nevertheless, there is something peculiar about this weakness. The voice of the intellect is a soft one, but it will not rest until it has gained a hearing. Finally, after a countless succession of rebuffs, it succeeds." -- Sigmund Freud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132893-socialism-like-the-ancient-ideas-from-which-it-springs-confuses</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 20:36:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Quee add a quote by Frederic Bastiat]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132893-socialism-like-the-ancient-ideas-from-which-it-springs-confuses]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Socialism, like the ancient ideas from which it springs, confuses the distinction between government and society. As a result of this, every time we object to a thing being done by government, the socialists conclude that we object to its being done at all. We disapprove of state education. Then the socialists say that we are opposed to any education. We object to a state religion. Then the socialists say that we want no religion at all. We object to a state-enforced equality. Then they say that we are against equality. And so on, and so on. It is as if the socialists were to accuse us of not wanting persons to eat because we do not want the state to raise grain." -- Frederic Bastiat]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66643-he-who-knows-only-his-own-side-of-the-case</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 20:44:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Quee add a quote by John Stuart Mill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66643-he-who-knows-only-his-own-side-of-the-case]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He who knows only his own side of the case knows little of that. His reasons may be good, and no one may have been able to refute them. But if he is equally unable to refute the reasons on the opposite side, if he does not so much as know what they are, he has no ground for preferring either opinion... Nor is it enough that he should hear the opinions of adversaries from his own teachers, presented as they state them, and accompanied by what they offer as refutations. He must be able to hear them from persons who actually believe them...he must know them in their most plausible and persuasive form." -- John Stuart Mill]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
