<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/434004-yvonne]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/434004-yvonne" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 09:47:06 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/869-benedicto-may-your-trails-be-crooked-winding-lonesome-dangerous-leading</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 09:47:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvonne add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/869-benedicto-may-your-trails-be-crooked-winding-lonesome-dangerous-leading]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Benedicto: May your trails be crooked, winding, lonesome, dangerous, leading to the most amazing view. May your mountains rise into and above the clouds. May your rivers flow without end, meandering through pastoral valleys tinkling with bells, past temples and castles and poets towers into a dark primeval forest where tigers belch and monkeys howl, through miasmal and mysterious swamps and down into a desert of red rock, blue mesas, domes and pinnacles and grottos of endless stone, and down again into a deep vast ancient unknown chasm where bars of sunlight blaze on profiled cliffs, where deer walk across the white sand beaches, where storms come and go as lightning clangs upon the high crags, where something strange and more beautiful and more full of wonder than your deepest dreams waits  for you -- beyond that next turning of the canyon walls." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258113-we-are-each-other-s-harvest-we-are-each-other-s-business</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2013 11:50:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvonne add a quote by Gwendolyn Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258113-we-are-each-other-s-harvest-we-are-each-other-s-business]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are each other's harvest; we are each other's business; we are each other's magnitude and bond." -- Gwendolyn Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303285-i-do-not-pretend-to-understand-the-moral-universe-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 15:24:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvonne add a quote by Theodore Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303285-i-do-not-pretend-to-understand-the-moral-universe-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not pretend to understand the moral universe; the arc is a long one, my eye reaches but little ways; I cannot calculate the curve and complete the figure by the experience of sight, I can divine it by conscience. And from what I see I am sure it bends towards justice." -- Theodore Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/609780-if-you-want-your-ministry-to-have-it-more-important</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 18:22:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvonne add a quote by Craig Groeschel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/609780-if-you-want-your-ministry-to-have-it-more-important]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want your ministry to have ‘it’, more important than anything else we’ve discussed, you must have ‘it’. When it has filtered through your heart - the rare combination of passion, integrity, focus, faith, expectation, drive, hunger, and God’s anointing - God tends to infuse your ministry with ‘it’. He blesses your work. People are changed. Leaders grow. Resources flow. The ministry seems to take on a life of its own." -- Craig Groeschel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1718-the-very-least-you-can-do-in-your-life-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 09:58:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvonne add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1718-the-very-least-you-can-do-in-your-life-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The very least you can do in your life is figure out what you hope for. And the most you can do is live inside that hope. Not admire it from a distance but live right in it, under its roof." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
