<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/434988-mentyrosa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/434988-mentyrosa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 21:17:57 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31440-brecht-managed-to-live-and-work-in-the-tension-between</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 21:17:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Eugene Lunn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31440-brecht-managed-to-live-and-work-in-the-tension-between]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Brecht managed to live and work in the tension between despair and hope, emphasizing the contradictory nature of every historical moment." -- Eugene Lunn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31446-but-we-are-living-in-a-skeptical-and-if-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 08:14:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31446-but-we-are-living-in-a-skeptical-and-if-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But we are living in a skeptical and, if I may use the phrase, a thought-tormented age; and sometimes I fear that this new generation, educated or hypereducated as it is, will lack those qualities of humanity, of hospitality, of kindly humor which belonged to an older day.." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31450-here-you-will-find-marvelous-moustaches-which-neither-pen-nor</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 21:26:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Andrei Biely]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31450-here-you-will-find-marvelous-moustaches-which-neither-pen-nor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here you will find marvelous moustaches, which neither pen nor brush could depict. To which the best part of a lifetime has been devoted, objects of long vigils by day and midnight; moustaches on which the most ravishing ointments have been poured, which have been anointed with the most precious pomades and which are the envy of passerby.." -- Andrei Biely]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31451-but-yet-with-all-this-although-of-course-one-may</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 21:26:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Nikolai Gogol]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31451-but-yet-with-all-this-although-of-course-one-may]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But yet with all this, although, of course, one may admit this, that and the other, may even... and after all, where aren't there incongruities?" -- Nikolai Gogol]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31452-but-he-had-hardly-felt-the-absurdity-of-those-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 21:26:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Samuel Beckett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31452-but-he-had-hardly-felt-the-absurdity-of-those-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But he had hardly felt the absurdity of those things, on the one hand, and the necessity of those others, on the other, (for it is rare that the feeling of absurdity is not followed by the feeling of necessity), when he felt the absurdity of those things of which he had just felt the necessity (for it is rare that the feeling of necessity is not followed by the feeling of absurdity.)" -- Samuel Beckett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31453-the-centripetal-force-on-our-planet-is-still-fearfully-strong</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 21:30:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31453-the-centripetal-force-on-our-planet-is-still-fearfully-strong]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The centripetal force on our planet is still fearfully strong, Alyosha. I have a longing for life, and I go on living in spite of logic. Though I may not believe in the order of the universe, yet I love the sticky little leaves as they open in spring. I love the blue sky, I love some people, whom one loves you know sometimes without knowing why. I love some great deeds done by men, though I’ve long ceased perhaps to have faith in them, yet from old habit one’s heart prizes them. Here they have brought the soup for you, eat it, it will do you good. It’s first-rate soup, they know how to make it here. I want to travel in Europe, Alyosha, I shall set off from here. And yet I know that I am only going to a graveyard, but it’s a most precious graveyard, that’s what it is! Precious are the dead that lie there, every stone over them speaks of such burning life in the past, of such passionate faith in their work, their truth, their struggle and their science, that I know I shall fall on the ground and kiss those stones and weep over them; though I’m convinced in my heart that it’s long been nothing but a graveyard. And I shall not weep from despair, but simply because I shall be happy in my tears, I shall steep my soul in emotion. I love the sticky leaves in spring, the blue sky — that’s all it is. It’s not a matter of intellect or logic, it’s loving with one’s inside, with one’s stomach." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33014-you-can-t-imagine-how-stupid-the-whole-world-has-grown</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 12:40:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Nikolai V. Gogol]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33014-you-can-t-imagine-how-stupid-the-whole-world-has-grown]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can't imagine how stupid the whole world has grown nowadays. The things these scribblers write! " -- Nikolai V. Gogol]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49799-jemu-watched-his-father-disappear-he-didn-t-throw-the-coconut</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 20:47:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Kiran Desai]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49799-jemu-watched-his-father-disappear-he-didn-t-throw-the-coconut]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jemu watched his father disappear. He didn't throw the coconut and he didn't cry. Never again would he know love for another human being that wasn't adulterated by another, contradictory emotion." -- Kiran Desai]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30941-she-had-been-forced-into-prudence-in-her-youth-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 00:04:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Jane Austen ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30941-she-had-been-forced-into-prudence-in-her-youth-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had been forced into prudence in her youth, she learned romance as she grew older: the natural sequel of an unnatural beginning." -- Jane Austen ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57524-incredible-the-animal-that-first-dreamed-of-another-animal</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 00:54:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Carlos Fuentes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57524-incredible-the-animal-that-first-dreamed-of-another-animal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Incredible the animal that first dreamed of another animal." -- Carlos Fuentes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41336-such-a-captive-maiden-having-plenty-of-time-to-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2008 21:56:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41336-such-a-captive-maiden-having-plenty-of-time-to-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Such a captive maiden, having plenty of time to think, soon realizes that her tower, its height and architecture, are like her ego only incidental: that what really keeps her where she is is magic, anonymous and malignant, visited on her from outside and for no reason at all. Having no apparatus except gut fear and female cunning to examine this formless magic, to understand how it works, how to measure its field strength, count its lines of force, she may fall back on superstition, or take up a useful hobby like embroidery, or go mad, or marry a disk jockey. If the tower is everywhere and the knight of deliverance no proof against its magic, what else?" -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62567-someday-she-might-replace-whatever-of-her-had-gone-away</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 22:46:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62567-someday-she-might-replace-whatever-of-her-had-gone-away]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Someday she might replace whatever of her had gone away by some prosthetic device, a dress of a certain color, a phrase in a letter, another lover. " -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21044-we-die-containing-a-richness-of-lovers-and-tribes-tastes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 22:48:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21044-we-die-containing-a-richness-of-lovers-and-tribes-tastes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We die containing a richness of lovers and tribes, tastes we have swallowed, bodies we have plunged into and swum up as if rivers of wisdom, characters we have climbed into as if trees, fears we have hidden in as if caves. 

I wish for all this to be marked on by body when I am dead.  I believe in such cartography - to be marked by nature, not just to label ourselves on a map like the names of rich men and women on buildings.  We are communal histories, communal books.  We are not owned or monogamous in our taste or experience." -- Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62569-there-are-stories-of-elopements-unrequited-love-family-feuds-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 22:56:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62569-there-are-stories-of-elopements-unrequited-love-family-feuds-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are stories of elopements, unrequited love, family feuds and exhausting vendettas, which everyone was drawn into, had to be involved with. But nothing is said of the closeness between two people: how they grew in the shade of each other's presence. No one speaks of that exchange of gift and character - the way a person took on and recognized in himself the smile of a lover...

Where is the intimate and truthful in all this? Teenager and Uncle. Husband and lover. A lost father in his solace. And why do I want to know of this privacy? After the cups of tea, coffee, public conversations ... I want to sit down with someone and talk with utter directness, want to talk to all the lost history like that deserving lover. " -- Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76165-the-timorous-may-stay-home</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 11:49:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Benjamin Cardozo, Murphy v. Steeplechase Amusement Co., 250 NY 479 (1929)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76165-the-timorous-may-stay-home]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The timorous may stay home." -- Benjamin Cardozo, Murphy v. Steeplechase Amusement Co., 250 NY 479 (1929)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76170-a-spiritual-desert-is-spreading---an-interior-emptiness-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 11:53:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Pope Benedict XVI]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76170-a-spiritual-desert-is-spreading---an-interior-emptiness-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["a spiritual desert is spreading - an interior emptiness, an unnamed fear, a quiet sense of despair." -- Pope Benedict XVI]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178970-68-by-then-all-poets-will-live-in-artistic-communities</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 19:01:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178970-68-by-then-all-poets-will-live-in-artistic-communities]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["68. By then all poets will live in artistic communities calls jails or asylums. 69. Our imaginary home, the home we share. " -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178971-54-the-children-of-the-spanish-lion-said-ruben-dario</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 19:01:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178971-54-the-children-of-the-spanish-lion-said-ruben-dario]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["54. The children of the Spanish lion, said Ruben Dario, a born optimist. The children of Walt Whitman, Jose Marti, and Violeta Parra; torn apart, forgotten, in mass graves, at the bottom of the sea, the Trojan destiny of their mingled bones terrifying the survivors. " -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 00:50:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She is too fond of books, and it has turned her brain." -- Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27409-the-awful-thing-is-that-beauty-is-mysterious-as-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 00:51:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27409-the-awful-thing-is-that-beauty-is-mysterious-as-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The awful thing is that beauty is mysterious as well as terrible. God and the devil are fighting there and the battlefield is the heart of man." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241034-in-this-world-shipmates-sin-that-pays-its-way-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 00:52:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241034-in-this-world-shipmates-sin-that-pays-its-way-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In this world, shipmates, sin that pays its way can travel freely and without a passport; whereas Virtue, if a pauper, is stopped at all frontiers." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65049-like-most-others-i-was-a-seeker-a-mover-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 00:52:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65049-like-most-others-i-was-a-seeker-a-mover-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like most others, I was a seeker, a mover, a malcontent, and at times a stupid hell-raiser. I was never idle long enough to do much thinking, but I felt somehow that some of us were making real progress, that we had taken an honest road, and that the best of us would inevitably make it over the top. At the same time, I shared a dark suspicion that the life we were leading was a lost cause, that we were all actors, kidding ourselves along on a senseless odyssey. It was the tension between these two poles - a restless idealism on one hand and a sense of impending doom on the other - that kept me going." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143986-the-american-mirror-said-the-voice-the-sad-american-mirror</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 00:57:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143986-the-american-mirror-said-the-voice-the-sad-american-mirror]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The American mirror, said the voice, the sad American mirror of wealth and poverty and constant useless metamorphosis, the mirror that sails and whose sails are pain." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311911-of-all-the-islands-he-d-visited-two-stood-out-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 00:59:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311911-of-all-the-islands-he-d-visited-two-stood-out-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of all the islands he'd visited, two stood out. The island of the past, he said, where the only time was past time and the inhabitants were bored and more or less happy, but where the weight of illusion was so great that the island sank a little deeper into the river every day. And the island of the future, where the only time was the future, and the inhabitants were planners and strivers, such strivers, said Ulises, that they were likely to end up devouring one another." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26772-to-be-joyous-is-to-be-a-madman-in-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 00:24:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26772-to-be-joyous-is-to-be-a-madman-in-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be joyous is to be a madman in a world of sad ghosts." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208691-it-may-be-argued-that-the-past-is-a-country</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 00:24:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mentyrosa add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208691-it-may-be-argued-that-the-past-is-a-country]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It may be argued that the past is a country from which we have all emigrated, that its loss is part of our common humanity." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
