<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/436235-amy-crehore]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/436235-amy-crehore" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 18:09:34 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626618-he-wonders-again-if-the-dead-need-translators-perhaps-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 18:09:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626618-he-wonders-again-if-the-dead-need-translators-perhaps-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He wonders again if the dead need translators; perhaps in a moment, in a simple twist of unbecoming, they know everything they need to know." -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/535169-he-feels-as-if-he-is-floating-and-she-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 18:09:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/535169-he-feels-as-if-he-is-floating-and-she-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He feels as if he is floating, and she is weighting him to earth; he would like to put his arms around her and his face in her apron, and rest there listening to her heartbeat. But he doesn't want to mess her up, get blood all down the front of her." -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/611082-a-grey-wrinkled-vastness-like-the-residue-of-a-dream</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 18:09:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/611082-a-grey-wrinkled-vastness-like-the-residue-of-a-dream]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["a grey wrinkled vastness, like the residue of a dream" -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314189-arrange-your-face</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 18:09:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314189-arrange-your-face]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Arrange your face" -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242463-over-the-city-lies-the-sweet-rotting-odor-of-yesterday-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 18:10:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242463-over-the-city-lies-the-sweet-rotting-odor-of-yesterday-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Over the city lies the sweet, rotting odor of yesterday's unrecollected sins." -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394492-it-is-the-absence-of-facts-that-frightens-people-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 18:11:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394492-it-is-the-absence-of-facts-that-frightens-people-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is the absence of facts that frightens people: the gap you open, into which they pour their fears, fantasies, desires." -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215081-of-course-it-was-painful-and-there-were-times-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 14:21:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215081-of-course-it-was-painful-and-there-were-times-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of course it was painful, and there were times when, emotionally, I just wanted to chuck it all.  But pain seems to be a precondition for this kind of sport.  If pain weren't involved, who in the world would ever go to the trouble of taking part in sports like the triathlon or the marathon, which demand such an investment of time and energy?  It's precisely because of the pain, precisely because we want to overcome that pain, that we can get the feeling, through this process, of really being alive--or at least a partial sense of it.  Your quality of experience is based not on standards such as time or ranking, but on finally awakening to an awareness of the fluidity within action itself." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/613585-pain-is-inevitable-suffering-is-optional-say-you-re-running-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 14:21:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/613585-pain-is-inevitable-suffering-is-optional-say-you-re-running-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pain is inevitable.  Suffering is optional.  Say you’re running and you think, ‘Man, this hurts, I can’t take it anymore.  The ‘hurt’ part is an unavoidable reality, but whether or not you can stand anymore is up to the runner himself." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/670227-sometimes-i-run-fast-when-i-feel-like-it-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 14:23:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/670227-sometimes-i-run-fast-when-i-feel-like-it-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I run fast when I feel like it, but if I increase the pace I shorten the amount of time I run, the point being to let the exhilaration I feel at the end of each run carry over to the next day. This is the same sort of tack I find necessary when writing a novel. I stop every day right at the point where I feel I can write more. Do that, and the next day's work goes surprisingly smoothly. I think Ernest Hemingway did something like that. To keep on going, you have to keep up the rhythm. This is the important thing for long-term projects. Once you set the pace, the rest will follow. The problem is getting the flywheel to spin at a set speed-and to get to that point takes as much concentration and effort as you can manage." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/650752-no-matter-how-much-long-distance-running-might-suit-me-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 14:24:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/650752-no-matter-how-much-long-distance-running-might-suit-me-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No matter how much long-distance running might suit me, of course there are days when I feel kind of lethargic and don’t want to run. Actually, it happens a lot. On days like that, I try to think of all kinds of plausible excuses to slough it off. Once, I interviewed the Olympic running Toshihiko Seko, just after he retired from running and became manager of the S&amp;B company team. I asked him, “Does a runner at your level ever feel like you’d rather not run today, like you don’t want to run and would rather just sleep in?” He stared at me and then, in a voice that made it abundantly clear how stupid he thought the question was, replied, “Of course. All the time!" -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/555276-sixteen-is-an-intensely-troublesome-age-you-worry-about-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 14:26:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/555276-sixteen-is-an-intensely-troublesome-age-you-worry-about-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sixteen is an intensely troublesome age. You worry about little things, can't pinpoint where you are in any objective way, become really proficient at strange, pointless skills, and are held in thrall by inexplicable complexes. As you get older, though, through trial and error you can learn to get what you need, and throw out what should be discarded. And you start to recognize (or be resigned to the fact) that since your faults and deficiences are well nigh infinite, you'd best figure our your good points and learn to get by with what you have." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
