<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/436346-brett]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/436346-brett" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 11:59:20 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118438-thus-the-white-men-and-native-americans-were-able-through</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 11:59:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brett add a quote by Dave Barry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118438-thus-the-white-men-and-native-americans-were-able-through]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thus the white men and Native Americans were able, through the spirit of goodwill and compromise, to reach the first in what would become a long series of mutually beneficial, breached agreements that enabled the two cultures to coexist peacefully for stretches of twenty and sometimes even thirty days, after which it was usually necessary to negotiate new agreements that would be even more mutual and beneficial, until eventually the Native Americans were able to perceive the vast mutual benefits of living in rock-strewn sectors of South Dakota." -- Dave Barry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141729-i-got-dizzy-he-explained-i-should-think-you-did</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2009 07:18:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brett add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141729-i-got-dizzy-he-explained-i-should-think-you-did]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I got dizzy,&quot; he explained.
I should think you did.  What were you doing?'
Nothing,&quot; said Moon.  &quot;I was trying to face one way or the other and I got confused and fell over.&quot;
Let that be my epitaph." -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93629-i-agree-with-everything-you-say-but-i-would-attack</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2009 07:20:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brett add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93629-i-agree-with-everything-you-say-but-i-would-attack]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I agree with everything you say, but I would attack to the death your right to say it. " -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143219-i-would-rather-he-said-give-a-healthy-boy-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 20:56:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brett add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143219-i-would-rather-he-said-give-a-healthy-boy-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would rather,' he said, 'give a healthy boy or a healthy girl a phial of prussic acid than this novel.' (And here let me pause to make Mr. Douglas a sporting offer. I will provide a healthy boy, a phial of prussic acid, and a copy of The Well of Loneliness, and if he keeps his word and gives the boy the prussic acid I undertake to pay all expenses of his defense at the ensuing murder trial and to erect a monument to his memory after he has been hanged.)" -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145370-universal-education-has-created-an-immense-class-of-what-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 19:44:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brett add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145370-universal-education-has-created-an-immense-class-of-what-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Universal education has created an immense class of what I may call the New Stupid, hungering for certainty yet unable to find it in the traditional myths and their rationalizations." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185425-after-september-11-some-critics-even-tried-to-lump-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2009 18:54:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brett add a quote by Benjamin R. Barber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185425-after-september-11-some-critics-even-tried-to-lump-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After September 11, some critics even tried to lump the antiglobalization protesters in with the terrorists, casting them as irresponsible destabilizers of the world order. But the protesters are the children of McWorld, and their objections are not Jihadic but merely democratic. Their grievances concern not world order but world disorder, and if the young demonstrators are a little foolish in their politics, a little naive in their analysis, and a little short on viable solutions, they understand with a sophistication their leaderes apparently lack that globalization's current architecture breeds anarchy, nihilism, and violence." -- Benjamin R. Barber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 12:43:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brett add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hello babies. Welcome to Earth. It's hot in the summer and cold in the winter. It's round and wet and crowded. On the outside, babies, you've got a hundred years here. There's only one rule that I know of, babies-&quot;God damn it, you've got to be kind." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
