<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/439937-jim]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/439937-jim" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2008 13:20:14 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1845-young-castle-called-me-scoop-good-morning-scoop-what-s-new</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2008 13:20:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1845-young-castle-called-me-scoop-good-morning-scoop-what-s-new]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Young Castle called me &quot;Scoop.&quot; &quot;Good Morning, Scoop. What's new in the word game?&quot;

&quot;I might ask the same of you,&quot; I replied.

&quot;I'm thinking of calling a general strike of all writers until mankind finally comes to its senses. Would you support it?&quot;

&quot;Do writers have a right to strike? That would be like the police or the firemen walking out.&quot;

&quot;Or the college professors.&quot;

&quot;Or the college professors,&quot; I agreed. I shook my head. &quot;No, I don't think my conscience would let me support a strike like that. When a man becomes a writer, I think he takes a sacred obligation to produce beauty and enlightenment and comfort at top speed.&quot;

&quot;I just can't help thinking what a real shake up it would give people if, all of a sudden, there were no new books, new plays, new histories, new poems...&quot;

&quot;And how proud would you be when people started dying like flies?&quot; I demanded.

&quot;They'd die more like mad dogs, I think--snarling &amp; snapping at each other &amp; biting their own tails.&quot;

I turned to Castle the elder. &quot;Sir, how does a man die when he's deprived of the consolation of literature?&quot;

&quot;In one of two ways,&quot; he said, &quot;petrescence of the heart or atrophy of the nervous system.&quot;

&quot;Neither one very pleasant, I expect,&quot; I suggested.

&quot;No,&quot; said Castle the elder. &quot;For the love of God, both of you, please keep writing!" -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2136-the-covers-of-this-book-are-too-far-apart</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 05:23:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2136-the-covers-of-this-book-are-too-far-apart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The covers of this book are too far apart." -- Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84024-i-leaned-back-in-my-chair-my-fingers-laced-behind</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 09:51:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by James Lee Burke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84024-i-leaned-back-in-my-chair-my-fingers-laced-behind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I leaned back in my chair, my fingers laced behind my head, and wondered at the complexities and contradictions that must have existed in the earth's original clay when God first scooped it up in His palms." -- James Lee Burke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110597-chaos-it-has-no-plural</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 12:58:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Carlos Fuentes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110597-chaos-it-has-no-plural]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["chaos: it has no plural." -- Carlos Fuentes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151913-there-is-no-rest-stop-on-the-misinformation-highway</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 10:10:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Dahlia Lithwick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151913-there-is-no-rest-stop-on-the-misinformation-highway]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no rest stop on the misinformation highway." -- Dahlia Lithwick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246994-on-literary-festivals-when-you-go-and-see-a-band</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 05:36:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Nicholas Lezard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246994-on-literary-festivals-when-you-go-and-see-a-band]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["(On literary festivals) When you go and see a band play live, you are watching it do on stage what it is meant to do. When you watch an author perform live, you are, most of the time, watching a dog walk on its hind legs. " -- Nicholas Lezard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445346-who-but-a-brazen-crazy-person-would-go-one-on-one-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 11:26:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Mark Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445346-who-but-a-brazen-crazy-person-would-go-one-on-one-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who but a brazen crazy person would go one-on-one with blank paper or canvas armed with nothing but ideas?" -- Mark Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/646375-man-who-is-without-the-arts-is-little-above-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2012 10:13:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Haldane McFall]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/646375-man-who-is-without-the-arts-is-little-above-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man who is without the arts is little above the beasts of the field." -- Haldane McFall]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907552-critics-are-like-eunuchs-in-a-harem-they-ve-seen-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 06:14:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Brendan Behan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907552-critics-are-like-eunuchs-in-a-harem-they-ve-seen-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Critics are like eunuchs in a harem. They've seen it done every day of the week, but they can't do it themselves." -- Brendan Behan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/912600-travel-without-surprise-was-merely-an-agenda</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 10:26:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Jim Malusa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/912600-travel-without-surprise-was-merely-an-agenda]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Travel without surprise was merely an agenda." -- Jim Malusa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/955741-you-think-of-travelers-as-bold-but-our-guilty-secret</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 06:38:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Paul Theroux]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/955741-you-think-of-travelers-as-bold-but-our-guilty-secret]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think of travelers as bold, but our guilty secret is that travel is one of the laziest ways on earth of passing the time. Travel is not merely the business of being bone-idle, but also an elaborate bumming evasion, allowing us to call attention to ourselves with our conspicuous absence while we intrude upon other people’s privacy — being actively offensive as fugitive freeloaders. The traveler is the greediest kind of romantic voyeur, and in some well-hidden part of the traveler’s personality is an unpickable knot of vanity, presumption, and mythomania bordering on the pathological. This is why a traveler’s worst nightmare is not the secret police or the witch doctors or malaria, but rather the prospect of meeting another traveler.

Most writing about travel takes the form of jumping to conclusions, and so most travel books are superfluous, the thinnest, most transparent monologuing. Little better than a license to bore, travel writing is the lowest form of literary self-indulgence: dishonest complaining, creative mendacity, pointless heroics, and chronic posturing, much of it distorted with Munchausen syndrome." -- Paul Theroux]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
