<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/441343-jessica]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/441343-jessica" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 11:34:24 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302567-rules-even-as-the-world-of-phone-and-computer-sex</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 11:34:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Laura Antoniou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302567-rules-even-as-the-world-of-phone-and-computer-sex]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Rules. Even as the world of phone and computer sex (and dominance) were full of their own rules, so was the new world of doing-it-for real.  And some of these new rules, (OK, most of them, Robin admitted) were just as silly as the ones she had learned and followed before.  Safe words, for example.  Magic words that when said by the bottom, stopped a scene so that some kind of inconvenient or dangerous activity could be halted.  Robin had nothing against the concept.........
Having a code  to use so that you're free to pull  against the bondage or whimper &quot;no, no, no&quot; seemed to be a great idea.  But having all these possible ways to orchestrate what was happening seemed, well, contrary to the point........
I want to feel that I can't stop it.  I want to be really mastered, taken over by someone who isn't goin to stop doing things because I'm not getting off on it.  Someone who knows enough not to endanger me, unless that was what was intended........." -- Laura Antoniou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119183-the-holiday-season-is-a-time-for-storytelling-and-whether</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2012 09:17:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119183-the-holiday-season-is-a-time-for-storytelling-and-whether]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The holiday season is a time for storytelling, and whether you are hearing the story of a candelabra staying lit for more than a week, or a baby born in a barn without proper medical supervision, these stories often feature miracles.  Miracles are like pimples, because once you start looking for them you find more than you ever dreamed you'd see, and this holiday story features any number of miracles, depending on your point of view." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/675850-he-let-go-releasing-her-into-a-life-of-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2013 12:17:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Maggie Shipstead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/675850-he-let-go-releasing-her-into-a-life-of-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He let go, releasing her into a life of her own making." -- Maggie Shipstead]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
