<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/442036-angela]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/442036-angela" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 12:18:08 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216380-most-americans-who-read-at-all-read-junk-i-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 12:18:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216380-most-americans-who-read-at-all-read-junk-i-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most Americans who read at all read junk... I think it is a fair generalization to say that European readers of fiction like novels to be challenging, to be demanding; nor do they follow trends or fashions in reading taste in the lemminglike manner of many readers in the United States." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17002-people-worry-about-kids-playing-with-guns-and-teenagers-watching</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 19:44:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17002-people-worry-about-kids-playing-with-guns-and-teenagers-watching]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People worry about kids playing with guns, and teenagers watching violent videos; we are scared that some sort of culture of violence will take them over.  Nobody worries about kids listening to thousands - literally thousands - of songs about broken hearts and rejection and pain and misery and loss." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161721-if-it-s-true-your-life-flashes-past-your-eyes-before</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2009 08:15:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Amy Hempel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161721-if-it-s-true-your-life-flashes-past-your-eyes-before]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["if it's true your life flashes past your eyes before you die, then it is also the truth that your life rushes forth when you are ready to start to truly be alive." -- Amy Hempel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227831-to-cheat-your-way-into-a-job-bigger-than-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 08:58:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227831-to-cheat-your-way-into-a-job-bigger-than-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["to cheat your way into a job bigger than your mind can handle is to become a fear-corroded ape on borrowed motions and borrowed time, and to settle down into a job that requires less than your mind’s full capacity is to cut your motor and sentence yourself to another kind of motion: decay - that your work is the process of achieving your values, and to lose your ambition for values is to lose your ambition to live - that your body is a machine, but your mind is its driver, and you must drive as far as your mind will take you, with achievement as the goal of your road - that the man who has no purpose is a machine that coasts downhill at the mercy of any boulder to crash in the first chance ditch, that the man who stifles his mind is a stalled machine slowly going to rust, that the man who lets a leader prescribe his course is a wreck being towed to the scrap heap, and the man who makes another man his goal is a hitchhiker no driver should ever pick up - that your work is the purpose of your life, and you must speed past any killer who assumes the right to stop you, that any value you might find outside your work, any other loyalty or love, can be only travelers you choose to share your journey and must be travelers going on their own power in the same direction." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273541-the-lazio-fans-always-stop-at-the-bakery-on-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 16:27:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273541-the-lazio-fans-always-stop-at-the-bakery-on-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Lazio fans always stop [at the bakery] on their way home from the stadium to stand in the street for hours, leaning up against their motorcycles, talking about the game, looking macho as anything, and eating &lt;i&gt;cream puffs.&lt;/i&gt;
I love Italy." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286431-a-true-piece-of-writing-is-a-dangerous-thing-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 02:44:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Tobias Wolff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286431-a-true-piece-of-writing-is-a-dangerous-thing-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["a true piece of writing is a dangerous thing. It can change your life." -- Tobias Wolff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296878-were-this-world-an-endless-plain-and-by-sailing-eastward</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 18:14:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296878-were-this-world-an-endless-plain-and-by-sailing-eastward]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Were this world an endless plain, and by sailing eastward we could for ever reach new distances, and discover sights more sweet and strange than any Cyclades or Islands of King Solomon, then there were promise in the voyage. But in pursuit of those far mysteries we dream of, or in tormented chase of the demon phantom that, some time or other, swims before all human hearts; while chasing such over this round globe, they either lead us on in barren mazes or midway leave us whelmed." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/340297-with-all-respects-to-heaven-i-like-it-here</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 19:51:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Colum McCann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/340297-with-all-respects-to-heaven-i-like-it-here]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With all respects to heaven, I like it here." -- Colum McCann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163938-let-s-not-mince-words-the-inside-of-the-sydney-casino</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 06:38:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Steve Toltz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163938-let-s-not-mince-words-the-inside-of-the-sydney-casino]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let’s not mince words: the inside of the Sydney casino looks as if Vegas had an illegitimate child with Liberace’s underpants, and that child fell down a staircase and hit its head on the edge of a spade." -- Steve Toltz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/421139-nobody-is-worthy-to-be-loved-the-fact-that-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 20:05:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/421139-nobody-is-worthy-to-be-loved-the-fact-that-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody is worthy to be loved. The fact that God loves man shows us that in the divine order of ideal things it is written that eternal love is to be given to what is eternally unworthy. Or if that phrase seems to be a bitter one to bear, let us say that everybody is worthy of love, except him who thinks he is." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/504402-pierre-involuntarily-started-comparing-these-two-men-so-different-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 08:29:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/504402-pierre-involuntarily-started-comparing-these-two-men-so-different-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Pierre] involuntarily started comparing these two men, so different and at the same time so similar, because of the love he had for both of them, and because both had lived and both had died." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242463-over-the-city-lies-the-sweet-rotting-odor-of-yesterday-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 07:55:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242463-over-the-city-lies-the-sweet-rotting-odor-of-yesterday-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Over the city lies the sweet, rotting odor of yesterday's unrecollected sins." -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48021-we-don-t-read-and-write-poetry-because-it-s-cute-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 15:24:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by N.H. Kleinbaum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48021-we-don-t-read-and-write-poetry-because-it-s-cute-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't read and write poetry because it's cute. We read and write poetry because we are members of the human race. And the human race is filled with passion. So medicine, law, business, engineering... these are noble pursuits and necessary to sustain life. But poetry, beauty, romance, love... these are what we stay alive for." -- N.H. Kleinbaum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465988-sometimes-you-read-a-book-and-it-fills-you-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 17:44:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465988-sometimes-you-read-a-book-and-it-fills-you-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, you read a book and it fills you with this weird evangelical zeal, and you become convinced that the shattered world will never be put back together unless and until all living humans read the book." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/733338-listen-to-me-i-m-shy-i-m-not-stupid-i-can-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 06:46:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Jonathan Lethem]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/733338-listen-to-me-i-m-shy-i-m-not-stupid-i-can-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen to me. I’m shy. I’m not stupid. I can’t meet people’s eyes. I don’t know if you understand what that’s like. There’s a whole world going on around me, I’m aware of that. It’s not because I don’t want to look at you, Lucinda. It’s that I don’t want to be seen." -- Jonathan Lethem]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/996536-she-shared-the-curse-of-many-artists-that-praise-beaded-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 18:18:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Carol Anshaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/996536-she-shared-the-curse-of-many-artists-that-praise-beaded-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She shared the curse of many artists—that praise beaded up and rolled off her while criticism stuck like glue, glue embedded with ground glass." -- Carol Anshaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
