<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/44218-megan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/44218-megan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 10:56:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60759-there-is-an-ecstasy-that-marks-the-summit-of-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 10:56:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Jack London]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60759-there-is-an-ecstasy-that-marks-the-summit-of-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is an ecstasy that marks the summit of life, and beyond which life cannot rise. And such is the paradox of living, this ecstasy comes when one is most alive, and it comes as a complete forgetfulness that one is alive. 
This ecstasy, this forgetfulness of living, comes to the artist, caught up and out of himself in a sheet of flame; it comes to the soldier, war-mad in a stricken field and refusing quarter; and it came to Buck, leading the pack, sounding the old wolf-cry, straining after the food that was alive and that fled swiftly before him through the moonlight." -- Jack London]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352524-telephone-books-are-like-dictionaries-already-out-of-date-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 21:08:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Ammon Shea]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352524-telephone-books-are-like-dictionaries-already-out-of-date-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Telephone books are, like dictionaries, already out of date the moment they are printed...." -- Ammon Shea]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/409405-stories-have-a-way-of-changing-faces-they-are-unruly</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 22:52:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/409405-stories-have-a-way-of-changing-faces-they-are-unruly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories have a way of changing faces. They are unruly things, undisciplined, given to delinquency and the throwing of erasers. This is why we must close them up into thick, solid books, so they cannot get out and cause trouble." -- Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386152-september-let-go-a-long-held-breath-she-stared-into-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 22:54:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386152-september-let-go-a-long-held-breath-she-stared-into-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["September let go a long-held breath. She stared into the roiling black-violet soup, thinking furiously. The trouble was, September didn’t know what sort of story she was in. Was it a merry one or a serious one? How ought she to act? If it were merry, she might dash after a Spoon, and it would all be a marvelous adventure, with funny rhymes and somersaults and a grand party with red lanterns at the end. But if it were a serious tale, she might have to do something important, something involving, with snow and arrows and enemies. Of course, we would like to tell her which. But no one may know the shape of the tale in which they move. And, perhaps, we do not truly know which sort of beast it is, either. Stories have a way of changing faces. They are unruly things, undisciplined, given to delinquency and the throwing of erasers. This is why we must close them up into thick, solid books, so they cannot get out and cause trouble." -- Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/688812-reading-isn-t-the-opposite-of-doing-it-s-the-opposite-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 09:36:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Will Schwalbe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/688812-reading-isn-t-the-opposite-of-doing-it-s-the-opposite-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reading isn't the opposite of doing, it's the opposite of dying." -- Will Schwalbe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23164-we-live-for-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 14:31:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23164-we-live-for-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We live for books." -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
