<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/442114-gwen-perkins]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/442114-gwen-perkins" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 21:22:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251284-in-order-to-rise-from-its-own-ashes-a-phoenix</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 21:22:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gwen add a quote by Octavia Butler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251284-in-order-to-rise-from-its-own-ashes-a-phoenix]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In order to rise from its own ashes, a Phoenix first must burn." -- Octavia Butler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75165-if-they-give-you-ruled-paper-write-the-other-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 14:31:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gwen add a quote by Juan Ramon Jimenez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75165-if-they-give-you-ruled-paper-write-the-other-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If they give you ruled paper, write the other way." -- Juan Ramon Jimenez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111189-accept-the-children-the-way-we-accept-trees-with-gratitude-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 21:23:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gwen add a quote by Isabel Allende]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111189-accept-the-children-the-way-we-accept-trees-with-gratitude-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Accept the children the way we accept trees—with gratitude, because they are a blessing—but do not have expectations or desires. You don’t expect trees to change, you love them as they are." -- Isabel Allende]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85720-show-me-a-man-or-a-woman-alone-and-i-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 14:33:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gwen add a quote by Stephen King ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85720-show-me-a-man-or-a-woman-alone-and-i-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Show me a man or a woman alone and I'll show you a saint. Give me two and they'll fall in love. Give me three and they'll invent the charming thing we call 'society'. Give me four and they'll build a pyramid. Give me five and they'll make one an outcast. Give me six and they'll reinvent prejudice. Give me seven and in seven years they'll reinvent warfare. Man may have been made in the image of God, but human society was made in the image of His opposite number, and is always trying to get back home." -- Stephen King ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227321-never-forget-what-you-are-for-surely-the-world-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 14:33:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gwen add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227321-never-forget-what-you-are-for-surely-the-world-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never forget what you are, for surely the world will not. Make it your strength. Then it can never be your weakness. Armour yourself in it, and it will never be used to hurt you." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20292-there-is-a-kind-of-all-embracing-universality-evident-in-mother</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 14:34:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gwen add a quote by David James Duncan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20292-there-is-a-kind-of-all-embracing-universality-evident-in-mother]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[There is a] kind of all-embracing universality evident in Mother Teresa’s prayer: “May God break my heart so completely that the whole world falls in.” Not just fellow nuns, Catholics, Calcuttans, Indians. The whole world. It gives me pause to realize that, were such a prayer said by me and answered by God, I would afterward possess a heart so open that even hate-driven zealots would fall inside... [My] sense of the world as a gift, my sense of a grace operative in this world despite its terrors, propels me to allow the world to open my heart still wider, even if the openness comes by breaking—for I have seen the whole world fall into a few hearts, and nothing has ever struck me as more beautiful." -- David James Duncan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109817-rain-falls-on-everyone-lightning-strikes-some-what-cannot-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 14:35:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gwen add a quote by Mary Doria Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109817-rain-falls-on-everyone-lightning-strikes-some-what-cannot-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Rain falls on everyone, lightning strikes some. What cannot be changed is best forgotten. God made the world, and He saw that it was good. Not fair. Not happy. Not perfect. Good." -- Mary Doria Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141761-that-is-my-dilemma-because-if-i-was-led-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 14:35:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gwen add a quote by Mary Doria Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141761-that-is-my-dilemma-because-if-i-was-led-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...[That] is my dilemma. Because if I was led by God to love God, step by step, as it seemed, if I accept that the beauty and the rapture were real and true, the rest of it was God’s will too, and that gentlemen is cause for bitterness. But if I am simply a deluded ape who took a lot of old folktales far too seriously, then I brought all this on myself and my companions and the whole business becomes farcical, doesn’t it. The problem with atheism, I find, under these circumstances...is that I have no one to despise but myself. If, however, I choose to believe that God is &lt;i&gt;vicious&lt;/i&gt;, then at least I have the solace of hating God." -- Mary Doria Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265756-at-times-i-feel-as-if-i-had-lived-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 14:37:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gwen add a quote by Isabel Allende]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265756-at-times-i-feel-as-if-i-had-lived-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At times I feel as if I had lived all this before and that I have already written these very words, but I know it was not I: it was another woman, who kept her notebooks so that one day I could use them.  I write, she wrote, that memory is fragile and the space of a single life is brief, passing so quickly that we never get a chance to see the relationship between events; we cannot gauge the consequences of our acts, and we believe in the fiction of past, present, and future, but it may also be true that everything happens simultaneously. ... That's why my Grandmother Clara wrote in her notebooks, in order to see things in their true dimension and to defy her own poor memory." -- Isabel Allende]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/991-until-i-feared-i-would-lose-it-i-never-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 00:40:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gwen add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/991-until-i-feared-i-would-lose-it-i-never-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until I feared I would lose it, I never loved to read. One does not love breathing." -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335553-after-the-first-glass-of-absinthe-you-see-things-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 17:43:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gwen add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335553-after-the-first-glass-of-absinthe-you-see-things-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After the first glass of absinthe you see things as you wish they were. After the second you see them as they are not. Finally you see things as they really are, and that is the most horrible thing in the world. I mean disassociated. Take a top hat. You think you see it as it really is. But you don’t because you associate it with other things and ideas.If you had never heard of one before, and suddenly saw it alone, you’d be frightened, or you’d laugh. That is the effect absinthe has, and that is why it drives men mad. Three nights I sat up all night drinking absinthe, and thinking that I was singularly clear-headed and sane. The waiter came in and began watering the sawdust.The most wonderful flowers, tulips, lilies and roses, sprang up, and made a garden in the cafe. “Don’t you see them?” I said to him. “Mais non, monsieur, il n’y a rien." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
