<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/444985-edythe-cook]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/444985-edythe-cook" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 20:58:12 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7649-i-must-learn-to-love-the-fool-in-me--the-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 20:58:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Theodore I. Rubin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7649-i-must-learn-to-love-the-fool-in-me--the-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I must learn to love the fool in me--the one who feels too much, talks too much, takes too many chances, wins sometimes and loses often, lacks self-control, loves and hates, hurts and gets hurt, promises and breaks promises, laughs and cries. It alone protects me against that utterly self-controlled, masterful tyrant whom I also harbor and who would rob me of my human aliveness, humility, and dignity but for my Fool." -- Theodore I. Rubin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 20:59:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7096-listen-to-the-mustn-ts-child-listen-to-the-don-ts-listen</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 21:02:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Shel Silverstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7096-listen-to-the-mustn-ts-child-listen-to-the-don-ts-listen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen to the mustn'ts, child. Listen to the don'ts. Listen to the shouldn'ts, the impossibles, the won'ts. Listen to the never haves, then listen close to me... Anything can happen, child. Anything can be." -- Shel Silverstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3202-life-is-an-opportunity-benefit-from-it-life-is-beauty</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 21:02:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3202-life-is-an-opportunity-benefit-from-it-life-is-beauty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is an opportunity, benefit from it.
Life is beauty, admire it.
Life is a dream, realize it.
Life is a challenge, meet it.
Life is a duty, complete it.
Life is a game, play it.
Life is a promise, fulfill it.
Life is sorrow, overcome it.
Life is a song, sing it.
Life is a struggle, accept it.
Life is a tragedy, confront it.
Life is an adventure, dare it.
Life is luck, make it.
Life is too precious, do not destroy it.
Life is life, fight for it." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3616-i-am-nothing-special-of-this-i-am-sure-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 21:03:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3616-i-am-nothing-special-of-this-i-am-sure-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am nothing special, of this I am sure. I am a common man with common thoughts and I've led a common life. There are no monuments dedicated to me and my name will soon be forgotten, but I've loved another with all my heart and soul, and to me, this has always been enough.." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1280-you-can-go-through-life-and-make-new-friends-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 21:05:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Alexander McCall Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1280-you-can-go-through-life-and-make-new-friends-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can go through life and make new friends every year - every month practically - but there was never any substitute for those friendships of childhood that survive into adult years. Those are the ones in which we are bound to one another with hoops of steel." -- Alexander McCall Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170664-but-i-have-learned-that-you-make-your-own-happiness</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 00:57:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Emily Giffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170664-but-i-have-learned-that-you-make-your-own-happiness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I have learned that you make your own happiness, that part of going for what you want means losing something else. And when the stakes are high, the losses can be that much greater." -- Emily Giffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170994-love-and-friendship-they-are-what-make-us-who-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 01:00:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Emily Giffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170994-love-and-friendship-they-are-what-make-us-who-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love and friendship. They are what make us who we are, and what can change us, if we let them." -- Emily Giffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182621-when-you-are-in-a-relationship-you-are-aware-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 00:57:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Emily Giffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182621-when-you-are-in-a-relationship-you-are-aware-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you are in a relationship, you are aware that it might end. You might grow apart, find someone else, simply fall out of love. But a friendship isn't a zero-sum game, and as such, you assume that it will last forever, especially an old friendship. You take its permanence for grandted, whuch might be the very thing so dear about it." -- Emily Giffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182618-but-i-am-learning-that-perfection-isn-t-what-matters-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 00:58:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Emily Giffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182618-but-i-am-learning-that-perfection-isn-t-what-matters-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I am learning that perfection isn't what matters. In fact, it's the very thing that can destroy you if you let it." -- Emily Giffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170602-nothing-is-ever-perfect-it-is-what-you-make-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 00:58:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Emily Giffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170602-nothing-is-ever-perfect-it-is-what-you-make-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing is ever perfect. It is what you make of it." -- Emily Giffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299548-happiness-is-the-best-revenge-you-know-just-be-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 00:59:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Emily Giffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299548-happiness-is-the-best-revenge-you-know-just-be-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is the best revenge, you know? Just be happy. It's a choice." -- Emily Giffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350790-it-sucks-that-we-miss-people-like-that-you-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 19:14:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Rachel Hawkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350790-it-sucks-that-we-miss-people-like-that-you-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It sucks that we miss people like that. You think you've accepted that someone is out of your life, that you've grieved and it's over, and then bam. One little thing, and you feel like you've lost that person all over again." -- Rachel Hawkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 19:15:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41610-the-majority-of-us-lead-quiet-unheralded-lives-as-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 19:15:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Leo Buscaglia]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41610-the-majority-of-us-lead-quiet-unheralded-lives-as-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The majority of us lead quiet, unheralded lives as we pass through this world. There will most likely be no ticker-tape parades for us, no monuments created in our honor. But that does not lessen our possible impact, for there are scores of people waiting for someone just like us to come along; people who will appreciate our compassion, our unique talents. Someone who will live a happier life merely because we took the time to share what we had to give. Too often we underestimate the power of a touch, a smile, a kind word a listening ear, an honest compliment, or the smallest act of caring, all of which have a potential to turn a life around. It’s overwhelming to consider the continuous opportunities there are to make our love felt." -- Leo Buscaglia]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75485-the-most-courageous-act-is-still-to-think-for-yourself</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 19:17:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Coco Chanel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75485-the-most-courageous-act-is-still-to-think-for-yourself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most courageous act is still to think for yourself.  Aloud." -- Coco Chanel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6598-tell-the-truth-or-someone-will-tell-it-for-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 19:18:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Stephanie Klein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6598-tell-the-truth-or-someone-will-tell-it-for-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tell the truth, or someone will tell it for you." -- Stephanie Klein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 18:03:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155356-well-now-if-little-by-little-you-stop-loving-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 17:58:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155356-well-now-if-little-by-little-you-stop-loving-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, now
If little by little you stop loving me
I shall stop loving you
Little by little
If suddenly you forget me
Do not look for me
For I shall already have forgotten you

If you think it long and mad the wind of banners that passes through my life
And you decide to leave me at the shore of the heart where I have roots
Remember
That on that day, at that hour, I shall lift my arms
And my roots will set off to seek another land" -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144675-you-can-t-look-back---you-just-have-to-put</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 17:59:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144675-you-can-t-look-back---you-just-have-to-put]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can't look back - you just have to put the past behind you, and find something better in your future." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45978-even-though-you-may-want-to-move-forward-in-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 18:00:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Mary Manin Morrissey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45978-even-though-you-may-want-to-move-forward-in-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even though you may want to move forward in your life, you may have one foot on the brakes.  In order to be free, we must learn how to let go.  Release the hurt.  Release the fear.  Refuse to entertain your old pain.  The energy it takes to hang onto the past is holding you back from a new life.  What is it you would let go of today?" -- Mary Manin Morrissey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308031-you-can-close-your-eyes-to-the-things-you-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 18:00:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Tabitha Suzuma]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308031-you-can-close-your-eyes-to-the-things-you-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can close your eyes to the things you do not want to see, but you cannot close your heart to the things you do not want to feel." -- Tabitha Suzuma]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56789-maybe-our-girlfriends-are-our-soulmates-and-guys-are-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 18:04:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Candace Bushnell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56789-maybe-our-girlfriends-are-our-soulmates-and-guys-are-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe our girlfriends are our soulmates and guys are just people to have fun with." -- Candace Bushnell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2102-love-does-not-consist-of-gazing-at-each-other-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 18:10:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2102-love-does-not-consist-of-gazing-at-each-other-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love does not consist of gazing at each other, but in looking outward together in the same direction." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83175-all-grown-ups-were-once-children-but-only-few-of-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 18:10:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83175-all-grown-ups-were-once-children-but-only-few-of-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All grown-ups were once children... but only few of them remember it." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79349-you---you-alone-will-have-the-stars-as-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 18:10:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79349-you---you-alone-will-have-the-stars-as-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You - you alone will have the stars as no one else has them...In one of the stars I shall be living. In one of them I shall be laughing. And so it will be as if all the stars were laughing, when you look at the sky at night...You - only you - will have stars that can laugh." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87476-a-goal-without-a-plan-is-just-a-wish</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 18:11:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87476-a-goal-without-a-plan-is-just-a-wish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A goal without a plan is just a wish." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39718-what-saves-a-man-is-to-take-a-step-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 18:11:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39718-what-saves-a-man-is-to-take-a-step-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What saves a man is to take a step. Then another step." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19483-on-ne-voit-bien-qu-avec-le-c-ur-l-essentiel-est-invisible</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 18:11:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19483-on-ne-voit-bien-qu-avec-le-c-ur-l-essentiel-est-invisible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On ne voit bien qu'avec le cœur. L'essentiel est invisible pour les yeux." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219769-voici-mon-secret-il-est-tr-s-simple-on-ne-voit</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 18:12:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edythe add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219769-voici-mon-secret-il-est-tr-s-simple-on-ne-voit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Voici mon secret. Il est très simple: on ne voit bien qu'avec le cœur. L'essentiel est invisible pour les yeux." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
