<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/446092-gina]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/446092-gina" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 16:19:28 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252089-beware-of-any-work-for-god-that-causes-or-allows</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 16:19:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Oswald Chambers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252089-beware-of-any-work-for-god-that-causes-or-allows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beware of any work for God that causes or allows you to avoid concentrating on Him. A great number of Christian workers worship their work. The only concern of Christian workers should be their concentration on God. This will mean that all the other boundaries of life, whether they are mental, moral, or spiritual limits, are completely free with the freedom God gives His child; that is, a worshiping child, not a wayward one. A worker who lacks this serious controlling emphasis of concentration on God is apt to become overly burdened by his work. He is a slave to his own limits, having no freedom of his body, mind, or spirit. Consequently, he becomes burned out and defeated. There is no freedom and no delight in life at all. His nerves, mind, and heart are so overwhelmed that God’s blessing cannot rest on him." -- Oswald Chambers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/555902-ultimately-one-has-to-pity-these-poor-souls-who-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2014 15:27:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by David Ives]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/555902-ultimately-one-has-to-pity-these-poor-souls-who-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ultimately one has to pity these poor souls who know every secret about writing, directing, designing, producing, and acting but are stuck in those miserable day jobs writing reviews. Will somebody help them, please?" -- David Ives]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
