<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/448936-robin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/448936-robin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2008 18:39:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10894-so-we-dream-on-thus-we-invent-our-lives-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2008 18:39:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robin add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10894-so-we-dream-on-thus-we-invent-our-lives-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So we dream on.  Thus we invent our lives.  We give ourselves a sainted mother, we make our father a hero; and someone’s older brother and someone’s older sister – they become our heroes too.  We invent what we love and what we fear.  There is always a brave lost brother – and a little lost sister, too.  We dream on and on: the best hotel, the perfect family, the resort life.  And our dreams escape us almost as vividly as we can imagine them…  That’s what happens, like it or not.  And because that’s what happens, this is what we need: we need a good, smart bear…  Coach Bob knew it all along: you’ve got to get obsessed and stay obsessed. You have to keep passing the open windows." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2008 19:06:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robin add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finish each day and be done with it. You have done what you could.  Some blunders and absurdities no doubt crept in; forget them as soon as you can. Tomorrow is a new day.  You shall begin it serenely and with too high a spirit to be encumbered with your old nonsense." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
