<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/454237-hiyasmin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/454237-hiyasmin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 May 2008 08:48:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29875-the-world-is-a-dangerous-place-to-live-not-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2008 08:48:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29875-the-world-is-a-dangerous-place-to-live-not-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is a dangerous place to live, not because of the people who are evil, but because of the people who don't do anything about it." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24956-the-most-erroneous-stories-are-those-we-think-we-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:44:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24956-the-most-erroneous-stories-are-those-we-think-we-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most erroneous stories are those we think we know best - and therefore never scrutinize or question." -- Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1216-we-pass-through-this-world-but-once-few-tragedies-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:45:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1216-we-pass-through-this-world-but-once-few-tragedies-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We pass through this world but once. Few tragedies can be more extensive than the stunting of life, few injustices deeper than the denial of an opportunity to strive or even to hope, by a limit imposed from without, but falsely identified as lying within." -- Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99345-i-am-somehow-less-interested-in-the-weight-and-convolutions</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:45:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99345-i-am-somehow-less-interested-in-the-weight-and-convolutions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am, somehow, less interested in the weight and convolutions of Einstein’s brain than in the near certainty that people of equal talent have lived and died in cotton fields and sweatshops." -- Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4703-the-aim-of-life-is-to-live-and-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:46:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4703-the-aim-of-life-is-to-live-and-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The aim of life is to live, and to live means to be aware, joyously, drunkenly, serenely, divinely aware." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4786-every-day-we-slaughter-our-finest-impulses-that-is-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:46:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4786-every-day-we-slaughter-our-finest-impulses-that-is-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every day we slaughter our finest impulses. That is why we get a heartache when we read those lines written by the hand of a master and recognize them as our own, as the tender shoots which we stifled because we lacked the faith to believe in our own powers, our own criterion of truth and beauty. Every man, when he gets quiet, when he becomes desperately honest with himself, is capable of uttering profound truths. We all derive from the same source. there is no mystery about the origin of things. We are all part of creation, all kings, all poets, all musicians; we have only to open up, only to discover what is already there." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15244-there-were-always-in-me-two-women-at-least-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:50:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15244-there-were-always-in-me-two-women-at-least-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There were always in me, two women at least, one woman desperate and bewildered, who felt she was drowning and another who would leap into a scene, as upon a stage, conceal her true emotions because they were weaknesses, helplessness, despair, and present to the world only a smile, an eagerness, curiosity, enthusiasm, interest." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45328-there-are-two-ways-to-reach-me-by-way-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:50:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45328-there-are-two-ways-to-reach-me-by-way-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two ways to reach me: by way of kisses or by way of the imagination. But there is a hierarchy: the kisses alone don't work." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71485-the-greatest-feminists-have-also-been-the-greatest-lovers-i-m</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:50:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Erica Jong]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71485-the-greatest-feminists-have-also-been-the-greatest-lovers-i-m]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greatest feminists have also been the greatest lovers. I'm thinking not only of Mary Wollstonecraft and her daughter Mary Shelley, but of Anais Nin, Edna St. Vincent Millay, and of course Sappho. You cannot divide creative juices from human juices. And as long as juicy women are equated with bad women, we will err on the side of being bad." -- Erica Jong]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31920-i-am-the-most-tired-woman-in-the-world-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:50:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31920-i-am-the-most-tired-woman-in-the-world-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the most tired woman in the world. I am tired when I get up. Life requires an effort I cannot make. Please give me that heavy book. I need to put something heavy like that on top of my head. I have to place my feet under the pillows always, so as to be able to stay on earth. Otherwise I feel myself going away, going away at a tremendous speed, on account of my lightness. I know that I am dead. As soon as I utter a phrase my sincerity dies, becomes a lie whose coldness chills me. Don't say anything, because I see that you understand me, and I am afraid of your understanding. I have such a fear of finding another like myself, and such a desire to find one! I am so utterly lonely, but I also have such a fear that my isolation be broken through, and I no longer be the head and ruler of my universe. I am in great terror of your understanding by which you penetrate into my world; and then I stand revealed and I have to share my kingdom with you." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39899-man-can-never-know-the-loneliness-a-woman-knows-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:50:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39899-man-can-never-know-the-loneliness-a-woman-knows-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man can never know the loneliness a woman knows. Man lies in the woman's womb only to gather strength, he nourishes himself from this fusion, and then he rises and goes into the world, into his work, into battle, into art. He is not lonely. He is busy. The memory of the swim in amniotic fluid gives him energy, completion. Woman may be busy too, but she feels empty. Sensuality for her is not only a wave of pleasure in which she is bathed, and a charge of electric joy at contact with another. When man lies in her womb, she is fulfilled, each act of love a taking of man within her, an act of birth and rebirth, of child rearing and man bearing. Man lies in her womb and is reborn each time anew with a desire to act, to &lt;i&gt;be&lt;/i&gt;. But for woman, the climax is not in the birth, but in the moment man rests inside of her." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8782-i-have-no-brakes-on-analysis-is-for-those-who-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:51:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8782-i-have-no-brakes-on-analysis-is-for-those-who-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have no brakes on...analysis is for those who are paralyzed by life." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84169-anxiety-is-love-s-greatest-killer-it-makes-others-feel-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:51:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84169-anxiety-is-love-s-greatest-killer-it-makes-others-feel-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anxiety is love's greatest killer. It makes others feel as you might when a drowning man holds on to you. You want to save him, but you know he will strangle you with his panic." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18405-and-sometimes-i-believe-your-relentless-analysis-of-june-leaves</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:51:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18405-and-sometimes-i-believe-your-relentless-analysis-of-june-leaves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And sometimes I believe your relentless analysis of June leaves something out, which is your feeling for her beyond knowledge, or in spite of knowledge. I often see how you sob over what you destroy, how you want to stop and just worship; and you do stop, and then a moment later you are at it again with a knife, like a surgeon.
What will you do after you have revealed all there is to know about June? Truth. What ferocity in your quest of it. You destroy and you suffer. In some strange way I am not with you, I am against you. We are destined to hold two truths. I love you and I fight you. And you, the same. We will be stronger for it, each of us, stronger with our love and our hate. When you caricature and nail down and tear apart, I hate you. I want to answer you, not with weak or stupid poetry but with a wonder as strong as your reality. I want to fight your surgical knife with all the occult and magical forces of the world." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105767-like-all-dreamers-i-confuse-disenchantment-with-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:52:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Jean Paul Sarte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105767-like-all-dreamers-i-confuse-disenchantment-with-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like all dreamers I confuse disenchantment with truth." -- Jean Paul Sarte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8522-in-a-higher-phase-of-communist-society-after-the-enslaving</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:54:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Karl Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8522-in-a-higher-phase-of-communist-society-after-the-enslaving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a higher phase of communist society, after the enslaving subordination of the individual to the division of labor, and therewith also the antithesis between mental and physical labor, has vanished; after labor has become not only a means of life but life's prime want; after the productive forces have also increased with the all-around development of the individual, and all the springs of co-operative wealth flow more abundantly—only then can the narrow horizon of bourgeois right be crossed in its entirety and society inscribe on its banners: From each according to his ability, to each according to his needs!" -- Karl Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114782-men-make-their-own-history-but-they-do-not-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:54:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Karl Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114782-men-make-their-own-history-but-they-do-not-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men make their own history, but they do not make it as they please; they do not make it under self-selected circumstances, but under circumstances existing already, given and transmitted from the past. The tradition of all dead generations weighs like a nightmare on the brains of the living. And just as they seem to be occupied with revolutionizing themselves and things, creating something that did not exist before, precisely in such epochs of revolutionary crisis they anxiously conjure up the spirits of the past to their service, borrowing from them names, battle slogans, and costumes in order to present this new scene in world history in time-honored disguise and borrowed language." -- Karl Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75939-a-specter-is-haunting-europe-the-specter-of-communism-all-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:55:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Karl Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75939-a-specter-is-haunting-europe-the-specter-of-communism-all-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A specter is haunting Europe—the specter of Communism. All the powers of old Europe have entered into a holy alliance to exorcise this specter; Pope and Czar, Metternich and Guizot, French radicals and German police spies.

Where is the party in opposition that has not been decried as Communistic by its opponents in power? Where the opposition that has not hurled back the branding reproach of Communism, against the more advanced opposition parties, as well as against its reactionary adversaries?

Two things result from this fact.

I. Communism is already acknowledged by all European powers to be in itself a power.

II. It is high time that Communists should openly, in the face of the whole world, publish their views, their aims, their tendencies, and meet this nursery tale of the Specter of Communism with a Manifesto of the party itself." -- Karl Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13238-dear-future-generations-please-accept-our-apologies-we-were-rolling</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:56:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut, Jr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13238-dear-future-generations-please-accept-our-apologies-we-were-rolling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dear future generations: Please accept our apologies. We were rolling drunk on petroleum." -- Kurt Vonnegut, Jr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65-maturity-is-a-bitter-disappointment-for-which-no-remedy-exists</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:56:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65-maturity-is-a-bitter-disappointment-for-which-no-remedy-exists]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maturity is a bitter disappointment for which no remedy exists, unless laughter could be said to remedy anything." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2308-one-of-the-few-good-things-about-modern-times-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:58:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2308-one-of-the-few-good-things-about-modern-times-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the few good things about modern times: If you die horribly on television, you will not have died in vain. You will have entertained us." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16160-but-who-can-say-what-s-best-that-s-why-you-need</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:58:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16160-but-who-can-say-what-s-best-that-s-why-you-need]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But who can say what's best? That's why you need to grab whatever chance you have of happiness where you find it, and not worry about other people too much. My experience tells me that we get no more than two or three such chances in a life time, and if we let them go, we regret it for the rest of our lives." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22433-to-know-one-s-own-state-is-not-a-simple-matter</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 06:59:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22433-to-know-one-s-own-state-is-not-a-simple-matter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To know one’s own state is not a simple matter. One cannot look directly at one’s own face with one’s own eyes, for example. One has no choice but to look at one’s reflection in the mirror. Through experience, we come to believe that the image is correct, but that is all." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408160-all-their-life-in-this-world-and-all-their-adventures</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 12:52:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408160-all-their-life-in-this-world-and-all-their-adventures]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All their life in this world and all their adventures had only been the cover and the title page: now at last they were beginning Chapter One of the Great Story which no one on earth has read: which goes on for ever: in which every chapter is better than the one before." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/775591-mas-madaling-mamatay-kaysa-mabuhay-tumataas-ang-halaga-ng-pagkain</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2014 05:17:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Jun Cruz Reyes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/775591-mas-madaling-mamatay-kaysa-mabuhay-tumataas-ang-halaga-ng-pagkain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mas madaling mamatay kaysa mabuhay, tumataas ang halaga ng pagkain habang bumababa naman ang halaga ng buhay." -- Jun Cruz Reyes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44630-when-the-heart-speaks-the-mind-finds-it-indecent-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2014 05:18:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44630-when-the-heart-speaks-the-mind-finds-it-indecent-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the heart speaks, the mind finds it indecent to object." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169843-there-are-a-lot-of-children-in-afghanistan-but-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2014 05:21:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169843-there-are-a-lot-of-children-in-afghanistan-but-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are a lot of children in Afghanistan, but little childhood." -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/319450-when-all-else-fails-philosophize</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2014 05:59:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/319450-when-all-else-fails-philosophize]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When all else fails, philosophize." -- J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1033962-fiction-allows-us-to-slide-into-these-other-heads-these</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 06:32:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1033962-fiction-allows-us-to-slide-into-these-other-heads-these]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fiction allows us to slide into these other heads, these other places, and look out through other eyes. And then in the tale we stop before we die, or we die vicariously and unharmed, and in the world beyond the tale we turn the page or close the book, and we resume our lives. A life that is, like any other, unlike any other." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189429-go-to-old-delhi-and-look-at-the-way-they-keep</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 13:09:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hiyasmin add a quote by Aravind Adiga]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189429-go-to-old-delhi-and-look-at-the-way-they-keep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Go to Old Delhi,and look at the way they keep chickens there in the market. Hundred of pale hens and brightly colored roosters, stuffed tightly into wire-mesh cages. They see the organs of their brothers lying around them.They know they are next, yet they cannot rebel. They do not try to get out of the coop. The very same thing is done with humans in this country." -- Aravind Adiga]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
