<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/455137-kira-mead]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/455137-kira-mead" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 19:27:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18277-the-minute-i-heard-my-first-love-story-i-started</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 19:27:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kira add a quote by Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18277-the-minute-i-heard-my-first-love-story-i-started]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The minute I heard my first love story,
I started looking for you, not knowing
how blind that was.
Lovers don't finally meet somewhere.
They're in each other all along." -- Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 19:34:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kira add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 19:37:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kira add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that's what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that is holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life.  

A true soul mate is probably the most important person you'll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake.  But to live with a soul mate forever?  Nah. Too painful.  Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then leave.  

A soul mates purpose is to shake you up, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light can get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you have to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57741-dumbledore-watched-her-fly-away-and-as-her-silvery-glow</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 19:40:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kira add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57741-dumbledore-watched-her-fly-away-and-as-her-silvery-glow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dumbledore watched her fly away, and as her silvery glow faded he turned back to Snape, and his eyes were full of tears.
&quot;After all this time?&quot;
&quot;Always,&quot; said Snape." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59937-everyone-at-some-point-in-their-lives-wakes-up-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 19:43:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kira add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59937-everyone-at-some-point-in-their-lives-wakes-up-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone, at some point in their lives, wakes up in the middle of the night with the feeling that they are all alone in the world, and that nobody loves them now and that nobody will ever love them, and that they will never have a decent night's sleep again and will spend their lives wandering blearily around a loveless landscape, hoping desperately that their circumstances will improve, but suspecting, in their heart of hearts, that they will remain unloved forever. The best thing to do in these circumstances is to wake somebody else up, so that they can feel this way, too." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26620-we-waste-time-looking-for-the-perfect-lover-instead-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 19:50:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kira add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26620-we-waste-time-looking-for-the-perfect-lover-instead-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We waste time looking for the perfect lover, instead of creating the perfect love." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
