<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/455531-colin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/455531-colin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 16:37:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/436338-in-his-madness-and-his-blindness-he-was-lear-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 16:37:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Colin add a quote by Susanna Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/436338-in-his-madness-and-his-blindness-he-was-lear-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In his madness and his blindness he was Lear and Gloucester combined." -- Susanna Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6766-i-can-listen-no-longer-in-silence-i-must-speak</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 17:06:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Colin add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6766-i-can-listen-no-longer-in-silence-i-must-speak]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can listen no longer in silence.  I must speak to you by such means as are within my reach.  You pierce my soul.  I am half agony, half hope.  Tell me not that I am too late, that such precious feelings are gone for ever.  I offer myself to you again with a heart even more your own than when you almost broke it, eight years and a half ago.  Dare not say that man forgets sooner than  woman, that his love has an earlier death.  I have loved none but you. Unjust I may have been, weak and resentful I have been, but never inconstant.  You alone have brought me to Bath. For you alone, I think and plan.  Have you not seen this? Can you fail to have understood my wishes?  I had not waited even these ten days, could I have read your feelings, as I think you must have penetrated mine.  I can hardly write.  I am every instant hearing something which overpowers me.  You sink your voice, but I can distinguish the tones of that voice when they would be lost on others. Too good, too excellent creature!  You do us justice, indeed. You do believe that there is true attachment and constancy among men. Believe it to be most fervent, most undeviating, in F. W.

I must go, uncertain of my fate; but I shall return hither, or follow your party, as soon as possible.  A word, a look, will be enough to decide whether I enter your father's house this evening or never." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108191-she-wore-a-gown-the-color-of-storms-shadows-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 17:08:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Colin add a quote by Susanna Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108191-she-wore-a-gown-the-color-of-storms-shadows-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She wore a gown the color of storms, shadows, and rain and a necklace of broken promises and regrets." -- Susanna Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491983-there-is-no-nature-that-exists-devoid-of-nurture-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 14:50:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Colin add a quote by Matt Ridley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491983-there-is-no-nature-that-exists-devoid-of-nurture-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no nature that exists devoid of nurture; there is no nurture that develops without nature. To say otherwise is like saying that the area of a field is determined by its length but not its width. Every behavior is the product of an instinct trained by experience. 

The study of human beings remained resolutely unreformed by these ideas until a few years ago. Even now, most anthropologists and social scientists are firmly committed to the view that evolution has nothing to tell them. Human bodies are products of &quot;culture,&quot; and human culture does not reflect human nature, but the reverse. This restricts social scientists to investigation only differences between cultures and between individuals--and to exaggerating them. Yet what is most interesting to me about human beings is the things that are the same, not what is different--things like grammatical language, hierarchy, romantic love, sexual jealousy, long-term bongs between the genders (&quot;marriage&quot;, in a sense). These are trainable instincts peculiar to out species and are just as surely the products of evolution as eyes and thumbs." -- Matt Ridley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 14:59:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Colin add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The person, be it gentleman or lady, who has not pleasure in a good novel, must be intolerably stupid." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21847-there-is-nothing-i-would-not-do-for-those-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 14:59:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Colin add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21847-there-is-nothing-i-would-not-do-for-those-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing I would not do for those who are really my friends. I have no notion of loving people by halves, it is not my nature." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
