<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/45902-margaret-feinberg]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/45902-margaret-feinberg" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 11:59:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419999-while-some-dismiss-the-bible-as-a-dusty-old-book</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 11:59:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419999-while-some-dismiss-the-bible-as-a-dusty-old-book]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["While some dismiss the Bible as a dusty old book, I view its pages as portals to adventure. Not only is the book chock-full of clever plots and compelling stories, but it’s laced with historical insights and literary beauty. When I open the Scripture, I imagine myself exploring an ancient kingdom . . . With every encounter, I learn something new about their life journeys and am reminded that the Bible is more than a record of the human quest for God: it’s the revelation of God’s quest for us.” - Scouting the Divine" -- Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420001-jesus-knew-that-many-of-his-listeners-believed-the-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 12:03:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420001-jesus-knew-that-many-of-his-listeners-believed-the-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jesus knew that many of his listeners believed the old wineskin (or way of doing things) was good enough. They were comfortable with their beliefs and practices, but Jesus hadn't come to patch up old religious traditions. He was offering a new garment, a new wineskin, a way of life that didn't abolish the old ways, but fulfilled them.

The teaching illuminated my own need to remain pliable before God. I realize that I must have a softer housing for my growing faith, one that can flex and change as God is at work inside of me. All too often I find myself clinging to that which is comfortable and familiar, rather than embracing the challenges that emerge with change and growth. Sometimes I shy away from people who have strong views that differ from mine, even though sharing a great conversation... could temper both our viewpoints and deepen our relationship. Why do I run away from strong opinions and potential conflict? Am I too comfortable and unwilling to change? Such a realization highlights the need for the Spirit in my life not just to discern and distinguish, but also to illuminate and invite me to move forward into the fullness of life with him.&quot; -Scouting the Divine" -- Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420003-and-god-did-not-just-ask-for-the-perfect-sheep</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 12:06:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420003-and-god-did-not-just-ask-for-the-perfect-sheep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And God did not just ask for the perfect sheep; He also wanted its wool.  Deuteronomy 18:4 instructs shepherds to give the first shearing of the sheep as on offering to God.  Above the crackling warmth radiating from the stove, I read the verse aloud to Lynne.  &quot;Is a first shearing a once-in-a-lifetime offering?&quot;  I asked.  &quot;Yes, everybody wants the first shearing, especially if it's from one of your best lambs.  The first shearing is the finest fleese that's used to the best clothes...to ask for that is a real sacrifice.&quot; ... For the first time in a long while, maybe ever, I had felt with my own hands what God desired from sacrifice.  It was nothing like what I expected...In asking for the first fleece, God isn't asking for the biggest.  He wants to smallest and the softest.  He doesn't want more-He wants the best.&quot; -Scouting the Divine" -- Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420005-scripture-breathes-wisdom-like-we-breathe-oxygen-it-can-t-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 12:12:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420005-scripture-breathes-wisdom-like-we-breathe-oxygen-it-can-t-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Scripture breathes wisdom like we breathe oxygen. It can't not. Through Scripture, God reveals himself. This wisdom cannot be captured, let alone contained, on a neon bumper sticker or rubber bracelet. Wisdom itself invites us to go deeper- right into a relationship with God himself.

Through wisdom, we learn to love God and love what he loves. We find rich counsel on the life we were meant for- in our families, communities, and world. We discover our personal responsibilities to others. And we unearth how to put love into action.&quot; -Organic God" -- Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420010-i-call-them-sacred-echoes-because-i-noticed-that-throughout</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 12:21:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420010-i-call-them-sacred-echoes-because-i-noticed-that-throughout]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I call them sacred echoes because I noticed that throughout my relationships, daily life, and study, the same scripturally sound idea or phrase or word will keep reappearing until I can no longer avoid its presence.&quot; -The Sacred Echo" -- Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420011-and-like-an-echo-god-often-uses-the-repetitive-events</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 12:22:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420011-and-like-an-echo-god-often-uses-the-repetitive-events]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And like an echo, God often uses the repetitive events and themes in daily life to get my attention and draw me closer to himself.&quot; - The Sacred Echo" -- Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420026-slowly-god-is-opening-my-eyes-to-needs-all-around</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 12:34:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420026-slowly-god-is-opening-my-eyes-to-needs-all-around]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Slowly, God is opening my eyes to needs all around me. In Scripture, God revisits this issue of caring for the poor- an echo that repeats itself from Genesis to Revelation. The Bible acknowledges that the poor will always be part of society, but God takes on their cause. The Mosaic law of the Old Testament is filled with regulations to prevent and eliminate poverty. The poor were given the right to glean- to take produce from the unharvested edges of the fields, a portion of the tithes, and a daily wage. The law prevented permanent slavery by releasing Jewish bondsmen and women on the sabbatical and Jubilee year and forbade charging interest on loans. In one of his most tender acts, God made sure that the poor- the aliens, widows, and orphans- were all invited to the feasts." -- Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420480-whenever-god-thinks-of-you-he-has-your-best-interests</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 11:34:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420480-whenever-god-thinks-of-you-he-has-your-best-interests]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever God thinks of you, he has your best interests in mind; he has plans to take you further, deeper, and higher than you ever dreamed. This process begins when you seek God and spend time with him. Look for every opportunity to know God. Consider your daily schedule. What does it include? A workout at the gym? A trip to the post office? A lunch hour? A commute? Look for ways to include God in your activities. Invite God to accompany you by talking together. Look for moments- even if it's only ten or twenty seconds- to steal away with him. God will reward your efforts as you reshape your inner life to be focused around him. As you seek God, you will find yourself abiding in him.&quot; -Hungry for God" -- Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420490-one-of-my-favorite-prayers-is-god-how-can-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 11:46:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420490-one-of-my-favorite-prayers-is-god-how-can-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of my favorite prayers is God, how can I love on you today? As I sit in silence of those words, sometimes I'll feel compelled to sing or read a passage of Scripture, or I'll be reminded of someone with a need I can meet; but on some of the most meaningful days, God simply says, just be with me. I sit in the silence and enjoy stillness with God. No agenda. No words. No words. No challenge. No correction or instruction. Just being together. In those moments, I'm reminded that the heart of faith is simply being with God. I sense God's love. Some of my best friendships reach a level at which we can sit together without having to say anything and still enjoy each other's presence. The same is true for God, and I love to experience that depth of love in my relationship with Christ.&quot; -Hungry for God" -- Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420523-god-is-constantly-on-the-move-i-cannot-stay-where</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 13:03:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420523-god-is-constantly-on-the-move-i-cannot-stay-where]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God is constantly on the move. I cannot stay where I am and follow God at the same time; responding requires movement.&quot; -Hungry for God" -- Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420525-hunger-for-god-compels-us-to-seek-the-lord-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 13:09:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margaret add a quote by Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420525-hunger-for-god-compels-us-to-seek-the-lord-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hunger for God compels us to seek the Lord. At times our desire for God overcomes our physical desires, and the ache for God is palpable. Throughout the Scriptures, God is faithful to reward those who search for him. Written during one of King David's low points, while living on the run in the wilderness, he cries, &quot;Oh God, you are my God, earnestly I seek you; my soul thirsts for you, my body longs for you, in a dry and weary land where there is no water.&quot; Though David hides in the wilderness, he doesn't stay there physically or spiritually. When we seek God with our whole hearts and souls, he promises to reveal himself to us.&quot; -Hungry for God" -- Margaret Feinberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
