<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/461596-carrie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/461596-carrie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 14:50:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37658-but-you-won-t-abdicate-of-course-not-it-s-my-duty</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 14:50:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Mark Helprin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37658-but-you-won-t-abdicate-of-course-not-it-s-my-duty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But you won’t abdicate.&quot;
Of course not. It’s my duty to go on, to maintain the line. I can’t possibly fail in that. It’s as if you and I were throwing a ball back and forth to establish a record, and had been doing so for a millennium. You cannot drop a ball that has remained airborne through good effort for most of a thousand years. You cannot stop an unlikely heart that has been beating for so long. I would rather die than betray continuity, for its own sake if for nothing else. And Britain needs a king, just as it needs motormen and cooks and a prime minister. Just as it needs soldiers who will die for it if they must. It’s my job, or it will be, but you should know that I’ve never wanted it. I was only born to it, as if with a deformity, to which I hope I can respond with grace.&quot;
Fredericka had been running her finger over the carpet, tracing a pattern in the way children do when they have learnt something overwhelming and are moved, but cannot say so. Freddy expected her to look up, with tears, and that in this moment she might have begun the long and arduous process of becoming a queen. She was so beautiful. To embrace her now, with high emotion flowing from her physical majesty, was all he wanted in the world. Her finger stopped moving, and she turned her eyes to him.
Freddy?&quot;
Yes?&quot; he answered.
What’s raw egg? I read a recipe in She that called for a cup of raw egg. What is that?&quot;
After a long silence, Freddy asked, &quot;Which part of the formulation escapes you? Egg? Raw? The link between the two?&quot;
The two what?&quot;
Fredericka?&quot;
Yes, Freddy?&quot;
Would you like to go dancing?&quot;
Oh, yes Freddy!&quot;
Come then. We will." -- Mark Helprin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445721-skip-meeting-him-the-butterflies-the-pounding-heart-the-blushing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 12:40:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Laini Taylor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445721-skip-meeting-him-the-butterflies-the-pounding-heart-the-blushing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Skip meeting him? The butterflies, the pounding heart, the blushing? The part where you enter each other's magnetic fields for the first time, and it's like invisble lines of energy are drawing you together-" -- Laini Taylor]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
