<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/46194-rachel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/46194-rachel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 23:03:40 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84202-to-love-is-good-too-love-being-difficult-for-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 23:03:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84202-to-love-is-good-too-love-being-difficult-for-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love is good, too: love being difficult. For one human being to love another: that is perhaps the most difficult of all our tasks, the ultimate, the last test and proof, the work for which all other work is but preparation...Love is a high inducement to the individual to ripen, to become something in himself, to become world for himself for another's sake, it is a great exacting claim upon him, something that chooses him out and calls him to vast things." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64052-let-life-happen-to-you-believe-me-life-is-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 23:04:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Rainer Marie Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64052-let-life-happen-to-you-believe-me-life-is-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let life happen to you. Believe me: life is in the right, always." -- Rainer Marie Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140809-only-someone-who-is-ready-for-everything-who-doesn-t-exclude</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 23:04:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140809-only-someone-who-is-ready-for-everything-who-doesn-t-exclude]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["only someone who is ready for everything, who doesn't exclude any experience, even the most incomprehensible, will live the relationship with another person as something alive and will himself sound the depths of his own being." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15303-ah-how-good-it-is-to-be-among-people-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 23:04:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15303-ah-how-good-it-is-to-be-among-people-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ah, how good it is to be among people who are reading!" -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9371-the-purpose-of-life-is-to-be-defeated-by-greater</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 23:04:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9371-the-purpose-of-life-is-to-be-defeated-by-greater]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The purpose of life is to be defeated by greater and greater things." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102204-it-seems-to-me-that-almost-all-our-sadnesses-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 23:04:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102204-it-seems-to-me-that-almost-all-our-sadnesses-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seems to me that almost all our sadnesses are moments of tension, which we feel as paralysis because we no longer hear our astonished emotions living. Because we are alone with the unfamiliar presence that has entered us; because everything we trust and are used to is for a moment taken away from us; because we stand in the midst of a transition where we cannot remain standing. That is why the sadness passes: the new presence inside us, the presence that has been added, has entered our heart, has gone into its innermost chamber and is no longer even there, - is already in our bloodstream. And we don't know what it was. We could easily be made to believe that nothing happened, and yet we have changed, as a house that a guest has entered changes. We can't say who has come, perhaps we will never know, but many signs indicate that the future enters us in this way in order to be transformed in us, long before it happens. And that is why it is so important to be solitary and attentive when one is sad: because the seemingly uneventful and motionless moment when our future steps into us is so much closer to life than that other loud and accidental point of time when it happens to us as if from outside. The quieter we are, the more patient and open we are in our sadnesses, the more deeply and serenely the new presence can enter us, and the more we can make it our own, the more it becomes our fate." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140777-therefore-dear-sir-love-your-solitude-and-try-to-sing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 23:05:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140777-therefore-dear-sir-love-your-solitude-and-try-to-sing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Therefore, dear Sir, love your solitude and try to sing out with the pain it causes you. For those who are near you are far away... and this shows that the space around you is beginning to grow vast.... be happy about your growth, in which of course you can't take anyone with you, and be gentle with those who stay behind; be confident and calm in front of them and don't torment them with your doubts and don't frighten them with your faith or joy, which they wouldn't be able to comprehend. Seek out some simple and true feeling of what you have in common with them, which doesn't necessarily have to alter when you yourself change again and again; when you see them, love life in a form that is not your own and be indulgent toward those who are growing old, who are afraid of the aloneness that you trust.... and don't expect any understanding; but believe in a love that is being stored up for you like an inheritance, and have faith that in this love there is a strength and a blessing so large that you can travel as far as you wish without having to step outside it." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/935-we-need-in-love-to-practice-only-this-letting-each</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 23:05:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/935-we-need-in-love-to-practice-only-this-letting-each]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We need, in love, to practice only this: letting each other go. For holding on comes easily; we do not need to learn it." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 23:05:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be patient toward all that is unsolved in your heart and try to love the questions themselves, like locked rooms and like books that are now written in a very foreign tongue. Do not now seek the answers, which cannot be given you because you would not be able to live them. And the point is, to live everything. Live the questions now. Perhaps you will then gradually, without noticing it, live along some distant day into the answer." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
