<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/46284-shireen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/46284-shireen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 02:00:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408630-if-you-are-kind-people-may-accuse-you-of-selfish</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 02:00:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408630-if-you-are-kind-people-may-accuse-you-of-selfish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are kind, people may accuse you of selfish, ulterior motives: Be kind anyway. 

If you are successful you will win some false friends and true enemies: Succeed anyway. 

If you are honest and frank people will try to cheat you: Be honest anyway. 

What you spend years building, someone could destroy overnight: Build anyway. 

If you find serenity and happiness, they may be jealous of you: Be happy anyway. 

The good you do today, will often be forgotten by tomorrow: Do good anyway. 

Give the world the best you have, and it may never be enough: Give your best anyway." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/923-always-do-what-is-right-it-will-gratify-half-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:09:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/923-always-do-what-is-right-it-will-gratify-half-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Always do what is right. It will gratify half of mankind and astound the other." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181694-life-is-short-break-the-rules-forgive-quickly-kiss-slowly</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:09:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181694-life-is-short-break-the-rules-forgive-quickly-kiss-slowly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is short, Break the Rules.
Forgive quickly, Kiss SLOWLY.
Love truly. Laugh uncontrollably
And never regret ANYTHING
That makes you smile." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:11:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:12:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50321-whatever-happens-around-you-don-t-take-it-personally-nothing-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:12:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Don Miguel Ruiz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50321-whatever-happens-around-you-don-t-take-it-personally-nothing-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever happens around you, don't take it personally... Nothing other people do is because of you.  It is because of themselves." -- Don Miguel Ruiz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4339-is-it-so-bad-then-to-be-misunderstood-pythagoras-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:12:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4339-is-it-so-bad-then-to-be-misunderstood-pythagoras-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is it so bad, then, to be misunderstood? Pythagoras was misunderstood, and Socrates, and Jesus, and Luther, and Copernicus, and Galileo, and Newton, and every pure and wise spirit that ever took flesh. To be great is to be misunderstood." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10743-loneliness-is-the-human-condition-cultivate-it-the-way-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:12:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Janet Fitch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10743-loneliness-is-the-human-condition-cultivate-it-the-way-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[" Loneliness is the human condition. Cultivate it. The way it tunnels into you allows your soul room to grow. Never expect to outgrow loneliness. Never hope to find people who will understand you, someone to fill that space. An intelligent, sensitive person is the exception, the very great exception. If you expect to find people who will understand you, you will grow murderous with disappointment. The best you'll ever do is to understand yourself, know what it is that you want, and not let the cattle stand in your way." -- Janet Fitch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175364-when-you-re-different-sometimes-you-don-t-see-the-millions-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:12:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175364-when-you-re-different-sometimes-you-don-t-see-the-millions-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you're different, sometimes you don't see the millions of people who accept you for what you are. All you notice is the person who doesn't." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103512-deep-in-the-meadow-hidden-far-away-a-cloak-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:12:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103512-deep-in-the-meadow-hidden-far-away-a-cloak-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Deep in the meadow, hidden far away
A cloak of leaves, a moonbeam ray
Forget your woes and let your troubles lay
And when it's morning again, they'll wash away
Here it's safe, here it's warm
Here the daisies guard you from every harm
Here your dreams are sweet and tomorrow brings them true
Here is the place where I love you." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58548-i-believe-that-love--not-imitation--is-the-sincerest-form-of-flattery</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:11:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Marilyn Vos Savant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58548-i-believe-that-love--not-imitation--is-the-sincerest-form-of-flattery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that love--not imitation--is the sincerest form of flattery. Your imitator thinks that you can be duplicated; your lover knows you can't." -- Marilyn Vos Savant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7128-never-be-bullied-into-silence-never-allow-yourself-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:11:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Harvey Fierstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7128-never-be-bullied-into-silence-never-allow-yourself-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never be bullied into silence. Never allow yourself to be made a victim. Accept no one's definition of your life, but define yourself." -- Harvey Fierstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:11:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:11:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one can make you feel inferior without your consent." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:11:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2887-if-you-judge-people-you-have-no-time-to-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:13:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2887-if-you-judge-people-you-have-no-time-to-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you judge people, you have no time to love them." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187115-why-fit-in-when-you-were-born-to-stand-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:13:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187115-why-fit-in-when-you-were-born-to-stand-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why fit in when you were born to stand out?" -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21401-anybody-can-become-angry-that-is-easy-but-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:13:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Aristotle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21401-anybody-can-become-angry-that-is-easy-but-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anybody can become angry — that is easy, but to be angry with the right person and to the right degree and at the right time and for the right purpose, and in the right way — that is not within everybody's power and is not easy." -- Aristotle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13639-the-doctor-of-the-future-will-give-no-medication-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:13:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Thomas A. Edison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13639-the-doctor-of-the-future-will-give-no-medication-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The doctor of the future will give no medication, but will interest his patients in the care of the human frame, diet and in the cause and prevention  of disease. ~ " -- Thomas A. Edison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193372-be-awesome-be-a-book-nut</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 12:42:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193372-be-awesome-be-a-book-nut]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be awesome! Be a book nut!" -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22617-you-can-get-help-from-teachers-but-you-are-going</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 12:43:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22617-you-can-get-help-from-teachers-but-you-are-going]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can get help from teachers, but you are going to have to learn a lot by yourself, sitting alone in a room." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/553729-no-matter-how-old-you-are-now-you-are-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 12:46:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Pablo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/553729-no-matter-how-old-you-are-now-you-are-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No matter how old you are now. You are never too young or too old for success or going after what you want. Here’s a short list of people who accomplished great things at different ages
1) Helen Keller, at the age of 19 months, became deaf and blind. But that didn’t stop her. She was the first deaf and blind person to earn a Bachelor of Arts degree.
2) Mozart was already competent on keyboard and violin; he composed from the age of 5.
3) Shirley Temple was 6 when she became a movie star on “Bright Eyes.”
4) Anne Frank was 12 when she wrote the diary of Anne Frank.
5) Magnus Carlsen became a chess Grandmaster at the age of 13.
6) Nadia Comăneci was a gymnast from Romania that scored seven perfect 10.0 and won three gold medals at the Olympics at age 14.
7) Tenzin Gyatso was formally recognized as the 14th Dalai Lama in November 1950, at the age of 15.
8) Pele, a soccer superstar, was 17 years old when he won the world cup in 1958 with Brazil.
9) Elvis was a superstar by age 19.
10) John Lennon was 20 years and Paul Mcartney was 18 when the Beatles had their first concert in 1961.
11) Jesse Owens was 22 when he won 4 gold medals in Berlin 1936.
12) Beethoven was a piano virtuoso by age 23
13) Issac Newton wrote Philosophiæ Naturalis Principia Mathematica at age 24
14) Roger Bannister was 25 when he broke the 4 minute mile record
15) Albert Einstein was 26 when he wrote the theory of relativity
16) Lance E. Armstrong was 27 when he won the tour de France 
17) Michelangelo created two of the greatest sculptures “David” and “Pieta” by age 28
18) Alexander the Great, by age 29, had created one of the largest empires of the ancient world
19) J.K. Rowling was 30 years old when she finished the first manuscript of Harry Potter
20) Amelia Earhart was 31 years old when she became the first woman to fly solo across the Atlantic Ocean
21) Oprah was 32 when she started her talk show, which has become the highest-rated program of its kind
22) Edmund Hillary was 33 when he became the first man to reach Mount Everest
23) Martin Luther King Jr. was 34 when he wrote the speech “I Have a Dream.&quot;
24) Marie Curie was 35 years old when she got nominated for a Nobel Prize in Physics 
25) The Wright brothers, Orville (32) and Wilbur (36) invented and built the world's first successful airplane and making the first controlled, powered and sustained heavier-than-air human flight
26) Vincent Van Gogh was 37 when he died virtually unknown, yet his paintings today are worth millions.
27) Neil Armstrong was 38 when he became the first man to set foot on the moon.
28) Mark Twain was 40 when he wrote &quot;The Adventures of Tom Sawyer&quot;, and 49 years old when he wrote &quot;Adventures of Huckleberry Finn&quot;
29) Christopher Columbus was 41 when he discovered the Americas
30) Rosa Parks was 42 when she refused to obey the bus driver’s order to give up her seat to make room for a white passenger
31) John F. Kennedy was 43 years old when he became President of the United States
32) Henry Ford Was 45 when the Ford T came out.
33) Suzanne Collins was 46 when she wrote &quot;The Hunger Games&quot;
34) Charles Darwin was 50 years old when his book On the Origin of Species came out.
35) Leonardo Da Vinci was 51 years old when he painted the Mona Lisa.
36) Abraham Lincoln was 52 when he became president.
37) Ray Kroc Was 53 when he bought the McDonalds Franchise and took it to unprecedented levels.
38) Dr. Seuss was 54 when he wrote &quot;The Cat in the Hat&quot;.
40) Chesley &quot;Sully&quot; Sullenberger III was 57 years old when he successfully ditched US Airways Flight 1549 in the Hudson River in 2009. All of the 155 passengers aboard the aircraft survived
41) Colonel Harland Sanders was 61 when he started the KFC Franchise
42) J.R.R Tolkien was 62 when the Lord of the Ring books came out
43) Ronald Reagan was 69 when he became President of the US
44) Jack Lalane at age 70 handcuffed, shackled, towed 70 rowboats
45) Nelson Mandela was 76 when he became President" -- Pablo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 12:47:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186456-if-peeta-and-i-were-both-to-die-or-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 12:55:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186456-if-peeta-and-i-were-both-to-die-or-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If Peeta and I were both to die, or they thought we were....My fingers fumble with the pouch on my belt, freeing it.  Peeta sees it and his hand clamps on my wrist. &quot;No, I won't let you.&quot; &quot;Trust me,&quot; I whisper. He holds my gaze for a long moment then lets go. I loosen the top of the pouch and pour a few spoonfuls of berries into his palm. Then I fill my own. &quot;On the count of three?&quot; Peeta leans down and kisses me once, very gently. &quot;The count of three,&quot; he says. We stand, our backs pressed together, our empty hands locked tight. &quot;Hold them out. I want everyone to see,&quot; he says. I spread out my fingers, and the dark berries glisten in the sun. I give Peeta's hand one last squeeze as a signal, as a good-bye, and we begin counting. &quot;One.&quot; Maybe I'm wrong. &quot;Two.&quot; Maybe they don't care if we both die. &quot;Three!&quot; It's too late to change my mind. I lift my hand to my mouth taking one last look at the world. The berries have just passed my lips when the trumpets begin to blare. The frantic voice of Claudius Templesmith shouts above them. &quot;Stop! Stop! Ladies and gentlemen, I am pleased to present the victors of the 74th Hunger Games, Katniss Everdeen and Peeta Mellark!  I give you - the tributes of District 12!" -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268034-here-your-dreams-are-sweet-and-tomorrow-brings-them-true</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 12:56:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268034-here-your-dreams-are-sweet-and-tomorrow-brings-them-true]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here your dreams are sweet and tomorrow brings them true, here is the place where I love you." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335873-pity-does-not-get-you-aid-admiration-at-your-refusal</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:01:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335873-pity-does-not-get-you-aid-admiration-at-your-refusal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pity does not get you aid. Admiration at your refusal to give in does." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/804933-we-gotta-start-teaching-our-daughters-to-be-somebodies-instead</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 07:19:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Kifah Shah]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/804933-we-gotta-start-teaching-our-daughters-to-be-somebodies-instead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We gotta start teaching our daughters to be somebodies instead of somebody's." -- Kifah Shah]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/799-i-m-for-truth-no-matter-who-tells-it-i-m-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 11:27:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Malcolm X]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/799-i-m-for-truth-no-matter-who-tells-it-i-m-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm for truth, no matter who tells it. I'm for justice, no matter who it is for or against. I'm a human being, first and foremost, and as such I'm for whoever and whatever benefits humanity as a whole." -- Malcolm X]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5647-and-when-you-want-something-all-the-universe-conspires-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 16:47:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5647-and-when-you-want-something-all-the-universe-conspires-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And, when you want something, all the universe conspires in helping you to achieve it." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2533-of-course-motivation-is-not-permanent-but-then-neither-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 09:12:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[shireen add a quote by Zig Ziglar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2533-of-course-motivation-is-not-permanent-but-then-neither-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of course motivation is not permanent. But then, neither is bathing; but it is something you should do on a regular basis." -- Zig Ziglar]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
