<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/463743-kathryn]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/463743-kathryn" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 11:21:10 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78670-if-personality-is-an-unbroken-series-of-successful-gestures-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 11:21:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78670-if-personality-is-an-unbroken-series-of-successful-gestures-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If personality is an unbroken series of successful gestures, then there was something gorgeous about him, some heightened sensitivity to the promise of life, as if he were related to one of those intricate machines that register earthquakes ten thousand miles away. This responsiveness had nothing to do with that flabby impressionability which is dignified under the name of the 'creative temperament'--it was an extraordinary gift for hope, a romantic readiness such as I have never found in any other person and which it is not likely I shall ever find again. No--Gatsby turned out all right at the end; it is what preyed on Gatsby, what foul dust floated in the wake of his dreams that temporarily closed out my interest in the abortive sorrows and short-winded elations of men." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11087-books-are-the-carriers-of-civilization-without-books-history-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 13:55:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Barbara Tuchman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11087-books-are-the-carriers-of-civilization-without-books-history-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are the carriers of civilization. Without books, history is silent, literature dumb, science crippled, thought and speculation at a standstill.  Without books, the development of civilization would have been impossible.  They are engines of change (as the poet said), windows on the world and lighthouses erected in the sea of time.  They are companions, teachers, magicians, bankers of the treasures of the mind. Books are humanity in print.

[&lt;i&gt;Bulletin of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences&lt;/i&gt;, Vol. 34, No. 2 (Nov. 1980), pp. 16-32]" -- Barbara Tuchman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49307-research-is-formalized-curiosity-it-is-poking-and-prying-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 10:52:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49307-research-is-formalized-curiosity-it-is-poking-and-prying-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Research is formalized curiosity. It is poking and prying with a purpose." -- Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2464-there-s-no-money-in-poetry-but-there-s-no-poetry-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 08:48:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Robert Graves]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2464-there-s-no-money-in-poetry-but-there-s-no-poetry-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's no money in poetry, but there's no poetry in money, either." -- Robert Graves]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/753099-the-writer-s-object-should-be-to-hold-the-reader-s-attention</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 16:00:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Barbara W. Tuchman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/753099-the-writer-s-object-should-be-to-hold-the-reader-s-attention]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The writer's object should be to hold the reader's attention. I want the reader to turn the page and keep on turning until the end. This is accomplished only when the narrative moves steadily ahead, not when it comes to a weary standstill, overloaded with every item uncovered in the research." -- Barbara W. Tuchman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78669-paris-had-its-sweetest-smell-the-smell-of-chestnut-trees</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 07:22:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Irene Nemirovsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78669-paris-had-its-sweetest-smell-the-smell-of-chestnut-trees]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Paris had its sweetest smell, the smell of chestnut trees in bloom and of petrol with a few grains of dust that crack under your teeth like pepper.  In the darknes the danger seemed to grow.  You could smell the suffering in the air, in the silence.  Everyone looked at their house and thought, &quot;Tomorrow it will be in ruins, tomorrow I'l have nothing left." -- Irene Nemirovsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78856-every-few-weeks-she-would-shut-herself-up-in-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 07:35:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78856-every-few-weeks-she-would-shut-herself-up-in-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every few weeks she would shut herself up in her room, put on her scribbling suit, and fall into a vortex, as she expressed it, writing away at her novel with all her heart and soul, for till that was finished she could find no peace." -- Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4642-i-m-just-going-to-write-because-i-cannot-help-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 02:54:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4642-i-m-just-going-to-write-because-i-cannot-help-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm just going to write because I cannot help it." -- Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176747-far-over-the-misty-mountains-cold-to-dungeons-deep-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 14:54:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176747-far-over-the-misty-mountains-cold-to-dungeons-deep-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Far over the misty mountains cold
To dungeons deep and caverns old
We must away ere break of day
To seek the pale enchanted gold.

The dwarves of yore made mighty spells,
While hammers fell like ringing bells
In places deep, where dark things sleep,
In hollow halls beneath the fells.

For ancient king and elvish lord
There many a gleaming golden hoard
They shaped and wrought, and light they caught
To hide in gems on hilt of sword.

On silver necklaces they strung
The flowering stars, on crowns they hung
The dragon-fire, in twisted wire
They meshed the light of moon and sun.

Far over the misty mountains cold
To dungeons deep and caverns old
We must away, ere break of day,
To claim our long-forgotten gold.

Goblets they carved there for themselves
And harps of gold; where no man delves
There lay they long, and many a song
Was sung unheard by men or elves.

The pines were roaring on the height,
The wind was moaning in the night.
The fire was red, it flaming spread;
The trees like torches blazed with light.

The bells were ringing in the dale
And men looked up with faces pale;
The dragon's ire more fierce than fire
Laid low their towers and houses frail.

The mountain smoked beneath the moon;
The dwarves, they heard the tramp of doom.
They fled their hall to dying fall
Beneath his feet, beneath the moon.

Far over the misty mountains grim
To dungeons deep and caverns dim
We must away, ere break of day,
To win our harps and gold from him!" -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245160-jellicle-cats-are-black-and-white-jellicle-cats-are-rather</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 14:50:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245160-jellicle-cats-are-black-and-white-jellicle-cats-are-rather]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jellicle Cats are black and white
Jellicle Cats are rather small
Jellicle Cats are merry and bright
And pleasant to hear when they caterwaul.
Jellicle Cats have cheerful faces,
Jellicle Cats have bright black eyes;
They like to practise their airs and graces
And wait for the Jellicle Moon to rise." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78854-as-for-his-sudden-change-of-heart-he-had-suddenly</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 02:54:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Barbara Pym]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78854-as-for-his-sudden-change-of-heart-he-had-suddenly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As for his sudden change of heart, he had suddenly remembered the end of Mansfield Park, and how Edmund fell out of love with Mary Crawford and came to care for Fanny.  Dulcie must surely know the novel well, and would understand how such things can happen." -- Barbara Pym]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/575724-but-most-of-these-women----the-famous-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2012 10:46:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Kathryn J. Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/575724-but-most-of-these-women----the-famous-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But most of these women -- the famous and the obscure -- had one thing in common: they did not think of themselves as heroes. They followed their consciences, saw something that needed to be done, and they did it. And all of them helped win a war, even though many of them paid the ultimate price for their contribution.  But their sacrifice was not in vain, especially if their courage continues to inspire others to fight injustice and evil wherever they find it.
--From &lt;i&gt;Women Heroes of WWII&lt;/i&gt;" -- Kathryn J. Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38459-go-where-your-best-prayers-take-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 13:24:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38459-go-where-your-best-prayers-take-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Go where your best prayers take you." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/690084-in-paris-i-found-myself-surrounded-by-germans-they-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 08:07:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Pearl Witherington Cornioley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/690084-in-paris-i-found-myself-surrounded-by-germans-they-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In Paris, I found myself surrounded by Germans; they were all over the place. They played music, and people would go and listen to them! All along rue de Rivoli, as far as you could see from place de la Concorde, there were enormous swastika banners five or six floors high. I just thought, This is impossible.
Imagine that someone comes into your home—someone you don’t like—he settles down, gives orders: “Here we are, we’re at home now; you must obey.” To me that was unbearable." -- Pearl Witherington Cornioley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/689700-we-could-see-the-bombing-in-london-and-we-heard</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 08:10:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Pearl Witherington Cornioley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/689700-we-could-see-the-bombing-in-london-and-we-heard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We could see the bombing in London and we heard of the battles going on in Africa and other places. But what made me really furious was the occupation. When I arrived in Paris from Normandy, shortly after July 14, 1940, notices were placarded, “Mr. So and So was shot last night.” There were notices like that on columns along rue de Rivoli. Those poor people had been caught outside after the curfew, taken to a police station, and if there was any action whatsoever against the Germans during the night, they were shot." -- Pearl Witherington Cornioley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7787-the-true-measure-of-a-man-is-how-he-treats</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 16:31:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Malcolm Forbes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7787-the-true-measure-of-a-man-is-how-he-treats]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The true measure of a man is how he treats someone  who can do him absolutely no good." -- Malcolm Forbes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127079-she-had-always-been-an-unashamed-reader-of-novels</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 14:47:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Barbara Pym]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127079-she-had-always-been-an-unashamed-reader-of-novels]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had always been an unashamed reader of novels ..." -- Barbara Pym]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/285029-once-outside-the-magic-circle-the-writers-became-their-lonely</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 09:40:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Barbara Pym]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/285029-once-outside-the-magic-circle-the-writers-became-their-lonely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once outside the magic circle the writers became their lonely selves, pondering on poems, observing their fellow men ruthlessly, putting people they knew into novels; no wonder they were without friends." -- Barbara Pym]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/726166-woe-alas-to-the-one-who-shall-have-loved-bodies</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 08:10:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Victor Hugo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/726166-woe-alas-to-the-one-who-shall-have-loved-bodies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Woe, alas, to the one who shall have loved bodies, forms, appearances only. Death will take everything from him. Try to love souls, you shall find them again" -- Victor Hugo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/960898-during-the-conflict-that-was-placed-before-them-they-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 14:47:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Kathryn J. Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/960898-during-the-conflict-that-was-placed-before-them-they-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["During the conflict that was placed before them, they not only gained the gratitude of many in their own generation but they proved, for the first time on a global scale, the enormous value of a woman’s contribution, paving the way for future generations of women to do the same." -- Kathryn J. Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/960901-ironically-the-memory-of-the-women-heroes-of-world-war</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 14:50:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Kathryn J. Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/960901-ironically-the-memory-of-the-women-heroes-of-world-war]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ironically, the memory of the women heroes of World War I was largely eclipsed by the very women they had inspired. The more blatant evil enacted into law by Nazi Germany during the Second World War ensured that those who fought against it would continue to fascinate long after the first war had become a vague, unpleasant memory—one brought to mind only by fading photographs of serious, helmeted young men standing in sandbagged trenches or smiling young women in ankle-length nursing uniforms, or by the presence of poppies in Remembrance Day ceremonies." -- Kathryn J. Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1268368-the-second-world-war-created-the-need-for-a-new</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 09:41:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathryn add a quote by Kathryn J. Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1268368-the-second-world-war-created-the-need-for-a-new]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Second World War created the need for a new generation of female heroes. Where could these women look for role models? The women of the previous war had by this time been largely forgotten. Although efforts had been made during the 1920s to memorialize the war's heroes, both men and women, with monuments, books, and films, most Europeans, impatient to forget the war, also forgot its heroes.

But now the memory of their courage was needed and eagerly recalled..." -- Kathryn J. Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
