<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/465642-cathy-day]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/465642-cathy-day" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 15:46:28 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77496-a-man-to-be-greatly-good-must-imagine-intensely-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 15:46:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Percy Bysshe Shelley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77496-a-man-to-be-greatly-good-must-imagine-intensely-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man, to be greatly good, must imagine intensely and comprehensively; he must put himself in the place of another and many others; the pains and pleasures of his species must become his own. The great instrument of moral good is the imagination." -- Percy Bysshe Shelley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183211-i-have-an-idea-that-the-only-thing-which-makes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 21:53:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183211-i-have-an-idea-that-the-only-thing-which-makes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have an idea that the only thing which makes it possible to regard this world we live in without disgust is the beauty which now and then men create out of the chaos. The pictures they paint, the music they compose, the books they write, and the lives they lead. Of all these the richest in beauty is the beautiful life. That is the perfect work of art." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167493-being-alone-is-not-the-most-awful-thing-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2012 17:57:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Zoë Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167493-being-alone-is-not-the-most-awful-thing-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being alone is &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; the most awful thing in the world. You visit your museums and cultivate your interests and remind yourself how lucky you are not to be one of those spindly Sudanese children with flies beading their mouths. You make out To Do lists - reorganise linen cupboard, learn two sonnets. You dole out little treats to yourself - slices of ice-cream cake, concerts at Wigmore Hall. And then, every once in a while, you wake up and gaze out of the window at another bloody daybreak, and think, &lt;i&gt;I cannot do this anymore. I cannot pull myself together again and spend the next fifteen hours of wakefulness fending off the fact of my own misery&lt;/i&gt;.

People like Sheba think that they know what it's like to be lonely. They cast their minds back to the time they broke up with a boyfriend in 1975 and endured a whole month before meeting someone new. Or the week they spent in a Bavarian steel town when they were fifteen years old, visiting their greasy-haired German pen pal and discovering that her hand-writing was the best thing about her. But about the drip drip of long-haul, no-end-in-sight solitude, they know nothing. They don't know what it is to construct an entire weekend around a visit to the laundrette. Or to sit in a darkened flat on Halloween night, because you can't bear to expose your bleak evening to a crowd of jeering trick-or-treaters. Or to have the librarian smile pityingly and say, ‘Goodness, you're a quick reader!’ when you bring back seven books, read from cover to cover, a week after taking them out. They don't know what it is to be so chronically untouched that the accidental brush of a bus conductor's hand on your shoulder sends a jolt of longing straight to your groin. I have sat on park benches and trains and schoolroom chairs, feeling the great store of unused, objectless love sitting in my belly like a stone until I was sure I would cry out and fall, flailing, to the ground. About all of this, Sheba and her like have no clue." -- Zoë Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28397-there-are-moments-when-one-has-to-choose-between-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 19:37:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28397-there-are-moments-when-one-has-to-choose-between-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are moments when one has to choose between living one's own life, fully, entirely, completely-or dragging out some false, shallow, degrading existence that the world in its hypocrisy demands." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140650-scandal-is-gossip-made-tedious-by-morality</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 19:38:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140650-scandal-is-gossip-made-tedious-by-morality]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Scandal is gossip made tedious by morality." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114228-i-like-grit-i-like-love-and-death-i-m-tired</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 19:39:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Jim Harrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114228-i-like-grit-i-like-love-and-death-i-m-tired]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like grit, I like love and death, I'm tired of irony. ... A lot of good fiction is sentimental. ... The novelist who refuses sentiment refuses the full spectrum of human behavior, and then he just dries up. ... I would rather give full vent to all human loves and disappointments, and take a chance on being corny, than die a smartass." -- Jim Harrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/858658-parties-of-this-sort-are-as-a-rule-premature-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 18:20:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/858658-parties-of-this-sort-are-as-a-rule-premature-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Parties of this sort are as a rule premature. They have little reality until the following day, when they occupy the attention of the people who were not invited." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
