<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/466803-joycesu]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/466803-joycesu" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 03:04:17 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158239-we-pass-through-the-present-with-our-eyes-blindfolded-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 03:04:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158239-we-pass-through-the-present-with-our-eyes-blindfolded-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We pass through the present with our eyes blindfolded.  We are permitted merely to sense and guess at what we are actually experiencing.  Only later when the cloth is untied can we glance at the past and find out what we have experienced and what meaning it has." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82076-why-in-fact-should-one-tell-the-truth-what-obliges</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 03:04:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82076-why-in-fact-should-one-tell-the-truth-what-obliges]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why in fact should one tell the truth?  What obliges us to do it?  And why do we consider telling the truth to be a virtue?  Imagine that you meet a madman, who claims that he is a fish and that we are all fish. Are you going to argue with him?  Are you going to undress in front of him and show him that you don't have fins?  Are you going to say to his face what you think?...If you told him the whole truth and nothing but the truth, only what you thought, you would enter into a serious conversation with a madman and you yourself would become mad.  And it is the same way with the world that surrounds us.  If I obstinately told the truth to its face, it would mean that I was taking it seriously.  And to take seriously something so unserious means to lose all one's own seriousness.  I have to lie, if I don't want to take madmen seriously and become a madman myself." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96570-the-worth-of-a-human-being-lies-in-the-ability</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 03:04:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96570-the-worth-of-a-human-being-lies-in-the-ability]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worth of a human being lies in the ability to extend oneself, to go outside oneself, to exist in and for other people." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161868-it-was-futile-to-attack-with-reason-the-stout-wall</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 03:04:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161868-it-was-futile-to-attack-with-reason-the-stout-wall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was futile to attack with reason the stout wall of irrational feelings that, as is known, is the stuff of which the female mind is made." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161648-even-in-the-game-there-lurks-a-lack-of-freedom</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 03:07:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161648-even-in-the-game-there-lurks-a-lack-of-freedom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even in the game there lurks a lack of freedom; even in a game is a trap for the players." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161656-jealousy-isn-t-a-pleasant-quality-but-if-it-isn-t-overdone</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 03:07:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161656-jealousy-isn-t-a-pleasant-quality-but-if-it-isn-t-overdone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jealousy isn't a pleasant quality, but if it isn't overdone (and if it's combined with modesty), apart from its inconvenience there's even something touching about it." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17144-love-is-the-longing-for-the-half-of-ourselves-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 03:08:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17144-love-is-the-longing-for-the-half-of-ourselves-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is the longing for the half of ourselves we have lost." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18532-we-can-never-know-what-to-want-because-living-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 03:08:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18532-we-can-never-know-what-to-want-because-living-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can never know what to want, because, living only one life, we can neither compare it with our previous lives nor perfect it in our lives to come." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65833-we-all-need-someone-to-look-at-us-we-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 03:16:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65833-we-all-need-someone-to-look-at-us-we-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all need someone to look at us. we can be divided into four categories according to the kind of look we wish to live under. the first category longs for the look of an infinite number of anonymous eyes, in other words, for the look of the public. the second category is made up of people who have a vital need to be looked at by many known eyes. they are the tireless hosts of cocktail parties and dinners. they are happier than the people in the first category, who, when they lose their public, have the feeling that the lights have gone out in the room of their lives. this happens to nearly all of them sooner or later. people in the second category, on the other hand, can always come up with the eyes they need. then there is the third category, the category of people who need to be constantly before the eyes of the person they love. their situation is as dangerous as the situation of people in the first category. one day the eyes of their beloved will close, and the room will go dark. and finally there is the fourth category, the rarest, the category of people who live in the imaginary eyes of those who are not present. they are the dreamers." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106110-i-want-you-to-be-weak-as-weak-as-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 03:17:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106110-i-want-you-to-be-weak-as-weak-as-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want you to be weak. As weak as I am." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105522-physical-love-is-unthinkable-without-violence</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 03:17:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105522-physical-love-is-unthinkable-without-violence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Physical love is unthinkable without violence." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53767-why-don-t-you-ever-use-your-strength-on-me-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 03:18:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53767-why-don-t-you-ever-use-your-strength-on-me-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why don't you ever use your strength on me?&quot; she said.
Because love means renouncing strength,&quot; said Franz softly." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21374-happiness-is-the-longing-for-repetition</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 03:18:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21374-happiness-is-the-longing-for-repetition]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is the longing for repetition." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49277-the-worst-thing-is-not-that-the-world-is-unfree</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 03:18:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49277-the-worst-thing-is-not-that-the-world-is-unfree]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worst thing is not that the world is unfree, but that people have unlearned their liberty.

The more indifferent people are to politics, to the interests of others, the more obsessed they become with their own faces. The individualism of our time.

Not being able to fall asleep and not allowing oneself to move: the marital bed.

If high culture is coming to an end, it is also the end of you and your paradoxical ideas, because paradox as such belongs to high culture and not to childish prattle. You remind me of the young men who supported the Nazis or communists not out of cowardice or out of opportunism but out of an excess of intelligence. For nothing requires a greater effort of thought than arguments to justify the rule of nonthought… You are the brilliant ally of your own gravediggers.

In the world of highways, a beautiful landscape means: an island of beauty connected by a long line with other islands of beauty.

How to live in a world with which you disagree? How to live with people when you neither share their suffering nor their joys? When you know that you don’t belong among them?... our century refuses to acknowledge anyone’s right to disagree with the world…All that remains of such a place is the memory, the ideal of a cloister, the dream of a cloister… 

Humor can only exist when people are still capable of recognizing some border between the important and the unimportant. And nowadays this border has become unrecognizable.

The majority of people lead their existence within a small idyllic circle bounded by their family, their home, and their work... They live in a secure realm somewhere between good and evil. They are sincerely horrified by the sight of a killer. And yet all you have to do is remove them from this peaceful circle and they, too, turn into murderers, without quite knowing how it happened.

The longing for order is at the same time a longing for death, because life is an incessant disruption of order. Or to put it the other way around: the desire for order is a virtuous pretext, an excuse for virulent misanthropy.

A long time a go a certain Cynic philosopher proudly paraded around Athens in a moth-eaten coat, hoping that everyone would admire his contempt for convention. When Socrates met him, he said: Through the hole in your coat I see your vanity. Your dirt, too, dear sir, is self-indulgent and your self-indulgence is dirty.

You are always living below the level of true existence, you bitter weed, you anthropomorphized vat of vinegar! You’re full of acid, which bubbles inside you like an alchemist’s brew. Your highest wish is to be able to see all around you the same ugliness as you carry inside yourself. That’s the only way you can feel for a few moments some kind of peace between yourself and the world. That’s because the world, which is beautiful, seems horrible to you, torments you and excludes you.

If the novel is successful, it must necessarily be wiser than its author. This is why many excellent French intellectuals write mediocre novels. They are always more intelligent than their books.

By a certain age, coincidences lose their magic, no longer surprise, become run-of-the-mill.

Any new possibility that existence acquires, even the least likely, transforms everything about existence." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311733-when-he-looks-at-beauty-in-the-only-way-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2010 10:50:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Plato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311733-when-he-looks-at-beauty-in-the-only-way-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...when he looks at Beauty in the only way that Beauty can be seen - only then will it become possible for him to give birth not to images of virtue (because he's in touch with no images), but to true virtue [arete] (because he is in touch with true Beauty). The love of the gods belongs to anyone who has given to true virtue and nourished it, and if any human being could become immortal, it would be he." -- Plato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33460-let-there-be-spaces-in-your-togetherness-and-let-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 01:23:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33460-let-there-be-spaces-in-your-togetherness-and-let-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let there be spaces in your togetherness, And let the winds of the heavens dance between you. Love one another but make not a bond of love: Let it rather be a moving sea between the shores of your souls. Fill each other's cup but drink not from one cup. Give one another of your bread but eat not from the same loaf. Sing and dance together and be joyous, but let each one of you be alone, Even as the strings of a lute are alone though they quiver with the same music. Give your hearts, but not into each other's keeping. For only the hand of Life can contain your hearts. And stand together, yet not too near together: For the pillars of the temple stand apart, And the oak tree and the cypress grow not in each other's shadow." -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63521-for-what-is-your-friend-that-you-should-seek-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 01:25:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63521-for-what-is-your-friend-that-you-should-seek-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For what is your friend that you should seek him with hours to kill? 

Seek him always with hours to live.

For it is his to fill your need, but not your emptiness.

And in th sweetness of friendship let there be laughter, and sharing of pleasures.

For in the dew of little things the heart finds its morning and is refreshed." -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312500-beauty-is-life-when-life-unveils-her-holy-face-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 01:28:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312500-beauty-is-life-when-life-unveils-her-holy-face-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beauty is life when life unveils her holy face. But you are life and you are the veil. Beauty is eternity gazing at itself in a mirror. But you are eternity and you are the mirror." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312501-love-has-no-other-desire-but-to-fulfill-itself-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 01:29:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312501-love-has-no-other-desire-but-to-fulfill-itself-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love has no other desire but to fulfill itself. But if to love and must needs have desires, let these be your desires: to melt and be like a running brook that sings its melody to the night. To know the pain of too much tenderness. To be wounded by your own understanding of love; and to bleed willingly and joyfully. To wake at dawn with a winged heart and give thanks for another day of loving; to rest at noon and meditate love's ecstasy; to return home at eventide with gratitude; and then to sleep with a prayer for the beloved in your heart and a song of praise upon your lips." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312780-amory-took-to-writing-poetry-on-spring-afternoons-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 01:29:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312780-amory-took-to-writing-poetry-on-spring-afternoons-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Amory took to writing poetry on spring afternoons, in the gardens of the big estates near Princeton, while swans made effective atmosphere in the artificial pools, and slow clouds sailed harmoniously above the willow. May came too soon, and suddenly unable to bear walls, he wandered the campus at all hours through starlight and rain." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313626-he-could-transform-the-barest-incident-into-a-thing-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 01:51:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313626-he-could-transform-the-barest-incident-into-a-thing-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["he could transform the barest incident into a thing of curve and contour." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314277-my-imagination-persisted-in-sticking-horrors-into-the-dark--so</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 20:43:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314277-my-imagination-persisted-in-sticking-horrors-into-the-dark--so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["my imagination persisted in sticking horrors into the dark- so I stuck my imagination into the dark instead, and let it look out at me." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314279-amory-i-love-you-rosalind-i-love-you--now</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 20:46:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314279-amory-i-love-you-rosalind-i-love-you--now]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Amory: I love you.
Rosalind: I love you- now." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314281-how-the-unforgettable-faces-of-dusk-would-blend-to-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 20:52:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314281-how-the-unforgettable-faces-of-dusk-would-blend-to-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How the unforgettable faces of dusk would blend to her, the myriad footsteps, a thousand overtures, would blend to her footsteps; and there would be more drunkenness than wine in the softness of her eyes on his." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314537-they-always-believe-that-things-are-in-a-bad-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 21:08:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314537-they-always-believe-that-things-are-in-a-bad-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They always believe that 'things are in a bad way now,' but they 'haven't any faith in these idealists.' One minute they call Wilson 'just a dreamer, not practical'- a year later they rail at him for making his dreams realities. They haven't clear logical ideas on one single subject except a sturdy, stolid opposition to all change. They don't think uneducated people should be highly paid, but they won't see that if they don't pay the uneducated people their children are going to be uneducated too, and we're going round and round in a circle. That- is the great middle class." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18988-i-don-t-want-to-repeat-my-innocence-i-want-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 21:36:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18988-i-don-t-want-to-repeat-my-innocence-i-want-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't want to repeat my innocence. I want the pleasure of losing it again." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8238-he-dug-so-deeply-into-her-sentiments-that-in-search</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2010 12:28:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8238-he-dug-so-deeply-into-her-sentiments-that-in-search]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He dug so deeply into her sentiments that in search of interest he found love, because by trying to make her love him he ended up falling in love with her. Petra Cotes, for her part, loved him more and more as she felt his love increasing, and that was how in the ripeness of autumn she began to believe once more in the youthful superstition that poverty was the servitude of love. Both looked back then on the wild revelry, the gaudy wealth, and the unbridled fornication as an annoyance and they lamented that it had cost them so much of their lives to find the paradise of shared solitude. Madly in love after so many years of sterile complicity, they enjoyed the miracle of living each other as much at the table as in bed, and they grew to be so happy that even when they were two worn-out people they kept on blooming like little children and playing together like dogs." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6001-think-you-re-escaping-and-run-into-yourself-longest-way-round</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 12:46:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6001-think-you-re-escaping-and-run-into-yourself-longest-way-round]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Think you're escaping and run into yourself. Longest way round is the shortest way home." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2578-but-my-body-was-like-a-harp-and-her-words</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 12:46:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2578-but-my-body-was-like-a-harp-and-her-words]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But my body was like a harp and her words and gestures were like fingers running upon the wires." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121184-shut-your-eyes-and-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 12:46:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[joycesu add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121184-shut-your-eyes-and-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Shut your eyes and see." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
