<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/469169-gigg]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/469169-gigg" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 17:06:30 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151143-whether-you-believe-in-god-or-not-does-not-matter</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 17:06:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Dalai Lama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151143-whether-you-believe-in-god-or-not-does-not-matter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whether you believe in God or not does not matter much, whether you believe in Buddha or not does not matter so much; as a Buddhist, whether you believe in reincarnation or not does not matter so much. You must lead a good life." -- Dalai Lama]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154499-we-always-hope-for-the-easy-fix-the-one-simple</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 17:21:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Atul Gawande]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154499-we-always-hope-for-the-easy-fix-the-one-simple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We always hope for the easy fix:  the one simple change that will erase a problem in a stroke.  But few things in life work this way.  Instead, success requires making a hundred small steps go right - one after the other, no slipups, no goofs, everyone pitching in." -- Atul Gawande]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158658-no-there-is-no-escape-there-is-no-heaven-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 17:30:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by George MacDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158658-no-there-is-no-escape-there-is-no-heaven-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No, there is no escape. There is no heaven with a little of hell in it - no place to retain this or that of the devil in our hearts or our pockets. Out Satan must go, every hair and feather." -- George MacDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 22:24:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that no matter what happens, or how bad it seems today, life does go on, and it will be better tomorrow. I've learned that you can tell a lot about a person by the way he/she handles these three things: a rainy day, lost luggage, and tangled Christmas tree lights. I've learned that regardless of your relationship with your parents, you'll miss them when they're gone from your life. I've learned that making a &quot;living&quot; is not the same thing as making a &quot;life.&quot; I've learned that life sometimes gives you a second chance. I've learned that you shouldn't go through life with a catcher's mitt on both hands; you need to be able to throw something back. I've learned that whenever I decide something with an open heart, I usually make the right decision. I've learned that even when I have pains, I don't have to be one. I've learned that every day you should reach out and touch someone. People love a warm hug, or just a friendly pat on the back. I've learned that I still have a lot to learn. I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225830-have-enough-courage-to-trust-love-one-more-time-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 22:29:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225830-have-enough-courage-to-trust-love-one-more-time-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have enough courage to trust love one more time and always one more time." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265684-never-make-someone-a-priority-when-all-you-are-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 22:29:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265684-never-make-someone-a-priority-when-all-you-are-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never make someone a priority when all you are to them is an option." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40630-when-you-learn-teach-when-you-get-give</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 22:29:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40630-when-you-learn-teach-when-you-get-give]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you learn, teach, when you get, give." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40498-i-ve-learned-that-even-when-i-have-pains-i-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 22:29:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40498-i-ve-learned-that-even-when-i-have-pains-i-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that even when I have pains, I don't have to be one." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60178-the-desire-to-reach-for-the-stars-is-ambitious-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 22:30:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Maya Angelou ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60178-the-desire-to-reach-for-the-stars-is-ambitious-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The desire to reach for the stars is ambitious. The desire to reach hearts is wise." -- Maya Angelou ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93512-you-may-encounter-many-defeats-but-you-must-not-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 22:30:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93512-you-may-encounter-many-defeats-but-you-must-not-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may encounter many defeats, but you must not be defeated.  In fact, it may be necessary to encounter the defeats, so you can know who you are, what you can rise from, how you can still come out of it." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197720-my-great-hope-is-to-laugh-as-much-as-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 22:31:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197720-my-great-hope-is-to-laugh-as-much-as-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My great hope is to laugh as much as I cry; to get my work done and try to love somebody and have the courage to accept the love in return." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51195-most-people-don-t-grow-up-most-people-age-they-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 22:31:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51195-most-people-don-t-grow-up-most-people-age-they-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most people don't grow up.  Most people age.  They find parking spaces, honor their credit cards, get married, have children, and call that maturity.  What that is, is aging." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103456-try-to-be-a-rainbow-in-someone-s-cloud</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 22:35:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103456-try-to-be-a-rainbow-in-someone-s-cloud]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Try to be a rainbow in someone's cloud." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8287-i-have-not-failed-i-ve-just-found-10-000-ways-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 08:10:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Thomas A. Edison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8287-i-have-not-failed-i-ve-just-found-10-000-ways-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work." -- Thomas A. Edison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5829-be-nice-to-nerds-you-may-end-up-working-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 08:10:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Charles J. Sykes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5829-be-nice-to-nerds-you-may-end-up-working-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be nice to nerds. You may end up working for them. We all could." -- Charles J. Sykes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 08:12:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5402-so-it-s-not-gonna-be-easy-it-s-going-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 08:12:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5402-so-it-s-not-gonna-be-easy-it-s-going-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So it's not gonna be easy. It's going to be really hard; we're gonna have to work at this everyday, but I want to do that because I want you. I want all of you, forever, everyday. You and me... everyday." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32234-seven-deadly-sins-wealth-without-work-pleasure-without-conscience-science</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 08:13:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32234-seven-deadly-sins-wealth-without-work-pleasure-without-conscience-science]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Seven Deadly Sins

Wealth without work
Pleasure without conscience
Science without humanity
Knowledge without character
Politics without principle
Commerce without morality
Worship without sacrifice." -- Mahatma Gandhi ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2584-i-always-arrive-late-at-the-office-but-i-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 08:13:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Charles Lamb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2584-i-always-arrive-late-at-the-office-but-i-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I always arrive late at the office, but I make up for it by leaving early." -- Charles Lamb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1611-others-have-seen-what-is-and-asked-why-i-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 08:16:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Pablo Picasso]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1611-others-have-seen-what-is-and-asked-why-i-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Others have seen what is and asked why. I have seen what could be and asked why not. " -- Pablo Picasso]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228647-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 08:30:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228647-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up. You build up all these defenses, you build up a whole suit of armor, so that nothing can hurt you, then one stupid person, no different from any other stupid person, wanders into your stupid life...You give them a piece of you. They didn't ask for it. They did something dumb one day, like kiss you or smile at you, and then your life isn't your own anymore. Love takes hostages. It gets inside you. It eats you out and leaves you crying in the darkness, so simple a phrase like 'maybe we should be just friends' turns into a glass splinter working its way into your heart. It hurts. Not just in the imagination. Not just in the mind. It's a soul-hurt, a real gets-inside-you-and-rips-you-apart pain. I hate love." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1323-here-s-what-i-think-mr-wind-up-bird-said-may-kasahara</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 08:32:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1323-here-s-what-i-think-mr-wind-up-bird-said-may-kasahara]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's what I think, Mr. Wind-Up Bird,&quot; said May Kasahara. &quot;Everybody's born with some different thing at the core of their existence. And that thing, whatever it is, becomes like a heat source that runs each person from the inside. I have one too, of course. Like everybody else. But sometimes it gets out of hand. It swells or shrinks inside me, and it shakes me up. What I'd really like to do is find a way to communicate that feeling to another person. But I can't seem to do it. They just don't get it. Of course, the problem could be that I'm not explaining it very well, but I think it's because they're not listening very well. They pretend to be listening, but they're not, really. So I get worked up sometimes, and I do some crazy things." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128778-is-it-possible-in-the-final-analysis-for-one-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 11:16:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128778-is-it-possible-in-the-final-analysis-for-one-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is it possible, in the final analysis, for one human being to achieve perfect understanding of another?
We can invest enormous time and energy in serious efforts to know another person, but in the end, how close can we come to that person's essence? We convince ourselves that we know the other person well, but do we really know anything important about anyone?" -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25265-continuous-effort---not-strength-or-intelligence---is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 11:16:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25265-continuous-effort---not-strength-or-intelligence---is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Continuous effort - not strength or intelligence - is the key to unlocking our potential." -- Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130061-be-of-good-cheer-do-not-think-of-today-s-failures</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 11:16:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Helen Keller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130061-be-of-good-cheer-do-not-think-of-today-s-failures]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be of good cheer.  Do not think of today's failures, but of the success that may come tomorrow.  You have set yourselves a difficult task, but you will succeed if you persevere; and you will find a joy in overcoming obstacles.  Remember, no effort that we make to attain something beautiful is ever lost." -- Helen Keller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84300-people-tend-to-think-that-happiness-is-a-stroke-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 11:21:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84300-people-tend-to-think-that-happiness-is-a-stroke-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People tend to think that happiness is a stroke of luck, something that will descend like fine weather if you're fortunate. But happiness is the result of personal effort. You fight for it, strive for it, insist upon it, and sometimes even travel around the world looking for it. You have to participate relentlessly." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145712-speak-quietly-to-yourself-promise-there-will-be-better</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 11:22:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by mary anne radmacher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145712-speak-quietly-to-yourself-promise-there-will-be-better]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["speak quietly to yourself &amp; promise there will be better days.  whisper gently to yourself and provide assurance that you really are extending your best effort.  console your bruised and tender spirit with reminders of many other successes.  offer comfort in practical and tangible ways - as if you were encouraging your dearest friend.  recognize that on certain days the greatest grace is that the day is over and you get to close your eyes.  tomorrow comes more brightly..." -- mary anne radmacher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13079-it-is-truth-that-liberates-not-your-effort-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 11:26:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Jiddu Krishnamurti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13079-it-is-truth-that-liberates-not-your-effort-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is truth that liberates, not your effort to be free." -- Jiddu Krishnamurti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58848-the-thing-about-life-is-that-you-must-survive-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 11:26:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Katharine Hepburn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58848-the-thing-about-life-is-that-you-must-survive-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The thing about life is that you must survive. Life is going to be difficult, and dreadful things will happen. What you do is move along, get on with it, and be tough. Not in the sense of being mean to others, but being tough with yourself and making a deadly effort not to be defeated." -- Katharine Hepburn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292065-despite-your-best-efforts-people-are-going-to-be-hurt</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 11:26:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gigg add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292065-despite-your-best-efforts-people-are-going-to-be-hurt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Despite your best efforts, people are going to be hurt when it's time for them to be hurt." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
