<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/4711-marilyn]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/4711-marilyn" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 23:09:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27176-you-can-hear-now-your-inner-ear-is-formed-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 23:09:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[marilyn add a quote by Suzanne Finnamore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27176-you-can-hear-now-your-inner-ear-is-formed-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can hear now.  Your inner ear is formed.
I shout &quot;I love you&quot; into the bedroom. Then I feel stupid.  Then I don't.  This is pretty much the story of my life." -- Suzanne Finnamore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155485-do-you-also-believe-that-what-gives-our-lives-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 07:06:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[marilyn add a quote by Sándor Márai]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155485-do-you-also-believe-that-what-gives-our-lives-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you also believe that what gives our lives their meaning is the passion that suddenly invades us heart, soul, and body, and burns in us forever, no matter what else happens in our lives?  And that if we have experienced this much, then perhaps we haven’t lived in vain?  Is passion so deep and terrible and magnificent and inhuman?  Is it indeed about desiring any one person, or is it about desiring desire itself?  That is the question.  Or perhaps, is it indeed about desiring a particular person, a single, mysterious other, once and for always, no matter whether that person is good or bad, and the intensity of our feelings bears no relation to that individual’s qualities or behavior?" -- Sándor Márai]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207568-she-went-around-with-the-attitude-that-she-would-rather</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 07:09:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[marilyn add a quote by Stieg Larsson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207568-she-went-around-with-the-attitude-that-she-would-rather]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She went around with the attitude that she would rather be beaten to death than take any shit." -- Stieg Larsson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81417-how-could-a-just-god-permit-great-misery-the-haitian</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 07:39:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[marilyn add a quote by Tracy Kidder, Paul Farmer (Mountains Beyond Mountains)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81417-how-could-a-just-god-permit-great-misery-the-haitian]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How could a just God permit great misery?  The Haitian peasants answered with a proverb:  &quot;Bondye konn bay, men li pa konn separe,&quot;  in literal translation, &quot;God gives but doesn't share.&quot;  This meant... God gives us humans everything we need to flourish, but he's not the one who's supposed to divvy up the loot.  That charge was laid upon us." -- Tracy Kidder, Paul Farmer (Mountains Beyond Mountains)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158609-and-i-can-imagine-farmer-saying-he-doesn-t-care-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 07:48:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[marilyn add a quote by Tracy Kidder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158609-and-i-can-imagine-farmer-saying-he-doesn-t-care-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I can imagine Farmer saying he doesn't care if no one else is willing to follow their example. He's still going to make these hikes, he'd insist, because if you say that seven hours is too long to walk for two families of patients, you're saying that their lives matter less than some others', and the idea that some lives matter less is the root of all that's wrong with the world." -- Tracy Kidder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170423-farmer-went-to-dozens-of-american-and-canadian-universities-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 07:48:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[marilyn add a quote by Tracy Kidder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170423-farmer-went-to-dozens-of-american-and-canadian-universities-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Farmer] went to dozens of American and Canadian universities and colleges, preaching his O for the P [Preferential Option for the Poor] gospel, and to South Africa, where he debated a World Bank official at an international AIDS conference. &quot;Africans must learn to curb their sexual appetites,&quot; the banker remarked, and Farmer replied, &quot;I want to talk about other bankers, not the World Bankers, but bankers in general. My suspicion is they're not getting a lot of sex, because they spend a lot of time screwing the poor." -- Tracy Kidder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43252-the-white-man-is-very-clever-he-came-quietly-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 07:50:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[marilyn add a quote by Chinua Achebe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43252-the-white-man-is-very-clever-he-came-quietly-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The white man is very clever. He came quietly and peaceably with his religion. We were amused at his foolishness and allowed him to stay. Now he has won our brothers, and our clan can no longer act like one. He has put a knife on the things that held us together and we have fallen apart." -- Chinua Achebe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16890-and-i-get-refill-number-three-or-four-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 07:57:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[marilyn add a quote by Aimee Bender]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16890-and-i-get-refill-number-three-or-four-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["and I get refill number three or four and the wine is making my bones loose and it's giving my hair a red sheen and my breasts are blooming and my eyes feel sultry and wise and the dress is water." -- Aimee Bender]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214896-the-wine-glasses-are-empty-except-for-that-one-undrinkable</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 07:57:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[marilyn add a quote by Aimee Bender]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214896-the-wine-glasses-are-empty-except-for-that-one-undrinkable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The wine glasses are empty except for that one undrinkable red spot at the bottom." -- Aimee Bender]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218873-but-what-i-kept-wondering-about-is-this-that-first</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 07:58:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[marilyn add a quote by Aimee Bender]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218873-but-what-i-kept-wondering-about-is-this-that-first]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But what I kept wondering about is this: that first second when she felt her skirt burning, what did she think?  Before she knew it was candles, did she think she'd done it herself?  With the amazing turns of her hips, and the warmth of the music inside her, did she believe, for even one glorious second, that her passion had arrived?" -- Aimee Bender]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122124-i-want-to-be-violated-by-insight</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 07:58:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[marilyn add a quote by Aimee Bender]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122124-i-want-to-be-violated-by-insight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to be violated by insight." -- Aimee Bender]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/666143-my-heart-started-racing-not-the-bad-kind-of-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 09:00:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[marilyn add a quote by Maria Semple]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/666143-my-heart-started-racing-not-the-bad-kind-of-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My heart started racing, not the bad kind of heart racing, like I'm going to die. But the good kind of heart racing, like, Hello, can I help you with something? If not, please step aside because I'm about to kick the shit out of life." -- Maria Semple]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/662582-this-is-why-you-must-love-life-one-day-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 09:00:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[marilyn add a quote by Maria Semple]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/662582-this-is-why-you-must-love-life-one-day-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is why you must love life: one day you're offering up your social security number to the Russian Mafia; two weeks later you're using the word calve as a verb." -- Maria Semple]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/702772-that-s-right-she-told-the-girls-you-are-bored-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 09:00:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[marilyn add a quote by Maria Semple]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/702772-that-s-right-she-told-the-girls-you-are-bored-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's right,' she told the girls. 'You are bored. And I'm going to let you in on a little secret about life. You think it's boring now? Well, it only gets more boring. The sooner you learn it's on you to make life interesting, the better off you'll be." -- Maria Semple]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98534-for-need-can-blossom-into-all-the-compensation-it-requires</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 08:16:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[marilyn add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98534-for-need-can-blossom-into-all-the-compensation-it-requires]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For need can blossom into all the compensation it requires. To crave and to have are as like as a thing and its shadow. For when does a berry break upon the tongue as sweetly as when one longs to taste it, and when is the taste refracted into so many hues and savors of ripeness and earth, and when do our senses know any thing so utterly as when we lack it? And here again is a foreshadowing-the world will be made whole. For to wish for a hand on one's hair is all but to feel it. So whatever we may lose, very craving gives it back to us again. Though we dream and hardly know it, longing, like an angel, fosters us, smooths our hair, and brings us wild strawberries." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 09:15:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[marilyn add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to write the book that wants to be written. And if the book will be too difficult for grown-ups, then you write it for children." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
