<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/475307-alyssa-bicking]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/475307-alyssa-bicking" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 22:30:58 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140777-therefore-dear-sir-love-your-solitude-and-try-to-sing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 22:30:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140777-therefore-dear-sir-love-your-solitude-and-try-to-sing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Therefore, dear Sir, love your solitude and try to sing out with the pain it causes you. For those who are near you are far away... and this shows that the space around you is beginning to grow vast.... be happy about your growth, in which of course you can't take anyone with you, and be gentle with those who stay behind; be confident and calm in front of them and don't torment them with your doubts and don't frighten them with your faith or joy, which they wouldn't be able to comprehend. Seek out some simple and true feeling of what you have in common with them, which doesn't necessarily have to alter when you yourself change again and again; when you see them, love life in a form that is not your own and be indulgent toward those who are growing old, who are afraid of the aloneness that you trust.... and don't expect any understanding; but believe in a love that is being stored up for you like an inheritance, and have faith that in this love there is a strength and a blessing so large that you can travel as far as you wish without having to step outside it." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172382-have-patience-with-everything-that-remains-unsolved-in-your-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 22:35:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172382-have-patience-with-everything-that-remains-unsolved-in-your-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have patience with everything that remains unsolved in your heart. 
...live in the question." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/288835-have-patience-with-everything-that-remains-unsolved-in-your-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 22:37:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/288835-have-patience-with-everything-that-remains-unsolved-in-your-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have patience with everything that remains unsolved in your heart. Try to love the questions themselves, like locked rooms and like books written in a foreign language. Do not now look for the answers. They cannot now be given to you because you could not live them. It is a question of experiencing everything. At present you need to live the question. Perhaps you will gradually, without even noticing it, find yourself experiencing the answer, some distant day." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484086-there-was-just-one-moon-that-familiar-yellow-solitary-moon</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 21:42:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484086-there-was-just-one-moon-that-familiar-yellow-solitary-moon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was just one moon. That familiar, yellow, solitary moon. The same moon that silently floated over fields of pampas grass, the moon that rose--a gleaming, round saucer--over the calm surface of lakes, that tranquilly beamed down on the rooftops of fast-asleep houses. The same moon that brought the high tide to shore, that softly shone on the fur of animals and enveloped and protected travelers at night. The moon that, as a crescent, shaved slivers from the soul--or, as a new moon, silently bathed the earth in its own loneliness. THAT moon." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559389-the-moon-had-been-observing-the-earth-close-up-longer-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 21:43:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559389-the-moon-had-been-observing-the-earth-close-up-longer-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The moon had been observing the earth close-up longer than anyone. It must have witnessed all of the phenomena occurring - and all of the acts carried out - on this earth. But the moon remained silent; it told no stories. All it did was embrace the heavy past with a cool, measured detachment. On the moon there was neither air nor wind. Its vacuum was perfect for preserving memories unscathed. No one could unlock the heart of the moon. Aomame raised her glass to the moon and asked, “Have you gone to bed with someone in your arms lately?” 
The moon did not answer. 
“Do you have any friends?” she asked. 
The moon did not answer. 
“Don’t you get tired of always playing it cool?”
The moon did not answer." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/773066-kindness-covers-all-of-my-political-beliefs-no-need-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 19:49:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Roger Ebert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/773066-kindness-covers-all-of-my-political-beliefs-no-need-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kindness’ covers all of my political beliefs. No need to spell them out. I believe that if, at the end, according to our abilities, we have done something to make others a little happier, and something to make ourselves a little happier, that is about the best we can do. To make others less happy is a crime. To make ourselves unhappy is where all crime starts. We must try to contribute joy to the world. That is true no matter what our problems, our health, our circumstances. We must try. I didn’t always know this and am happy I lived long enough to find it out." -- Roger Ebert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95915-let-everything-happen-to-you-beauty-and-terror-just-keep</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2013 20:16:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95915-let-everything-happen-to-you-beauty-and-terror-just-keep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let everything happen to you
Beauty and terror
Just keep going
No feeling is final" -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119250-do-not-assume-that-he-who-seeks-to-comfort-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2013 20:18:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119250-do-not-assume-that-he-who-seeks-to-comfort-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not assume that he who seeks to comfort you now, lives untroubled among the simple and quiet words that sometimes do you good. His life may also have much sadness and difficulty, that remains far beyond yours. Were it otherwise, he would never have been able to find these words." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7059-love-consists-of-this-two-solitudes-that-meet-protect-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 06:17:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7059-love-consists-of-this-two-solitudes-that-meet-protect-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love consists of this: two solitudes that meet, protect and greet each other. " -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69566-once-the-realization-is-accepted-that-even-between-the-closest</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 06:28:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Rilke Rainer Maria]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69566-once-the-realization-is-accepted-that-even-between-the-closest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once the realization is accepted that even between the closest human beings infinite distances continue, a wonderful living side by side can grow, if they succeed in loving the distance between them which makes it possible for each to see the other whole against the sky." -- Rilke Rainer Maria]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
