<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/478420-jeremy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/478420-jeremy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 07:19:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/550226-mindfulness-meditation-doesn-t-change-life-life-remains-as-fragile-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 07:19:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Sylvia Boorstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/550226-mindfulness-meditation-doesn-t-change-life-life-remains-as-fragile-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mindfulness meditation doesn't change life.  Life remains as fragile and unpredictable as ever.  Meditation changes the heart's capacity to accept life as it is.  It teaches the heart to be more accommodating, not by beating it into submission, but by making it clear that accommodation is a gratifying choice." -- Sylvia Boorstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630701-don-t-try-to-win-over-the-haters-you-are-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 05:44:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Brené Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630701-don-t-try-to-win-over-the-haters-you-are-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't try to win over the haters; you are not a jackass whisperer." -- Brené Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158523-listen-to-your-life-see-it-for-the-fathomless-mystery</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 14:30:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158523-listen-to-your-life-see-it-for-the-fathomless-mystery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen to your life. See it for the fathomless mystery it is. In the boredom and pain of it, no less than in the excitement and gladness: touch, taste, smell your way to the holy and hidden heart of it, because in the last analysis all moments are key moments, and life itself is grace." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126649-compassion-is-the-sometimes-fatal-capacity-for-feeling-what-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 14:31:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126649-compassion-is-the-sometimes-fatal-capacity-for-feeling-what-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Compassion is the sometimes fatal capacity for feeling what it is like to live inside somebody else's skin. It's the knowledge that there can never really be any peace and joy for me until there is peace and joy finally for you too. " -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5258-we-are-here-to-awaken-from-our-illusion-of-separateness</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 07:18:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5258-we-are-here-to-awaken-from-our-illusion-of-separateness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are here to awaken from our illusion of separateness." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1392-when-we-honestly-ask-ourselves-which-person-in-our-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:18:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Henri Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1392-when-we-honestly-ask-ourselves-which-person-in-our-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we honestly ask ourselves which person in our lives mean the most to us, we often find that it is those who, instead of giving advice, solutions, or cures, have chosen rather to share our pain and touch our wounds with a warm and tender hand. The friend who can be silent with us in a moment of despair or confusion, who can stay with us in an hour of grief and bereavement, who can tolerate not knowing, not curing, not healing and face with us the reality of our powerlessness, that is a friend who cares." -- Henri Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:18:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184013-i-don-t-trust-people-who-don-t-love-themselves-and-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:22:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184013-i-don-t-trust-people-who-don-t-love-themselves-and-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't trust people who don't love themselves and tell me, 'I love you.' ... There is an African saying which is: Be careful when a naked person offers you a shirt." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:23:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't interest me what you do for a living. I want to know what you ache for, and if you dare to dream of meeting your heart's longing.
It doesn't interest me how old you are. I want to know if you will risk looking like a fool for love, for your dream, for the adventure of being alive. 
It doesn't interest me what planets are squaring your moon. I want to know if you have touched the center of your own sorrow, if you have been opened by life's betrayals or have become shriveled and closed from fear of further pain!I want to know if you can sit with pain, mine or your own, without moving to hide it or fade it, or fix it. 
I want to know if you can be with joy, mine or your own, if you can dance with wildness and let the ecstasy fill you to the tips of your fingers and toes without cautioning us to be careful, to be realistic, to remember the limitations of being human. 
It doesn't interest me if the story you are telling me is true. I want to know if you can disappoint another to be true to yourself; if you can bear the accusation of betrayal and not betray your own soul; if you can be faithlessand therefore trustworthy. 
I want to know if you can see beauty even when it's not pretty, every day,and if you can source your own life from its presence. 
I want to know if you can live with failure, yours and mine, and still stand on the edge of the lake and shout to the silver of the full moon, “Yes!”
It doesn't interest me to know where you live or how much money you have. I want to know if you can get up, after the night of grief and despair, weary and bruised to the bone, and do what needs to be done to feed the children. 
It doesn't interest me who you know or how you came to be here. I want to know if you will stand in the center of the fire with me and not shrink back. 
It doesn't interest me where or what or with whom you have studied. I want to know what sustains you, from the inside, when all else falls away. 
I want to know if you can be alone with yourself and if you truly like the company you keep in the empty moments." -- Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6231-even-in-literature-and-art-no-man-who-bothers-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:28:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6231-even-in-literature-and-art-no-man-who-bothers-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even in literature and art, no man who bothers about originality will ever be original: whereas if you simply try to tell the truth (without caring twopence how often it has been told before) you will, nine times out of ten, become original without ever having noticed it." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271044-i-m-about-to-make-a-wild-extreme-and-severe-relationship</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:29:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Greg Behrendt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271044-i-m-about-to-make-a-wild-extreme-and-severe-relationship]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm about to make a wild, extreme and severe relationship rule: the word busy is a load of crap and is most often used by assholes. The word &quot;busy&quot; is the relationship Weapon of Mass Destruction. It seems like a good excuse, but in fact in every silo you uncover, all you're going to find is a man who didn't care enough to call. Remember men are never to busy to get what they want." -- Greg Behrendt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:32:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The really important kind of freedom involves attention, and awareness, and discipline, and effort, and being able truly to care about other people and to sacrifice for them, over and over, in myriad petty little unsexy ways, every day." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365652-i-don-t-care-what-you-think-about-me-i-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:32:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by coco chanel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365652-i-don-t-care-what-you-think-about-me-i-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't care what you think about me. I don't think about you at all." -- coco chanel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282264-it-is-the-time-you-have-wasted-for-your-rose</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:34:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282264-it-is-the-time-you-have-wasted-for-your-rose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is the time you have wasted for your rose that makes your rose so important." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7480-real-isn-t-how-you-are-made-said-the-skin-horse</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:34:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7480-real-isn-t-how-you-are-made-said-the-skin-horse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Real isn't how you are made,' said the Skin Horse. 'It's a thing that happens to you. When a child loves you for a long, long time, not just to play with, but REALLY loves you, then you become Real.'

'Does it hurt?' asked the Rabbit. 

'Sometimes,' said the Skin Horse, for he was always truthful. 'When you are Real you don't mind being hurt.' 

'Does it happen all at once, like being wound up,' he asked, 'or bit by bit?' 

'It doesn't happen all at once,' said the Skin Horse. 'You become. It takes a long time. That's why it doesn't happen often to people who break easily, or have sharp edges, or who have to be carefully kept. Generally, by the time you are Real, most of your hair has been loved off, and your eyes drop out and you get loose in the joints and very shabby. But these things don't matter at all, because once you are Real you can't be ugly, except to people who don't understand." -- Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233569-my-story-is-important-not-because-it-is-mine-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 06:54:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233569-my-story-is-important-not-because-it-is-mine-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My story is important not because it is mine, God knows, but because if I tell it anything like right, the chances are you will recognize that in many ways it is also yours… it is precisely through these stories in all their particularity, as I have long believed and often said, that God makes himself known to each of us more powerfully and personally. If this is true, it means that to lose track of our stories is to be profoundly impoverished not only humanly but also spiritually." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/544061-until-we-can-receive-with-an-open-heart-we-re-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 14:37:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Brené Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/544061-until-we-can-receive-with-an-open-heart-we-re-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until we can receive with an open heart, we're never really giving with an open heart. When we attach judgment to receiving help, we knowingly or unknowingly attach judgment to giving help." -- Brené Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175108-once-there-was-a-young-warrior-her-teacher-told-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 12:34:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175108-once-there-was-a-young-warrior-her-teacher-told-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once there was a young warrior. Her teacher told her that she had to do battle with fear. She didn’t want to do that. It seemed too aggressive; it was scary; it seemed unfriendly. But the teacher said she had to do it and gave her the instructions for the battle. The day arrived. The student warrior stood on one side, and fear stood on the other. The warrior was feeling very small, and fear was looking big and wrathful. They both had their weapons. The young warrior roused herself and went toward fear, prostrated three times, and asked, &quot;May I have permission to go into battle with you?&quot; Fear said, &quot;Thank you for showing me so much respect that you ask permission.&quot; Then the young warrior said, &quot;How can I defeat you?&quot; Fear replied, &quot;My weapons are that I talk fast, and I get very close to your face. Then you get completely unnerved, and you do whatever I say. If you don’t do what I tell you, I have no power. You can listen to me, and you can have respect for me. You can even be convinced by me. But if you don’t do what I say, I have no power.&quot; In that way, the student warrior learned how to defeat fear. " -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215417-there-is-a-common-misunderstanding-among-the-human-beings-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 13:21:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215417-there-is-a-common-misunderstanding-among-the-human-beings-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a common misunderstanding among the human beings who have ever been born on earth that the best way to live is to try to avoid pain and just try to get comfortable.  You see this even in insects and animals and birds.  All of us are the some.  A much more interesting, kind and joyful approach to life is to begin to develop our curiosity, not caring whether the object of our curiosity is bitter or sweet.  To lead to a life that goes beyond pettiness and prejudice and always wanting to make sure that everything turns out on our own terms, to lead a more passionate, full, and delightful life than that, we must realize that we can endure a lot of pain and pleasure for the sake of finding out who we are and what this world is, how we tick and how our world ticks, how the whole thing just is.  If we are committed to comfort at any cost, as soon as we come up against the least edge of pain, we’re going to run; we’ll never know what’s beyond that particular barrier or wall or fearful thing." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/577161-it-isn-t-the-things-that-happen-to-us-in-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 13:34:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/577161-it-isn-t-the-things-that-happen-to-us-in-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It isn't the things that happen to us in our lives that cause us to suffer, it's how we relate to the things that happen to us that causes us to suffer." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219728-well-it-seems-to-me-that-the-best-relationships--</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 09:44:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Gillian Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219728-well-it-seems-to-me-that-the-best-relationships--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, it seems to me that the best relationships - the ones that last - are frequently the ones that are rooted in friendship. You know, one day you look at the person and you see something more than you did the night before. Like a switch has been flicked somewhere. And the person who was just a friend is... suddenly the only person you can ever imagine yourself with." -- Gillian Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
