<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/478468-jollene]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/478468-jollene" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 21:12:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410302-a-revolutionary-woman-can-t-have-no-reactionary-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 21:12:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jollene add a quote by Assata Shakur]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410302-a-revolutionary-woman-can-t-have-no-reactionary-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A revolutionary woman can't have no reactionary man." -- Assata Shakur]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419043-tomorrow-the-revolution-will-rise-up-again-clashing-its-weapons</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2011 16:43:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jollene add a quote by Rosa Luxemburg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419043-tomorrow-the-revolution-will-rise-up-again-clashing-its-weapons]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tomorrow the revolution will 'rise up again, clashing its weapons,' and to your horror it will proclaim with trumpets blazing: I was, I am, I shall be!" -- Rosa Luxemburg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35609-dare-to-change-the-world-there-is-nothing-quixotic-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 20:35:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jollene add a quote by Gioconda Belli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35609-dare-to-change-the-world-there-is-nothing-quixotic-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dare to change the world

There is nothing quixotic or romantic in wanting to change the world. It is possible. It is the age-old vocation of all humanity. I can't think of a better life than one dedicated to passion, to dreams, to the stubborness that defies chaos and disillusionment." -- Gioconda Belli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/748876-leaving-is-not-enough-you-must-stay-gone-train-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2013 18:54:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jollene add a quote by Marty McConnell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/748876-leaving-is-not-enough-you-must-stay-gone-train-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Leaving is not enough. You must stay gone. Train your heart like a dog. Change the locks even on the house he's never visited. You lucky, lucky girl. You have an apartment just your size. A bathtub full of tea. A heart the size of Arizona, but not nearly so arid. Don't wish away your cracked past, your crooked toes, your problems are papier mache puppets you made or bought because the vendor at the market was so compelling you just had to have them. You had to have him. And you did. And now you pull down the bridge between your houses, you make him call before he visits, you take a lover for granted, you take a lover who looks at you like maybe you are magic. Make the first bottle you consume in this place a relic. Place it on whatever altar you fashion with a knife and five cranberries. Don't lose too much weight. Stupid girls are always trying to disappear as revenge. And you are not stupid. You loved a man with more hands than a parade of beggars, and here you stand. Heart like a four-poster bed. Heart like a canvas. Heart leaking something so strong they can smell it in the street." -- Marty McConnell]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
