<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/478604-amy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/478604-amy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 May 2008 21:01:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2008 21:01:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Insanity is doing the same thing, over and over again, but expecting different results." -- Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2008 21:03:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3278-i-may-not-have-gone-where-i-intended-to-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2008 21:05:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by douglas adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3278-i-may-not-have-gone-where-i-intended-to-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I may not have gone where I intended to go, but I think I have ended up where I needed to be." -- douglas adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/619-it-is-never-too-late-to-be-what-you-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2008 21:08:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/619-it-is-never-too-late-to-be-what-you-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is never too late to be what you might have been." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/806-it-takes-courage-to-grow-up-and-become-who-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2008 21:08:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by E.E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/806-it-takes-courage-to-grow-up-and-become-who-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It takes courage to grow up and become who you really are." -- E.E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/645-it-is-sometimes-an-appropriate-response-to-reality-to-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2008 21:14:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Philip K. Dick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/645-it-is-sometimes-an-appropriate-response-to-reality-to-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is sometimes an appropriate response to reality to go insane." -- Philip K. Dick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2416-the-major-problem-mdash-one-of-the-major-problems-for-there-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2008 21:16:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2416-the-major-problem-mdash-one-of-the-major-problems-for-there-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The major problem&amp;mdash;&lt;i&gt;one&lt;/i&gt; of the major problems, for there are several&amp;mdash;one of the many major problems with governing people is that of whom you get to do it; or rather of who manages to get people to let them do it to them. 
To summarize: it is a well-known fact that those people who must &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to rule people are, ipso facto, those least suited to do it. 
To summarize the summary: anyone who is capable of getting themselves made President should on no account be allowed to do the job." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2008 21:17:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She is too fond of books, and it has turned her brain." -- Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110144-character-building-begins-in-our-infancy-and-continues-until-death</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2008 07:03:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110144-character-building-begins-in-our-infancy-and-continues-until-death]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Character building begins in our infancy and continues until death." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42442-i-can-t-sit-still-and-see-another-man-slaving-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 17:28:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42442-i-can-t-sit-still-and-see-another-man-slaving-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can't sit still and see another man slaving and working. I want to get up and superintend, and walk round with my hands in my pockets, and tell him what to do. It is my energetic nature. I can't help it." -- Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42444-but-who-wants-to-be-foretold-the-weather-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 17:28:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42444-but-who-wants-to-be-foretold-the-weather-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But who wants to be foretold the weather? It is bad enough when it comes, without our having the misery of knowing about it beforehand." -- Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206108-were-all-instructors-to-realize-that-the-quality-of-mental</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 17:50:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by John Dewey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206108-were-all-instructors-to-realize-that-the-quality-of-mental]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Were all instructors to realize that the quality of mental process, not the production of correct answers, is the measure of educative growth something hardly less than a revolution in teaching would be worked." -- John Dewey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/569302-so-perhaps-it-occurs-to-billy-this-is-the-whole</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 17:26:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Ben Fountain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/569302-so-perhaps-it-occurs-to-billy-this-is-the-whole]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So perhaps, it occurs to Billy, this is the whole point of civilization, the eating of beautiful meals and the taking of decorous dumps, in which case he is for it, having had a bellyful of the other way." -- Ben Fountain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/569311-at-some-point-billy-realized-he-was-expecting-the-president</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 17:39:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Ben Fountain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/569311-at-some-point-billy-realized-he-was-expecting-the-president]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At some point Billy realized he was expecting the president to act, well, embarrassed? Ashamed? For how fucked up everything obviously was. But the commander in chief seemed well pleased with the state of things." -- Ben Fountain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19977-it-s-really-a-wonder-that-i-haven-t-dropped-all-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 21:23:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19977-it-s-really-a-wonder-that-i-haven-t-dropped-all-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's really a wonder that I haven't dropped all my ideals, because they seem so absurd and impossible to carry out. Yet I keep them, because in spite of everything, I still believe that people are really good at heart." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706492-you-like-being-in-love-with-someone-who-s-not-going</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 21:47:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Leah Stewart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706492-you-like-being-in-love-with-someone-who-s-not-going]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You like being in love with someone who’s not going to love you back.” She opened her eyes. He looked at her. “Why would I like that?” she asked. He shrugged. “I don’t know." -- Leah Stewart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40501-enjoy-the-power-and-beauty-of-your-youth-oh-nevermind</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 20:13:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Baz Luhrmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40501-enjoy-the-power-and-beauty-of-your-youth-oh-nevermind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Enjoy the power and beauty of your youth; oh nevermind; you will not 
understand the power and beauty of your youth until they have faded. 
But trust me, in 20 years you’ll look back at photos of yourself and 
recall in a way you can’t grasp now how much possibility lay before 
you and how fabulous you really looked….You’re not as fat as you 
imagine. Don’t worry about the future; or worry, but know that worrying is as 
effective as trying to solve an algebra equation by chewing 
bubblegum. The real troubles in your life are apt to be things that 
never crossed your worried mind; the kind that blindside you at 4pm 
on some idle Tuesday. Do one thing everyday that scares you Sing Don’t be reckless with other people’s hearts, don’t put up with 
people who are reckless with yours. Floss Don’t waste your time on jealousy; sometimes you’re ahead, sometimes 
you’re behind…the race is long, and in the end, it’s only with 
yourself. Remember the compliments you receive, forget the insults; if you 
succeed in doing this, tell me how. Keep your old love letters, throw away your old bank statements. Stretch Don’t feel guilty if you don’t know what you want to do with your 
life…the most interesting people I know didn’t know at 22 what they 
wanted to do with their lives, some of the most interesting 40 year 
olds I know still don’t. Get plenty of calcium. Be kind to your knees, you’ll miss them when they’re gone. Maybe you’ll marry, maybe you won’t, maybe you’ll have children,maybe 
you won’t, maybe you’ll divorce at 40, maybe you’ll dance the funky 
chicken on your 75th wedding anniversary…what ever you do, don’t 
congratulate yourself too much or berate yourself either – your 
choices are half chance, so are everybody else’s. Enjoy your body, 
use it every way you can…don’t be afraid of it, or what other people 
think of it, it’s the greatest instrument you’ll ever 
own.. Dance…even if you have nowhere to do it but in your own living room. Read the directions, even if you don’t follow them. Do NOT read beauty magazines, they will only make you feel ugly. Get to know your parents, you never know when they’ll be gone for 
good. Be nice to your siblings; they are the best link to your past and the 
people most likely to stick with you in the future. Understand that friends come and go,but for the precious few you 
should hold on. Work hard to bridge the gaps in geography and 
lifestyle because the older you get, the more you need the people you 
knew when you were young." -- Baz Luhrmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
