<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/479665-afromom]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/479665-afromom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 06:05:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98949-you-don-t-need-no-gun-control-you-know-what-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 06:05:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Afromom add a quote by Chris Rock]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98949-you-don-t-need-no-gun-control-you-know-what-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t need no gun control, you know what you need? We need some bullet control. Men, we need to control the bullets, that’s right. I think all bullets should cost five thousand dollars… five thousand dollars per bullet… You know why? Cause if a bullet cost five thousand dollars there would be no more innocent bystanders. 
Yeah! Every time somebody get shut we’d say, ‘Damn, he must have done something ... Shit, he’s got fifty thousand dollars worth of bullets in his ass.’
And people would think before they killed somebody if a bullet cost five thousand dollars. ‘Man I would blow your fucking head off…if I could afford it.’ ‘I’m gonna get me another job, I’m going to start saving some money, and you’re a dead man. You’d better hope I can’t get no bullets on layaway.’
So even if you get shot by a stray bullet, you wouldn't have to go to no doctor to get it taken out. Whoever shot you would take their bullet back, like &quot;I believe you got my property." -- Chris Rock]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30798-if-you-can-control-a-man-s-thinking-you-do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 17:32:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Afromom add a quote by Carter Godwin Woodson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30798-if-you-can-control-a-man-s-thinking-you-do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can control a man's thinking you do not have to worry about his action. When you determine what a man shall think you do not have to concern yourself about what he will do. If you make a man feel that he is inferior, you do not have to compel him to accept an inferior status, for he will seek it himself. If you make a man think that he is justly an outcast, you do not have to order him to the back door. He will go without being told; and if there is no back door, his very nature will demand one." -- Carter Godwin Woodson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
