<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/47975-rob]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/47975-rob" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 07:53:07 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38963-the-earth-is-a-very-small-stage-in-a-vast</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 07:53:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38963-the-earth-is-a-very-small-stage-in-a-vast]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The earth is a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena. Think of the rivers of blood spilled by all those generals and emperors so that in glory and in triumph they could become the momentary masters of a fraction of a dot. Think of the endless cruelties visited by the inhabitants of one corner of the dot on scarcely distinguishable inhabitants of some other corner of the dot. How frequent their misunderstandings, how eager they are to kill one another, how fervent their hatreds. Our posturings, our imagined self-importance, the delusion that we have some privileged position in the universe, are challenged by this point of pale light. Our planet is a lonely speck in the great enveloping cosmic dark. In our obscurity -- in all this vastness -- there is no hint that help will come from elsewhere to save us from ourselves. It is up to us. It's been said that astronomy is a humbling, and I might add, a character-building experience. To my mind, there is perhaps no better demonstration of the folly of human conceits than this distant image of our tiny world. To me, it underscores our responsibility to deal more kindly and compassionately with one another and to preserve and cherish that pale blue dot, the only home we've ever known." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97180-no-matter-how-you-care-to-define-it-i-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 09:15:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97180-no-matter-how-you-care-to-define-it-i-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No matter how you care to define it, I do not identify with the local group.  Planet, species, race, nation, state, religion, party, union, club, association, neighborhood improvement committee; I have no interest in any of it.  I love and treasure individuals as I meet them, I loathe and despise the groups they identify with and belong to." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30066-there-are-those-who-scoff-at-the-schoolboy-calling-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 09:15:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30066-there-are-those-who-scoff-at-the-schoolboy-calling-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are those who scoff at the schoolboy, calling him frivolous and
shallow: Yet it was the schoolboy who said 'Faith is believing what you
know ain't so'." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3730-i-find-television-very-educating-every-time-somebody-turns-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 09:15:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Groucho Marx ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3730-i-find-television-very-educating-every-time-somebody-turns-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I find television very educating. Every time somebody turns on the set, I go into the other room and read a book." -- Groucho Marx ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48918-how-is-it-that-hardly-any-major-religion-has-looked</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 07:53:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48918-how-is-it-that-hardly-any-major-religion-has-looked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How is it that hardly any major religion has looked at science and concluded, “This is better than we thought! The Universe is much bigger than our prophets said, grander, more subtle, more elegant?” Instead they say, “No, no, no! My god is a little god, and I want him to stay that way.” A religion, old or new, that stressed the magnificence of the Universe as revealed by modern science might be able to draw forth reserves of reverence and awe hardly tapped by the conventional faiths." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132553-we-will-restore-science-to-its-rightful-place-and-wield</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 07:54:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Barack Obama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132553-we-will-restore-science-to-its-rightful-place-and-wield]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We will restore science to its rightful place and wield technology's wonders to raise health care's quality and lower its cost." -- Barack Obama]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32170-one-of-the-great-tragedies-of-mankind-is-that-morality</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 07:53:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32170-one-of-the-great-tragedies-of-mankind-is-that-morality]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the great tragedies of mankind is that morality has been hijacked by religion. So now people assume that religion and morality have a necessary connection. But the basis of morality is really very simple and doesn't require religion at all." -- Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44909-science-is-not-only-compatible-with-spirituality-it-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 09:46:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44909-science-is-not-only-compatible-with-spirituality-it-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Science is not only compatible with spirituality; it is a profound source of spirituality. When we recognize our place in an immensity of light‐years and in the passage of ages, when we grasp the intricacy, beauty, and subtlety of life, then that soaring feeling, that sense of elation and humility combined, is surely spiritual. So are our emotions in the presence of great art or music or literature, or acts of exemplary selfless courage such as those of Mohandas Gandhi or Martin Luther King, Jr. The notion that science and spirituality are somehow mutually exclusive does a disservice to both." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56958-the-best-way-to-avoid-abuses-is-for-the-populace</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 09:47:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56958-the-best-way-to-avoid-abuses-is-for-the-populace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best way to avoid abuses is for the populace in general to be scientifically literate, to understand the implications of such investigations. In exchange for freedom of inquiry, scientists are obliged to explain their work. If science is considered a closed priesthood, too difficult and arcane for the average person to understand, the dangers of abuse are greater. But if science is a topic of general interest and concern - if both its delights and its social consequences are discussed regularly and competently in the schools, the press, and at the dinner table - we have greatly improved our prospects for learning how the world really is and for improving both it and us." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50379-extraordinary-claims-require-extraordinary-evidence</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 07:52:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50379-extraordinary-claims-require-extraordinary-evidence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Extraordinary claims require extraordinary evidence." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 19:48:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.

So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/646-reality-is-that-which-when-you-stop-believing-in-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 19:49:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Philip K. Dick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/646-reality-is-that-which-when-you-stop-believing-in-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reality is that which, when you stop believing in it, doesn't go away." -- Philip K. Dick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1716-travel-is-fatal-to-prejudice-bigotry-and-narrow-mindedness-and-many</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 13:15:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1716-travel-is-fatal-to-prejudice-bigotry-and-narrow-mindedness-and-many]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Travel is fatal to prejudice, bigotry, and narrow-mindedness, and many of our people need it sorely on these accounts. Broad, wholesome, charitable views of men and things cannot be acquired by vegetating in one little corner of the earth all one's lifetime." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4082-now-my-own-suspicion-is-that-the-universe-is-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 17:30:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by J. B. S. Haldane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4082-now-my-own-suspicion-is-that-the-universe-is-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now, my own suspicion is that the universe is not only queerer than we suppose, but queerer than we can suppose. I have read and heard many attempts at a systematic account of it, from materialism and theosophy to the Christian system or that of Kant, and I have always felt that they were much too simple. I suspect that there are more things in heaven and earth that are dreamed of, or can be dreamed of, in any philosophy. That is the reason why I have no philosophy myself, and must be my excuse for dreaming." -- J. B. S. Haldane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111138-once-when-a-religionist-denounced-me-in-unmeasured-terms-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 10:03:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Isaac Asimov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111138-once-when-a-religionist-denounced-me-in-unmeasured-terms-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once, when a religionist denounced me in unmeasured terms, I sent him a card saying, &quot;I am sure you believe that I will go to hell when I die, and that once there I will suffer all the pains and tortures the sadistic ingenuity of your deity can devise and that this torture will continue forever. Isn't that enough for you? Do you have to call me bad names in addition?" -- Isaac Asimov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98719-come-live-with-me-and-be-my-love-and-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 06:12:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Ogden Nash]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98719-come-live-with-me-and-be-my-love-and-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Come live with me and be my love 
And we will all the pleasures prove 
Of a marriage conducted with economy 
In the Twentieth Century Anno Donomy. 
We’ll live in a dear little walk-up flat 
With practically room to swing a cat 
And a potted cactus to give it hauteur 
And a bathtub equipped with dark brown water. 
We’ll eat, without undue discouragement, 
Foods low in cost but high in nouragement 
And quaff with pleasure, while chatting wittily,
The peculiar wine of Little Italy. 
We’ll remind each other it’s smart to be thrifty
And buy our clothes for something-fifty. 
We’ll bus for miles on holidays 
For seas at depressing matinees, 
And every Sunday we’ll have a lark 
And take a walk in Central Park. 
And one of these days not too remote 
You’ll probably up and cut my throat." -- Ogden Nash]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4419-science-is-not-only-compatible-with-spirituality-it-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 06:53:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4419-science-is-not-only-compatible-with-spirituality-it-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Science is not only compatible with spirituality; it is a profound source of spirituality." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
