<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/482838-david-antrobus]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/482838-david-antrobus" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 00:23:29 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25350-it-had-ceased-raining-in-the-night-and-he-walked</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 00:23:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25350-it-had-ceased-raining-in-the-night-and-he-walked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It had ceased raining in the night and he walked out on the road and called for the dog. He called and called. Standing in that inexplicable darkness. Where there was no sound anywhere save only the wind. After a while he sat in the road. He took off his hat and placed it on the tarmac before him and he bowed his head and held his face in his hands and wept. He sat there for a long time and after a while the east did gray and after a while the right and godmade sun did rise, once again, for all and without distinction." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93593-no-live-organism-can-continue-for-long-to-exist-sanely</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 20:16:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Shirley Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93593-no-live-organism-can-continue-for-long-to-exist-sanely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No live organism can continue for long to exist sanely under conditions of absolute reality; even larks and katydids are supposed, by some, to dream. Hill House, not sane, stood by itself against its hills, holding darkness within; it had stood so for eighty years and might stand for eighty more. Within, walls continued upright, bricks met neatly, floors were firm, and doors were sensibly shut; silence lay steadily against the wood and stone of Hill House, and whatever walked there, walked alone." -- Shirley Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119482-i-lingered-round-them-under-that-benign-sky-watched-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 12:47:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119482-i-lingered-round-them-under-that-benign-sky-watched-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I lingered round them, under that benign sky; watched the moths fluttering among the heath and hare-bells; listened to the soft wind breathing through the grass; and wondered how anyone could ever imagine unquiet slumbers for the sleepers in that quiet earth." -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2787-we-write-to-taste-life-twice-in-the-moment-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 12:47:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2787-we-write-to-taste-life-twice-in-the-moment-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We write to taste life twice, in the moment and in retrospect." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/613268-astral-weeks-insofar-as-it-can-be-pinned-down-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 12:50:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Lester Bangs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/613268-astral-weeks-insofar-as-it-can-be-pinned-down-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Astral Weeks,” insofar as it can be pinned down, is a record about people stunned by life, completely overwhelmed, stalled in their skins, their ages and selves, paralyzed by the enormity of what in one moment of vision they can comprehend. It is a precious and terrible gift, born of a terrible truth, because what they see is both infinitely beautiful and terminally horrifying: the unlimited human ability to create or destroy, according to whim. It’s no Eastern mystic or psychedelic vision of the emerald beyond, nor is it some Baudelairean perception of the beauty of sleaze and grotesquerie. Maybe what it boils down to is one moment’s knowledge of the miracle of life, with its inevitable concomitant, a vertiginous glimpse of the capacity to be hurt, and the capacity to inflict that hurt." -- Lester Bangs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221868-i-do-know-that-for-the-sympathy-of-one-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 12:50:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Mary Shelley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221868-i-do-know-that-for-the-sympathy-of-one-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do know that for the sympathy of one living being, I would make peace with all. I have love in me the likes of which you can scarcely imagine and rage the likes of which you would not believe. If I cannot satisfy the one, I will indulge the other." -- Mary Shelley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358111-terror-is-the-desire-to-save-your-own-ass-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 12:50:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Joe Hill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358111-terror-is-the-desire-to-save-your-own-ass-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Terror is the desire to save your own ass, but horror is rooted in sympathy." -- Joe Hill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1982-that-it-will-never-come-again-is-what-makes-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 22:13:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Emily Dickinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1982-that-it-will-never-come-again-is-what-makes-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That it will never come again is what makes life so sweet." -- Emily Dickinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/496800-do-not-rush-when-you-read-a-book-has-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 22:13:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Ingrid Holm-Garibay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/496800-do-not-rush-when-you-read-a-book-has-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not rush when you read, a book has no expiration date." -- Ingrid Holm-Garibay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/471750-in-prehistoric-times-early-man-was-bowled-over-by-natural</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 22:13:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Signe Pike]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/471750-in-prehistoric-times-early-man-was-bowled-over-by-natural]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In prehistoric times, early man was bowled over by natural events: rain, thunder, lightning, the violent shaking and moving of the ground, mountains spewing deathly hot lava, the glow of the moon, the burning heat of the sun, the twinkling of the stars.  Our human brain searched for an answer, and the conclusion was that it all must be caused by something greater than ourselves - this, of course, sprouted the earliest seeds of religion.  This theory is certainly reflected in faery lore.  In the beautiful sloping hills of Connemara in Ireland, for example, faeries were believed to have been just as beautiful, peaceful, and pleasant as the world around them.  But in the Scottish Highlands, with their dark, brooding mountains and eerie highland lakes, villagers warned of deadly water-kelpies and spirit characters that packed a bit more punch." -- Signe Pike]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57688-i-hate-writing-i-love-having-written</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2013 09:18:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Dorothy Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57688-i-hate-writing-i-love-having-written]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hate writing, I love having written." -- Dorothy Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/772434-we-are-consciousness-wanting-to-expand</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2013 22:45:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Helene Cardona]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/772434-we-are-consciousness-wanting-to-expand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are consciousness wanting to expand." -- Helene Cardona]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104400-from-daydreams-on-the-road-there-was-no-waking-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 19:24:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104400-from-daydreams-on-the-road-there-was-no-waking-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From daydreams on the road there was no waking. He plodded on. He could remember everything of her save her scent. Seated in a theatre with her beside him leaning forward listening to the music. Gold scrollwork and sconces and the tall columnar folds of the drapes at either side of the stage. She held his hand in her lap and he could feel the tops of her stockings through the thin stuff of her summer dress. Freeze this frame. Now call down your dark and your cold and be damned." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128493-he-lay-listening-to-the-water-drip-in-the-woods</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 19:37:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128493-he-lay-listening-to-the-water-drip-in-the-woods]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He lay listening to the water drip in the woods. Bedrock, this. The cold and the silence. The ashes of the late world carried on the bleak and temporal winds to and fro in the void. Carried forth and scattered and carried forth again. Everything uncoupled from its shoring. Unsupported in the ashen air. Sustained by a breath, trembling and brief. If only my heart were stone." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72386-in-the-morning-they-came-up-out-of-the-ravine</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 19:39:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72386-in-the-morning-they-came-up-out-of-the-ravine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the morning they came up out of the ravine and took to the road again. He'd carved the boy a flute from a piece of roadside cane and he took it from his coat and gave it to him. The boy took it wordlessly. After a while he fell back and after a while the man could hear him playing. A formless music for the age to come. Or perhaps the last music on earth called up from out of the ashes of its ruin. The man turned and looked back at him. He was lost in concentration. The man thought he seemed some sad and solitary changeling child announcing the arrival of a traveling spectacle in shire and village who does not know that behind him the players have all been carried off by wolves." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9712-in-the-dream-from-which-he-d-wakened-he-had-wandered</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 21:28:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9712-in-the-dream-from-which-he-d-wakened-he-had-wandered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the dream from which he'd wakened he had wandered in a cave where the child led him by the hand. Their light playing over the wet flowstone walls. Like pilgrims in a fable swallowed up and lost among the inward parts of some granitic beast. Deep stone flues where the water dripped and sang. Tolling in the silence the minutes of the earth and the hours and the days of it and the years without cease. Until they stood in a great stone room where lay a black and ancient lake. And on the far shore a creature that raised its dripping mouth from the rimstone pool and stared into the light with eyes dead white and sightless as the eggs of spiders. It swung its head low over the water as if to take the scent of what it could not see. Crouching there pale and naked and translucent, its alabaster bones cast up in shadow on the rocks behind it. Its bowels, its beating heart. The brain that pulsed in a dull glass bell. It swung its head from side to side and then gave out a low moan and turned and lurched away and loped soundlessly into the dark." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/264886-and-perhaps-beyond-those-shrouded-swells-another-man-did-walk</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 21:28:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/264886-and-perhaps-beyond-those-shrouded-swells-another-man-did-walk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And perhaps beyond those shrouded swells another man did walk with another child on the dead gray sands. Slept but a sea apart on another beach among the bitter ashes of the world or stood in their rags lost to the same indifferent sun." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137029-he-d-watched-a-falcon-fall-down-the-long-blue-wall</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 21:34:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137029-he-d-watched-a-falcon-fall-down-the-long-blue-wall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He'd watched a falcon fall down the long blue wall of the mountain and break with the keel of its breastbone the midmost from a flight of cranes and take it to the river below all gangly and wrecked and trailing its loose and blowsy plumage in the still autumn air." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329305-there-were-times-when-he-sat-watching-the-boy-sleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 21:35:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329305-there-were-times-when-he-sat-watching-the-boy-sleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There were times when he sat watching the boy sleep that he would begin to sob uncontrollably but it wasn't about death. He wasn't sure what it was about but he thought it was about beauty or goodness. Things that he'd no longer any way to think about at all." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291293-creedless-shells-of-men-tottering-down-the-causeways-like-migrants</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 21:35:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291293-creedless-shells-of-men-tottering-down-the-causeways-like-migrants]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Creedless shells of men tottering down the causeways like migrants in a feverland." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/561015-they-trekked-out-along-the-crescent-sweep-of-beach-keeping</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 21:43:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/561015-they-trekked-out-along-the-crescent-sweep-of-beach-keeping]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They trekked out along the crescent sweep of beach, keeping to the firmer sand below the tidewrack. They stood, their clothes flapping softly. Glass floats covered with a gray crust. The bones of seabirds. At the tideline a woven mat of weeds and the ribs of fishes in their millions stretching along the shore as far as the eye could see like an isocline of death. One vast salt sepulchre. Senseless. Senseless." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/802271-are-you-okay-he-said-the-boy-nodded-then-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 21:43:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/802271-are-you-okay-he-said-the-boy-nodded-then-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Are you okay? he said. The boy nodded. Then they set out along the blacktop in the gunmetal light, shuffling through the ash, each the other's world entire." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498662-all-things-of-grace-and-beauty-such-that-one-holds</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 21:43:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498662-all-things-of-grace-and-beauty-such-that-one-holds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All things of grace and beauty such that one holds them to one's heart  have a common provenance in pain. Their birth in grief and ashes. So, he whispered to the sleeping boy. I have you." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878810-i-awoke-from-this-nightmare-into-a-freezing-cold-motel</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 20:37:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Maggie Nelson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878810-i-awoke-from-this-nightmare-into-a-freezing-cold-motel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I awoke from this nightmare into a freezing cold motel room: the heater had broken at some point during the night, and the fan was now blowing icy air into the room.

At first I tried to keep warm under the crappy motel bedspread by thinking about the man I loved. At the time he was traveling in Europe, and was thus unreachable. I didn't know it yet, but as I lay there, he was traveling with another woman. Does it matter now? I tried hard to feel his body wrapped tightly around mine.

Next I tried to imagine everyone I had ever loved, and everyone who had ever loved me, wrapped around me. I tried to feel that I was the composite of all these people, instead of alone in a shitty motel room with a broken heater somewhere outside of Detroit, a few miles from where Jane's body was dumped thirty-six years ago on a March night just like this one.

'Need each other as much as you can bear,' writes Eileen Myles. 'Everywhere you go in the world.'

I felt the wild need for any or all of these people that night. Lying there alone, I began to feel - perhaps even to know - that I did not exist apart from their love and need of me.

Of this latter I felt less sure, but it seemed possible, if the equation worked both ways.

Falling asleep I thought, 'Maybe this, for me, is the hand of God." -- Maggie Nelson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13494-how-do-our-lives-ravel-out-into-the-no-wind-no-sound</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 17:34:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13494-how-do-our-lives-ravel-out-into-the-no-wind-no-sound]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How do our lives ravel out 
into the no-wind, no-sound,
the weary gestures wearily recapitulant:
echoes of old compulsions with no-hand on no-string:
in sunset we fall into furious attitudes,
dead gestures of dolls." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329272-it-s-because-i-m-alone-if-i-could-just-feel-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 17:36:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329272-it-s-because-i-m-alone-if-i-could-just-feel-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's because I'm alone.. If I could just feel it, it would be different, because I would not be alone. But if I were not alone, everybody would know it. And he could do so much for me, and then I would not be alone. Then I could be all right alone." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/880347-before-us-the-thick-dark-current-runs-it-talks-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 17:39:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/880347-before-us-the-thick-dark-current-runs-it-talks-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Before us the thick dark current runs. It talks up to us in a murmur become ceaseless and myriad, the yellow surface dimpled monstrously into fading swirls travelling along the surface for an instant, silent, impermanent and profoundly significant, as though just beneath the surface something huge and alive waked for a moment of lazy alertness out of and into light slumber again." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 17:56:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the only people for me are the mad ones, the ones who are mad to live, mad to talk, mad to be saved, desirous of everything at the same time, the ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn like fabulous yellow roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79318-they-threw-me-off-the-haytruck-about-noon</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 07:10:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by James M. Cain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79318-they-threw-me-off-the-haytruck-about-noon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They threw me off the haytruck about noon." -- James M. Cain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/872172-i-kissed-her-her-eyes-were-shining-up-at-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 07:10:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by James M. Cain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/872172-i-kissed-her-her-eyes-were-shining-up-at-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I kissed her. Her eyes were shining up at me like two blue stars. It was like being in church." -- James M. Cain]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
