<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/48686-jessica-n]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/48686-jessica-n" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 10:43:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290425-and-yet-i-wasn-t-sure-what-his-weakness-was-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 10:43:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Wayne Elise]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290425-and-yet-i-wasn-t-sure-what-his-weakness-was-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And yet I wasn't sure what his weakness was. We all do that as we get to know someone. Like a tabloid editor, we search for both greatness and weakness, jotting down notes in our heads for future exploitation.  We are never comfortable with those who have no visible flaw." -- Wayne Elise]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17002-people-worry-about-kids-playing-with-guns-and-teenagers-watching</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 23:40:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17002-people-worry-about-kids-playing-with-guns-and-teenagers-watching]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People worry about kids playing with guns, and teenagers watching violent videos; we are scared that some sort of culture of violence will take them over.  Nobody worries about kids listening to thousands - literally thousands - of songs about broken hearts and rejection and pain and misery and loss." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117986-it-seems-to-me-if-you-add-music-and-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 23:42:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117986-it-seems-to-me-if-you-add-music-and-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seems to me if you add music (and books, probably, and films, and plays, and anything that makes you feel) at the center of your being, then you can't afford to sort out your love life, start to think of it as the finished product. You've got to pick at it, keep it alive and in turmoil, you've got to pick at it and unravel it until it all comes apart and you're compelled to start all over again. Maybe we live life at too high a pitch, those of us who absorb emotional things all day, and as a consequence we can never feel merely content: we have to be unhappy, or ecstatically, head-over-heels happy, and those states are difficult to achieve within a stable, solid relationship." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117039-i-used-to-think--and-given-the-way-we-ended-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 10:42:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117039-i-used-to-think--and-given-the-way-we-ended-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I used to think--and given the way we ended up, maybe I still do--that all relationships need the kind of violent shove that a crush brings, just to get you started and to push you over the humps. And then, when the energy from that shove has gone and you come to something approaching a halt, you have to look around and see what you've got. It could be something completely different, it could be something roughly the same, but gentler and calmer, or it could be nothing at all." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18645-the-surest-way-to-corrupt-a-youth-is-to-instruct</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 10:42:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18645-the-surest-way-to-corrupt-a-youth-is-to-instruct]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The surest way to corrupt a youth is to instruct him to hold in higher esteem those who think alike than those who think differently." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6873-i-think-it-s-so-foolish-for-people-to-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2010 18:26:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Georgia O'Keefe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6873-i-think-it-s-so-foolish-for-people-to-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think it's so foolish for people to want to be happy.  Happy is so momentary--you're happy for an instant and then you start thinking again.  Interest is the most important thing in life; happiness is temporary, but interest is continuous." -- Georgia O'Keefe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328134-socialism-never-took-root-in-america-because-the-poor-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 00:31:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328134-socialism-never-took-root-in-america-because-the-poor-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Socialism never took root in America because the poor see themselves not as an exploited proletariat but as temporarily embarrassed millionaires." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
