<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/4884-roshny]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/4884-roshny" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 08:56:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28854-maybe-i-couldn-t-make-it-maybe-i-don-t-have-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 08:56:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[roshny add a quote by Germaine Greer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28854-maybe-i-couldn-t-make-it-maybe-i-don-t-have-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe I couldn’t make it. Maybe I don’t have a pretty smile, good teeth, nice tits, long legs, a cheeky arse, a sexy voice. Maybe I don’t know how to handle men and increase my market value, so that the rewards due to the feminine will accrue to me. Then again, maybe I’m sick of the masquerade. I’m sick of pretending eternal youth. I’m sick of belying my own intelligence, my own will, my own sex. I’m sick of peering at the world through false eyelashes, so everything I see is mixed with a shadow of bought hairs; I’m sick of weighting my head with a dead mane, unable to move my neck freely, terrified of rain, of wind, of dancing too vigorously in case I sweat into my lacquered curls. I’m sick of the Powder Room. I’m sick of pretending that some fatuous male’s self-important pronouncements are the objects of my undivided attention, I’m sick of going to films and plays when someone else wants to, and sick of having no opinions of my own about either. I’m sick of being a transvestite. I refuse to be a female impersonator. I am a woman, not a castrate." -- Germaine Greer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37394-holding-anger-is-a-poison-it-eats-you-from-inside-we-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 19:33:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[roshny add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37394-holding-anger-is-a-poison-it-eats-you-from-inside-we-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Holding anger is a poison...It eats you from inside...We think that by hating someone we hurt them...But hatred is a curved blade...and the harm we do to others...we also do to ourselves." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
