<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/49049-mr-5x5]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/49049-mr-5x5" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 17:42:59 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77496-a-man-to-be-greatly-good-must-imagine-intensely-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 17:42:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mr add a quote by Percy Bysshe Shelley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77496-a-man-to-be-greatly-good-must-imagine-intensely-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man, to be greatly good, must imagine intensely and comprehensively; he must put himself in the place of another and many others; the pains and pleasures of his species must become his own. The great instrument of moral good is the imagination." -- Percy Bysshe Shelley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94673-the-passion-for-naming-things-is-an-odd-human-trait</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 17:06:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mr add a quote by George Gaylord Simpson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94673-the-passion-for-naming-things-is-an-odd-human-trait]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The passion for naming things is an odd human trait.  It is strange that men always feel so much more at ease when they have put appellations on the things around them and that a wild, new region almost seems familiar and subdued once enough names have been used on it, even though in fact it is not changed in the slightest.  Or, on second thought, it is perhaps not really strange.  The urge to name must be as old as the human race, as old as speech which is one of the really fundamental characteristics by which  we rise above the brutes, and thus a basic and essential part of the human spirit or soul.  The naming fallacy is common enough even in science.  Many a scientist claims to have explained some phenomenon when in truth all he has done is to give it a name. " -- George Gaylord Simpson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147756-maybe-each-human-being-lives-in-a-unique-world-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 15:40:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mr add a quote by Philip K. Dick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147756-maybe-each-human-being-lives-in-a-unique-world-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe each human being lives in a unique world, a private world different from those inhabited and experienced by all other humans. . . If reality differs from person to person, can we speak of reality singular, or shouldn't we really be talking about plural realities? And if there are plural realities, are some more true (more real) than others? What about the world of a schizophrenic? Maybe it's as real as our world. Maybe we cannot say that we are in touch with reality and he is not, but should instead say, His reality is so different from ours that he can't explain his to us, and we can't explain ours to him. The problem, then, is that if subjective worlds are experienced too differently, there occurs a breakdown in communication ... and there is the real illness." -- Philip K. Dick]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
