<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/4914-dustin-langan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/4914-dustin-langan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 11:27:58 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160206-the-only-difference-between-reality-and-fiction-is-that-fiction</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 11:27:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dustin add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160206-the-only-difference-between-reality-and-fiction-is-that-fiction]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only difference between reality and fiction is that fiction needs to be credible." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4650-truth-is-stranger-than-fiction-but-it-is-because-fiction</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 11:29:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dustin add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4650-truth-is-stranger-than-fiction-but-it-is-because-fiction]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Truth is stranger than fiction, but it is because Fiction is obliged to stick to possibilities; Truth isn't." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40581-we-were-keeping-our-eye-on-1984-when-the-year</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 23:28:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dustin add a quote by Neil Postman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40581-we-were-keeping-our-eye-on-1984-when-the-year]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We were keeping our eye on 1984. When the year came and the prophecy didn't, thoughtful Americans sang softly in praise of themselves. The roots of liberal democracy had held. Wherever else the terror had happened, we, at least, had not been visited by [author:Orwellian|3706] nightmares.

But we had forgotten that alongside [author:Orwell|3706]'s dark vision, there was another - slightly older, slightly less well known, equally chilling: [author:Aldous Huxley|3487]'s Brave New World. Contrary to common belief even among the educated, [author:Huxley|3487] and [author:Orwell|3706] did not prophesy the same thing. [author:Orwell|3706] warns that we will be overcome by an externally imposed oppression. But in [author:Huxley|3487]'s vision, no Big Brother is required to deprive people of their autonomy, maturity and history. As he saw it, people will come to love their oppression, to adore the technologies that undo their capacities to think.

What [author:Orwell|3706] feared were those who would ban books. What [author:Huxley|3487] feared was that there would be no reason to ban a book, for there would be no one who wanted to read one. [author:Orwell|3706] feared those who would deprive us of information. [author:Huxley|3487] feared those who would give us so much that we would be reduced to passivity and egoism. [author:Orwell|3706] feared that the truth would be concealed from us. [author:Huxley|3487] feared the truth would be drowned in a sea of irrelevance. [author:Orwell|3706] feared we would become a captive culture. [author:Huxley|3487] feared we would become a trivial culture, preoccupied with some equivalent of the feelies, the orgy porgy, and the centrifugal bumblepuppy. As [author:Huxley|3487] remarked in Brave New World Revisited, the civil libertarians and rationalists who are ever on the alert to oppose tyranny &quot;&lt;i&gt;failed to take into account man's almost infinite appetite for distractions&lt;/i&gt;.&quot; In 1984, [author:Orwell|3706] added, people are controlled by inflicting pain. In Brave New World, they are controlled by inflicting pleasure. In short, [author:Orwell|3706] feared that what we fear will ruin us. [author:Huxley|3487] feared that what we desire will ruin us.

This book is about the possibility that [author:Huxley|3487], not [author:Orwell|3706], was right." -- Neil Postman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
