<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/491972-michelle-ye]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/491972-michelle-ye" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 01:13:07 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1502-facts-do-not-cease-to-exist-because-they-are-ignored</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 01:13:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1502-facts-do-not-cease-to-exist-because-they-are-ignored]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Facts do not cease to exist because they are ignored." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 00:49:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is our choices, Harry, that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 18:13:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 18:13:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened." -- Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3356-i-like-nonsense-it-wakes-up-the-brain-cells-fantasy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 18:15:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3356-i-like-nonsense-it-wakes-up-the-brain-cells-fantasy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like nonsense, it wakes up the brain cells. Fantasy is a necessary ingredient in living." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3443-when-one-door-of-happiness-closes-another-opens-but-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 18:33:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Helen Keller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3443-when-one-door-of-happiness-closes-another-opens-but-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When one door of happiness closes, another opens; but often we look so long at the closed door that we do not see the one which has been opened for us." -- Helen Keller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8-talent-hits-a-target-no-one-else-can-hit-genius</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 18:33:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8-talent-hits-a-target-no-one-else-can-hit-genius]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Talent hits a target no one else can hit. Genius hits a target no one else can see." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1908-if-you-make-a-mistake-and-do-not-correct-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 18:36:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Confucius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1908-if-you-make-a-mistake-and-do-not-correct-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you make a mistake and do not correct it, this is called a mistake." -- Confucius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17266-never-never-be-afraid-to-do-what-s-right-especially-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 18:36:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17266-never-never-be-afraid-to-do-what-s-right-especially-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never, never be afraid to do what's right, especially if the well-being of a person or animal is at stake. Society's punishments are small compared to the wounds we inflict on our soul when we look the other way." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13287-you-see-things-you-say-why-but-i-dream-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 18:37:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13287-you-see-things-you-say-why-but-i-dream-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You see things; you say, 'Why?' But I dream things that never were; and I say 'Why not?" -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4078-the-saddest-aspect-of-life-right-now-is-that-science</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 18:42:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Isaac Asimov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4078-the-saddest-aspect-of-life-right-now-is-that-science]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The saddest aspect of life right now is that science gathers knowledge faster than society gathers wisdom." -- Isaac Asimov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26930-he-who-knows-all-the-answers-has-not-been-asked</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 18:43:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Confucius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26930-he-who-knows-all-the-answers-has-not-been-asked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He who knows all the answers has not been asked all the questions." -- Confucius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22276-knowledge-speaks-but-wisdom-listens</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 18:43:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Jimi Hendrix]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22276-knowledge-speaks-but-wisdom-listens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Knowledge speaks, but wisdom listens" -- Jimi Hendrix]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4940-don-t-join-the-book-burners-don-t-think-you-re-going-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 22:28:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Dwight D. Eisenhower]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4940-don-t-join-the-book-burners-don-t-think-you-re-going-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't join the book burners. Don't think you're going to conceal faults by concealing evidence that they ever existed. Don't be afraid to go in your library and read every book..." -- Dwight D. Eisenhower]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18115-those-who-deny-freedom-to-others-deserve-it-not-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 22:29:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18115-those-who-deny-freedom-to-others-deserve-it-not-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who deny freedom to others deserve it not for themselves." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5989-i-don-t-like-that-man-i-must-get-to-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 22:32:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5989-i-don-t-like-that-man-i-must-get-to-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't like that man. I must get to know him better." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2175-the-easy-confidence-with-which-i-know-another-man-s-religion</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 22:38:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2175-the-easy-confidence-with-which-i-know-another-man-s-religion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The easy confidence with which I know another man's religion is folly teaches me to suspect that my own is also." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4502-the-president-of-the-united-states-has-claimed-on-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 22:39:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4502-the-president-of-the-united-states-has-claimed-on-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The president of the United States has claimed, on more than one occasion, to be in dialogue with God. If he said that he was talking to God through his hairdryer, this would precipitate a national emergency. I fail to see how the addition of a hairdryer makes the claim more ridiculous or offensive." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5236-religion-begins-in-story-yes-it-does-because-religion-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 22:41:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5236-religion-begins-in-story-yes-it-does-because-religion-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Religion begins in story. Yes, it does, because religion is an attempt to make sense of what is incomprehensible to us, what is inexplicable, what is awe-inspiring, what is frightening, what moves us to great wonder, and so on. That is the religious impulse, and it is part of our psychological makeup -- of everyone's psychological makeup." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2349-the-philosophy-of-atheism-represents-a-concept-of-life-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 22:41:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Emma Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2349-the-philosophy-of-atheism-represents-a-concept-of-life-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The philosophy of Atheism represents a concept of life without any metaphysical Beyond or Divine Regulator. It is the concept of an actual, real world with its liberating, expanding and beautifying possibilities, as against an unreal world, which, with its spirits, oracles, and mean contentment has kept humanity in helpless degradation." -- Emma Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4951-the-truth-does-not-change-according-to-our-ability-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 22:44:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4951-the-truth-does-not-change-according-to-our-ability-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth does not change according to our ability to stomach it." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10730-4-religion-your-reason-is-now-mature-enough-to-examine</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 22:46:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10730-4-religion-your-reason-is-now-mature-enough-to-examine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["4. Religion. Your reason is now mature enough to examine this object. In the first place, divest yourself of all bias in favor of novelty &amp; singularity of opinion... shake off all the fears &amp; servile prejudices, under which weak minds are servilely crouched. &lt;b&gt;Fix reason firmly in her seat, and call to her tribunal every fact, every opinion. Question with boldness even the existence of a God; because, if there be one, he must more approve of the homage of reason, than that of blindfolded fear&lt;/b&gt;. You will naturally examine first, the religion of your own country. Read the Bible, then as you would read [author:Livy|2840091] or [author:Tacitus|2936846]. The facts which are within the ordinary course of nature, you will believe on the authority of the writer, as you do those of the same kind in [author:Livy|2840091] and [author:Tacitus|2936846]. The testimony of the writer weighs in their favor, in one scale, and their not being against the laws of nature, does not weigh against them. But those facts in the Bible which contradict the laws of nature, must be examined with more care, and under a variety of faces. Here you must recur to the pretensions of the writer to inspiration from God. Examine upon what evidence his pretensions are founded, and whether that evidence is so strong, as that its falsehood would be more improbable than a change in the laws of nature, in the case he relates. For example in the book of Joshua we are told the sun stood still several hours. Were we to read that fact in [author:Livy|2840091] or [author:Tacitus|2936846] we should class it with their showers of blood, speaking of statues, beasts, &amp;c. But it is said that the writer of that book was inspired. Examine therefore candidly what evidence there is of his having been inspired. The pretension is entitled to your inquiry, because millions believe it. On the other hand you are astronomer enough to know how contrary it is to the law of nature that a body revolving on its axis as the earth does, should have stopped, should not by that sudden stoppage have prostrated animals, trees, buildings, and should after a certain time have resumed its revolution, &amp; that without a second general prostration. Is this arrest of the earth's motion, or the evidence which affirms it, most within the law of probabilities? You will next read the New Testament. It is the history of a personage called Jesus. Keep in your eye the opposite pretensions: 1, of those who say he was begotten by God, born of a virgin, suspended &amp; reversed the laws of nature at will, &amp; ascended bodily into heaven; and 2, of those who say he was a man of illegitimate birth, of a benevolent heart, enthusiastic mind, who set out without pretensions to divinity, ended in believing them, and was punished capitally for sedition, by being gibbeted, according to the Roman law, which punished the first commission of that offence by whipping, &amp; the second by exile, or death &lt;i&gt;in fureâ&lt;/i&gt;.

...Do not be frightened from this inquiry by any fear of its consequences. If it ends in a belief that there is no God, you will find incitements to virtue in the comfort and pleasantness you feel in its exercise, and the love of others which it will procure you... In fine, I repeat, you must lay aside all prejudice on both sides, and neither believe nor reject anything, because any other persons, or description of persons, have rejected or believed it... I forgot to observe, when speaking of the New Testament, that you should read all the histories of Christ, as well of those whom a council of ecclesiastics have decided for us, to be Pseudo-evangelists, as those they named Evangelists. Because these Pseudo-evangelists pretended to inspiration, as much as the others, and you are to judge their pretensions by your own reason, and not by the reason of those ecclesiastics. Most of these are lost...

[&lt;i&gt;Letter to his nephew, Peter Carr, advising him in matters of religion, 1787&lt;/i&gt;]" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103730-he-who-knows-nothing-is-closer-to-the-truth-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 22:54:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103730-he-who-knows-nothing-is-closer-to-the-truth-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He who knows nothing is closer to the truth than he whose mind is filled with falsehoods and errors." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129692-the-moral-truth-here-is-obvious-anyone-who-feels-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 23:08:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129692-the-moral-truth-here-is-obvious-anyone-who-feels-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The moral truth here is obvious: anyone who feels that the interests of a blastocyst just might supersede the interests of a child with a spinal cord injury has had his moral sense blinded by religious metaphysics." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129701-in-fact-atheism-is-a-term-that-should-not-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 23:10:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129701-in-fact-atheism-is-a-term-that-should-not-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In fact, &quot;atheism&quot; is a term that should not even exist. No one ever needs to identify himself as a &quot;non-astrologer&quot; or a &quot;non-alchemist.&quot; We do not have words for people who doubt that Elvis is still alive or that aliens have traversed the galaxy only to molest ranchers and their cattle. Atheism is nothing more than the noises reasonable people make in the presence of unjustified religious beliefs." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153830-are-you-really-surprised-by-the-endurance-of-religion-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 23:11:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153830-are-you-really-surprised-by-the-endurance-of-religion-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Are you really surprised by the endurance of religion? What ideology is likely to be more durable than one that conforms, at every turn, to our powers of wishful thinking? Hope is easy; knowledge is hard. Science is the one domain in which we human beings make a truly heroic effort to counter our innate biases and wishful thinking. Science is the one endeavor in which we have developed a refined methodology for separating what a person hopes is true from what he has good reason to believe. The methodology isn't perfect, and the history of science is riddled with abject failures of scientific objectivity. But that is just the point-these have been failures of science, discovered and corrected by-what, religion? No, by good science." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1719-yes-the-long-war-on-christianity-i-pray-that-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 23:13:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Jon Stewart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1719-yes-the-long-war-on-christianity-i-pray-that-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yes, the long war on Christianity. I pray that one day we may live in an America where Christians can worship freely! In broad daylight! Openly wearing the symbols of their religion... perhaps around their necks? And maybe -- dare I dream it? -- maybe one day there can be an openly Christian President. Or, perhaps, 43 of them. Consecutively." -- Jon Stewart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50457-the-bible-has-noble-poetry-in-it-and-some-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 01:22:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50457-the-bible-has-noble-poetry-in-it-and-some-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Bible has noble poetry in it... and some good morals and a wealth of obscenity, and upwards of a thousand lies." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129697-you-are-using-your-own-moral-intuitions-to-authenticate-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 01:24:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129697-you-are-using-your-own-moral-intuitions-to-authenticate-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are using your own moral intuitions to authenticate the wisdom of the Bible - and then, in the next moment, you assert that we human beings cannot possibly rely upon our own intuitions to rightly guide us in the world." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190601-the-core-of-science-is-not-a-mathematical-modeling--it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 01:25:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190601-the-core-of-science-is-not-a-mathematical-modeling--it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The core of science is not a mathematical modeling--it is intellectual honesty.  It is a willingness to have our certainties about the world constrained by good evidence and good argument." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
