<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/49989-kathy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/49989-kathy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2009 20:40:24 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8165-it-is-only-a-novel-or-in-short-only-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2009 20:40:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8165-it-is-only-a-novel-or-in-short-only-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is only a novel... or, in short, only some work in which the greatest powers of the mind are displayed, in which the most thorough knowledge of human nature, the happiest delineation of its varieties, the liveliest effusions of wit and humour, are conveyed to the world in the best-chosen language" -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191969-to-my-thinking-a-great-librarian-must-have-a-clear</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2009 20:55:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Melvil Dewey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191969-to-my-thinking-a-great-librarian-must-have-a-clear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To my thinking, a great librarian must have a clear head, a strong hand, and, above all, a great heart. And when I look into the future, I am inclined to think that most of the men who achieve this greatness will be women." -- Melvil Dewey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51889-fiction-is-the-lie-through-which-we-tell-the-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2009 20:56:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51889-fiction-is-the-lie-through-which-we-tell-the-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fiction is the lie through which we tell the truth." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218368-this-is-why-the-liberian-waiter-laughed-at-me-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 07:25:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Rose George]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218368-this-is-why-the-liberian-waiter-laughed-at-me-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is why the Liberian waiter laughed at me. He thought that I thought a toilet was my right, when he knew it was a privilege.
&quot;It must be, when 2.6 billion people don't have sanitation. I don't mean that they have no toilet in their house and must use a public one with queues and fees. Or that they have an outhouse, or a ricety shack that empties into a filthy drain or pigsty. All that counts as sanitation, though not a safe variety. The people who have those are the fortunate ones. Four in ten people have no access to any latrine, toilet, bucket, or box. Nothing. Instead, they defecate by train tracks and in forests. They do it in plastic bags and fling them through the air in narrow slum alleyways. If they are women, they get up at 4 A.M. to be able to do their business under cover of darkness for reasons of modesty, risking rape and snakebites. Four in ten people live in situations where they are surrounded by human excrement because it is in the bushes outside the village or in their city yards, left by children outside the backdoor. It is tramped back in on their feet, carried on fingers onto clothes, food and drinking water.
&quot;The disease toll of this is stunning. A gram of feces can contain 10 million viruses, 1 million bacteria, 1,000 parasite cysts, and 100 worm eggs..." -- Rose George]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
