<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/502012-tom]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/502012-tom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 19:52:46 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6060-the-people-that-once-bestowed-commands-consulships-legions-and-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 19:52:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Juvenal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6060-the-people-that-once-bestowed-commands-consulships-legions-and-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The people that once bestowed commands, consulships, legions, and all else, now concerns itself no more, and longs eagerly for just two things:  bread and circuses!" -- Juvenal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71665-justice----you-get-justice-in-the-next-world-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 21:44:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by William Gaddis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71665-justice----you-get-justice-in-the-next-world-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Justice? -- You get justice in the next world.  In this one you have the law." -- William Gaddis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224000-then-what-is-sacrelige-sic-if-it-is-nothing-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 21:44:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by William Gaddis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224000-then-what-is-sacrelige-sic-if-it-is-nothing-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then, what is sacrelige [sic]? If it is nothing more than a rebellion against dogma, it is eventually as meaningless as the dogma it defies, and they are both become hounds ranting in the high grass, never see the boar in the thicket. Only a religious person can perpetrate sacrelige: and if its blasphemy reaches the heart of the question; if it investigates deeply enough to unfold, not the pattern, but the materials of the pattern, and the necessity of a pattern; if it questions so deeply that the doubt it arouses is frightening and cannot be dismissed; then it has done its true sacreligious [sic] work, in the service of its adversary: the only service that nihilism can ever perform.

(unused 1949 prefatory note to The Recognitions) " -- William Gaddis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16731-it-s-been-a-prevalent-notion-fallen-sparks-fragments-of-vessels</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 21:46:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16731-it-s-been-a-prevalent-notion-fallen-sparks-fragments-of-vessels]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's been a prevalent notion. Fallen sparks. Fragments of vessels broken at the Creation. And someday, somehow, before the end, a gathering back to home. A messenger from the Kingdom, arriving at the last moment. But I tell you there is no such message, no such home -- only the millions of last moments . . . nothing more. Our history is an aggregate of last moments." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187405-paranoids-are-not-paranoid-because-they-re-paranoid-but-because-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 21:46:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187405-paranoids-are-not-paranoid-because-they-re-paranoid-but-because-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Paranoids are not paranoid because they're paranoid, but because they keep putting themselves, fucking idiots, deliberately into paranoid situations." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234483-damned-beaver-jeremy-is-the-war-he-is-every-assertion-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 21:55:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234483-damned-beaver-jeremy-is-the-war-he-is-every-assertion-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Damned Beaver/Jeremy &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; the War, he is every assertion the fucking War has ever made--that we are meant for work and government, for austerity: and these shall take priority over love, dreams, the spirit, the senses and the other second-class trivia that are found among the idle and mindless hours of the day....Damn them, they are wrong. They are insane." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257125-kekul-dreams-the-great-serpent-holding-its-own-tail-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 22:54:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257125-kekul-dreams-the-great-serpent-holding-its-own-tail-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kekulé dreams the Great Serpent holding its own tail in its mouth, the dreaming Serpent which surrounds the World. But the meanness, the cynicism with which this dream is to be used. The Serpent that announces, &quot;The World is a closed thing, cyclical, resonant, eternally-returning,&quot; is to be delivered into a system whose only aim is to violate the Cycle. Taking and not giving back, demanding that &quot;productivity&quot; and &quot;earnings&quot; keep on increasing with time, the System removing from the rest of the World these vast quantities of energy to keep its own tiny desperate fraction showing a profit: and not only most of humanity—most of the World, animal, vegetable, and mineral, is laid waste in the process. The System may or may not understand that it's only buying time. And that time is an artificial resource to begin with, of no value to anyone or anything but the System, which must sooner or later crash to its death, when its addiction to energy has become more than the rest of the World can supply, dragging with it innocent souls all along the chain of life. Living inside the System is like riding across the country in a bus driven by a maniac bent on suicide . . . though he's amiable enough, keeps cracking jokes back through the loudspeaker . . ." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289848-young-tchitcherine-was-the-one-who-brought-up-political-narcotics</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 23:32:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289848-young-tchitcherine-was-the-one-who-brought-up-political-narcotics]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Young Tchitcherine was the one who brought up political narcotics. Opiates of the people.

Wimpe smiled back. An old, old smile to chill even the living fire in Earth’s core. &quot;Marxist dialectics? That’s &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; an opiate, eh?&quot;

&quot;It’s the antidote.&quot;

&quot;No.&quot; It can go either way. The dope salesman may know everything that’s ever going to happen to Tchitcherine, and decide it’s no use—or, out of the moment’s velleity, lay it right out for the young fool.

&quot;The basic problem,&quot; he proposes, &quot;has always been getting other people to die for you. What’s worth enough for a man to give up his life? That’s where religion had the edge, for centuries. Religion was always about death. It was used not as an opiate so much as a technique—it got people to die for one particular set of beliefs about death. Perverse, natürlich, but who are you to judge? It was a good pitch while it worked. But ever since it became impossible to die for death, we have had a secular version—yours. Die to help History grow to its predestined shape. Die knowing your act will bring will bring a good end a bit closer. Revolutionary suicide, fine. But look: if History’s changes are inevitable, why not &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; die? Vaslav? If it’s going to happen anyway, what does it matter?&quot;

&quot;But you haven’t ever had the choice to make, have you.&quot;

&quot;If I ever did, you can be sure—&quot;

&quot;You don’t know. Not till you’re there, Wimpe. You can’t say.&quot;

&quot;That doesn’t sound very dialectical.&quot;

&quot;I don’t know what it is.&quot;

&quot;Then, right up to the point of decision,&quot; Wimpe curious but careful, &quot;a man could still be perfectly pure . . .&quot;

&quot;He could be anything. &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; don’t care. But he’s only real at the points of decision. The time between doesn’t matter.&quot;

&quot;Real to a Marxist.&quot;

&quot;No. Real to himself.&quot;

Wimpe looks doubtful.

&quot;I've been there. You haven't." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209682-the-greater-intellect-one-has-the-more-originality-one-finds</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 23:09:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Blaise Pascal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209682-the-greater-intellect-one-has-the-more-originality-one-finds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greater intellect one has, the more originality one finds in men. Ordinary persons find no difference between men." -- Blaise Pascal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20194-what-has-he-found-who-has-lost-god-and-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 00:27:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Ibn 'Ata' Allah Al-Iskandari]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20194-what-has-he-found-who-has-lost-god-and-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What has he found who has lost God?
And what has he lost who has found God?" -- Ibn 'Ata' Allah Al-Iskandari]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173582-i-become-more-than-ever-convinced-that-it-was-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 00:30:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173582-i-become-more-than-ever-convinced-that-it-was-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I become more than ever convinced that it was not the sword that won a place for Islam in those days. It was the rigid simplicity, the utter self-effacement of Hussein, the scrupulous regard for pledges, his intense devotion to his friends and followers and his intrepidity, his fearlessness, his absolute trust in God and in his own mission. These and not the sword carried everything before them and surmounted every obstacle." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132920-i-began-to-see-algiers-as-one-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 00:38:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Ryszard Kapuściński]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132920-i-began-to-see-algiers-as-one-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[…] I began to see Algiers as one of the most fascinating and dramatic places on earth. In the small space of this beautiful but congested city intersected two great conflicts of the contemporary world. The first was the one between Christianity and Islam (expressed here in the clash between colonizing France and colonized Algeria). The second, which acquired a sharpness of focus immediately after the independence and departure of the French, was a conflict at the very heart of Islam, between its open, dialectical — I would even say “Mediterranean” — current and its other, inward-looking one, born of a sense of uncertainty and confusion vis-à-vis the contemporary world, guided by fundamentalists who take advantage of modern technology and organizational principles yet at the same time deem the defense of faith and custom against modernity as the condition of their own existence, their sole identity.

[…] In Algiers one speaks simply of the existence of two varieties of Islam — one, which is called the Islam of the desert, and a second, which is defined as the Islam of the river (or of the sea). The first is the religion practiced by warlike nomadic tribes struggling to survive in one of the world's most hostile environments, the Sahara. The second Islam is the faith of merchants, itinerant peddlers, people of the road and of the bazaar, for whom openness, compromise, and exchange are not only beneficial to trade, but necessary to life itself." -- Ryszard Kapuściński]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123126-the-construction-of-civilizational-difference-is-not-exclusive-in-any</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 00:41:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Talal Asad]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123126-the-construction-of-civilizational-difference-is-not-exclusive-in-any]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The construction of civilizational difference is not exclusive in any simple sense. The de-essentialization of Islam is paradigmatic for all thinking about the assimilation of non-European peoples to European civilization. The idea that people's historical experience is inessential to them, that it can be shed at will, makes it possible to argue more strongly for the Enlightenment's claim to universality: Muslims, as members of the abstract category &quot;humans,&quot; can be assimilated or (as some recent theorist have put it) &quot;translated&quot; into a global (&quot;European&quot;) civilization once they have divested themselves of what many of them regard (mistakenly) as essential to themselves. The belief that human beings can be separated from their histories and traditions makes it possible to urge a Europeanization of the Islamic world. And by the same logic, it underlies the belief that the assimilation to Europe's civilization of Muslim immigrants who are--for good or for ill--already in European states is necessary and desirable.
" -- Talal Asad]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48618-there-is-no-head-of-state-in-the-world-today</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 10:49:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Giorgio Agamben]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48618-there-is-no-head-of-state-in-the-world-today]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;i&gt;...there is no head of state in the world today who is not in virtuality a criminal&lt;/i&gt;. Those who shoulder the dreary mantle of sovereignty know that their turn may come to be branded a criminal by their colleagues. We certainly will not be the ones to complain. For the sovereign, who freely consented to donning the executioner's clothes, is now finally manifesting his originary kinship with the criminal. " -- Giorgio Agamben]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161725-one-day-humanity-will-play-with-law-just-as-children</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2012 17:57:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Giorgio Agamben]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161725-one-day-humanity-will-play-with-law-just-as-children]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One day humanity will play with law just as children play with disused objects, not in order to restore them to their canonical use but to free them from it for good." -- Giorgio Agamben]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/356842-remembrance-restores-possibility-to-the-past-making-what-happened-incomplete</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2012 17:57:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by Giorgio Agamben]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/356842-remembrance-restores-possibility-to-the-past-making-what-happened-incomplete]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remembrance restores possibility to the past, making what happened incomplete and completing what never was.  Remembrance is neither what happened nor what did not happen but, rather, their potentialization, their becoming possible once again." -- Giorgio Agamben]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
