<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/502738-christopher]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/502738-christopher" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 22:30:55 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/936845-you-can-weave-your-life-so-long----only-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 22:30:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Patricia A. McKillip]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/936845-you-can-weave-your-life-so-long----only-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can weave your life so long -- only so long, and then a thing in the world out of your control will tug at one vital thread and leave you patternless and subdued." -- Patricia A. McKillip]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/936846-clothes-when-abstracted-from-the-flow-of-present-time-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 22:32:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Robert Musil]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/936846-clothes-when-abstracted-from-the-flow-of-present-time-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Clothes, when abstracted from the flow of present time and their transmogrifying function on the human body, and seen as forms in themselves, are strange tubes and excrescences worthy of being classed with such facial decorations as the ring through the nose or the lip-stretching disk.  But how enchanting they become when seen together
with the qualities they bestow on their wearer!  What happens then is no less than the infusion, into some tangled lines on a piece of paper, of the meaning of a great word." -- Robert Musil]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/936848-should-we-only-be-interested-to-view-the-cherry-blossoms</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 22:36:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Kenkō Yoshida/吉田兼好]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/936848-should-we-only-be-interested-to-view-the-cherry-blossoms]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Should we only be interested to view the cherry blossoms at their peak, or the moon when it is full? To yearn for the moon when it is raining, or to be closed up in ones room, failing to notice the passing of Spring, is far more moving. Treetops just before they break into blossom, or gardens strewn with fallen flowers are just as worthy of notice. There is much to see in them. Is it any less wonderful to say, in the preface to a poem, that it was written on viewing the cherry blossoms just after they had peaked, or that something had prevented one from seeing them altogether, than to say &quot;on seeing the cherry blossoms&quot;? Of course not. Flowers fall and the moon sets, these are the cyclic things of the world, but still there are brutish people who say that there is nothing left worth seeing, and fail to appreciate." -- Kenkō Yoshida/吉田兼好]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
