<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/50448-becky]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/50448-becky" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 12:11:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140158-idleness-like-kisses-to-be-sweet-must-be-stolen</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 12:11:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140158-idleness-like-kisses-to-be-sweet-must-be-stolen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Idleness, like kisses, to be sweet must be stolen." -- Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106003-i-like-idling-when-i-ought-not-to-be-idling</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 12:11:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106003-i-like-idling-when-i-ought-not-to-be-idling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like idling when I ought not to be idling; not when it is the only thing I have to do. Thatis my pig-headed nature. The time when I like best to stand with my back to the fire, calculating how much I owe, is when my desk is heaped highest with letters that must be answered by the next post. When I like to dawdle longest over my dinner is when I have a heavy evening's work before me. And if, for some urgent reason, I ought to be up particularly early in the morning, it is then, more than at any other time, that I love to lie an extra half-hour in bed.

Ah! how delicious it is to turn over and go to sleep again: &quot;just for
five minutes.&quot; Is there any human being, I wonder, besides the hero of
a Sunday-school &quot;tale for boys,&quot; who ever gets up willingly?" -- Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/574752-it-is-in-our-faults-and-failings-not-in-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 12:11:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/574752-it-is-in-our-faults-and-failings-not-in-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is in our faults and failings, not in our virtues, that we touch one another and find sympathy. We differ widely enough in our nobler qualities. It is in our follies that we are at one." -- Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/574756-if-you-are-foolish-enough-to-be-contented-don-t-show</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 12:11:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/574756-if-you-are-foolish-enough-to-be-contented-don-t-show]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are foolish enough to be contented, don't show it, but grumble with the rest; and if you can do with a little, ask for a great deal. Because if you don't you won't get any." -- Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/575658-it-is-so-pleasant-to-come-across-people-more-stupid</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 12:12:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/575658-it-is-so-pleasant-to-come-across-people-more-stupid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is so pleasant to come across people more stupid than ourselves. We love them at once for being so." -- Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/582123-speak-truth-and-right-will-take-care-of-itself</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 12:13:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Jerome K. Jerome‏]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/582123-speak-truth-and-right-will-take-care-of-itself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Speak truth, and right will take care of itself." -- Jerome K. Jerome‏]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/587768-homework-i-have-discovered-involves-a-sharp-pencil-and-thick</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 18:01:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Katherine Applegate]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/587768-homework-i-have-discovered-involves-a-sharp-pencil-and-thick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Homework, I have discovered, involves a sharp pencil and thick books and long sighs." -- Katherine Applegate]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/587770-my-visitors-are-often-surprised-when-they-see-the-tv</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 18:02:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Katherine Applegate]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/587770-my-visitors-are-often-surprised-when-they-see-the-tv]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My visitors are often surprised when they see the TV Mack put in my domain. They seem to find it odd, the sight of a gorilla staring at tiny humans in a box. Sometimes I wonder, though: Isn't the way they stare at me, sitting in my tiny box, just as strange?" -- Katherine Applegate]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/591346-man-if-he-would-live-must-worship-he-looks-around</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 14:42:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/591346-man-if-he-would-live-must-worship-he-looks-around]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man, if he would live, must worship. He looks around, and what to him, within the vision of his life, is the greatest and the best, that he falls down and does reverence to." -- Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/591349-truth-and-fact-are-old-fashioned-and-out-of-date-my-friends-fit</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 14:44:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/591349-truth-and-fact-are-old-fashioned-and-out-of-date-my-friends-fit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Truth and fact are old-fashioned and out-of-date, my friends, fit only for the dull and vulgar to live by. Appearance, not reality, is what the clever dog grasps at in these clever days. We spurn the dull-brown solid earth; we build our lives and homes in the fair-seeming rainbow-land of shadow and chimera." -- Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/592246-my-favorite-thing-in-the-world-to-do-is-read</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 10:46:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Mindy Warshaw Skolsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/592246-my-favorite-thing-in-the-world-to-do-is-read]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My favorite thing in the world to do is read a book. I read Heidi, which I love, then I read another book, then I read Heidi again. If I stopped reading Heidi in between the other books, I'd be able to read twice as many books, but the thing is I like reading Heidi. So I do." -- Mindy Warshaw Skolsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/660902-the-greatest-encouragement-throughout-the-bible-is-god-s-love-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2012 16:48:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by A.W. Tozer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/660902-the-greatest-encouragement-throughout-the-bible-is-god-s-love-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greatest encouragement throughout the Bible is God's love for His lost race and the willingness of Christ, the eternal Son, to show forth that love in God's plan of redemption. The love of Jesus is so inclusive that it knows no boundaries. At the point where we stop caring and loving, Jesus is still there loving and caring" -- A.W. Tozer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674547-i-long-ago-discovered-that-you-can-t-tell-about-pollyanna</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 12:56:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Eleanor H. Porter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674547-i-long-ago-discovered-that-you-can-t-tell-about-pollyanna]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I long ago discovered that you can't TELL about Pollyanna. The minute you try to, she sounds priggish and preachy, and--impossible. Yet you and I know she is anything but that." -- Eleanor H. Porter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674548-aunt-polly-is-all-stirred-up-over-it-you-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 12:57:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Eleanor H. Porter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674548-aunt-polly-is-all-stirred-up-over-it-you-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Aunt Polly is all stirred up over it. You see, she wants Uncle Tom to have what he wants, only she wants him to want what she wants him to want. See?&quot; Mrs. Carew laughed suddenly. (22)" -- Eleanor H. Porter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674586-dear-papa-i-love-you-so-much-she-replied-twining</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 14:12:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Martha Finley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674586-dear-papa-i-love-you-so-much-she-replied-twining]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dear papa, I love you so much!' she replied, twining her arms around his neck. 'I love you all the better for never letting me have my own way, but always making me obey and keep to rules." -- Martha Finley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674587-though-not-a-remarkably-precocious-child-in-other-respects-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 14:12:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Martha Finley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674587-though-not-a-remarkably-precocious-child-in-other-respects-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Though not a remarkably precocious child in other respects, she seemed to have very clear and correct views on almost every subject connected with her duty to God and her neighbor; was very truthful both in word and deed, very strict in her observance of the Sabbath--though the rest of the family were by no means particular in that respect--very diligent in her studies; respectful to superiors, and kind to inferiors and equals; and she was gentle, sweet-tempered, patient, and forgiving to a remarkable degree." -- Martha Finley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405489-and-two-years-ago-this-morning-i-woke-wondering-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 16:43:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405489-and-two-years-ago-this-morning-i-woke-wondering-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And two years ago this morning I woke wondering what delightful gift the new day would give me. These are the two years I thought would be filled with fun.&quot; &quot;Would you exchange them - now - for two years filled with fun &quot; &quot;No &quot; said Rilla slowly. &quot;I wouldn't. It's strange - isn't it - They have been two terrible years - and yet I have a queer feeling of thankfulness for them - as if they had brought me something very precious in all their pain. I wouldn't want to go back and be the girl I was two years ago not even if I could. Not that I think I've made any wonderful progress - but I'm not quite the selfish frivolous little doll I was then. I suppose I had a soul then Miss Oliver - but I didn't know it. I know it now - and that is worth a great deal - worth all the suffering of the past few years." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/695674-your-parents-oskar-and-mina-they-are-dead-and-gone</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 12:38:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Alan Gratz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/695674-your-parents-oskar-and-mina-they-are-dead-and-gone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your parents, Oskar and Mina. They are dead and gone now, Yanek, and we would grieve them if we could. But we have only one purpose now: survive. Survive at all costs, Yanek. We cannot let these monsters tear us from the pages of the world." -- Alan Gratz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/704350-holiness-as-taught-in-the-scriptures-is-not-based-upon</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2013 15:20:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by A.W. Tozer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/704350-holiness-as-taught-in-the-scriptures-is-not-based-upon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Holiness, as taught in the Scriptures, is not based upon knowledge on our part. Rather, it is based upon the resurrected Christ in-dwelling us and changing us into His likeness." -- A.W. Tozer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/704353-the-only-cross-in-all-of-history-that-was-turned</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2013 15:22:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by A.W. Tozer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/704353-the-only-cross-in-all-of-history-that-was-turned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only cross in all of history that was turned into an altar was the cross on which Jesus Christ died. It was a Roman cross. They nailed Him on it, and God, in His majesty and mystery, turned it into an altar. The Lamb who was dying in the mystery and wonder of God was turned into the Priest who offered Himself. No one else was a worthy offering." -- A.W. Tozer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/704355-if-man-had-his-way-the-plan-of-redemption-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2013 15:23:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by A.W. Tozer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/704355-if-man-had-his-way-the-plan-of-redemption-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If man had his way, the plan of redemption would be an endless and bloody conflict. In reality, salvation was bought not by Jesus' fist, but by His nail-pierced hands; not by muscle but by love; not by vengeance but by forgiveness; not by force but by sacrifice. Jesus Christ our Lord surrendered in order that He might win; He destroyed His enemies by dying for them and conquered death by allowing death to conquer Him." -- A.W. Tozer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/704358-some-books-claiming-to-be-exhaustive-are-only-exhausting-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2013 15:25:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by A.W. Tozer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/704358-some-books-claiming-to-be-exhaustive-are-only-exhausting-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some books claiming to be exhaustive are only exhausting to read." -- A.W. Tozer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309896-sir-richard-sighed-rid-yourself-of-the-notion-that-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 13:06:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Georgette Heyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309896-sir-richard-sighed-rid-yourself-of-the-notion-that-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sir Richard sighed. &quot;Rid yourself of the notion that I cherish any villainous designs upon your person,&quot; he said. &quot;I imagine I might well be your father. How old are you?&quot;

&quot;I am turned seventeen.&quot;

&quot;Well, I am nearly thirty,&quot; said Sir Richard.

Miss Creed worked this out. &quot;You couldn't possibly be my father!&quot;

&quot;I am far too drunk to solve arithmetical problems. Let it suffice that I have not the slightest intention of making love to you." -- Georgette Heyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/733586-were-you-locked-in-your-room-enquired-sir-richard-oh</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 13:07:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Georgette Heyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/733586-were-you-locked-in-your-room-enquired-sir-richard-oh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Were you locked in your room?&quot; enquired Sir Richard.
&quot;Oh no! I daresay I should have been if Aunt had guessed what I meant to do, but she would never think of such a thing.&quot;
&quot;Then--forgive my curiosity!--why did you climb out of the window?&quot; asked Sir Richard.
&quot;Oh, that was on account of Pug!&quot; replied Pen sunnily.
&quot;Pug?&quot;
&quot;Yes, a horrid little creature! He sleeps in a basket in the hall, and he always yaps if he thinks one is going out. That would have awakened Aunt Almeria. There was nothing else I could do.&quot;
Sir Richard regarded her with a lurking smile. &quot;Naturally not. Do you know, Pen, I owe you a debt of gratitude?&quot;
&quot;Oh!&quot; she said again. &quot;Do you mean that I don't behave as a delicately bred femaile should?&quot;
&quot;That is one way of putting it, certainly.&quot;
&quot;It is the way Aunt Almeria puts it.&quot;
&quot;She would, of course.&quot;
&quot;I am afraid,&quot; confessed Pen, &quot;that I am not very well-behaved. Aunt says that I had a lamentable upbringing, because my father treated me as though I had been a boy. I ought to have been, you understand.&quot;
&quot;I cannot agree with you,&quot; said Sir Richard. &quot;As a boy you would have been in no way remarkable; as a female, believe me, you are unique.&quot;
She flushed to the roots of her hair. &quot;I think that is a compliment.&quot;
&quot;It is,&quot; Sir Richard said, amused.
&quot;Well, I wasn't sure, because I am not out yet, and I do not know any men except my uncle and Fred, and they don't pay compliments. That is to say, not like that." -- Georgette Heyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/733590-what-sir-would-you-think-of-a-member-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 13:11:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Georgette Heyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/733590-what-sir-would-you-think-of-a-member-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What, sir, would you think of a member of the Weaker Sex who assumed the guise of a man, and left the home of her natural protector by way of the window?&quot;
&quot;I should assume,&quot; replied Sir Richard, &quot;that she had strong reasons for acting with such resolution.&quot;
&quot;She did not wish to marry me,&quot; said Mr. Griffin gloomily.
&quot;Oh!&quot; said Sir Richard.
&quot;Well, I'm sure I can't see why she should be so set against me, but that's not it, sir. The thing is that here's my mother determined to find her, and to make her marry me, and so hush up the scandal. But I don't like it above half. If she dislikes the notion so much, I don't think I ought to marry her, do you?&quot;
&quot;Emphatically not!&quot;
&quot;I must say I am very glad to hear you say that, Sir Richard!&quot; said Mr. Griffin, much cheered. &quot;For you must know that my mother has been telling me ever since yesterday that I must marry her now, to save her name. But I think she would very likely make me uncomfortable, and nothing could make up for that, in my opinion.&quot;
&quot;A lady capable of escaping out of a window in the guise of a a man would quite certainly make you more than uncomfortable,&quot; said Sir Richard.
&quot;Yes, though she's only a chit of a girl, you know. In fact, she is not yet out. I am very happy to have had the benefit of the opinion of a Man of the World. I feel that I can rely on your judgment.&quot;
&quot;On my judgment, you might, but in nothing else, I assure you,&quot; said Sir Richard. &quot;You know nothing of me, after all. How do you know that I am not now concealing your cousin from you?&quot;
&quot;Ha-ha! Very good, upon my word! Very good, indeed!&quot; said Mr. Griffin, saluting a jest of the first water." -- Georgette Heyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/744820-the-sinner-is-the-gospel-s-reason-for-existence</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 12:54:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Charles Spurgeon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/744820-the-sinner-is-the-gospel-s-reason-for-existence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sinner is the gospel's reason for existence." -- Charles Spurgeon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/744822-the-doctrine-of-the-atonement-is-to-my-mind-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 12:55:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Charles H. Spurgeon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/744822-the-doctrine-of-the-atonement-is-to-my-mind-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The doctrine of the atonement is to my mind one of the surest proofs of the divine inspiration of Holy Scripture. Who would or could have thought of the just Ruler dying for the unjust rebel? This is no teaching of human mythology, or dream of poetical imagination. This method of expiation is only known among men because it is a fact; fiction could not have devised it. God himself ordained it; it is not a matter which could have been imagined." -- Charles H. Spurgeon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/744823-faith-never-makes-herself-her-own-plea-she-rests-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 12:56:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Charles H. Spurgeon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/744823-faith-never-makes-herself-her-own-plea-she-rests-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Faith never makes herself her own plea, she rests all her argument upon the blood of Christ." -- Charles H. Spurgeon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/744825-begin-as-you-mean-to-go-on-and-go-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 12:56:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Charles H. Spurgeon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/744825-begin-as-you-mean-to-go-on-and-go-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Begin as you mean to go on, and go on as you began, and let the Lord be all in all to you." -- Charles H. Spurgeon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/744827-the-saints-shall-persevere-in-holiness-because-god-perseveres-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 12:57:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Charles H. Spurgeon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/744827-the-saints-shall-persevere-in-holiness-because-god-perseveres-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The saints shall persevere in holiness, because God perseveres in grace." -- Charles H. Spurgeon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
