<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/51255-jenni]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/51255-jenni" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2007 07:36:31 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3041-like-our-bodies-and-like-our-desires-the-machines-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2007 07:36:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenni add a quote by W.G. Sebald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3041-like-our-bodies-and-like-our-desires-the-machines-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like our bodies and like our desires, the machines we have devised are possessed of a heart which is slowly reduced to embers." -- W.G. Sebald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106935-but-what-is-the-philosophy-of-this-generation-not-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2008 08:45:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenni add a quote by Saul Bellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106935-but-what-is-the-philosophy-of-this-generation-not-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But what is the philosophy of this generation? Not God is dead, that point was passed long ago. Perhaps it should be stated Death is God. This generation thinks – and this is its thought of thoughts – that nothing faithful, vulnerable, fragile can be durable or have any true power. Death waits for these things as a cement floor waits for a dropping light bulb. The brittle shell of glass loses its tiny vacuum with a burst, and that is that. And this is how we teach metaphysics on each other. &quot;You think history is the history of loving hearts? You fool! Look at these millions of dead. Can you pity them, feel for them? You can nothing! There were too many. We burned them to ashes, we buried them with bulldozers. History is the history of cruelty, not love as soft men think." -- Saul Bellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129301-inasmuch-as-art-preserves-with-the-promise-of-happiness-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 19:57:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenni add a quote by Herbert Marcuse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129301-inasmuch-as-art-preserves-with-the-promise-of-happiness-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Inasmuch as art preserves, with the promise of happiness, the memory of the goal that failed, it can enter, as a 'regulative idea,' the desperate struggle for changing the world. Against all fetishism of the productive forces, against the continued enslavement of individuals by the objective conditions (which remain those of domination), art represents the ultimate goal of all revolutions: the freedom and happiness of the individual." -- Herbert Marcuse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22877-there-is-always-something-for-which-there-is-no-accounting</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 19:58:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenni add a quote by Leonard Michaels]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22877-there-is-always-something-for-which-there-is-no-accounting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is always something for which there is no accounting. Take, for example, the whole world." -- Leonard Michaels]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134748-but-then-i-cannot-escape-the-objection-that-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 14:47:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenni add a quote by Henri Bergson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134748-but-then-i-cannot-escape-the-objection-that-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But, then, I cannot escape the objection that there is no state of mind, however simple, which does not change every moment, since there is no consciousness without memory, and no continuation of a state without the addition, to the present feeling, of the memory of past moments. It is this which constitutes duration.  Inner duration is the continuous life of a memory which prolongs the past into the present, the present either containing within it in a distinct form the ceaselessly growing image of the past, or, more profoundly, showing by its continual change of quality the heavier and still heavier load we drag behind us as we grow older.  Without this survival of the past into the present there would be no duration, but only instantaneity." -- Henri Bergson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
