<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/513028-sarah-lewis]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/513028-sarah-lewis" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 16:37:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 16:37:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to write the book that wants to be written. And if the book will be too difficult for grown-ups, then you write it for children." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2203-it-is-what-you-read-when-you-don-t-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 22:14:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2203-it-is-what-you-read-when-you-don-t-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is what you read when you don't have to that determines what you will be when you can't help it." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162173-first-came-bright-spirits-not-the-spirits-of-men-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2012 10:58:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162173-first-came-bright-spirits-not-the-spirits-of-men-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First came bright Spirits, not the Spirits of men, who danced and scattered flowers.  Then, on the left and right, at each side of the forest avenue, came youthful shapes, boys upon one hand, and girls upon the other.  If I could remember their singing and write down the notes, no man who read that score would ever grow sick or old.  Between them went musicians: and after these a lady in whose honour all this was being done.  

	I cannot now remember whether she was naked or clothed.  If she were naked, then it must have been the almost visible penumbra of her courtesy and joy which produces in my memory the illusion of a great and shining train that followed her across the happy grass.  If she were clothed, then the illusion of nakedness is doubtless due to the clarity with which her inmost spirit shone through the clothes.  For clothes in that country are not a disguise: the spiritual body lives along each thread and turns them into living organs.  A robe or a crown is there as much one of the wearer's features as a lip or an eye. 
 
	But I have forgotten.  And only partly do I remember the unbearable beauty of her face.  

	“Is it?...is it?” I whispered to my guide.
	“Not at all,” said he.  “It's someone ye'll never have heard of.  Her name on earth was Sarah Smith and she lived at Golders Green.”
	“She seems to be...well, a person of particular importance?”
	“Aye.  She is one of the great ones.  Ye have heard that fame in this country and fame on Earth are two quite different things.”
	“And who are these gigantic people...look!  They're like emeralds...who are dancing and throwing flowers before here?”
	“Haven't ye read your Milton? A thousand liveried angels lackey her.”
	“And who are all these young men and women on each side?”
	“They are her sons and daughters.”
	“She must have had a very large family, Sir.”
	“Every young man or boy that met her became her son – even if it was only the boy that brought the meat to her back door.  Every girl that met her was her daughter.”
	“Isn't that a bit hard on their own parents?”
	“No.  There are those that steal other people's children.  But her motherhood was of a different kind.  Those on whom it fell went back to their natural parents loving them more.  Few men looked on her without becoming, in a certain fashion, her lovers.  But it was the kind of love that made them not less true, but truer, to their own wives.”
	“And how...but hullo!  What are all these animals?  A cat-two cats-dozens of cats.  And all those dogs...why, I can't count them.  And the birds.  And the horses.”
	“They are her beasts.”
	“Did she keep a sort of zoo?  I mean, this is a bit too much.”
	“Every beast and bird that came near her had its place in her love.  In her they became themselves.  And now the abundance of life she has in Christ from the Father flows over into them.”
	I looked at my Teacher in amazement.
	“Yes,” he said.  “It is like when you throw  a stone into a pool, and the concentric waves spread out further and further.  Who knows where it will end?  Redeemed humanity is still young, it has hardly come to its full strength.  But already there is joy enough int the little finger of a great saint such as yonder lady to waken all the dead things of the universe into life." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45451-isn-t-it-nice-to-think-that-tomorrow-is-a-new</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 08:18:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45451-isn-t-it-nice-to-think-that-tomorrow-is-a-new]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't it nice to think that tomorrow is a new day with no mistakes in it yet?" -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80146-i-d-like-to-add-some-beauty-to-life-said-anne</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 08:22:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80146-i-d-like-to-add-some-beauty-to-life-said-anne]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd like to add some beauty to life,&quot; said Anne dreamily. &quot;I don't exactly want to make people KNOW more... though I know that IS the noblest ambition... but I'd love to make them have a pleasanter time because of me... to have some little joy or happy thought that would never have existed if I hadn't been born." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392353-a-well-known-principle-of-human-behavior-says-that-when-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 11:26:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Robert B. Cialdini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392353-a-well-known-principle-of-human-behavior-says-that-when-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A well-known principle of human behavior says that when we ask someone to do us a favor we will be more successful if we provide a reason. People simply like to have reasons for what they do." -- Robert B. Cialdini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6979-i-am-trying-here-to-prevent-anyone-saying-the-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 11:27:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6979-i-am-trying-here-to-prevent-anyone-saying-the-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am trying here to prevent anyone saying the really foolish thing that people often say about Him: I’m ready to accept Jesus as a great moral teacher, but I don’t accept his claim to be God. That is the one thing we must not say. A man who was merely a man and said the sort of things Jesus said would not be a great moral teacher. He would either be a lunatic — on the level with the man who says he is a poached egg — or else he would be the Devil of Hell. You must make your choice. Either this man was, and is, the Son of God, or else a madman or something worse. You can shut him up for a fool, you can spit at him and kill him as a demon or you can fall at his feet and call him Lord and God, but let us not come with any patronizing nonsense about his being a great human teacher. He has not left that open to us. He did not intend to." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
