<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/513697-kim-marshall]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/513697-kim-marshall" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 14:50:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44907-few-people-have-had-much-training-in-listening-the-training-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 14:50:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by S.I. Hayakawa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44907-few-people-have-had-much-training-in-listening-the-training-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Few people...have had much training in listening. The training of most oververbalized professional intellectuals is in the opposite direction. Living in a competitive culture, most of us are most of the time chiefly concerned with getting our own views across, and we tend to find other people's speeches a tedious interruption of the flow of our own ideas." -- S.I. Hayakawa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101449-when-one-person-suffers-from-a-delusion-it-is-called</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 14:51:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Robert M. Pirsig]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101449-when-one-person-suffers-from-a-delusion-it-is-called]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When one person suffers from a delusion, it is called insanity. When many people suffer from a delusion it is called a Religion." -- Robert M. Pirsig]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/807-the-place-to-improve-the-world-is-first-in-one-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 14:51:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Robert M. Pirsig]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/807-the-place-to-improve-the-world-is-first-in-one-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The place to improve the world is first in one's own heart and head and hands, and then work outward from there." -- Robert M. Pirsig]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122460-we-seldom-realize-for-example-that-our-most-private-thoughts</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 12:36:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Alan Watts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122460-we-seldom-realize-for-example-that-our-most-private-thoughts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We seldom realize, for example that our most private thoughts and emotions are not actually our own. For we think in terms of languages and images which we did not invent, but which were given to us by our society." -- Alan Watts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59836-really-the-fundamental-ultimate-mystery----the-only-thing-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 12:41:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Alan Watts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59836-really-the-fundamental-ultimate-mystery----the-only-thing-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Really, the fundamental, ultimate mystery -- the only thing you need to know to understand the deepest metaphysical secrets -- is this: that for every outside there is an inside and for every inside there is an outside, and although they are different, they go together." -- Alan Watts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61482-in-a-very-real-sense-people-who-have-read-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 20:02:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by S. I. Hayakawa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61482-in-a-very-real-sense-people-who-have-read-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a very real sense, people who have read good literature
have lived more than people who cannot or will not read.
It is not true that we have only one life to lead; if we can read,
we can live as many more lives and as many kinds of lives as we wish.
" -- S. I. Hayakawa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84739-i-glanced-at-my-watch---it-was-two-minutes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 20:14:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84739-i-glanced-at-my-watch---it-was-two-minutes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I glanced at my watch - it was two minutes to eleven; just right for lunch when and if we ever got to the godforsaken lodge - and took some comfort from the thought that at least I still had my wits about me. Or at least I felt as if I did. Presumably, a confused person would be too addled to recognize that he was confused. Ergo, if you know that you are not confused then you are not confused. Unless, it suddenly occurred to me - and here was an arresting notion - unless persuading yourself that you are not confused is merely a cruel, early symptom of confusion. Or even an advanced symptom. Who could tell? For all I knew I could be stumbling into some kind of helpless preconfusional state characterized by the fear on the part of the sufferer that he may be stumbling into some kind of helpless preconfusional state. That's the trouble with losing your mind; by the time it's gone, it's too late to get it back." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207142-the-doctrinal-differences-between-hinduism-and-buddhism-and-taoism-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 20:17:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Robert M. Pirsig]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207142-the-doctrinal-differences-between-hinduism-and-buddhism-and-taoism-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…the doctrinal differences between Hinduism and Buddhism and Taoism are not anywhere near as important as doctrinal differences among Christianity and Islam and Judaism. Holy wars are not fought over them because verbalized statements about reality are never presumed to be reality itself." -- Robert M. Pirsig]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172489-oh-lord-most-high-creator-of-the-cosmos-spinner-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 19:25:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172489-oh-lord-most-high-creator-of-the-cosmos-spinner-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh Lord Most High, Creator of the Cosmos, Spinner of Galaxies, Soul of Electromagnetic Waves, Inhaler and Exhaler of Inconceivable Volumes of Vacuum, Spitter of Fire and Rock, Trifler with Millennia — what could we do for Thee that Thou couldst not do for Thyself one octillion times better? Nothing. What could we do or say that could possibly interest Thee? Nothing. Oh, Mankind, rejoice in the apathy of our Creator, for it makes us free and truthful and dignified at last. No longer can a fool point to a ridiculous accident of good luck and say, 'Somebody up there likes me.' And no longer can a tyrant say, 'God wants this or that to happen, and anyone who doesn't help this or that to happen is against God.' O Lord Most High, what a glorious weapon is Thy Apathy, for we have unsheathed it, have thrust and slashed mightily with it, and the claptrap that has so often enslaved us or driven us into the madhouse lies slain!&quot; -The prayer of the Reverend C. Horner Redwine" -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334702-we-take-a-handful-of-sand-from-the-endless-landscape</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 04:40:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Robert M. Pirsig]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334702-we-take-a-handful-of-sand-from-the-endless-landscape]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We take a handful of sand from the endless landscape of awareness around us and call that handful of sand the world." -- Robert M. Pirsig]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
