<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/513996-kirsten]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/513996-kirsten" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 07:28:08 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218696-and-i-declare-myself-free-from-ignorant-love-you-easy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 07:28:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Wendall Berry, from The Mad Farmer Manifesto: The First Amendment]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218696-and-i-declare-myself-free-from-ignorant-love-you-easy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I declare myself free
from ignorant love. You easy lovers
and forgivers of mankind, stand back!
I will love you at a distance,
and not because you deserve it.
My love must be descriminate
or fail to bear its weight." -- Wendall Berry, from The Mad Farmer Manifesto: The First Amendment]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254579-it-is-to-be-broken-it-is-to-be-torn</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 07:04:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254579-it-is-to-be-broken-it-is-to-be-torn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is to be broken. It is to be
torn open. It is not to be
reached and come to rest in
ever. I turn against you,
I break from you, I turn to you.
We hurt, and are hurt,
and have each other for healing.
It is healing. It is never whole." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/421715-birds-except-when-broiled-and-in-the-society-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 19:10:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/421715-birds-except-when-broiled-and-in-the-society-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Birds, except when broiled and in the society of a cold bottle, bored him stiff." -- P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431286-it-seemed-a-place-where-heroes-could-fitly-feast-after</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 09:15:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Kenneth Grahame]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431286-it-seemed-a-place-where-heroes-could-fitly-feast-after]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seemed a place where heroes could fitly feast after victory, where weary harvesters could line up in scores along the table and keep their Harvest Home with mirth and song, or where two or three friends of simple tastes could sit about as they pleased and eat and smoke and talk in comfort and contentment." -- Kenneth Grahame]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878852-i-could-not-have-desired-her-enough-she-was-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 18:45:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878852-i-could-not-have-desired-her-enough-she-was-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I could not have desired her enough. She was a living soul and could be loved forever. Like every living creature, she carried in her the presence of eternity. That was why, as she grew older, I saw in her always the child she had been, and why, looking at her when she was a child, I felt the influence of the woman she would be. That is why, in marrying one another, we mortals say &quot;till death.&quot; We must take love to the limit of time, because time cannot limit it. A life cannot limit it. Maybe to have it in your hear all your life in this world, even while it fails here, is to succeed. Maybe that is enough" -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/817315-god-loves-port-william-as-it-is-why-else-should</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 18:49:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/817315-god-loves-port-william-as-it-is-why-else-should]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God loves Port William as it is... Why else should He want it to be better than it is?
All my life I had heard preachers quoting John 3:16 &quot;For God so loved the world, that He gave His only begotten Son, that whosoever believeth in Him should not perish by have everlasting life.&quot; They would preach on the second part of the verse, to show the easiness of being saved (&quot;only believe&quot;). Where I hung now was the first part. If God loved the world even before the event at Bethlehem, that meant He loved it as it was, with all its faults. That would be Hell itself, in part. He would be like a father with a wayward child, whom He can't help and can't forget. But it would be even worse than that, for He would also know the wayward child and the course of its waywardness and its suffering. That His love contains all the world does not show that the world does not matter, or that He and we do not suffer it unto death; it shows that the world is Hell only in part. But His love can contain it only by compassion and mercy, which, if not Hell entirely, would be at least a crucifixion." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878862-sometimes-i-knew-in-all-my-mind-and-heard-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 18:58:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878862-sometimes-i-knew-in-all-my-mind-and-heard-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I knew in all my mind and heard why I had done what I had done, and I welcomed the sacrifice. But there were times too when I lived in a desert and felt no joy and saw no hope and could not remember my old feelings. Then I lived by faith alone, faith without hope.
What good did I get from it? I got to have love in my heart." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878866-he-was-lonely-because-he-could-imagine-himself-as-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 19:05:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878866-he-was-lonely-because-he-could-imagine-himself-as-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was lonely because he could imagine himself as anything but himself and as anywhere but where he was. His competitiveness and self-centeredness cut him off from any thought of shared life. He wanted to have more because he thought that having more would make him able to live more, and he was lonely because he never thought of the sources, the places, where he was going to get what he wanted to have, or of what his having it might cost others. It was loneliness that sometimes even he felt; you could see it. A self-praiser has got to accept a big loneliness in order to accept a little credit." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414254-over-a-long-time-the-coming-and-passing-of-several</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 19:26:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414254-over-a-long-time-the-coming-and-passing-of-several]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Over a long time, the coming and passing of several generations, the old farm had settled into its patterns and cycles of work - its annual plowing moving from field to field; its animals arriving by birth or purchase, feeding and growing, thriving and departing. Its patterns and cycles were virtually the farm's own understanding of what it was doing, of what it could do without diminishment. This order was not unintelligent or rigid. It tightened and slackened, shifted and changed in response to the markets and the weather. The Depression had changed it somewhat, and so had the war. But through all changes so far, the farm had endured. Its cycles of cropping and grazing, thought and work, were articulations of its wish to cohere and to last. The farm, so to speak, desired all of its lives to flourish.
Athey was not exactly, or not only, what is called a &quot;landowner.&quot; He was the farm's farmer, but also its creature and belonging. He lived its life, and it lived his; he knew that, of the two lives, his was meant to be the smaller and the shorter." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432285-some-of-the-best-things-i-have-ever-thought-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 19:29:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432285-some-of-the-best-things-i-have-ever-thought-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some of the best things I have ever thought of I have thought of during bad sermons." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/586259-in-general-i-weathered-even-the-worst-sermons-pretty-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 19:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/586259-in-general-i-weathered-even-the-worst-sermons-pretty-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In general, I weathered even the worst sermons pretty well. They had the great virtue of causing my mind to wander. Some of the best things I have ever thought of I have thought of during bad sermons. Or I would look out the windows. In winter, when the windows were closed, the church seemed to admit the light strictly on its own terms, as if uneasy about the frank sunshine of this benighted world. In summer, when the sashes were raised, I watched with a great, eager pleasure the town and the fields beyond, the clouds, the trees, the movements of the air—but then the sermons would seem more improbable. I have always loved a window, especially an open one." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878878-i-loved-the-different-voices-all-singing-one-song-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 19:33:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878878-i-loved-the-different-voices-all-singing-one-song-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I loved the different voices all singing one song, the various tones and qualities, the passing lifts of feeling, rising up and going out forever. Old Man Profet, who was a different man on Sunday, used to draw out the notes at the ends of verses so he could listen to himself, and in fact it sounded pretty." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878888-i-thought-that-some-of-the-hymns-bespoke-the-true</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 19:39:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by wendell berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878888-i-thought-that-some-of-the-hymns-bespoke-the-true]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I thought that some of the hymns bespoke the true religion of the place. The people didn't really want to be saints of self-deprivation and hatred of the world. They knew that the world would sooner or later deprive them of all it had given them, but still they liked it. What they came together for was to acknowledge, just by coming, their losses and failures and sorrows, their need for comfort, their faith always needing to be greater, their wish (in spite of all words and acts to the contrary) to love one another and to forgive and be forgiven, their need for one another's help and company and divine gifts, their hope (and experience) of love surpassing death, their gratitude." -- wendell berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878904-finally-bill-mixter-would-lower-his-head-lay-his-bow</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 19:53:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by wendell berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878904-finally-bill-mixter-would-lower-his-head-lay-his-bow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finally Bill Mixter would lower his head, lay his bow upon the strings, and draw out the first notes of a tune, and the others would come in behind him. The music, while it lasted, brought a new world into being. They would play some tunes they had learned on the radio, but their knowledge was far older than that and they played too the music that was native to the place, or that the people of the place were native to. Just the names of the tunes were a kind of music; they cal l back the music to my mind still, after so many years: &quot;Sand Riffle,&quot; &quot;Last Gold Dollar,&quot; &quot;Billy in the Low Ground,&quot; &quot;Gate to Go Through,&quot; and a lot of others. &quot;A fiddle, now, is an atmospheric thing,&quot; said Burley Coulter. The music was another element filling the room and pouring out through the cracks. When at last they'd had their fill and had gone away, the shop felt empty, the silence larger than before." -- wendell berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878911-by-then-i-wasn-t-just-asking-questions-i-was-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 19:58:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by wendell berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878911-by-then-i-wasn-t-just-asking-questions-i-was-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By then I wasn't just asking questions; I was being changed by them. I was being changed by my prayers, which dwindled down nearer and nearer to silence, which weren't confrontations with God but with the difficulty--in my own mind, or in the human lot--of knowing what or how to pray. Lying awake at night, I could feel myself being changed--into what,  I had no idea." -- wendell berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878954-from-my-college-courses-and-my-reading-i-knew-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 21:18:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878954-from-my-college-courses-and-my-reading-i-knew-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From my college courses and my reading I knew the various names that came at the end of a line of questions or were placed as periods to bafflement: the First Cause, the First Mover, the Life Force, the Universal Mind, the First Principle, the Unmoved Mover, even Providence. I too had used those names in arguing with others, and with myself, trying to explain the world to myself. And now I saw that those names explained nothing. They were of no more use than Evolution or Natural Selection or Nature or The Big Bang of these later days. All such names do is catch us within the length and breadth of our own thoughts and our own bewilderment. Though I knew the temptation of simple reason, to know nothing that can't be proved, still I supposed that those were not the right names.
I imagined that the right name might be Father, and I imagined all that that name would imply: the love, the compassion, the taking offense, the disappointment, the anger, the bearing of wounds, the weeping of tears, the forgiveness, the suffering unto death. If love could force my own thoughts over the edge of the world and out of time, then could I not see how even divine omnipotence might by the force of its own love be swayed down into the world? Could I not see how it might, because it could know its creatures only by compassion, put on mortal flesh, become a man, and walk among us, assume our nature and our fate, suffer our faults and our death?
Yes. I could imagine a Father who is yet like a mother hen spreading her wings before the storm or in the dusk before the dark night for the little ones of Port William to come in under, some of whom do, and some do not. I could imagine Port William riding its humble wave through time under the sky, its little flames of wakefulness lighting and going out, its lives passing through birth, pleasure, sufferning, and death. I could imagine God looking down upon it, its lives living by His spirit, breathing by His breath, knowing by His light, but each life living also (inescapably) by its own will--His own body given to be broken." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882630-if-god-loves-the-world-might-that-not-be-proved</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2013 20:02:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882630-if-god-loves-the-world-might-that-not-be-proved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If God loves the world, might that not be proved in my own love for it? I prayed to know in my heart His love for the world, and this was my most prideful, foolish, and dangerous prayer. It was my step into the abyss. As soon as I prayed it, I knew that I would die. I knew the old wrong and the death that lay in the world. Just as a good man would not coerce the love of his wife, God does not coerce the love of His human creatures, not for Himself or for the world or for one another. To allow that love to exist fully and freely, He must allow it not to exist at all. His love is suffering. It is our freedom and His sorrow. To love the world as much even as I could love it would be suffering also, for I would fail. And yet all the good I know is in this, that a man might so love this world that it would break his heart." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882633-you-may-say-that-i-am-just-another-outdated-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2013 20:07:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by wendell berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882633-you-may-say-that-i-am-just-another-outdated-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may say that I am just another outdated old man complaining about progress and the changes of time. But, you see, I have well considered that possibility myself, and am prepared o submit to correction by anybody who cares about a community, who can show me how the world is improved by that community's dying." -- wendell berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/887951-through-my-history-s-despite-and-ruin-i-have-come-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2013 05:08:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/887951-through-my-history-s-despite-and-ruin-i-have-come-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Through my history's despite
and ruin, I have come
to its remainder, and here
have made the beginning
of a farm intended to become
my art of being here.
By it I would instruct
my wants: they should belong
to each other and to this place.
Until my song comes here
to learn its words, my art
is but the hope of song.

(Part 2 from History is Clearing, p 174)" -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/887954-and-yet-a-knowledge-is-here-that-tenses-the-throat</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2013 05:14:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/887954-and-yet-a-knowledge-is-here-that-tenses-the-throat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...And yet a knowledge
is here that tenses the throat
as for song: the inheritance
of the ones, alive or once
alive, who stand behind
the ones I have imagined,
who took into their minds
the troubles of this place,
blights of love and race,
but saw a good fate here
and willingly paid its cost,
kept it the best they could,
thought of its good,
and mourned the good they lost.

(From the ending of Where in Clearing, p179)" -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/897880-but-faith-is-not-necessarily-or-not-soon-a-resting</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 20:14:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/897880-but-faith-is-not-necessarily-or-not-soon-a-resting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But faith is not necessarily, or not soon, a resting place. Faith puts you out on a wide river in a boat, in the fog, in the dark. Even a man of faith knows that (as Burley Coulter used to say) we've all got to go through enough to kill us." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/897882-it-is-not-a-terrible-thing-to-love-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 20:18:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by wendell berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/897882-it-is-not-a-terrible-thing-to-love-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not a terrible thing to love the world, knowing that the world is always passing and irrecoverable, to be known only in loss. To love anything good, at any cost, is a bargain." -- wendell berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916809-then-jip-went-up-to-the-front-of-the-ship</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 08:16:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by Hugh Lofting]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916809-then-jip-went-up-to-the-front-of-the-ship]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then Jip went up to the front of the ship and smelt the wind; and he started muttering to himself,

&quot;Tar; Spanish onions; kerosene oil; wet raincoats; crushed laurel-leaves; rubber burning; lace-curtains being washed--No, my mistake, lace-curtains hanging out to dry; and foxes--hundreds of 'em--cubs; and--&quot;

&quot;Can you really smell all those different things in this one wind?&quot; asked the Doctor.

&quot;Why, of course!&quot; said Jip.  &quot;And those are only a few of the easy smells--the strong ones. Any mongrel could smell those with a cold in the head.  Wait now, and I'll tell you some of the harder scents that are coming on this wind--a few of the dainty ones.&quot;

Then the dog shut his eyes tight, poked his nose straight up in the air and sniffed hard with his mouth half-open.

For a long time he said nothing.  He kept as still as a stone.  He hardly seemed to be breathing at all.  When at last he began to speak, it sounded almost as though he were singing, sadly, in a dream.

&quot;Bricks,&quot; he whispered, very low--&quot;old yellow bricks, crumbling with age in a garden-wall; the sweet breath of young cows standing in a mountain-stream; the lead roof of a dove-cote--or perhaps a
granary--with the mid-day sun on it; black kid gloves lying in a bureau-drawer of walnut-wood; a dusty road with a horses' drinking-trough beneath the sycamores; little mushrooms bursting
through the rotting leaves; and--and--and--&quot;

&quot;Any parsnips?&quot; asked Gub-Gub.

&quot;No,&quot; said Jip.  &quot;You always think of things to eat.  No parsnips whatever." -- Hugh Lofting]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
