<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/51416-kim]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/51416-kim" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 07:29:54 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141511-suffering-has-been-stronger-than-all-other-teaching-and-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 07:29:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141511-suffering-has-been-stronger-than-all-other-teaching-and-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suffering has been stronger than all other teaching, and has taught me to understand what your heart used to be. I have been bent and broken, but - I hope - into a better shape." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65487-there-either-is-or-is-not-that-s-the-way-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 07:32:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65487-there-either-is-or-is-not-that-s-the-way-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There either is or is not, that’s the way things are. The colour of the day. The way it felt to be a child. The saltwater on your sunburnt legs. Sometimes the water is yellow, sometimes it’s red. But what colour it may be in memory, depends on the day. I’m not going to tell you the story the way it happened. I’m going to tell it the way I remember it." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209089-it-was-one-of-those-march-days-when-the-sun</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 07:39:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209089-it-was-one-of-those-march-days-when-the-sun]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was one of those March days when the sun shines hot and the wind blows cold:  when it is summer in the light, and winter in the shade." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46353-my-view-is-that-if-there-is-no-evidence-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 21:02:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46353-my-view-is-that-if-there-is-no-evidence-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My view is that if there is no evidence for it, then forget about it. An agnostic is somebody who doesn’t believe in something until there is evidence for it, so I’m agnostic." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/719127-a-company-is-a-moral-imbecile-it-has-no-sense</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 20:24:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Iain Pears]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/719127-a-company-is-a-moral-imbecile-it-has-no-sense]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A company is a moral imbecile. It has no sense of right or wrong. Any restraints have to come from the outside, from laws and customs which forbid it from doing certain things of which we disapprove. But it is a restraint that reduces profits. Which is why all companies will strain forever to break the bounds of the law, to act unfettered in their pursuit of advantage. That is the only way they can survive because the more powerful will devour the weak. And because it is the nature of capital, which is wild, longs to be free and chafes at each and every restriction imposed upon it." -- Iain Pears]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/719134-the-next-day-was-a-dream-of-such-perfection-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 20:29:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Iain Pears]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/719134-the-next-day-was-a-dream-of-such-perfection-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The next day was a dream of such perfection that I have never approached the like again. It was, of course, all illusion, but I like to think of it still in isolation from what came after,as a moment of bliss, one of those days when on is no longer oneself, but becomes bigger, and better, able to overcome the normal preoccupations of life and breathe more freely." -- Iain Pears]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/721987-you-see-we-had-on-the-whole-liked-him-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 10:31:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Joseph Conrad]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/721987-you-see-we-had-on-the-whole-liked-him-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You see we had on the whole liked him well enough. And liking is not sufficient to keep going the interest one takes in a human being. With hatred, apparently, it is otherwise." -- Joseph Conrad]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/748347-it-was-the-very-essence-of-his-life-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 20:43:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Joseph Conrad]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/748347-it-was-the-very-essence-of-his-life-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was the very essence of his life to be a solitary achievement, accomplished not by hermit-like withdrawal with it's silence and immobility but by a system of restless wandering, by the detachment of an impermanent dweller amongst changing scenes. In this scheme he had perceived the means of passing through life without suffering and almost without a single care in the world- invulnerable because elusive." -- Joseph Conrad]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/748352-dreams-are-madness-my-dear-it-s-things-that-happen-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 20:46:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Joseph Conrad]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/748352-dreams-are-madness-my-dear-it-s-things-that-happen-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["dreams are madness, my dear. It's things that happen in the waking world, while one is asleep, that one would be glad to know the meaning of." -- Joseph Conrad]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/748356-woe-to-the-man-whose-heart-has-not-learned-while</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 20:50:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Joseph Conrad]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/748356-woe-to-the-man-whose-heart-has-not-learned-while]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Woe to the man whose heart has not learned while young to hope, to love - and to put it's trust in life!" -- Joseph Conrad]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25238-all-morning-i-struggled-with-the-sensation-of-stray-wisps</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 07:26:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Diane Setterfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25238-all-morning-i-struggled-with-the-sensation-of-stray-wisps]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All morning I struggled with the sensation of stray wisps of one world seeping through the cracks of another. Do you know the feeling when you start reading a new book before the membrane of the last one has had time to close behind you?  You leave the previous book with ideas and themes -- characters even -- caught in the fibers of your clothes, and when you open the new book, they are still with you." -- Diane Setterfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25375-i-have-always-been-a-reader-i-have-read-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 07:27:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Diane Setterfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25375-i-have-always-been-a-reader-i-have-read-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always been a reader; I have read at every stage of my life, and there has never been a time when reading was not my greatest joy. And yet I cannot pretend that the reading I have done in my adult years matches in its impact on my soul the reading I did as a child. I still believe in stories. I still forget myself when I am in the middle of a good book. Yet it is not the same. Books are, for me, it must be said, the most important thing; what I cannot forget is that there was a time when they were at once more banal and more essential than that. When I was a child, books were everything. And so there is in me, always, a nostalgic yearning for the lost pleasure of books. It is not a yearning that one ever expects to be fulfilled." -- Diane Setterfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12297-a-birth-is-not-really-a-beginning-our-lives-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 07:27:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Diane Setterfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12297-a-birth-is-not-really-a-beginning-our-lives-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A birth is not really a beginning. Our lives at the start are not really our own but only the continuation of someone else's story." -- Diane Setterfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11573-all-i-meant-was-that-people-take-their-same-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 21:56:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Julia Glass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11573-all-i-meant-was-that-people-take-their-same-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All I meant was that people take their same old lives wherever they go. No place is perfect enough to strip you of that. And some places have a way of magnifying your demons, or of, I don't know, giving them pep pills." -- Julia Glass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/851735-when-it-comes-to-love-there-is-the-timeworn-caution</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 10:23:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Julia Glass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/851735-when-it-comes-to-love-there-is-the-timeworn-caution]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When it comes to love, there is the timeworn caution that the very qualities you fall hardest for may be those you grow to despise. With Stavros, she wonders if the opposite might hold true: that this quality she nearly fears - his aversion to sanctifying the past - is something for which she will someday be grateful." -- Julia Glass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1056691-my-father-also-told-me-that-people-had-always-suffered</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2014 21:43:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Ivan Klíma]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1056691-my-father-also-told-me-that-people-had-always-suffered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My father also told me that people had always suffered from being tied to the ground, from not being able to detach themselves from it. But they had dreamed of leaving it, and so they had invented the garden of paradise, which had in it everything they yearned for but lacked in their lives, and they had dreamed up creatures similar to themselves but equipped with wings. But what in the past had only been dreamed of was now beginning to materialize, my father said, pointing to the sky. Angels did not exist, but people could now fly. There was no paradise for human souls to dwell in, but one day I would understand that it was more important for people to live well and happily here on earth." -- Ivan Klíma]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1056697-man-is-reluctant-to-accept-that-his-life-has-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2014 21:49:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Ivan Klíma]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1056697-man-is-reluctant-to-accept-that-his-life-has-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man is reluctant to accept that his life has come to a conclusion in that most important respect, that his hopes have been fulfilled. He hesitates to look death in the face, and there is little that comes so close to death as fulfilled love." -- Ivan Klíma]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1056698-what-we-need-kafka-wrote-are-books-which-strike-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2014 21:56:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Ivan Klíma]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1056698-what-we-need-kafka-wrote-are-books-which-strike-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What we need [Kafka] wrote, are books which strike us like the most painful misfortune, like the death of someone we loved more than ourselves, books which would make us feel that we've been driven out into the forest far from another human being. A book must be an axe for the frozen sea within us." -- Ivan Klíma]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
