<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/51411-laura]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/51411-laura" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 14:34:38 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39828-i-ve-come-up-with-a-set-of-rules-that-describe</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 14:34:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39828-i-ve-come-up-with-a-set-of-rules-that-describe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've come up with a set of rules that describe our reactions to technologies:
1. Anything that is in the world when you’re born is normal and ordinary and is just a natural part of the way the world works.
2. Anything that's invented between when you’re fifteen and thirty-five is new and exciting and revolutionary and you can probably get a career in it.
3. Anything invented after you're thirty-five is against the natural order of things." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13822-this-must-be-thursday-said-arthur-to-himself-sinking-low</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 14:35:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13822-this-must-be-thursday-said-arthur-to-himself-sinking-low]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This must be Thursday,' said Arthur to himself, sinking low over his beer. 'I never could get the hang of Thursdays." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83277-we-can-t-win-against-obsession-they-care-we-don-t-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 14:38:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83277-we-can-t-win-against-obsession-they-care-we-don-t-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can't win against obsession.  They care, we don't.  They win." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35419-all-opinions-are-not-equal-some-are-a-very-great</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 14:39:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35419-all-opinions-are-not-equal-some-are-a-very-great]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All opinions are not equal. Some are a very great deal more robust, sophisticated and well supported in logic and argument than others." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120016-beethoven-tells-you-what-it-s-like-to-be-beethoven-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 14:40:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120016-beethoven-tells-you-what-it-s-like-to-be-beethoven-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beethoven tells you what it's like to be Beethoven and Mozart tells you what it's like to be human. Bach tells you what it's like to be the universe." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36835-there-s-always-a-moment-when-you-start-to-fall-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 14:39:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36835-there-s-always-a-moment-when-you-start-to-fall-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's always a moment when you start to fall out of love, whether it's with a person or an idea or a cause, even if it's one you only narrate to yourself years after the event: a tiny thing, a wrong word, a false note, which means that things can never be quite the same again." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54480-arthur-if-i-asked-you-where-the-hell-we-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 14:40:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54480-arthur-if-i-asked-you-where-the-hell-we-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Arthur: If I asked you where the hell we were, would I regret it?
Ford: We're safe.
Arthur: Oh good.
Ford: We're in a small galley cabin in one of the spaceships of the Vogon Constructor Fleet.
Arthur: Ah, this is obviously some strange use of the word &lt;i&gt;safe&lt;/i&gt; that I wasn't previously aware of." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142100-there-is-no-point-in-using-the-word-impossible-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 14:41:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142100-there-is-no-point-in-using-the-word-impossible-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no point in using the word 'impossible' to describe something that has clearly happened." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45158-now-the-invention-of-the-scientific-method-and-science-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 14:42:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45158-now-the-invention-of-the-scientific-method-and-science-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now, the invention of the scientific method and science is, I'm sure we'll all agree, the most powerful intellectual idea, the most powerful framework for thinking and investigating and understanding and challenging the world around us that there is, and that it rests on the premise that any idea is there to be attacked and if it withstands the attack then it lives to fight another day and if it doesn't withstand the attack then down it goes. Religion doesn't seem to work like that; it has certain ideas at the heart of it which we call sacred or holy or whatever. That's an idea we're so familiar with, whether we subscribe to it or not, that it's kind of odd to think what it actually means, because really what it means is 'Here is an idea or a notion that you're not allowed to say anything bad about; you're just not. Why not? - because you're not!" -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83034-we-demand-rigidly-defined-areas-of-doubt-and-uncertainty</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 14:43:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83034-we-demand-rigidly-defined-areas-of-doubt-and-uncertainty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We demand rigidly defined areas of doubt and uncertainty!" -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92489-the-hitchhiker-s-guide-to-the-galaxy-s-definition-of-universe-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 15:02:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92489-the-hitchhiker-s-guide-to-the-galaxy-s-definition-of-universe-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy's definition of &quot;Universe&quot;:

The Universe is a very big thing that contains a great number of planets and a great number of beings. It is Everything. What we live in. All around us. The lot. Not nothing. It is quite difficult to actually define what the Universe means, but fortunately the Guide doesn't worry about that and just gives us some useful information to live in it. 

Area: The area of the Universe is infinite.

Imports: None. This is a by product of infinity; it is impossible to import things into something that has infinite volume because by definition there is no outside to import things from.

Exports: None, for similar reasons as imports.

Population: None. Although you might see people from time to time, they are most likely products of your imagination. Simple mathematics tells us that the population of the Universe must be zero. Why? Well given that the volume of the universe is infinite there must be an infinite number of worlds. But not all of them are populated; therefore only a finite number are. Any finite number divided by infinity is zero, therefore the average population of the Universe is zero, and so the total population must be zero.

Art: None. Because the function of art is to hold a mirror up to nature there can be no art because the Universe is infinite which means there simply isn't a mirror big enough. 

Sex: None. Although in fact there is quite a lot, given the zero population of the Universe there can in fact be no beings to have sex, and therefore no sex happens in the Universe." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70827-this-is-rather-as-if-you-imagine-a-puddle-waking</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 15:03:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70827-this-is-rather-as-if-you-imagine-a-puddle-waking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is rather as if you imagine a puddle waking up one morning and thinking, 'This is an interesting world I find myself in — an interesting hole I find myself in — fits me rather neatly, doesn't it? In fact it fits me staggeringly well, must have been made to have me in it!' This is such a powerful idea that as the sun rises in the sky and the air heats up and as, gradually, the puddle gets smaller and smaller, frantically hanging on to the notion that everything's going to be alright, because this world was meant to have him in it, was built to have him in it; so the moment he disappears catches him rather by surprise. I think this may be something we need to be on the watch out for." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79251-if-life-is-going-to-exist-in-a-universe-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 15:05:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79251-if-life-is-going-to-exist-in-a-universe-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If life is going to exist in a Universe of this size, then the one thing it cannot afford to have is a sense of proportion." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196350-we-have-normality-i-repeat-we-have-normality-anything-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 15:05:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Douglas Adams ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196350-we-have-normality-i-repeat-we-have-normality-anything-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have normality. I repeat, we have normality. Anything you still can't cope with is therefore your own problem." -- Douglas Adams ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59937-everyone-at-some-point-in-their-lives-wakes-up-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 16:11:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59937-everyone-at-some-point-in-their-lives-wakes-up-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone, at some point in their lives, wakes up in the middle of the night with the feeling that they are all alone in the world, and that nobody loves them now and that nobody will ever love them, and that they will never have a decent night's sleep again and will spend their lives wandering blearily around a loveless landscape, hoping desperately that their circumstances will improve, but suspecting, in their heart of hearts, that they will remain unloved forever. The best thing to do in these circumstances is to wake somebody else up, so that they can feel this way, too." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43717-nothing-of-me-is-original-i-am-the-combined-effort</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 16:11:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43717-nothing-of-me-is-original-i-am-the-combined-effort]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing of me is original. I am the combined effort of everyone I've ever known." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1981-my-experience-of-life-is-that-it-is-not-divided</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 16:16:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1981-my-experience-of-life-is-that-it-is-not-divided]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My experience of life is that it is not divided up into genres; it’s a horrifying, romantic, tragic, comical, science-fiction cowboy detective novel. You know, with a bit of pornography if you're lucky." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3160-today-you-are-you-that-is-truer-than-true-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 06:50:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3160-today-you-are-you-that-is-truer-than-true-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today you are You, that is truer than true. There is no one alive who is Youer than You." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175214-i-m-afraid-that-sometimes-you-ll-play-lonely-games-too-games</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 07:26:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175214-i-m-afraid-that-sometimes-you-ll-play-lonely-games-too-games]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm afraid that sometimes you'll play lonely games too. Games you can't win 'cause you'll play against you." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6805-sometimes-the-questions-are-complicated-and-the-answers-are-simple</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 07:32:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6805-sometimes-the-questions-are-complicated-and-the-answers-are-simple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes the questions are complicated and the answers are simple." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
