<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/519248-nat]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/519248-nat" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 12:32:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163011-the-truth-is-everyone-likes-to-look-down-on-someone</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 12:32:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nat add a quote by Brent weeks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163011-the-truth-is-everyone-likes-to-look-down-on-someone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is, everyone likes to look down on someone. If your favorites are all avant-garde writers who throw in Sanskrit and German, you can look down on everyone. If your favorites are all Oprah Book Club books, you can at least look down on mystery readers. Mystery readers have sci-fi readers. Sci-fi can look down on fantasy. And yes, fantasy readers have their own snobbishness. I’ll bet this, though: in a hundred years, people will be writing a lot more dissertations on Harry Potter than on John Updike. Look, Charles Dickens wrote popular fiction. Shakespeare wrote popular fiction—until he wrote his sonnets, desperate to show the literati of his day that he was real artist. Edgar Allan Poe tied himself in knots because no one realized he was a genius. The core of the problem is how we want to define “literature”. The Latin root simply means “letters”. Those letters are either delivered—they connect with an audience—or they don’t. For some, that audience is a few thousand college professors and some critics. For others, its twenty million women desperate for romance in their lives. Those connections happen because the books successfully communicate something real about the human experience. Sure, there are trashy books that do really well, but that’s because there are trashy facets of humanity. What people value in their books—and thus what they count as literature—really tells you more about them than it does about the book." -- Brent weeks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7916-we-shall-meet-in-the-place-where-there-is-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 05:56:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nat add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7916-we-shall-meet-in-the-place-where-there-is-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We shall meet in the place where there is no darkness." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6711-a-common-mistake-that-people-make-when-trying-to-design</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 09:26:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nat add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6711-a-common-mistake-that-people-make-when-trying-to-design]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A common mistake that people make when trying to design something completely foolproof is to underestimate the ingenuity of complete fools." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
