<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/522689-sarah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/522689-sarah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 18:38:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36027-it-is-in-vain-to-say-human-beings-ought-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 18:38:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36027-it-is-in-vain-to-say-human-beings-ought-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is in vain to say human beings ought to be satisfied with tranquillity: they must have action; and they will make it if they cannot find it. Millions are condemned to a stiller doom than mine, and millions are in silent revolt against their lot. Nobody knows how many rebellions besides political rebellions ferment in the masses of life which people earth. Women are supposed to be very calm generally: but women feel just as men feel; they need exercise for their faculties, and a field for their efforts, as much as their brothers do; they suffer from too rigid a restraint, to absolute a stagnation, precisely as men would suffer; and it is narrow-minded in their more privileged fellow-creatures to say that they ought to confine themselves to making puddings and knitting stockings, to playing on the piano and embroidering bags. It is thoughtless to condemn them, or laugh at them, if they seek to do more or learn more than custom has pronounced necessary for their sex." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57410-perhaps-all-our-loves-are-merely-hints-and-symbols-vagabond-language</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 18:44:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57410-perhaps-all-our-loves-are-merely-hints-and-symbols-vagabond-language]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps all our loves are merely hints and symbols; vagabond-language scrawled on gate-posts and paving-stones along the weary road that others have tramped before us; perhaps you and I are types and this sadness which sometimes falls between us springs from disappointment in our search, each straining through and beyond the other, snatching a glimpse now and then of the shadow which turns the corner always a pace or two ahead of us." -- Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122822-when-i-began-to-write-our-story-down-i-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 18:44:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122822-when-i-began-to-write-our-story-down-i-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I began to write our story down, I thought I was writing a record of hate, but somehow the hate has got mislaid and all I know is that in spite of her mistakes and her unreliability, she was better than most. It's just as well that one of us should believe in her: she never did in herself." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35084-the-social-mould-civilization-fits-us-into-have-no-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 18:50:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Thomas Hardy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35084-the-social-mould-civilization-fits-us-into-have-no-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...the social mould civilization fits us into have no more relation to our actual shapes than the conventional shapes of the constellations have to the real star-patterns. I am called Mrs. Richard Phillotson, living a calm wedded life with my counterpart of that name. But I am not really Mrs. Richard Phillotson, but a woman tossed about, all alone, with aberrant passions, and unaccountable antipathies..." -- Thomas Hardy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37083-to-have-lost-is-less-disturbing-than-to-wonder-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 18:50:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Thomas Hardy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37083-to-have-lost-is-less-disturbing-than-to-wonder-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To have lost is less disturbing than to wonder if we may possibly have won; and Eustacia could now, like other people at such a stage, take a standing-point outside herself, observe herself as a disinterested spectator, and think what a sport for Heaven this woman Eustacia was." -- Thomas Hardy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35134-there-are-things-that-happen-and-leave-no-discernible-trace</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 19:22:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by A. S. Byatt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35134-there-are-things-that-happen-and-leave-no-discernible-trace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are things that happen and leave no discernible trace, are not spoken or written of, though it would be very wrong to say that subsequent events go on indifferently, all the same, as though such things had never been." -- A. S. Byatt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10868-his-heart-beat-faster-and-faster-as-daisy-s-white-face</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 19:25:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10868-his-heart-beat-faster-and-faster-as-daisy-s-white-face]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His heart beat faster and faster as Daisy’s white face came up to his own.  He knew that when he kissed this girl, and forever wed his unutterable visions to her perishable breath, his mind would never romp again like the mind of God.  So he waited, listening for a moment longer to the tuning fork that had been struck upon a star.  Then he kissed her. At his lips’ touch she blossomed like a flower and the incarnation was complete." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121705-sonnet-xvii-i-do-not-love-you-as-if-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 19:26:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121705-sonnet-xvii-i-do-not-love-you-as-if-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sonnet XVII

I do not love you as if you were salt-rose, or topaz,
or the arrow of carnations the fire shoots off.
I love you as certain dark things are to be loved,
in secret, between the shadow and the soul.

I love you as the plant that never blooms
but carries in itself the light of hidden flowers;
thanks to your love a certain solid fragrance,
risen from the earth, lives darkly in my body.

I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where.
I love you straightforwardly, without complexities or pride;
so I love you because I know no other way than this: 

where I does not exist, nor you,
so close that your hand on my chest is my hand,
so close that your eyes close as I fall asleep. " -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11669-had-i-the-heavens-embroidered-cloths-enwrought-with-golden-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 19:27:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by William Butler Yeats]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11669-had-i-the-heavens-embroidered-cloths-enwrought-with-golden-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Had I the heavens' embroidered cloths,
Enwrought with golden and silver light,
The blue and the dim and the dark cloths
Of night and light and the half light,
I would spread the cloths under your feet:
But I, being poor, have only my dreams;
I have spread my dreams under your feet;
Tread softly because you tread on my dreams." -- William Butler Yeats]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1174-he-is-outside-of-everything-and-alien-everywhere-he-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 19:30:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1174-he-is-outside-of-everything-and-alien-everywhere-he-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He is outside of everything, and alien everywhere. He is an aesthetic solitary. His beautiful, light imagination is the wing that on the autumn evening just brushes the dusky window." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106780-twice-in-her-life-she-had-mistaken-something-else-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 19:30:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Nancy Mitford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106780-twice-in-her-life-she-had-mistaken-something-else-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twice in her life she had mistaken something else for it; it was like seeing somebody in the street who you think is a friend, you whistle and wave and run after him, and it is not only not the friend, but not even very like him. A few minutes later the real friend appears in view, and then you can't imagine how you ever mistook that other person for him. Linda was now looking upon the authentic face of love, and she knew it, but it frightened her. That it should come so casually, so much by a series of accidents, was frightening." -- Nancy Mitford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/999-oh-jake-brett-said-we-could-have-had-such-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 19:32:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/999-oh-jake-brett-said-we-could-have-had-such-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh Jake,&quot; Brett said, &quot;We could have had such a damned good time together.&quot;
Ahead was a mounted policeman in khaki directing traffic. He raised his baton. The car slowed suddenly, pressing Brett against me.
Yes,&quot; I said. &quot;Isn't it pretty to think so?" -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35671-between-skin-and-skin-there-is-only-light</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 19:34:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by John Fowles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35671-between-skin-and-skin-there-is-only-light]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Between skin and skin, there is only light." -- John Fowles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15197-a-kiss-about-apple-pie-a-la-mode-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 19:35:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Francesca Lia Block]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15197-a-kiss-about-apple-pie-a-la-mode-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A kiss about apple pie a la mode with the vanilla creaminess melting in the pie heat. A kiss about chocolate, when you haven't eaten chocolate in a year. A kiss about palm trees speeding by, trailing pink clouds when you drive down the Strip sizzling with champagne. A kiss about spotlights fanning the sky and the swollen sea spilling like tears all over your legs." -- Francesca Lia Block]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25-we-are-all-in-the-gutter-but-some-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 19:36:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25-we-are-all-in-the-gutter-but-some-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all in the gutter, but some of us are looking at the stars." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12009-yet-each-man-kills-the-thing-he-loves-by-each</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 19:37:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12009-yet-each-man-kills-the-thing-he-loves-by-each]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yet each man kills the thing he loves
By each let this be heard
Some do it with a bitter look
Some with a flattering word
The coward does it with a kiss
The brave man with a sword" -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23152-to-be-a-poet-is-to-have-a-soul-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 19:39:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23152-to-be-a-poet-is-to-have-a-soul-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be a poet is to have a soul so quick to discern, that no shade of quality escapes it, and so quick to feel, that discernment is but a hand playing with finely-ordered variety on the chords of emotion--a soul in which knowledge passes instantaneously into feeling, and feeling flashes back as a new organ of knowledge." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4484-there-is-a-crack-in-everything-that-s-how-the-light</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 14:51:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Leonard Cohen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4484-there-is-a-crack-in-everything-that-s-how-the-light]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a crack in everything.
That's how the light gets in." -- Leonard Cohen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8637-as-our-eyes-grow-accustomed-to-sight-they-armour-themselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 14:51:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Leonard Cohen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8637-as-our-eyes-grow-accustomed-to-sight-they-armour-themselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As our eyes grow accustomed to sight they armour themselves against wonder.  " -- Leonard Cohen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124052-dearest-charles---i-found-a-box-of-this-paper-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 13:53:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124052-dearest-charles---i-found-a-box-of-this-paper-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dearest Charles--
I found a box of this paper at the back of a bureau so I must write to you as I am mourning for my lost innocence.  It never looked like living.  The doctors despaired of it from the start...
I am never quite alone.  Members of my family keep turning up and collecting luggage and going away again, but the white raspberries are ripe.
I have a good mind not to take Aloysius to Venice.  I don't want him to meet a lot of horrid Italian bears and pick up bad habits.
Love or what you will.
S." -- Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124054-they-took-to-silence-they-touched-each-other-without-comment</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 18:51:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by A.S. Byatt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124054-they-took-to-silence-they-touched-each-other-without-comment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They took to silence. They touched each other without comment and without progression. A hand on a hand, a clothed arm, resting on an arm. An ankle overlapping an ankle, as they sat on a beach, and not removed. One night they fell asleep, side by side... He slept curled against her back, a dark comma against her pale elegant phrase." -- A.S. Byatt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124053-these-memories-are-the-memorials-and-pledges-of-the-vital</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 18:51:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124053-these-memories-are-the-memorials-and-pledges-of-the-vital]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These memories are the memorials and pledges of the vital hours of a lifetime.  These hours of afflatus in the human spirit, the springs of art, are, in their mystery, akin to the epochs of history, when a race which for centuries has lived content, unknown, behind its own frontiers, digging, eating, sleeping, begetting, doing what was requisite for survival and nothing else, will, for a generation or two, stupefy the world; commit all manner of crimes, perhaps; follow the wildest chimeras, go down in the end in agony, but leave behind a record of new heights scaled and new rewards won for all mankind; the vision fades, the soul sickens, and the routine of survival starts again." -- Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125911-a-story-has-no-beginning-or-end-arbitrarily-one-chooses</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2009 21:25:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125911-a-story-has-no-beginning-or-end-arbitrarily-one-chooses]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A story has no beginning or end: arbitrarily one chooses that moment of experience from which to look back or from which to look ahead." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180447-she-thought-it-was-part-of-the-hardship-of-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2010 20:57:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180447-she-thought-it-was-part-of-the-hardship-of-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She thought it was part of the hardship of her life that there was laid upon her the burthen of larger wants than others seemed to feel – that she had to endure this wide hopeless yearning for that something, whatever it was, that was greatest and best on this earth." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67667-saints-and-martyrs-had-never-interested-maggie-so-much-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2010 20:59:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67667-saints-and-martyrs-had-never-interested-maggie-so-much-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Saints and martyrs had never interested Maggie so much as sages and poets." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70058-i-am-simply-a-book-drunkard-books-have-the-same</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 18:09:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70058-i-am-simply-a-book-drunkard-books-have-the-same]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am simply a 'book drunkard.'  Books have the same irresistible temptation for me that liquor has for its devotee. I cannot withstand them." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80146-i-d-like-to-add-some-beauty-to-life-said-anne</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 18:11:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80146-i-d-like-to-add-some-beauty-to-life-said-anne]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd like to add some beauty to life,&quot; said Anne dreamily. &quot;I don't exactly want to make people KNOW more... though I know that IS the noblest ambition... but I'd love to make them have a pleasanter time because of me... to have some little joy or happy thought that would never have existed if I hadn't been born." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165078-may-you-walk-a-lighted-path-may-you-fight-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 17:24:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Marisha Pessl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165078-may-you-walk-a-lighted-path-may-you-fight-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May you walk a lighted path. May you fight for truth - your truth, not someone else's - and may you understand, above all things, that you are the most important concept, theory, and philosophy I have ever known." -- Marisha Pessl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292631-i-felt-like-a-jane-austen-heroine-all-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 16:30:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Julie Powell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292631-i-felt-like-a-jane-austen-heroine-all-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I felt like a Jane Austen heroine all of a sudden, confusedly looking on at all the people she loves, their myriad unpredictable couplings and uncouplings. There would be no marriages at the end of this Austen novel, though, no happy endings, no endings at all. Just jokes and friendships and romances and delicious declarations of independence." -- Julie Powell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/327352-don-t-be-afraid-it-won-t-be-perfect-the-only-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 20:20:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Stephen Sondheim Company]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/327352-don-t-be-afraid-it-won-t-be-perfect-the-only-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't be afraid it won't be perfect. The only thing to be afraid of, really, is that it won't be." -- Stephen Sondheim Company]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
