<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/523543-derek]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/523543-derek" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 18:20:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36419-what-we-call-man-s-power-over-nature-turns-out-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 18:20:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36419-what-we-call-man-s-power-over-nature-turns-out-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What we call Man's power over Nature turns out to be a power exercised by some men over other men with Nature as its instrument." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36421-some-people-in-order-to-discover-god-read-books-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 18:21:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by St. Augustine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36421-some-people-in-order-to-discover-god-read-books-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people, in order to discover God, read books. But there is a great book: the very appearance of created things. Look above you! Look below you! Read it. God, whom you want to discover, never wrote that book with ink. Instead, He set before your eyes the things that He had made. Can you ask for a louder voice than that?" -- St. Augustine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39131-our-liberty-depends-on-the-freedom-of-the-press-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 05:01:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39131-our-liberty-depends-on-the-freedom-of-the-press-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our liberty depends on the freedom of the press, and that cannot be limited without being lost." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39166-plans-are-one-thing-and-fate-another-when-they-coincide</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 08:45:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39166-plans-are-one-thing-and-fate-another-when-they-coincide]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Plans are one thing and fate another. When they coincide, success results. Yet success mustn't be considered the absolute. It is questionable, for that matter, whether success is an adequate resposne to life. Success can eliminate as many options as failure." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39167-take-now-the-clockworks-the-clockworks-being-genuine-and-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 08:50:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39167-take-now-the-clockworks-the-clockworks-being-genuine-and-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Take now the clockworks... The clockworks, being genuine and not much to look at, don't generate the drama of an Earth-tilt or a flying saucer, nor do they seem to offer any immediate panacea for humanity's fifty-seven varieties of heartburn. But suppose that you're one of those persons who feels trapped, to some degree, trapped matrimonially, occupationally, eductionally or geographically, or trapped in something larger than all those; trapped in a system, or what you might descrbie as an &quot;incresingly deadening technocracy&quot; or a &quot;theater of paranoia and desperation&quot; or something like that. Now, if you are one of those persons... wouldn't the very knowledge that there are clockworks ticking away behind the wallpaper of civilization, unbeknownst to leaders, organizers and managers (the President included), wouldn't that knowledge, suggesting as it does the possibility of unimaginable alternatives, wouldn't that knowledge be a bubble bath for your heart?" -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40728-this-sentence-is-made-of-lead-and-a-sentence-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2008 22:43:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40728-this-sentence-is-made-of-lead-and-a-sentence-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This sentence is made of lead (and a sentence of lead gives a reader an entirely different sensation from one made of magnesium). This sentence is made of yak wool. This sentence is made of sunlight and plums. This sentence is made of ice. This sentence is made from the blood of the poet. This sentence was made in Japan. This sentence glows in the dark. This sentence was born with a caul. This sentence has a crush on Norman Mailer. This sentence is a wino and doesn't care who knows it. Like many italic sentences, this one has Mafia connections. This sentence is a double Cancer with a Pisces rising. This sentence lost its mind searching for the perfect paragraph. This sentence refuses to be diagrammed. This sentence ran off with an adverb clause. This sentence is 100 percent organic: it will not retain a facsimile of freshness like those sentences of Homer, Shakespeare, Goethe et al., which are loaded with preservatives. This sentence leaks. This sentence doesn't look Jewish... This sentence has accepted Jesus Christ as its personal savior. This sentence once spit in a book reviewer's eye. This sentence can do the funky chicken. This sentence has seen too much and forgotten too little. This sentence is called &quot;Speedoo&quot; but its real name is Mr. Earl. This sentence may be pregnant. This sentence suffered a split infinitive - and survived. If this sentence has been a snake you'd have bitten it. This sentence went to jail with Clifford Irving. This sentence went to Woodstock. And this little sentence went wee wee wee all the way home." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40732-sounds-travel-through-space-long-after-their-wave-patterns-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2008 22:44:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40732-sounds-travel-through-space-long-after-their-wave-patterns-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sounds travel through space long after their wave patterns have ceased to be detectable by the human ear: some cut right through the ionosphere and barrel on out into the cosmic heartland, while others bounce around, eventually being absorbed into the vibratory fields of earthly barriers, but in neither case does the energy succumb; it goes on forever - which is why we, each of us, should take pains to make sweet notes." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40733-let-us-rather-gather-facts-all-the-facts-regardless-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2008 22:47:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40733-let-us-rather-gather-facts-all-the-facts-regardless-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let us, rather, gather facts, all the facts, regardless of aesthetic appeal or theoretical social  worth, and spread those facts before us not as the soothsayer spreads the innards of a turkey but as a newspaper spreads its columns. Let us be journalists, then. And like all good journalists, we shall present our facts in an order that will satisfy the famous five W's: wow, whoopee, wahoo, why-not and whew." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12483-all-good-books-are-alike-in-that-they-are-truer</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 07:43:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Ernest Hemingway ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12483-all-good-books-are-alike-in-that-they-are-truer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All good books are alike in that they are truer than if they had really happened and after you are finished reading one you will feel that all that happened to you and afterwards it all belongs to you: the good and the bad, the ecstasy, the remorse and sorrow, the people and the places and how the weather was. If you can get so that you can give that to people, then you are a writer." -- Ernest Hemingway ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8646-this-above-all-to-thine-own-self-be-true-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 11:12:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8646-this-above-all-to-thine-own-self-be-true-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This above all: to thine own self be true, 
And it must follow, as the night the day, 
Thou canst not then be false to any man." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2008 08:38:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fairy tales are more than true: not because they tell us that dragons exist, but because they tell us that dragons can be beaten." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43810-as-a-child-i-was-an-imaginary-playmate</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 15:11:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43810-as-a-child-i-was-an-imaginary-playmate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As a child, I was an imaginary playmate." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43811-you-ve-heard-of-people-calling-in-sick-you-may-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 15:13:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43811-you-ve-heard-of-people-calling-in-sick-you-may-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've heard of people calling in sick. You may have called in sick a few times yourself. But have you ever thought about calling in well?

It'd go like this: You'd get the boss on the line and say, &quot;Listen, I've been sick ever since I started working here, but today I'm well and I won't be in anymore.&quot; Call in well." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43812-despite-his-title-the-secretary-of-the-interior-was-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 15:15:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43812-despite-his-title-the-secretary-of-the-interior-was-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Despite his title, the Secretary of the Interior was a shallow man. He was given to surfaces, not depths; to cortex, not medulla; to the puff, not the cream. He didn't understand the interior of anything: not the interior of a tenor sax solo, a painting or a poem; not the interior of an atom, a planet, a spider or his wife's body; not the interior, least of all, of his own heart and head." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43813-the-enemy-of-the-black-is-not-the-white-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 15:20:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43813-the-enemy-of-the-black-is-not-the-white-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The enemy of the black is not the white. The enemy of capitalist is not communist, the enemy of homosexual is not heterosexual, the enemy of Jew is not Arab, the enemy of youth is not the old, the enemy of hip is not redneck, the enemy of Chicano is not gringo and the enemy of women is not men.

We all have the same enemy.

The enemy is the tyranny of the dull mind.

The enemy is every expert who practices technocratic manipulation, the enemy is every proponent of standardization and the enemy is every victim who is so dull and lazy and weak as to allow himself to be manipulated and standardized." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9402-if-you-want-a-picture-of-the-future-imagine-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2009 01:35:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9402-if-you-want-a-picture-of-the-future-imagine-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want a picture of the future, imagine a boot stamping on a human face—for ever." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 09:11:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44871-oh-god-are-there-so-many-of-them-in-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 05:12:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44871-oh-god-are-there-so-many-of-them-in-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh God, are there so many of them in our land! Students who can’t be happy until they’ve graduated, servicemen who can’t be happy until they are discharged, single folks who can’t be happy until they’ve found a mate, workers who can’t be happy until they’ve retired, adolescents who aren’t happy until they’re grown, ill people who aren’t happy until they’re well, failures who aren’t happy until they succeed, restless who can’t wait until they get out of town, and in most cases, vice versa, people waiting, waiting for the world to begin." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44872-to-the-extent-that-this-world-surrenders-its-richness-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 05:13:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44872-to-the-extent-that-this-world-surrenders-its-richness-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To the extent that this world surrenders its richness and diversity, it surrenders its poetry; to the extent that it relinquishes its capacity to surprise, it relinquishes its music; to the extent that it loses its ability to tolerate ridiculous and even dangerous exceptions, it loses its grace." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4737-cut-out-all-these-exclamation-points-an-exclamation-point-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 20:11:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Derek add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4737-cut-out-all-these-exclamation-points-an-exclamation-point-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cut out all these exclamation points. An exclamation point is like laughing at your own joke." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
