<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/52503-angela]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/52503-angela" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 23:53:53 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 23:53:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be patient toward all that is unsolved in your heart and try to love the questions themselves, like locked rooms and like books that are now written in a very foreign tongue. Do not now seek the answers, which cannot be given you because you would not be able to live them. And the point is, to live everything. Live the questions now. Perhaps you will then gradually, without noticing it, live along some distant day into the answer." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/288835-have-patience-with-everything-that-remains-unsolved-in-your-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 23:55:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/288835-have-patience-with-everything-that-remains-unsolved-in-your-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have patience with everything that remains unsolved in your heart. Try to love the questions themselves, like locked rooms and like books written in a foreign language. Do not now look for the answers. They cannot now be given to you because you could not live them. It is a question of experiencing everything. At present you need to live the question. Perhaps you will gradually, without even noticing it, find yourself experiencing the answer, some distant day." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/563483-i-beg-you-to-have-patience-with-everything-unresolved-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 23:58:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/563483-i-beg-you-to-have-patience-with-everything-unresolved-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I beg you, to have patience with everything unresolved in your heart and to try to love the questions themselves as if they were locked rooms or books written in a very foreign language. Don’t search for the answers, which could not be given to you now, because you would not be able to live them. And the point is to live everything. Live the questions now. Perhaps then, someday far in the future, you will gradually, without even noticing it, live your way into the answer." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353300-there-is-only-one-way-go-within-search-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 23:59:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353300-there-is-only-one-way-go-within-search-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is only one way: Go within. Search for the cause, find the impetus that bids you write. Put it to this test: Does it stretch out its roots in the deepest place of your heart? Can you avow that you would die if you were forbidden to write? Above all, in the most silent hour of your night, ask yourself this: Must I write? Dig deep into yourself for a true answer. And if it should ring its assent, if you can confidently meet this serious question with a simple, “I must,” then build your life upon it. It has become your necessity. Your life, in even the most mundane and least significant hour, must become a sign, a testimony to this urge." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432769-what-else-can-i-tell-you-it-seems-to-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:01:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Rilke,Letters to a Young Poet]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432769-what-else-can-i-tell-you-it-seems-to-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What else can I tell you? It seems to me that everything has its proper emphasis; and finally I want to add just one more bit of advice: to keep growing, silently and earnestly, through your whole development; you couldn't disturb it any more violently than by looking outside and waiting for outside answers to questions that only your innermost feeling, in your quietest hour, can perhaps answer." -- Rilke,Letters to a Young Poet]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432765-nothing-touches-a-work-of-art-so-little-as-words</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:01:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432765-nothing-touches-a-work-of-art-so-little-as-words]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing touches a work of art so little as words of criticism: they always result in more or less fortunate misunderstandings. Things aren't all so tangible and sayable as people would usually have us believe; most experiences are unsayable, they happen in a space that no word has ever entered, and more unsay able than all other things are works of art, those mysterious existences, whose life endures beside our own small, transitory life." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65611-i-am-an-excitable-person-who-only-understands-life-lyrically</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:26:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65611-i-am-an-excitable-person-who-only-understands-life-lyrically]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am an excitable person who only understands life lyrically, musically, in whom feelings are much stronger as reason. I am so thirsty for the marvelous that only the marvelous has power over me. Anything I can not transform into something marvelous, I let go. Reality doesn't impress me. I only believe in intoxication, in ecstasy, and when ordinary life shackles me, I escape, one way or another. No more walls." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45328-there-are-two-ways-to-reach-me-by-way-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:27:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45328-there-are-two-ways-to-reach-me-by-way-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two ways to reach me: by way of kisses or by way of the imagination. But there is a hierarchy: the kisses alone don't work." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119899-i-do-not-want-to-be-the-leader-i-refuse</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:28:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119899-i-do-not-want-to-be-the-leader-i-refuse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not want to be the leader. I refuse to be the leader. I want to live darkly and richly in my femaleness. I want a man lying over me, always over me. His will, his pleasure, his desire, his life, his work, his sexuality the touchstone, the command, my pivot. I don’t mind working, holding my ground intellectually, artistically; but as a woman, oh, God, as a woman I want to be dominated. I don’t mind being told to stand on my own feet, not to cling, be all that I am capable of doing, but I am going to be pursued, fucked, possessed by the will of a male at his time, his bidding." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18404-everything-with-me-is-either-worship-and-passion-or-pity</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:27:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18404-everything-with-me-is-either-worship-and-passion-or-pity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything with me is either worship and passion or pity and understanding. I hate rarely, though when I hate, I hate murderously. For example now, I hate the bank and everything connected with it. I also hate Dutch paintings, penis-sucking, parties, and cold rainy weather. But I am much more preoccupied with loving." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227714-what-can-i-do-with-my-happiness-how-can-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:28:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227714-what-can-i-do-with-my-happiness-how-can-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What can I do with my happiness?  How can I keep it, conceal it, bury it where I may never lose it?  I want to kneel as it falls over me like rain, gather it up with lace and silk, and press it over myself again." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27022-the-body-is-an-instrument-which-only-gives-off-music</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:32:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27022-the-body-is-an-instrument-which-only-gives-off-music]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The body is an instrument which only gives off music when it is used as a body. Always an orchestra, and just as music traverses walls, so sensuality traverses the body and reaches up to ecstasy." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194688-i-m-awaiting-a-lover-i-have-to-be-rent-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:33:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194688-i-m-awaiting-a-lover-i-have-to-be-rent-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm awaiting a lover. I have to be rent and pulled apart and live according to the demons and the imagination in me. I'm restless. Things are calling me away. My hair is being pulled by the stars again." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242956-i-had-a-feeling-that-pandora-s-box-contained-the-mysteries</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:34:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242956-i-had-a-feeling-that-pandora-s-box-contained-the-mysteries]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had a feeling that Pandora's box contained the mysteries of woman's sensuality, so different from a man's and for which man's language was so inadequate. The language of sex had yet to be invented. The language of the senses was yet to be explored." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382396-i-want-to-hear-raucous-music-to-see-faces-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:35:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382396-i-want-to-hear-raucous-music-to-see-faces-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to hear raucous music, to see faces, to brush against bodies, to drink fiery Benedictine. Beautiful women and handsome men arouse fierce desires in me. I want to dance. I want drugs. I want to know perverse people, to be intimate with them. I never look at naive faces. I want to bite into life, and to be torn by it." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/463732-you-do-not-know-what-you-are-missing-by-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:37:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/463732-you-do-not-know-what-you-are-missing-by-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You do not know what you are missing by your microscopic examination of sexual activity to the exclusion of aspects which are fuel that ignites it. Intellectual, imaginative, romantic, emotional. This is what gives sex its surprising textures, its subtle transformations, its aphrodisiac elements. You are shrinking your world of sensations. You are withering it, starving it, draining its blood." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/435331-the-source-of-sexual-power-is-curiosity-passion-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:37:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/435331-the-source-of-sexual-power-is-curiosity-passion-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The source of sexual power is curiosity, passion. You are watching its little flame die of asphyxiation." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/611974-she-had-lost-herself-somewhere-along-the-frontier-between-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:41:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/611974-she-had-lost-herself-somewhere-along-the-frontier-between-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had lost herself somewhere along the frontier between her inventions, her stories, her fantasies and her true self. The boundaries had become effaced, the tracks lost, she had walked into pure chaos, and not a chaos which carried her like the galloping of romantic riders in operas and legends, but which suddenly revealed the stage props: a papier-mâché horse." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/603298-i-take-pleasure-in-my-transformations-i-look-quiet-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:42:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/603298-i-take-pleasure-in-my-transformations-i-look-quiet-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I take pleasure in my transformations. I look quiet and consistent, but few know how many women there are in me." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/609030-pain-is-something-to-master-not-to-wallow-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:43:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/609030-pain-is-something-to-master-not-to-wallow-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pain is something to master, not to wallow in." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/585201-in-the-world-of-the-dreamer-there-was-solitude-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:46:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/585201-in-the-world-of-the-dreamer-there-was-solitude-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the world of the dreamer there was solitude: all the exaltations and joys came in the moment of preparation for living. They took place in solitude. But with action came anxiety, and the sense of insuperable effort made to match the dream, and with it came weariness, discouragement, and the flight into solitude again. And then in solitude, in the opium den of remembrance, the possibility of pleasure again. What was she seeking to salvage from the daily current of living, what sudden revulsions drove her back into the solitary cell of the dream?" -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
