<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/52528-amanda-norwood]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/52528-amanda-norwood" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 16:36:24 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200140-i-am-the-middle-sister-the-one-in-between-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 16:36:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200140-i-am-the-middle-sister-the-one-in-between-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the middle sister. The one in between. Not oldest, not youngest, not boldest, not nicest. I am the shade of gray, the glass half empty or full, depending on your view. In my life, there has been little that I have done first or better than the one preceding or following me. Of all of us, though, I am the only one who has been broken." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241462-there-are-no-faster-or-firmer-friendships-than-those-formed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2012 10:47:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Irving Stone]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241462-there-are-no-faster-or-firmer-friendships-than-those-formed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are no faster or firmer friendships than those formed between people who love the same books." -- Irving Stone]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204145-books-cats-life-is-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 05:29:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Edward Gorey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204145-books-cats-life-is-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books, Cats, Life is Good." -- Edward Gorey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111013-the-arc-of-the-moral-universe-is-long-but-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 04:00:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111013-the-arc-of-the-moral-universe-is-long-but-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The arc of the moral universe is long, but it bends towards justice." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100888-because-here-s-something-else-that-s-weird-but-true-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 12:31:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by David Foster Wallace  ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100888-because-here-s-something-else-that-s-weird-but-true-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because here's something else that's weird but true: in the day-to day trenches of adult life, there is actually no such thing as atheism. There is no such thing as not worshipping. Everybody worships. The only choice we get is what to worship. And the compelling reason for maybe choosing some sort of god or spiritual-type thing to worship -- be it JC or Allah, be it YHWH or the Wiccan Mother Goddess, or the Four Noble Truths, or some inviolable set of ethical principles -- is that pretty much anything else you worship will eat you alive. If you worship money and things, if they are where you tap real meaning in life, then you will never have enough, never feel you have enough. It's the truth. Worship your body and beauty and sexual allure and you will always feel ugly. And when time and age start showing, you will die a million deaths before they finally grieve you. On one level, we all know this stuff already. It's been codified as myths, proverbs, clichés, epigrams, parables; the skeleton of every great story. The whole trick is keeping the truth up front in daily consciousness." -- David Foster Wallace  ]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
