<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/526331-richard]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/526331-richard" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2009 15:42:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159709-not-writing-is-a-good-deal-worse-than-writing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2009 15:42:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159709-not-writing-is-a-good-deal-worse-than-writing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not-writing is a good deal worse than writing." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79366-fiction-is-about-everything-human-and-we-are-made-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 19:30:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79366-fiction-is-about-everything-human-and-we-are-made-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fiction is about everything human and we are made out of dust, and if you scorn getting yourself dusty, then you shouldn't try to write fiction. It's not a grand enough job for you." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207062-six-principles-that-make-for-a-good-story-1-absence</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 06:31:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Anton Chekhov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207062-six-principles-that-make-for-a-good-story-1-absence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Six principles that make for a good story:] 1. Absence of lengthy verbiage of a political-social-economic nature; 2. total objectivity; 3. truthful descriptions of persons and objects; 4. extreme brevity; 5. audacity and originality: flee the stereotype; 6. compassion." -- Anton Chekhov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449248-this-is-no-occupation-for-an-adult-who-can-look</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 06:31:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Franz Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449248-this-is-no-occupation-for-an-adult-who-can-look]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is no occupation for an adult who can look other adults in the eye, carry his own weight, and count himself one of them." -- Franz Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449960-just-as-the-creative-artist-is-not-allowed-to-choose</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 06:14:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449960-just-as-the-creative-artist-is-not-allowed-to-choose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just as the creative artist is not allowed to choose, neither is he permitted to turn his back on anything: a single refusal, and he is cast out of the state of grace and becomes sinful all the way through." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449962-for-the-past-thirty-years-or-so-much-american-poetry</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 06:36:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Stephen Dobyns]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449962-for-the-past-thirty-years-or-so-much-american-poetry]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the past thirty years or so, much American poetry has been marked by an earnestness that rejects the comic.  This has nothing to do with seriousness.  The comic can be very serious.  The trouble with the earnest is that it seeks to be commended.  It seeks to be praised for its intention more than for what it is saying." -- Stephen Dobyns]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207061-anyone-who-says-the-artist-s-field-is-all-answers-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 06:31:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Anton Chekhov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207061-anyone-who-says-the-artist-s-field-is-all-answers-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who says the artist's field is all answers and no questions has never done any writing or had any dealings with imagery...You are confusing two concepts: answering the questions and formulating them correctly. Only the latter is required of an author." -- Anton Chekhov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491281-never-before-had-she-seen-such-writers-they-were-impossibly</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 09:11:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491281-never-before-had-she-seen-such-writers-they-were-impossibly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never before had she seen such writers.  They were impossibly vain, but quite openly so, as if thereby fulfilling a duty.  Some (though by no means all) even came drunk, but it was as if they perceived som special, just-yesterday-discovered beauty in it.  They were all proud of something to the point of strangeness." -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150203-i-write-to-discover-what-i-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 06:31:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150203-i-write-to-discover-what-i-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I write to discover what I know." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269944-happy-the-writer-who-passing-by-characters-that-are-boring</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 20:08:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Nikolai Gogol]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269944-happy-the-writer-who-passing-by-characters-that-are-boring]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happy the writer who, passing by characters that are boring, disgusting, shocking in their mournful reality, approaches characters that manifest the lofty dignity of man, who from the great pool of daily whirling images has chosen only the rare exceptions, who has never once betrayed the exalted turning of his lyre, nor descended from his height to his poor, insignificant brethren, and, without touching the ground, has given the whole of himself to his elevated images so far removed from it.  Twice enviable is his beautiful lot: he is among them as in his own family; and meanwhile his fame spreads loud and far.  With entrancing smoke he has clouded people's eyes; he has flattered them wondrously, concealing what is mournful in life, showing them a beautiful man.  Everything rushes after him, applauding, and flies off following his triumphal chariot.  Great world poet they name him, soaring high above all other geniuses in the world, as the eagle soars above the other high fliers.  At the mere mention of his name, young ardent hearts are filled with trembling, responsive tears shine in all eyes...No one equals him in power--he is God!  But such is not the lot, and other is the destiny of the writer who has dared to call forth all that is before our eyes every moment and which our indifferent eyes do not see--all the stupendous mire of trivia in which our life in entangled, the whole depth of cold, fragmented, everyday characters that swarm over our often bitter and boring earthly path, and with the firm strength of his implacable chisel dares to present them roundly and vividly before the eyes of all people!  It is not for him to win people's applause, not for him to behold the grateful tears and unanimous rapture of the souls he has stirred; no sixteen-year-old girl will come flying to meet him with her head in a whirl and heroic enthusiasm; it is not for him to forget himself in the sweet enchantment of sounds he himself has evoked; it is not for him, finally, to escape contemporary judgment, hypocritically callous contemporary judgment, which will call insignificant and mean the creations he has fostered, will allot him a contemptible corner in the ranks of writers who insult mankind, will ascribe to him the quality of the heroes he has portrayed, will deny him heart, and soul, and the divine flame of talent.  For contemporary judgment does not recognize that equally wondrous are the glasses that observe the sun and those that look at the movement of inconspicuous insect; for contemporary judgment does not recognize that much depth of soul is needed to light up the picture drawn from contemptible life and elevate it into a pearl of creation; for contemporary judgment does not recognize that lofty ecstatic laughter is worthy to stand beside the lofty lyrical impulse, and that a whole abyss separates it from the antics of the street-fair clown!  This contemporary judgment does not recognize; and will turn it all into a reproach and abuse of the unrecognized writer; with no sharing, no response, no sympathy, like a familyless wayfarer, he will be left alone in the middle of the road.  Grim is his path, and bitterly he will feel his solitude." -- Nikolai Gogol]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223894-where-all-is-known-no-narrative-is-possible</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2010 18:22:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223894-where-all-is-known-no-narrative-is-possible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["where all is known, no narrative is possible." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8587-poetry-the-best-words-in-the-best-order</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2010 18:22:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Samuel Taylor Coleridge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8587-poetry-the-best-words-in-the-best-order]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Poetry: the best words in the best order." -- Samuel Taylor Coleridge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136959-epitaph-now-i-m-not-the-brightest-knife-in-the-drawer</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 20:22:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Franz Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136959-epitaph-now-i-m-not-the-brightest-knife-in-the-drawer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["EPITAPH

Now I'm not the brightest
knife in the drawer, but
I know a couple things
about this life: poverty
silence, impermanence
discipline and mystery

The world is not illusory, we are

From crimson thread to toe tag

If you are not disturbed
there is something seriously wrong with you, I'm sorry

And I know who I am
I'll be a voice
coming from nowhere,

inside--

be glad for me.
" -- Franz Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406023-the-worst-of-men-generally-have-the-words-rogue-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 07:35:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Henry Fielding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406023-the-worst-of-men-generally-have-the-words-rogue-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worst of men generally have the words rogue and villain most in their mouths, as the lowest of all wretches are the aptest to cry out low in the pit." -- Henry Fielding]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85753-stories-are-consoling-fiction-is-one-of-the-consolation-prizes</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2010 18:41:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85753-stories-are-consoling-fiction-is-one-of-the-consolation-prizes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories are consoling, fiction is one of the consolation prizes for having lived in the world." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187396-yet-it-is-the-narrative-that-is-the-life-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2009 15:47:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187396-yet-it-is-the-narrative-that-is-the-life-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yet it is the narrative that is the life of the dream while the events themselves are often interchangeable.  The events of the waking world on the other hand are forced upon us and the narrative is the unguessed axis along which they must be strung." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144152-music-is-the-highest-art-no-question-but-literature-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2009 13:31:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by James Richardson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144152-music-is-the-highest-art-no-question-but-literature-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Music is the highest art, no question.  But literature is a friendlier one.  It depends on us more, bores us more quickly, can't go on if we don't, can't stop saying what it means, can't stop giving us something to forgive." -- James Richardson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269937-like-all-of-us-sinners-general-betrishchev-was-endowed-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 20:23:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Nikolai Gogol]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269937-like-all-of-us-sinners-general-betrishchev-was-endowed-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like all of us sinners, General Betrishchev was endowed with many virtues and many defects.  Both the one and the other were scattered through him in a sort of picturesque disorder.  Self-sacrifice, magnanimity in decisive moments, courage, intelligence--and with all that, a generous mixture of self-love, ambition, vanity, petty personal ticklishness, and a good many of those things which a man simply cannot do without." -- Nikolai Gogol]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143548-only-half-of-writing-is-saying-what-you-mean-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2009 13:33:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by James Richardson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143548-only-half-of-writing-is-saying-what-you-mean-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only half of writing is saying what you mean. The other half is preventing people from reading what they expected you to mean. " -- James Richardson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159712-your-criticism-sounds-to-me-as-if-you-have-read</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 21:45:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159712-your-criticism-sounds-to-me-as-if-you-have-read]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your criticism sounds to me as if you have read too many critical books and are too smart in an artificial, destructive, and very limited way." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176864-poem-in-other-words-may-or-may-not-result-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 09:13:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Franz Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176864-poem-in-other-words-may-or-may-not-result-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Poem in other words may or may not result from inspiration but must (in reader and author alike) produce it--" -- Franz Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119397-an-old-man-is-never-at-home-save-in-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 09:18:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119397-an-old-man-is-never-at-home-save-in-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An old man is never at home save in his own garments: his own old thinking and beliefs; old hands and feet, elbow, knee, shoulder which he knows will fit." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178340-elizabeth-lifted-her-skirt-disregarding-modesty-and-delivered-a-swift</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 09:18:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Seth Grahame-Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178340-elizabeth-lifted-her-skirt-disregarding-modesty-and-delivered-a-swift]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Elizabeth lifted her skirt, disregarding modesty, and delivered a swift kick to the creature's head." -- Seth Grahame-Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7558-art-never-responds-to-the-wish-to-make-it-democratic</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 07:11:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7558-art-never-responds-to-the-wish-to-make-it-democratic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Art never responds to the wish to make it democratic; it is not for everybody; it is only for those who are willing to undergo the effort needed to understand it." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79367-people-without-hope-not-only-don-t-write-novels-but-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 07:12:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79367-people-without-hope-not-only-don-t-write-novels-but-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People without hope not only don't write novels, but what is more to the point, they don't read them." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234963-chaos-comes-before-all-principles-of-order-entropy-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 06:30:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Hakim Bey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234963-chaos-comes-before-all-principles-of-order-entropy-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chaos comes before all principles of order &amp; entropy, it's neither a god nor a maggot, its idiotic desires encompass &amp; define every possible choreography, all meaningless aethers &amp; phlogistons: its masks are crystallizations of its own facelessness, like clouds. " -- Hakim Bey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82708-i-don-t-believe-it-s-selfish-to-eat-defenseless-shellfish</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 06:30:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by NOFX, &quot;Clams Have Feelings Too (Actually They Don't)&quot;]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82708-i-don-t-believe-it-s-selfish-to-eat-defenseless-shellfish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't believe it's selfish
To eat defenseless shellfish." -- NOFX, &quot;Clams Have Feelings Too (Actually They Don't)&quot;]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269935-why-then-make-a-show-of-the-poverty-of-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 21:27:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Nikolai Gogol]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269935-why-then-make-a-show-of-the-poverty-of-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why, then, make a show of the poverty of our life and our sad imperfection, unearthing people from the backwoods, from remote corners of the state?  But what if this is in the writer's nature, and his own imperfection grieves him so, and the makeup of his talent is such, that he can only portray the poverty of our life, unearthing people from the backwoods, from the remote corners of the state!  So here we are again in the backwoods, again we have come out in some corner!" -- Nikolai Gogol]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/457395-all-my-friends-and-relatives-have-always-taken-a-condescending</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2011 17:01:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by Anton Chekhov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/457395-all-my-friends-and-relatives-have-always-taken-a-condescending]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All my friends and relatives have always taken a condescending tone to my writing, and never ceased urging me in a friendly way not to give up real work for the sake of scribbling." -- Anton Chekhov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465633-the-history-of-mankind-is-the-history-of-our-misunderstandings</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 19:30:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Richard add a quote by José Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465633-the-history-of-mankind-is-the-history-of-our-misunderstandings]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The history of mankind is the history of our misunderstandings with god, for he doesn't understand us, and we don't understand him." -- José Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
