<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/527426-sage]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/527426-sage" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 06:38:53 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10828-i-said-i-need-to-hear-something-that-s-going-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 06:38:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10828-i-said-i-need-to-hear-something-that-s-going-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I said, “I need to hear something that’s going to save my life.”

Re: Selecting songs from a jukebox.

" -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4999-there-were-so-many-pittsburgh-poets-in-my-hallway-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 06:39:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4999-there-were-so-many-pittsburgh-poets-in-my-hallway-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There were so many Pittsburgh poets in my hallway that if, at that instant, a meteorite had come smashing through my roof, there would never have been another stanza written about rusting fathers and impotent steelworkers and the Bessemer convertor of love." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6766-i-can-listen-no-longer-in-silence-i-must-speak</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 06:45:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6766-i-can-listen-no-longer-in-silence-i-must-speak]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can listen no longer in silence.  I must speak to you by such means as are within my reach.  You pierce my soul.  I am half agony, half hope.  Tell me not that I am too late, that such precious feelings are gone for ever.  I offer myself to you again with a heart even more your own than when you almost broke it, eight years and a half ago.  Dare not say that man forgets sooner than  woman, that his love has an earlier death.  I have loved none but you. Unjust I may have been, weak and resentful I have been, but never inconstant.  You alone have brought me to Bath. For you alone, I think and plan.  Have you not seen this? Can you fail to have understood my wishes?  I had not waited even these ten days, could I have read your feelings, as I think you must have penetrated mine.  I can hardly write.  I am every instant hearing something which overpowers me.  You sink your voice, but I can distinguish the tones of that voice when they would be lost on others. Too good, too excellent creature!  You do us justice, indeed. You do believe that there is true attachment and constancy among men. Believe it to be most fervent, most undeviating, in F. W.

I must go, uncertain of my fate; but I shall return hither, or follow your party, as soon as possible.  A word, a look, will be enough to decide whether I enter your father's house this evening or never." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16999-run-mad-as-often-as-you-choose-but-do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 06:45:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16999-run-mad-as-often-as-you-choose-but-do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Run mad as often as you choose, but do not faint!" -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59654-mr-elliot-was-rational-discreet-polished-but-he-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 06:46:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59654-mr-elliot-was-rational-discreet-polished-but-he-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mr. Elliot was rational, discreet, polished, – but he was not open. There was never any burst of feeling, any warmth of indignation or delight, at the evil or good of others. This, to Anne, was a decided imperfection. Her early impressions were incurable. She prized the frank, the open-hearted, the eager character beyond all others. Warmth and enthusiasm did captivate her still. She felt that she could so much more depend upon the sincerity of those who sometimes looked or said a careless or a hasty thing, than of those whose presence of mind never varied, whose tongue never slipped." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2086-what-is-hardest-to-accept-about-the-passage-of-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 06:48:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2086-what-is-hardest-to-accept-about-the-passage-of-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is hardest to accept about the passage of time is that the people who once mattered the most to us wind up in parentheses." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15663-for-long-the-two-enemies-looked-at-one-another-hook</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 06:53:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15663-for-long-the-two-enemies-looked-at-one-another-hook]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For long the two enemies looked at one another, Hook shuddering slightly, and Peter with the strange smile upon his face.
&quot;So, Pan,&quot; said Hook at last, &quot;this is all your doing.&quot;
&quot;Ay, James Hook,&quot; came the stern answer, &quot;it is all my doing.&quot;
&quot;Proud and insolent youth,&quot; said Hook, &quot;prepare to meet thy doom.&quot;
&quot;Dark and sinister man,“For long the two enemies looked at one another, Hook shuddering slightly, and Peter with the strange smile upon his face.
&quot;Dark and sinister man,&quot; Peter answered, &quot;have at thee." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131448-mr-mancini-had-a-singular-talent-for-making-me-uncomfortable</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:24:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131448-mr-mancini-had-a-singular-talent-for-making-me-uncomfortable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mr. Mancini had a singular talent for making me uncomfortable.  He forced me to consider things I’d rather not think about – the sex of my guitar, for instance.  If I honestly wanted to put my hands on a woman, would that automatically mean I could play?  Gretchen’s teacher never told her to think of her piano as a boy.  Neither did Lisa’s flute teacher, though in that case the analogy was obvious.  On the off chance that sexual desire was all it took, I steered clear of Lisa’s instrument, fearing that I might be labeled a prodigy." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131449-unlike-my-father-who-blindly-churned-out-one-canvas-after</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:25:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131449-unlike-my-father-who-blindly-churned-out-one-canvas-after]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Unlike my father, who blindly churned out one canvas after another, I had real ideas about the artistic life.  Seated at my desk, my beret as tight as an acorn’s cap, I projected myself into the world represented in the art books I’d borrowed from the public library.  Leafing past the paintings, I would admire the photographs of the artists seated in their garrets, dressed in tattered smocks and frowning in the direction of their beefy nude models.  To spend your days in the company of naked men – that was the life for me.  ‘Turn a bit to the left, Jean-Claude.  I long to capture the playful quality of your buttocks." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131452-frustrated-with-drawing-i-switched-to-the-printmaking-department-where</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:26:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131452-frustrated-with-drawing-i-switched-to-the-printmaking-department-where]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Frustrated with drawing, I switched to the printmaking department, where I overturned great buckets of ink.  After trying my hand at sculpture, I attempted pottery.  During class critiques the teacher would lift my latest project from the table and I’d watch her arm muscles strain and tighten against the weight.  With their thick, clumsy bases, my mugs weighed in at close to five pounds each.  The color was muddy and the lips rough and uninviting.  I gave my mother a matching set for Christmas, and she accepted them as graciously as possible, announcing that they would make the perfect pet bowls.  The mugs were set on the kitchen floor and remained there until the cat chipped a tooth and went on a hunger strike." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131453-i-had-paid-for-my-folly-and-as-a-reward</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:27:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131453-i-had-paid-for-my-folly-and-as-a-reward]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had paid for my folly and, as a reward, was invited to take part in the nest builder’s performance piece.  The script was great.

‘When I bleat here, do you want me to just bleat or to really let go and “bleat, bleat”?’ I asked.  ‘I feel like “bleat, bleating,” but if Mother/Destroyer is going to be crawling through the birth canal of concertina wire, I don’t want to steal focus, you know what I mean?" -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131455-when-forced-to-leave-my-house-for-an-extended-period</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:28:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131455-when-forced-to-leave-my-house-for-an-extended-period]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When forced to leave my house for an extended period of time, I take my typewriter with me, and together we endure the wretchedness of passing through the X-ray scanner.  The laptops roll merrily down the belt, while I’m instructed to stand aside and open my bag.  To me it seems like a normal enough thing to be carrying, but the typewriter’s declining popularity arouses suspicion and I wind up eliciting the sort of reaction one might expect when traveling with a cannon.

It’s a typewriter,’ I say.  ‘You use it to write angry letters to airport security." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131457-in-order-to-get-the-things-i-want-it-helps</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:29:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131457-in-order-to-get-the-things-i-want-it-helps]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In order to get the things I want, it helps me to pretend I’m a figure in a daytime drama, a schemer.  Soap opera characters make emphatic pronouncements.  They ball up their fists and state their goals out loud.  ‘I will destroy Buchanan Enterprises,’ they say.  ‘Phoebe Wallingford will pay for what she’s done to our family.’  Walking home with the back half of the twelve-foot ladder, I turned to look in the direction of Hugh’s loft.  ‘You will be mine,’ I commanded." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131460-for-the-first-twenty-years-of-my-life-i-rocked</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:30:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131460-for-the-first-twenty-years-of-my-life-i-rocked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the first twenty years of my life, I rocked myself to sleep.  It was a harmless enough hobby, but eventually, I had to give it up.  Throughout the next twenty-two years I lay still and discovered that after a few minutes I could drop off with no problem.  Follow seven beers with a couple of scotches and a thimble of good marijuana, and it’s funny how sleep just sort of comes on its own.  Often I never even made it to the bed.  I’d squat down to pet the cat and wake up on the floor eight hours later, having lost a perfectly good excuse to change my clothes.  I’m now told that this is not called “going to sleep” but rather “passing out,” a phrase that carries a distinct hint of judgment." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131461-during-the-few-months-troy-had-been-back-home-he-d</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:30:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Anthony Swofford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131461-during-the-few-months-troy-had-been-back-home-he-d]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["During the few months Troy had been back home, he’d told his friends about us, and so we quickly eased into the conversation as though we’d all known each other for many years.  They embarrassed us with great thanks for having served overseas.  They recounted combat events Troy had told them, and we realized by the context of their stories that Troy had made us heroes for his friends because we’d been heroes to him.  At this point I was the saddest I’d yet been over Troy’s passing, because the true friend from war is the friend who obliterates his own story by telling the stories of others." -- Anthony Swofford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131463-i-have-gone-to-war-and-now-i-can-issue</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:31:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Anthony Swofford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131463-i-have-gone-to-war-and-now-i-can-issue]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have gone to war and now I can issue my complaint.  I can sit on my porch and complain all day.  And you must listen.  Some of you will say to me: You signed the contract, you crying bitch, and you fought in a war because of your signature, no one held a gun to your head.  This is true, but because I signed the contract and fulfilled my obligation to fight one of America’s wars, I am entitled to speak, to say, I belong to a fucked situation." -- Anthony Swofford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131464-she-perched-on-her-windowsill-gazing-at-the-lurid-sun</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:32:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Ann Brashares]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131464-she-perched-on-her-windowsill-gazing-at-the-lurid-sun]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She perched on her windowsill, gazing at the lurid sun soaking into the Caldera, trying to appreciate it even though she couldn’t have it.  Why did she always feel she had to do something in the face of beauty?" -- Ann Brashares]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131465-barbara-appraised-her-with-critical-eyes-oh-my-well-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:32:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Ann Brashares]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131465-barbara-appraised-her-with-critical-eyes-oh-my-well-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Barbara appraised her with critical eyes.  ‘Oh my.  Well, this is going to need some work.’  She went right to Carmen’s hips and pulled the unfinished seams open.  ‘Yes, we’ll have to take this way out.  I’m not sure I have enough fabric.  I’ll check when I get back to my office.’
You are a horrible witch, Carmen thought.
She knew she looked absolutely awful in the dress.  She was part Bourbon Street whore and part Latina first-communion spectacle." -- Ann Brashares]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131466-dad-please-accept-this-money-to-fix-the-broken-window</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:33:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Ann Brashares]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131466-dad-please-accept-this-money-to-fix-the-broken-window]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dad,
Please accept this money to fix the broken window.  I’m sure it’s already fixed, considering Lydia’s house pride and her phobia about unconditioned air, but

Dear Al,
I can’t begin to explain my actions at Lydia’s – I mean yours and Lydia’s house.  When I get to Charleston, I never imagined that you would have

Dear Dad and Lydia,
I apologize to both of you for my irrational behavior.  I know it’s all my fault, but if you would have listened to ONE THING I had to say, I might not have

Dear Dad’s new family,
I hope you’ll all be very happy being blond together.  May people speak only in inside voices for the rest of your lives.
P.S.  Lydia, you wedding dress makes your arms look fat." -- Ann Brashares]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131467-it-was-her-last-breakfast-with-bapi-her-last-morning</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:36:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Ann Brashares]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131467-it-was-her-last-breakfast-with-bapi-her-last-morning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was her last breakfast with Bapi, her last morning in Greece.  In her frenetic bliss that kept her up till dawn, she’d scripted a whole conversation in Greek for her and Bapi to have as their grand finale of the summer.  Now she looked at him contentedly munching on his Rice Krispies, waiting for the right juncture for launchtime.

He looked up at her briefly and smiled, and she realized something important.  This was how they both liked it.  Though most people felt bonded by conversation, Lena and Bapi were two of a kind who didn’t.  They bonded by the routine of just eating cereal together.

She promptly forgot her script and went back to her cereal.

At one point, when she was down to just milk, Bapi reached over and put his hand on hers.  ‘You’re my girl,’ he said.

And Lena knew she was." -- Ann Brashares]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131468-tibby-sat-on-the-outside-of-a-group-of-kids</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:37:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Ann Brashares]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131468-tibby-sat-on-the-outside-of-a-group-of-kids]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tibby sat on the outside of a group of kids in the film program.  There was a lot of dark clothing and heavy footwear, and quite a few piercings glinting in sunlight.  They had invited her to sit with them while they all finished up their lunches before film seminar.  Tibby knew that they had invited her largely because she had a ring in her nose.  This bugged her almost as much as when people excluded her because she had a ring in her nose." -- Ann Brashares]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131469-different-people-were-good-at-different-things-lena-mused-lena</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:38:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Ann Brashares]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131469-different-people-were-good-at-different-things-lena-mused-lena]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Different people were good at different things, Lena mused.  Lena was good at writing thank-you notes, for instance, and Effie was good at being happy." -- Ann Brashares]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131470-a-kind-of-joyous-hysteria-moved-into-the-room-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:38:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Annie Proulx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131470-a-kind-of-joyous-hysteria-moved-into-the-room-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A kind of joyous hysteria moved into the room, everything flying before the wind, vehicles outside getting dented to hell, the crowd sweaty and the smells of aftershave, manure, clothes dried on the line, your money’s worth of perfume, smoke, booze; the music subdued by the shout and babble through the bass hammer could be felt through the soles of the feet, shooting up the channels of legs to the body fork, center of everything.  It is the kind of Saturday night that torches your life for a few hours, makes it seem like something is happening." -- Annie Proulx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131471-again-the-ranch-is-on-the-market-and-they-ve-shipped</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:39:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Annie Proulx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131471-again-the-ranch-is-on-the-market-and-they-ve-shipped]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Again the ranch is on the market and they’ve shipped out the last of the horses, paid everybody off the day before, the owner saying, ‘Give them to the real estate shark, I’m out a here,” dropping the keys in Ennis’s hand.  He might have to stay with his married daughter until he picks up another job, yet he is suffused with a sense of pleasure because Jack Twist was in his dream." -- Annie Proulx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131472-late-in-the-afternoon-thunder-growling-that-same-old-green</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:40:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Annie Proulx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131472-late-in-the-afternoon-thunder-growling-that-same-old-green]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Late in the afternoon, thunder growling, that same old green pickup rolled in and he saw Jack get out of the truck, beat up Resistol tilted back.  A hot jolt scalded Ennis and he was out on the landing pulling the door closed behind him.  Jack took the stairs two and two.  They seized each other by the shoulders, hugged mightily, squeezing the breath out of each other, saying, son of a bitch, son of a bitch, then, and easily as the right key turns the lock tumblers, their mouths came together, and hard, Jack’s big teeth bringing blood, his hat falling to the floor, stubble rasping, wet saliva welling, and the door opening and Alma looking out for a few seconds at Ennis’s straining shoulders and shutting the door again and still they clinched, pressing chest and groin and thigh and leg together, treading on each other’s toes until they pulled apart to breathe and Ennis, not big on endearments, said what he said to his horses and his daughters, little darlin." -- Annie Proulx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131473-however-displayed-right-alongside-all-the-confederate-flag-paraphernalia-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:41:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Sarah Vowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131473-however-displayed-right-alongside-all-the-confederate-flag-paraphernalia-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["However, displayed right alongside all the Confederate flag paraphernalia is a bunch of American flag merch – American flag place mats, patriotic “body crystals,” flag stickers you attach to your skin.  Personally, I’m small-minded and literal enough that I see the two symbols as contradictory, especially in a time of war.  But I fear that the consumer who buys a Confederate flag coffee cup, which she will then put on her American flag place mat, is the sort of sophisticated thinker who is open-minded enough that she is capable of hating blacks and Arabs at the same time." -- Sarah Vowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131475-until-that-moment-i-hadn-t-realized-that-i-embarked-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:42:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Sarah Vowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131475-until-that-moment-i-hadn-t-realized-that-i-embarked-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until that moment, I hadn’t realized that I embarked on the project of touring historic sites and monuments having to do with the assassinations of Lincoln, Garfield, and McKinley right around the time my country iffily went off to war, which is to say right around the time my resentment of the current president cranked up into contempt.  Not that I want the current president killed.  Like that director, I will, for the record (and for the FBI agent assigned to read this and make sure I mean no harm – hello there), clearly state that while I am obsessed with death, I am against it." -- Sarah Vowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131476-with-a-century-and-change-between-the-1880-convention-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:43:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Sarah Vowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131476-with-a-century-and-change-between-the-1880-convention-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With a century and change between the 1880 convention and now, I’ll admit I rolled my eyes at the ideological hairsplitting, wondering how a group of people who more or less agreed with one another about most issues could summon forth such stark animosity.  Thankfully, we Americans have evolved, our hearts made larger, our minds more open, welcoming the negligible differences among our fellows with compassion and respect.  As a Democrat who voted for Al Gore in the 2000 presidential election, an election suspiciously tipped to tragic Republican victory because of a handful of contested ballots in the state of Florida, I, for one, would never dream of complaining about the votes siphoned in that state by my fellow liberal Ralph Nader, who convinced citizens whose hopes for the country differ little from my own to vote for him, even though had those votes gone to Gore, perhaps those citizens might have spent their free time in the years to come more pleasurably pursuing leisure activities, such as researching the sacrifice of Family Garfield, instead of attending rallies and protests against wars they find objectionable, not to mention the money saved on aspirin alone considering they’ll have to pop a couple every time they read the newspaper, wondering if the tap water with which they wash down the pills is safe enough to drink considering the corporate polluter lobbyists now employed at the EPA." -- Sarah Vowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131479-it-goes-without-saying-that-in-order-for-me-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:44:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Sarah Vowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131479-it-goes-without-saying-that-in-order-for-me-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It goes without saying that in order for me to buy a teapot at the Oneida, Ltd., outlet store at the Sherrill Shopping Plaza, the second coming of Jesus Christ had to have taken place in the year 70 A.D.  To the Oneida Community, 70 A.D., the year the temple in Jerusalem was destroyed, marks the beginning of the New Jerusalem.  Which means we’ve all been living in heaven on earth for nearly two thousand years.  Everyone knows there is no marriage in heaven (though one suspects there’s no shortage of it in hell).  So, the Oneidans said, we’re here in heaven, already saved and perfect in the eyes of God, so let’s move upstate and sleep around.  (I’m paraphrasing.)" -- Sarah Vowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131480-the-subject-of-peter-gallagher-s-eyebrows-i-realize-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 15:44:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sage add a quote by Sarah Vowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131480-the-subject-of-peter-gallagher-s-eyebrows-i-realize-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["(The subject of Peter Gallagher’s eyebrows, I realize, is a digression away from the Oneida Community, and yet, I do feel compelled, indeed almost conspiracy theoretically bound to mention that one of the reasons the Oneida Community broke up and turned itself into a corporate teapot factory is that a faction within the group, led by a lawyer named James William Towner, was miffed that the community’s most esteemed elders were bogarting the teenage virgins and left in a huff for none other than Orange County, California, where Towner helped organize the Orange County government, became a judge, and picked the spot where the Santa Ana courthouse would be built, a courthouse where, it is reasonable to assume, Peter Gallagher’s attorney on The O.C. might defend his clients.)" -- Sarah Vowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
