<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/528751-apoorva]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/528751-apoorva" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 01:56:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68850-the-mind-is-not-a-book-to-be-opened-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 01:56:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Apoorva add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68850-the-mind-is-not-a-book-to-be-opened-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The mind is not a book, to be opened at will and examined at leisure. Thoughts are not etched on the inside of skulls, to be perused by an invader. The mind is a complex and many-layered thing." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/503606-oh-i-think-not-varys-said-swirling-the-wine-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 02:34:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Apoorva add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/503606-oh-i-think-not-varys-said-swirling-the-wine-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh, I think not,” Varys said, swirling the wine in his cup. “Power is a curious thing, my lord. Perchance you have considered the riddle I posed you that day in the inn?”
   “It has crossed my mind a time or to,” Tyrion admitted. “The king, the priest, the rich man—who lives and who dies? Who will the swordsman obey? It’s a riddle without an answer, or rather, two many answers. All depends on the man with the sword.”
  “And yet he is no one,” Varys said. “He has neither crown nor gold nor favor of the gods, only a piece of pointed steel.”
   “That piece of steel is the power of life and death.”
   “Just so…yet if it is the swordsmen who rule us in truth, who do we pretend our kings hold the power? Why should a strong man with a sword ever obey a child king like Joffrey, or a wine-sodden oaf like his father?”
   “Because these child kings and drunken oafs can call other strong men, with other swords.”
   “Then these other swordsmen have the true power. Or do they?” Varys smiled. “Some say knowledge is power. Some tell us that all power comes from the gods. Others say it derives from law. Yet that day on the steps of Baelor’s Sept, our godly High Septon and the lawful Queen Regent and your ever-so-knowledgeable servant were as powerless as any cobbler or cooper in the crowd. Who truly killed Eddard Stark, do you think? Joffrey, who gave the command? Ser Ilyn Payne, who swung the sword? Or…another?”
   Tyrion cocked his head sideways. “Did you mean to answer your damned riddle, or only to make my head ache worse?”
   Varys smiled. “Here, then. Power resides where men believe it resides. No more and no less.”
   “So power is a mummer’s trick?”
   “A shadow on the wall,” Varys murmured, “yet shadows can kill. And ofttimes a very small man can cast a very large shadow.”
   Tyrion smiled. “Lord Varyls, I am growing strangely fond of you. I may kill you yet, but I think I’d feel sad about it.”
   “I will take that as high praise." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/443193-why-is-it-that-when-one-man-builds-a-wall</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 02:35:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Apoorva add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/443193-why-is-it-that-when-one-man-builds-a-wall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why is it that when one man builds a wall, the next man immediately needs to know what's on the other side?" -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116119-sleep-is-good-he-said-and-books-are-better</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 01:59:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Apoorva add a quote by George R. R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116119-sleep-is-good-he-said-and-books-are-better]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sleep is good, he said, And books are better." -- George R. R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446427-we-lead-strange-lives-chasing-our-dreams-around-from-place</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2013 14:57:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Apoorva add a quote by Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446427-we-lead-strange-lives-chasing-our-dreams-around-from-place]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We lead strange lives, chasing our dreams around from place to place." -- Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/586641-let-me-give-you-some-advice-bastard-never-forget-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 14:22:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Apoorva add a quote by Tyrion Lannister]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/586641-let-me-give-you-some-advice-bastard-never-forget-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me give you some advice, bastard: Never forget what you are. The rest of the world will not. Wear it like armor, and it can never be used to hurt you." -- Tyrion Lannister]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/852454-on-a-deux-vies-et-la-deuxi-me-commence-le-jour</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 16:21:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Apoorva add a quote by Confucius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/852454-on-a-deux-vies-et-la-deuxi-me-commence-le-jour]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On a deux vies et la deuxième commence le jour ou l'on se rend compte qu'on n'en a qu'une." -- Confucius]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
