<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/53377-nanosh]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/53377-nanosh" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 22:47:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1169710-preserving-the-essence-in-fact-the-breath-when-it-opened-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 22:47:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nanosh add a quote by Greg Grandin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1169710-preserving-the-essence-in-fact-the-breath-when-it-opened-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["preserving the essence, in fact the breath—when it opened, his museum displayed Thomas Edison’s last exhalation, captured by his son in a test tube at Ford’s request—of a more durable American experience." -- Greg Grandin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1178389-they-were-galvanized-iron-bake-ovens-said-carl-larue-commenting</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 16:00:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nanosh add a quote by Greg Grandin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1178389-they-were-galvanized-iron-bake-ovens-said-carl-larue-commenting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They were “galvanized iron bake ovens,” said Carl LaRue, commenting on Fordlandia’s foibles years later. “It is incredible that anyone should build a house like that in the tropics.” Another visitor described them as “midget hells, where one lies awake and sweats the first half of the night, and frequently between midnight and dawn undergoes a fierce siege of heat-provoking nightmares.” They seemed to be “designed by Detroit architects who probably couldn’t envision a land without snow.”19 Ford managers, said the priest, “never really" -- Greg Grandin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1178675-after-centuries-of-observation-scientists-are-still-not-exactly-sure</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 20:30:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nanosh add a quote by Greg Grandin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1178675-after-centuries-of-observation-scientists-are-still-not-exactly-sure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["after centuries of observation scientists are still not exactly sure why the Amazon—unlike other forests, where leaves turn brown during the dry season—grows green and lush when the rain stops or how this reversed pattern of photosynthesis contributes to the broader seasonal distribution of water throughout the region." -- Greg Grandin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1178712-another-visitor-described-them-as-midget-hells-where-one-lies</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 21:18:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nanosh add a quote by Greg Grandin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1178712-another-visitor-described-them-as-midget-hells-where-one-lies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Another visitor described them as “midget hells, where one lies awake and sweats the first half of the night, and frequently between midnight and dawn undergoes a fierce siege of heat-provoking nightmares.” They seemed to be “designed by Detroit architects who probably couldn’t envision a land without snow.”19 Ford managers, said the priest, “never really figured out what country they were in." -- Greg Grandin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1188392-it-would-be-tempting-to-read-the-story-of-fordlandia</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2014 21:03:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nanosh add a quote by Greg Grandin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1188392-it-would-be-tempting-to-read-the-story-of-fordlandia]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["IT WOULD BE tempting to read the story of Fordlandia and Belterra as a parable of arrogance," -- Greg Grandin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1188846-ford-s-opinion-that-cows-were-the-crudest-most-inefficient-machines</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 07:40:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nanosh add a quote by Greg Grandin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1188846-ford-s-opinion-that-cows-were-the-crudest-most-inefficient-machines]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ford’s opinion that cows were the crudest, most inefficient machines in the world is not unjustified considering the amount of land and energy it takes to keep one alive. Between 2000 and 2005, cattle ranching accounted for 60 percent of deforestation, and today Brazil is the world’s largest exporter of cows, with its 180,000,000-head herd equaling the size of its population." -- Greg Grandin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1190034-but-the-most-profound-irony-is-currently-on-display-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 07:56:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nanosh add a quote by Greg Grandin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1190034-but-the-most-profound-irony-is-currently-on-display-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the most profound irony is currently on display at the very site of Ford’s most ambitious attempt to realize his pastoralist vision. In the Tapajós valley, three prominent elements of Ford’s vision—lumber, which he hoped to profit from while at the same time finding ways to conserve nature; roads, which he believed would knit small towns together and create sustainable markets; and soybeans, in which he invested millions, hoping that the industrial crop would revive rural life—have become the primary agents of the Amazon’s ruin, not just of its flora and fauna but of many of its communities." -- Greg Grandin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1195659-the-second-part-of-the-folk-theory-holds-that-racism</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 00:39:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nanosh add a quote by Jane H. Hill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1195659-the-second-part-of-the-folk-theory-holds-that-racism]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The second part of the folk theory holds that racism is entirely a matter of individual beliefs, intentions, and actions. In the folk theory, a racist is a person who believes that people of color are biologically inferior to Whites, so that White privilege is deserved and must be defended. Racism is what this kind of White supremacist thinks and does. The folk theory holds that such people are anachronisms, who are ignorant, vicious, and remote from the mainstream. Their ignorance can be cured by education. Their viciousness can be addressed by helping them to enjoy new advantages, so that they can gain self-esteem and will not have to look down on others. Since education and general well-being are increasing, racism should soon disappear entirely, except as a sign of mental derangement or disability.
One of the most difficult exercises that this book recommends is to move away from thinking of racism as entirely a matter of individual beliefs and psychological states. White Americans generally agree that things happen in the world because individuals, with beliefs, emotions, and intentions, cause them to happen. They consider this understanding to be the most obvious kind of common sense. Yet not everyone approaches the world from this perspective, and it is very interesting to try to think about racism from outside the framework that it imposes. Critical theorists do not deny that individual beliefs figure in racism. But we prefer to emphasize its collective, cultural dimensions, and to avoid singling out individuals and trying to decide whether they are racists or not. Furthermore, critical theorists insist that ordinary people who do not share White supremacist beliefs can still talk and behave in ways that advance the projects of White racism. I will try to show, in chapters to come, how" -- Jane H. Hill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1201097-for-far-too-long-economists-have-neglected-the-distribution-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 21:44:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nanosh add a quote by Thomas Piketty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1201097-for-far-too-long-economists-have-neglected-the-distribution-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For far too long, economists have neglected the distribution of wealth, partly because of Kuznets’s optimistic conclusions and partly because of the profession’s undue enthusiasm for simplistic mathematical models based on so-called representative agents." -- Thomas Piketty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1210809-when-a-country-goes-from-a-population-of-3-million</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 22:08:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nanosh add a quote by Thomas Piketty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1210809-when-a-country-goes-from-a-population-of-3-million]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a country goes from a population of 3 million to a population of 300 million (to say nothing of the radical increase in territory owing to westward expansion in the nineteenth century), it is clearly no longer the same country." -- Thomas Piketty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1179416-economists-are-all-too-often-preoccupied-with-petty-mathematical-problems</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 23:21:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nanosh add a quote by Thomas Piketty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1179416-economists-are-all-too-often-preoccupied-with-petty-mathematical-problems]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Economists are all too often preoccupied with petty mathematical problems of interest only to themselves. This obsession with mathematics is an easy way of acquiring the appearance of scientificity without having to answer the far more complex questions posed by the world we live in." -- Thomas Piketty]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
