<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/53686-leah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/53686-leah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 17:56:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919-the-man-who-does-not-read-has-no-advantage-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 17:56:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919-the-man-who-does-not-read-has-no-advantage-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who does not read has no advantage over the man who cannot read." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 17:56:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.

So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5399-if-you-want-to-know-what-a-man-s-like-take</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 04:39:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5399-if-you-want-to-know-what-a-man-s-like-take]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to know what a man's like, take a good look at how he treats his inferiors, not his equals." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66110-after-all-anne-had-said-to-marilla-once-i-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 19:43:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66110-after-all-anne-had-said-to-marilla-once-i-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After all,&quot; Anne had said to Marilla once, &quot;I believe the nicest and sweetest days are not those on which anything very splendid or wonderful or exciting happens but just those that bring simple little pleasures, following one another softly, like pearls slipping off a string." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68416-fear-is-the-original-sin-almost-all-of-the-evil</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 19:45:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68416-fear-is-the-original-sin-almost-all-of-the-evil]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fear is the original sin. Almost all of the evil in the world has its origin in the fact that some one is afraid of something.It is a cold slimy serpent coiling about you. It is horrible to live with fear; and it is of all things degrading." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6856-if-one-cannot-enjoy-reading-a-book-over-and-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 16:56:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6856-if-one-cannot-enjoy-reading-a-book-over-and-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If one cannot enjoy reading a book over and over again, there is no use in reading it at all." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6359-a-truly-great-book-should-be-read-in-youth-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 16:58:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by Robertson Davies]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6359-a-truly-great-book-should-be-read-in-youth-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A truly great book should be read in youth, again in maturity and once more in old age, as a fine building should be seen by morning light, at noon and by moonlight." -- Robertson Davies]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9766-in-the-shop-window-you-have-promptly-identified-the-cover</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 16:59:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9766-in-the-shop-window-you-have-promptly-identified-the-cover]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the shop window you have promptly identified the cover with the title you were looking for. Following this visual trail, you have forced your way through the shop past the thick barricade of Books You Haven't Read, which are frowning at you from the tables and shelves, trying to cow you...And thus you pass the outer girdle of ramparts, but then you are attacked by the infantry of Books That If You Had More Than One Life You Would Certainly Also Read But Unfortunately Your Days Are Numbered. With a rapid maneuver you bypass them and move into the phalanxes of the Books You Mean To Read But There Are Others You Must Read First, the Books Too Expensive Now And You'll Wait Till They're Remaindered, the Books ditto When They Come Out in Paperback, Books You Can Borrow From Somebody, Books That Everybody's Read So It's As If You Had Read Them, Too. " -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5115-loyalty-to-country-always-loyalty-to-government-when-it-deserves</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 21:04:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5115-loyalty-to-country-always-loyalty-to-government-when-it-deserves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Loyalty to country ALWAYS. Loyalty to government, when it deserves it." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76604-delusions-are-often-functional-a-mother-s-opinions-about-her-children-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 14:26:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by Robert Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76604-delusions-are-often-functional-a-mother-s-opinions-about-her-children-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Delusions are often functional. A mother's opinions about her children's beauty, intelligence, goodness, et cetera ad nauseam, keep her from drowning them at birth." -- Robert Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49016-remember-this-for-it-is-as-true-and-true-gets</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 14:29:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by Ina May Gaskin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49016-remember-this-for-it-is-as-true-and-true-gets]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember this, for it is as true and true gets: Your body is not a lemon. You are not a machine. The Creator is not a careless mechanic. Human female bodies have the same potential to give birth well as aardvarks, lions, rhinoceri, elephants, moose, and water buffalo. Even if it has not been your habit throughout your life so far, I recommend that you learn to think positively about your body." -- Ina May Gaskin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123237-it-is-as-great-a-crime-to-leave-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 14:48:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by Grantly Dick-Read]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123237-it-is-as-great-a-crime-to-leave-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is as great a crime to leave a woman alone in her agony and deny her relief from her suffering as it is to insist upon dulling the consciousness of a natural mother who desires above all things to be aware of the final reward of her efforts, whose ambition is to be present, in full possession of her senses, when the infant she already adores greets her with its first loud cry and the soft touch of its restless body upon her limbs." -- Grantly Dick-Read]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128325-what-ees-all-dees-stuff-in-africa-we-doan-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 14:48:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by Marie F. Mongan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128325-what-ees-all-dees-stuff-in-africa-we-doan-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["WHAT EES ALL DEES STUFF? IN AFRICA WE DOAN HAVE ALL DEES STUFF!! WE HAVE DEE BABEE!!!&quot;

His message was simple. It goes to the heart of what we in HypnoBirthing frequently puzzle over: Why has all the &quot;stuff&quot; that denies the normalcy of birth and portrays it as an inevitably risky and dangerous medical event become a routine part of most childbirth education classes? Why are couples in a low- or no-risk category being prepared for circumstances that only rarely occur? Even more puzzling, why do parents accept the negative premise that birth is a dangerous, painful ordeal at best or a medical calamity at worst? Why do they blindly accept the &quot;one-size-fits-all&quot; approach?&quot;

If what couples are hearing in childbirth classes is far removed from what they want their birthing experiences to be, why do they spend so much time entertaining negative outcomes that can color and shape their birth expectations and ultimately affect their birth experience? In other words, if it's not what they're wanting, why would they &quot;go there&quot;? In HypnoBirthing, we doan have all dees stuff, and deliberately so.&quot;

HypnoBirthing helps you to frame a positive expectation and to prepare for birth by developing a trust and belief in your birthing body and in nature's undeniable orchestration of birthing. By teaching you the basic physiology of birth and explaining the adverse effect that fear has upon the chemical and physiological responses of your body we help you to learn simple, self-conditioning techniques that will easily bring you into the optimal state of relaxation you will use during birthing. This will allow your birthing muscles to fully relax. In other words, we will help you prepare for the birth your plan and want for yourselves and your baby, rather than the birth that someone else directs. We will help you look forward to your pregnancy and birthing with joy and love, rather than fear and anxiety." -- Marie F. Mongan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116082-when-acog-american-college-of-obstetricians-and-gynecologists-claims-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 14:49:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by Jennifer Block]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116082-when-acog-american-college-of-obstetricians-and-gynecologists-claims-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When ACOG (American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists) claims that home birth and midwives are unsafe, they imply that the women who choose it and the midwives that provide it are acting irresponsibly and selfishly.  They stigmatize normal birth just as the political right has stigmatized abortion.  And they stigmatize women.  
&quot;Our country has created a mythology of women who are irresponsible and don't care,&quot; says Paltrow.  &quot;We talk about welfare queens, crack moms, and murderous women who have abortions.&quot; A culture that allows such language to permeate our national subconscious inevitably dehumanizes all women, including mothers. Lyon argues that this thinking perpetuates a phrase often invoked in exam rooms and delivery rooms: The goal is to have a healthy baby.  &quot;This phrase is used over and over and over to shut down women's requests,&quot; she says.  &quot;The context needs to be that the goal is a healthy mom.  Because mothers never make decisions without thinking about that healthy baby.  And to suggest otherwise is insulting and degrading and disrespectful.&quot; 
What's best for women is best for babies. 
...
The goal is to have a healthy family.  " -- Jennifer Block]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128324-the-premise-that-birthing-by-nature-had-to-be-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 14:49:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by Marie F. Mongan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128324-the-premise-that-birthing-by-nature-had-to-be-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...The premise that birthing, by nature, had to be a painful ordeal was totally unacceptable to me. I could not believe that a God who had created the body with such perfection could have designed a system of procreation that was flawed. So many questions prevented me from accepting the concept of pain in birthing. Why are the two sets of muscles of the uterus the only muscles that do not perform well under normal conditions? Why are the lesser animals blessed with smooth, easy birthing while we, the very highest of creatures, made in the image and likeness of God, are destined to suffer? And why are women in the some cultures able to have gentle, comfortable births? Are we women in the Western world less loved, less indulged, less blessed than they? It didn't make sense to me logically or physiologically.&quot;

    &quot;Even more importantly, I could not believe that a loving God would commit so cruel a hoax as to make us sexual beings so that we would come together in love to conceive and then make the means through which we would birth our children so excruciatingly painful.&quot;

    &quot;Dr. Christiane Northrup, author of Women's Bodies, Women's Wisdom, sums it up well with this challenge to all birthing mothers: Imagine what might happen if the majority of women emerged from their labor beds with a renewed sense of the strength and power of their bodies, and of their capacity for ecstasy through giving birth. When enough women realize that birth is a time of great opportunity to get in touch with their true power, and when they are willing to assume responsibility for this, we will reclaim the power of birth and help move technology where it belongs - in the women, not as their master." -- Marie F. Mongan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140322-in-3000-b-c-in-spain-france-the-british-isles-and-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 14:55:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by Marie F. Mongan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140322-in-3000-b-c-in-spain-france-the-british-isles-and-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["in 3000 b.c....in spain, france, the british isles and old europe, the lives of people centered on nature and motherhood. they honored mother nature, mother earth and mother creator. women were revered as the givers of life. as creators, they were thought to be connected to diety. statues of the goddesses of these early people were of full-breasted women with bodies clearly depicting the ballooning abdomen of women about to give birth. these primal people regarded birthing as the highest manifestation of nature. when a woman gave birth, everyone gathered around her in the temple for the &quot;celebration of life.&quot; birthing was a religious rite, and not at all the painful ordeal it came to be years later. " -- Marie F. Mongan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/778-it-is-not-a-lack-of-love-but-a-lack</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 18:28:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leah add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/778-it-is-not-a-lack-of-love-but-a-lack]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not a lack of love, but a lack of friendship that makes unhappy marriages." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
