<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/537039-allyson]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/537039-allyson" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 10:58:07 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40821-a-constitution-of-government-once-changed-from-freedom-can-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 10:58:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by John Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40821-a-constitution-of-government-once-changed-from-freedom-can-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A Constitution of Government once changed from Freedom, can never be restored. Liberty, once lost, is lost forever." -- John Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106675-there-are-men-in-all-ages-who-mean-to-govern</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 10:58:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Daniel Webster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106675-there-are-men-in-all-ages-who-mean-to-govern]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are men in all ages who mean to govern well, but they mean to govern.  They promise to be good masters, but they mean to be masters" -- Daniel Webster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106689-the-true-danger-is-when-liberty-is-nibbled-away-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 11:49:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Edmond Burke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106689-the-true-danger-is-when-liberty-is-nibbled-away-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The true danger is when liberty is nibbled away, for expedience, and by parts." -- Edmond Burke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106691-collectivism-and-freedom-are-mortal-enemies-only-one-will-survive</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 11:49:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by G. Edward Griffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106691-collectivism-and-freedom-are-mortal-enemies-only-one-will-survive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Collectivism and freedom are mortal enemies.  Only one will survive" -- G. Edward Griffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106692-error-is-better-than-apathy-error-can-be-corrected-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 11:50:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by G. Edward Griffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106692-error-is-better-than-apathy-error-can-be-corrected-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Error is better than apathy.  Error can be corrected in time to change the outcome.  Apathy is seldom corrected until it is too late." -- G. Edward Griffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/370-the-only-thing-necessary-for-the-triumph-of-evil-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 11:52:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Edmund Burke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/370-the-only-thing-necessary-for-the-triumph-of-evil-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only thing necessary for the triumph of evil is for good men to do nothing." -- Edmund Burke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106693-c-ourage-is-reckoned-the-greatest-of-all-virtues-because-unless</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 11:53:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Samuel Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106693-c-ourage-is-reckoned-the-greatest-of-all-virtues-because-unless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[C]ourage is reckoned the greatest of all virtues; because, unless a man has that virtue, he has no security for preserving any other." -- Samuel Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49810-i-do-not-say-that-democracy-has-been-more-pernicious</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 11:55:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by John Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49810-i-do-not-say-that-democracy-has-been-more-pernicious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not say that democracy has been more pernicious on the whole, and in the long run, than monarchy or aristocracy. Democracy has never been and never can be so durable as aristocracy or monarchy; but while it lasts, it is more bloody than either. … Remember, democracy never lasts long. It soon wastes, exhausts, and murders itself. There never was a democracy yet that did not commit suicide. It is in vain to say that democracy is less vain, less proud, less selfish, less ambitious, or less avaricious than aristocracy or monarchy. It is not true, in fact, and nowhere appears in history. Those passions are the same in all men, under all forms of simple government, and when unchecked, produce the same effects of fraud, violence, and cruelty. When clear prospects are opened before vanity, pride, avarice, or ambition, for their easy gratification, it is hard for the most considerate philosophers and the most conscientious moralists to resist the temptation. Individuals have conquered themselves. Nations and large bodies of men, never." -- John Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11289-if-a-nation-expects-to-be-ignorant-and-free-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 11:55:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11289-if-a-nation-expects-to-be-ignorant-and-free-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a nation expects to be ignorant and free, in a state of civilization, it expects what never was and never will be." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106695-a-general-state-education-is-a-mere-contrivance-for-moulding</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 11:56:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by John Stuart Mill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106695-a-general-state-education-is-a-mere-contrivance-for-moulding]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A general State education is a mere contrivance for moulding people to be exactly like one another; and as the mould in which it casts them is that which pleases the dominant power in the government, whether this be a monarch, an aristocracy, or a majority of the existing generation; in proportion as it is efficient and successful, it establishes a despotism over the mind, leading by a natural tendency to one over the body." -- John Stuart Mill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4056-a-government-big-enough-to-give-you-everything-you-want</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 11:56:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Gerald R. Ford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4056-a-government-big-enough-to-give-you-everything-you-want]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A government big enough to give you everything you want is a government big enough to take from you everything you have." -- Gerald R. Ford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106696-we-who-are-engaged-in-the-sacred-cause-of-education</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 11:57:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Horace Mann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106696-we-who-are-engaged-in-the-sacred-cause-of-education]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We who are engaged in the sacred cause of education are entitled to look upon all parents as having given hostages to our cause." -- Horace Mann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106697-the-education-of-all-children-from-the-moment-that-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 11:58:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Karl Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106697-the-education-of-all-children-from-the-moment-that-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The education of all children, from the moment that they can get along without a mother's care, shall be in state institutions." -- Karl Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106698-our-schools-have-been-scientifically-designed-to-prevent-over-education-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 11:58:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by William T. Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106698-our-schools-have-been-scientifically-designed-to-prevent-over-education-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our schools have been scientifically designed to prevent over-education from happening.  The average citizen should be content with their humble role in life." -- William T. Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106699-it-is-out-of-character-for-a-country-that-prides</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 11:59:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by David Kelley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106699-it-is-out-of-character-for-a-country-that-prides]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is out of character for a country that prides itself on intellectual freedom to put the education of its young in the hands of the state." -- David Kelley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106700-give-me-just-one-generation-of-youth-and-i-ll-transform</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 12:00:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Vladimir Lenin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106700-give-me-just-one-generation-of-youth-and-i-ll-transform]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Give me just one generation of youth, and I'll transform the whole world." -- Vladimir Lenin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106702-it-s-time-to-admit-that-public-education-operates-like-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 12:01:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Albert Shanker, Former Pres of American Federation of Teachers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106702-it-s-time-to-admit-that-public-education-operates-like-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's time to admit that public education operates like a planned economy, a bureaucratic system in which everybody's role is spelled out in advance and there are few incentives for innovation and productivity.  It's no surprise that our school system doesn't improve: it more resembles the communist economy than our own market economy." -- Albert Shanker, Former Pres of American Federation of Teachers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106704-wherever-is-found-what-is-called-a-paternal-government-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 12:02:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Benjamin Disraeli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106704-wherever-is-found-what-is-called-a-paternal-government-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wherever is found what is called a paternal government, there is found state education.  It has been discovered that the best way to insure implicit obedience is to commence tyranny in the nursery." -- Benjamin Disraeli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106705-the-tenth-plank-in-karl-marx-s-manifesto-for-destroying-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 12:03:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106705-the-tenth-plank-in-karl-marx-s-manifesto-for-destroying-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The tenth plank in Karl Marx's Manifesto for destroying our kind of civilization advocated the establishment of &quot;free education for all children in public schools.&quot; There were several reasons why Marx wanted government to run the schools.…one of them [was that] ‘It is capable of exact demonstration that if every party in the State has the right of excluding from public schools whatever he does not believe to be true, then he that believes most must give way to him that believes least, and then he that believes least must give way to him that believes absolutely nothing, no matter in how small a minority the atheists or agnostics may be.’

It is self-evident that on this scheme, if it is consistently and persistently carried out in all parts of the country, the United States system of national popular education will be the most efficient and widespread instrument for the propagation of atheism which the world has ever seen." -- Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106706-i-am-beginning-to-suspect-all-elaborate-special-systems</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 12:04:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Helen Keller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106706-i-am-beginning-to-suspect-all-elaborate-special-systems]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am beginning to suspect all elaborate &amp; special systems of education. They seem to me to be built upon the suposition that every child is an idiot who must be taught to think. Whereas, if the child is left to himself, he will think more and better, if less showily. Let him come and go freely, let him touch real things and combine his impressions for himself..." -- Helen Keller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106708-if-we-let-ourselves-we-shall-always-be-waiting-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 12:04:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106708-if-we-let-ourselves-we-shall-always-be-waiting-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we let ourselves, we shall always be waiting for some distraction or other to end before we can really get down to our work. The only people who achieve much are those who want knowledge so badly that they seek it while the conditions are still unfavorable. Favorable conditions never come." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106709-it-is-a-fundamental-truth-that-the-responsibilities-of-motherhood</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 12:06:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106709-it-is-a-fundamental-truth-that-the-responsibilities-of-motherhood]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a fundamental truth that the responsibilities of motherhood cannot be successfully delegated.  No, not to day-care centers, not to schools, not to nurseries, not to babysitters.  We become enamored with men’s theories such as the idea of preschool training outside the home for young children.   Not only does this put added pressure on the budget, but it places young children in an environment away from mother’s influence.  Too often the pressure for popularity, on children and teens, places an economic burden on the income of the father, so mother feels she must go to work to satisfy her children’s needs.  That decision can be most shortsighted.  It is mother’s influence during the crucial formative years that forms a child’s basic character.  Home is the place where a child learns faith, feels love, and thereby learns from mother’s loving example to choose righteousness.  How vital are mother’s influence and teaching in the home—and how apparent when neglected!" -- Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106711-if-you-detect-something-mindless-about-american-education-it-s-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 12:08:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Samuel L. Blumenfeld]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106711-if-you-detect-something-mindless-about-american-education-it-s-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you detect something mindless about American education, it's because the mind has been taken out of it.  Only visible behavior counts." -- Samuel L. Blumenfeld]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106712-in-many-places-it-is-literally-not-safe-physically-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 12:14:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allyson add a quote by Boyd K. Packer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106712-in-many-places-it-is-literally-not-safe-physically-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In many places it is literally not safe physically for youngsters to go to school.  And in many schools, and its becoming almost generally true, it is spiritually unsafe to attend public schools.  Look back over the history of education to the turn of the century and the beginning of the educational philosophies, pragmatism and humanism were the early ones, and they branched out into a number of other philosophies which have led us now into a circumstance where our schools are producing the problems that we face." -- Boyd K. Packer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
