<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/537407-kate]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/537407-kate" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 12:34:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497675-thomas-merton-wrote-there-is-always-a-temptation-to-diddle</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 12:34:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497675-thomas-merton-wrote-there-is-always-a-temptation-to-diddle]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thomas Merton wrote, “there is always a temptation to diddle around in the contemplative life, making itsy-bitsy statues.”  There is always an enormous temptation in all of life to diddle around making itsy-bitsy friends and meals and journeys for itsy-bitsy years on end.  It is so self-conscious, so apparently moral, simply to step aside from the gaps where the creeks and winds pour down, saying, I never merited this grace, quite rightly, and then to sulk along the rest of your days on the edge of rage.  

I won’t have it.  The world is wilder than that in all directions, more dangerous and bitter, more extravagant and bright.  We are making hay when we should be making whoopee; we are raising tomatoes when we should be raising Cain, or Lazarus.

Go up into the gaps.  If you can find them; they shift and vanish too.  Stalk the gaps.  Squeak into a gap in the soil, turn, and unlock-more than a maple- a universe.  This is how you spend this afternoon, and tomorrow morning, and tomorrow afternoon.  Spend the afternoon.  You can’t take it with you." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
