<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/53804-anthony-venn-brown]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/53804-anthony-venn-brown" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 17:00:50 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14446-people-who-exist-at-the-margins-of-society-are-very</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 17:00:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Jamake Highwater]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14446-people-who-exist-at-the-margins-of-society-are-very]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People who exist at the margins of society are very much like Alice in Wonderland.  They are not required to make the tough decision to risk their lives by embarking on an adventure of self-discovery. They have already been thrust beyond the city’s walls that keep ordinary people at a safe distance from the unknown. For at least some outsiders, “alienation” has destroyed traditional presumptions of identity and opened up the mythic hero’s path to the possibility of discovery. What outsiders discover in their adventures on the other side of the looking glass is the courage to repudiate self-contempt and recognise their “alienation” as a precious gift of freedom from arbitrary norms that they did not make and did not sanction. At the moment a person questions the validity of the rules, the victim is no longer a victim." -- Jamake Highwater]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143833-the-wall-that-separates-insiders-from-outsiders-is-not-born</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 06:58:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Jamake Highwater]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143833-the-wall-that-separates-insiders-from-outsiders-is-not-born]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The wall that separates insiders from outsiders is not born of human nature but methodically built, brick by brick, by tribal convention. The &quot;wall&quot; about which I will often speak in this book is not an organism or a membranous extension of some inborn aspect of &quot;human nature&quot;. It is a mechanistic process-a barrier meticulously constructed by erratic community decrees as a means of identifying those who are part of the group and marking those who are not. It is not difficult to imagine the chauvinism that require a community to mark its territories and distinguish its members from its enemies. It is far more difficult to understand the kind of &quot;outsiders&quot; who are the subjects of this book-those who are part of the group and yet are rejected by their peers and cast into a terrible internal exile. It is an exile called &quot;alienation&quot;." -- Jamake Highwater]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629713-my-morality-and-faith-are-choices-my-sexual-orientation-however</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 01:02:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629713-my-morality-and-faith-are-choices-my-sexual-orientation-however]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My morality and faith are choices. My sexual orientation however isn't." -- Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629714-homophobia-and-the-closet-are-allies-like-an-unhealthy-co-dependent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 01:05:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629714-homophobia-and-the-closet-are-allies-like-an-unhealthy-co-dependent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Homophobia and the closet are allies. Like an unhealthy co-dependent relationship they need each other to survive. One plays the victim living in fear and shame while the other plays the persecutor policing what is ‘normal’. The only way to dismantle homophobia is for every gay man and lesbian in the world to come out and live authentic lives. Once they realise how normal we are and see themselves in us….the controversy is over." -- Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629715-even-if-you-believe-the-genesis-record-of-creation-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 01:07:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629715-even-if-you-believe-the-genesis-record-of-creation-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even if you believe the Genesis record of creation you’ll see that God did not create a black and white world of male and female. Creation is not black and white, it is amazingly diverse, like a rainbow, including sexualities and a variety of non-heterosexual expressions of behaviour, affection and partnering occurring in most species, including humans. The ability to reproduce is only a small part of the creation. Before God created male and female he made an even more important statement; ‘it is not good for mankind to be alone’.  This is fundamental to all heterosexual and same-sex relationships. Lasting relationships are based on love, trust and commitment, not sex or reproduction. So stop with the ‘God created Adam and Eve not Adam and Steve’ quote already. It’s boring and an insult to the creator of this incredible universe." -- Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629717-the-enemy-is-not-individuals-churches-ex-gay-organisations-or-political</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 01:13:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629717-the-enemy-is-not-individuals-churches-ex-gay-organisations-or-political]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The enemy is not individuals, churches, 'ex-gay' organisations or political parties; the enemy is ignorance. Change is created by focusing our energies on overcoming the latter instead of attacking the former." -- Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629718-when-we-choose-to-live-authentically-we-chip-away-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 01:14:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629718-when-we-choose-to-live-authentically-we-chip-away-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we choose to live authentically we chip away at others prisons of pretend and create an opportunity for them to walk out of darkness into freedom." -- Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/634580-make-no-mistake-hiding-one-s-true-self-away-in-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 22:39:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/634580-make-no-mistake-hiding-one-s-true-self-away-in-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Make no mistake, hiding one's true self away in a closet and creating a facade of heterosexuality is not without its consequences. It may appear to have a degree of safety but from my experience they are very unhealthy places and do all kinds of terrible things to individuals psychologically, emotionally and behaviourally.....to say nothing of projection. The damage of the fear, shame, guilt and self-loathing that exist inside a closet are often reflected unknowingly in the external life of the individual. In or out of the closet; there is a price to pay. Each individual must weigh up the consequences of honesty, openness, secrecy and deception for themselves. Coming out, for most of us, is like an exorcism that releases us of the darkness we have lived in for years and caused us to believe awful things about ourselves. On the other side of the looking glass are freedom, light and life." -- Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/642881-if-you-are-in-the-closet-and-fall-in-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2012 15:51:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/642881-if-you-are-in-the-closet-and-fall-in-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are in the closet and fall in love with someone of the same gender, it doesn't automatically remove the shame and fear that's kept you locked away. The love you are experiencing encourages you to face the reality that this is who you really are and also has the power to set you free. The richness, beauty and depths of love can only be fully experienced in a climate of complete openness, honesty and vulnerability. Love, the most powerful of human emotions, is calling you to freedom and wholeness." -- Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/643537-midlife-dynamically-for-both-straight-and-gay-males-is-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 17:32:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/643537-midlife-dynamically-for-both-straight-and-gay-males-is-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Midlife dynamically, for both straight and gay males, is often challenging as we face the reality that many of the dreams we had for our lives might not become a reality and unresolved conflicts come to the surface. For us to successfully transition in to the next phase of our lives we must find reconciliation of these issues. And for the gay male there is a sense that the gay self we have tried to keep in the closet or so many years begins to scream out. &quot;Time is running out. When do I get to live?&quot; You can't ignore that voice in the end, you can try and suppress it, and you can try and deny it, you can try and silence it by filling your life with other noises and diverting attention ......but that voice still exists. &quot;Will my entire life be a lie?" -- Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/723448-according-to-my-previous-belief-system-being-a-christian-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 22:31:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/723448-according-to-my-previous-belief-system-being-a-christian-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["According to my previous belief system, being a Christian and homosexual was not only incompatible; like heaven and hell, they were in absolute opposition. The constant conflict of being one person inside but presenting another on the outside for twenty-two years eventually took its toll. 

The messages I got were loud and clear. Never ever admit to yourself or anyone who you are. Hide it, kill it, eradicate it, heal it, deliver it, break it, suppress it, deny it, marry it to a woman, heterosexualize it, therapy it, anything and everything, but whatever you do don’t stand up one day and say “I am gay” because that will mean the end.  I spent most of my life trying to destroy the real me, doing all I could to ensure he never found expression. A suicide of the soul, identity and meaning. When you finally embrace the gift of your sexual orientation it IS the end; the end of shame, fear and oppression. You leave the darkness of the closet and begin a life of honesty, authenticity and freedom." -- Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/755757-there-are-those-from-religious-backgrounds-who-resist-and-oppose</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 18:58:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/755757-there-are-those-from-religious-backgrounds-who-resist-and-oppose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are those from religious backgrounds who resist and oppose LGBT equality; some very obsessively and publicly. They make bold accusations and negative statements about gay and lesbian people, their supposed &quot;lifestyle&quot; and relationships. But when a son, daughter, brother, sister or close friend comes out it is no longer an &quot;issue&quot; it becomes a person. They realise everything they'd said was painfully targeted at someone they love. Then......everything changes." -- Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/793460-to-all-my-friends-who-constantly-talk-disparagingly-about-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 20:05:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/793460-to-all-my-friends-who-constantly-talk-disparagingly-about-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To all my friends who constantly talk disparagingly about the supposed 'homosexual lifestyle' and stereotype gay people and the community, I'd like to get this straight. 

There are essentially two worlds – the 'gay scene' and the gay (or LGBTIQ) community. The 'scene' is like the tip of the iceberg; what is seen by others because it is visible on a street, suburb or pride parade. Like the ninety percent of the submerged iceberg, the community is larger and less visible. It consists of organisations, groups, support networks and also gay and lesbian singles and couples living 'normal' lives in the suburbs. Occasionally there is an overlap but not often. Some live, socialise and work in both. Many never enter each others worlds. The values, lifestyles and culture of these two worlds are as different as Asian culture is to western is to African is to Middle Eastern. 

Dig down even deeper below the surface and you find it is not a single community but diverse communities and subcultures that are separate but not necessarily divided. The common thing that binds them together is their experience of inequality, discrimination and their desire to make a better world for themselves, others and future generations. 

If you believe that all gays and lesbians are shallow and obsessed with sex, body image, partying, nightclubs and bars then you are obviously an observer from the outside or mixing in the wrong circles." -- Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/863365-outing-someone-is-like-ripping-a-butterfly-from-its-cocoon</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2013 17:04:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/863365-outing-someone-is-like-ripping-a-butterfly-from-its-cocoon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Outing someone is like ripping a butterfly from its cocoon. You can damage them for life and rob them of THEIR  life changing experience of liberation. For a successful emergence THEY have to struggle through the cocoon of fear and shame. THEN they can fly." -- Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/879782-homophobia-and-the-closet-are-allies-like-an-unhealthy-co-dependent</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 22:37:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/879782-homophobia-and-the-closet-are-allies-like-an-unhealthy-co-dependent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Homophobia and the closet are allies. Like an unhealthy co-dependent relationship they need each other to survive. One plays the victim living in fear and shame while the other plays the persecutor policing what is ‘normal’. The only way to dismantle homophobia is for every gay man and lesbian in the world to come out and live authentic lives. Once they realise how normal we are and see themselves in us….the controversy is over.

It is interesting to think what would happen though....on a particularly pre-determined day that every single gay man and lesbian came out. Imagine the impact when, on that day, people all around the world suddenly discovered their bosses, mums, dads, daughters, sons, aunts, uncles, cousins, teachers, doctors, neighbours, colleagues, politicians, their favourite actors, celebrities and sports heroes, the people they loved and respected......were indeed gay. 

All stereotypes would immediately be broken.....just by the same single act of millions of people…..and at last there would no longer be need for secrecy. The closet would become the lounge room. How much healthier would we be emotionally and psychologically when we could all be ourselves doing life without the internal and societal negatives that have been attached to our sexual orientation." -- Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26056-every-artist-dips-his-brush-in-his-own-soul-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 21:33:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Henry Ward Beecher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26056-every-artist-dips-his-brush-in-his-own-soul-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every artist dips his brush in his own soul, and paints his own nature into his pictures." -- Henry Ward Beecher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1226515-it-s-better-to-live-one-day-on-this-planet-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 00:38:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1226515-it-s-better-to-live-one-day-on-this-planet-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's better to live one day on this planet being true to yourself than an entire lifetime which is a lie" -- Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1258537-when-you-hear-of-gay-pride-remember-it-was-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 08:22:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anthony add a quote by Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1258537-when-you-hear-of-gay-pride-remember-it-was-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you hear of Gay Pride, remember, it was not born out of a need to celebrate being gay. 

It evolved out of our need as human beings to break free of oppression and to exist without being criminalized, pathologized or persecuted. 

Depending on a number of factors, particularly religion, freeing ourselves from gay shame and coming to self-love and acceptance, can not only be an agonising journey, it can take years. 
Tragically some don't make it. 

Instead of wondering why there isn't a straight pride be grateful you have never needed one. 

Celebrate with us." -- Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
