<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/541416-teresa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/541416-teresa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:38:44 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320273-literature-can-teach-us-how-to-live-before-we-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:38:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Jayne Anne Phillips]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320273-literature-can-teach-us-how-to-live-before-we-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Literature can teach us how to live before we live, and how to die before we die. I believe that writing is practice for death, and for every (other) transformation human beings encounter." -- Jayne Anne Phillips]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16736-they-were-things-for-which-it-was-impossible-to-prepare</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 22:33:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Jhumpa Lahiri]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16736-they-were-things-for-which-it-was-impossible-to-prepare]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They were things for which it was impossible to prepare but which one spent a lifetime looking back at, trying to accept, interpret, comprehend. Things that should never have happened, that seemed out of place and wrong, these were what prevailed, what endured, in the end." -- Jhumpa Lahiri]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16740-i-had-considered-how-the-things-that-never-happen-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 22:38:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Charles Dickens (David Copperfield)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16740-i-had-considered-how-the-things-that-never-happen-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had considered how the things that never happen, are often as much realities to us, in their effects, as those that are accomplished." -- Charles Dickens (David Copperfield)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314-i-was-working-on-the-proof-of-one-of-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 22:59:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314-i-was-working-on-the-proof-of-one-of-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was working on the proof of one of my poems all the morning, and took out a comma. In the afternoon I put it back again." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15164-in-the-desert-in-the-desert-i-saw-a-creature</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 17:04:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Stephen Crane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15164-in-the-desert-in-the-desert-i-saw-a-creature]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;b&gt;In the Desert&lt;/b&gt;

In the desert 
I saw a creature, naked, bestial, 
Who, squatting upon the ground, 
Held his heart in his hands, 
And ate of it. 
I said, “Is it good, friend?” 
“It is bitter—bitter,” he answered; 

“But I like it 
“Because it is bitter, 
“And because it is my heart." -- Stephen Crane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20254-it-s-the-arrangement-of-events-which-makes-the-stories-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 17:04:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Carol Shields]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20254-it-s-the-arrangement-of-events-which-makes-the-stories-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's the arrangement of events which makes the stories.  It's throwing away, compressing, underlining.  Hindsight can give structure to anything, but you have to be able to see it.  Breathing, waking and sleeping: our lives are steamed and shaped into stories.  Knowing that is what keeps me from going insane, and though I don't like to admit it, sometimes it's the only thing." -- Carol Shields]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90794-eventually-everything-gets-stuck-between-a-pair-of-parentheses-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 17:04:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Carol Shields]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90794-eventually-everything-gets-stuck-between-a-pair-of-parentheses-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eventually, everything gets stuck between a pair of parentheses or buried in the bottom of a trunk.

(from &quot;Family Secrets&quot;)" -- Carol Shields]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74857-nothing-matters-except-for-the-harvest-the-gathering-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 17:05:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Carol Shields]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74857-nothing-matters-except-for-the-harvest-the-gathering-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing matters except for the harvest, the gathering in, the adding up, the bringing together, the whole story, the way it happens and happens and goes on happening.

(from &quot;Collision&quot;)" -- Carol Shields]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1336-piglet-sidled-up-to-pooh-from-behind-pooh-he-whispered</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 17:05:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1336-piglet-sidled-up-to-pooh-from-behind-pooh-he-whispered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Piglet sidled up to Pooh from behind. &quot;Pooh?&quot; he whispered.
&quot;Yes, Piglet?&quot;
&quot;Nothing,&quot; said Piglet, taking Pooh's hand. &quot;I just wanted to be sure of you." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37794-she-could-not-explain-in-so-many-words-but-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 17:05:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by E. M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37794-she-could-not-explain-in-so-many-words-but-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She could not explain in so many words, but she felt that those who prepare for all the emergencies of life beforehand may equip themselves at the expense of joy." -- E. M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44821-people-are-curious-a-few-people-are-they-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 17:05:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Alice Munro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44821-people-are-curious-a-few-people-are-they-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People are curious. A few people are. ... They will put things together, knowing all along that they may be mistaken. You see them going around with notebooks, scraping the dirt off gravestones, reading microfilm, just in the hope of seeing this trickle in time, making a connection, rescuing one thing from the rubbish." -- Alice Munro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22613-a-person-s-a-person-no-matter-how-small</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 17:05:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22613-a-person-s-a-person-no-matter-how-small]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A person's a person, no matter how small." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40073-one-sad-thing-about-this-world-is-that-the-acts</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 17:04:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Anne Tyler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40073-one-sad-thing-about-this-world-is-that-the-acts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One sad thing about this world is that the acts that take the most out of you are usually the ones that people will never know about.

(from 'Celestial Navigation')" -- Anne Tyler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50196-out-of-a-human-population-on-earth-of-four-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 09:12:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50196-out-of-a-human-population-on-earth-of-four-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Out of a human population on earth of four and a half billion, perhaps twenty people can write a book in a year.  Some people lift cars, too.  Some people enter week-long sled-dog races, go over Niagara Falls in a barrel, fly planes through the Arc de Triomphe.  Some people feel no pain in childbirth.  Some people eat cars.  There is no call to take human extremes as norms." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/168015-similarly-the-impulse-to-keep-to-yourself-what-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 17:02:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/168015-similarly-the-impulse-to-keep-to-yourself-what-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Similarly, the impulse to keep to yourself what you have learned is not only shameful, it is destructive.  Anything you do not give freely and abundantly becomes lost to you.  You open your safe and find ashes." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214623-in-your-life-there-are-a-few-places-or-maybe</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:36:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Alice Munro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214623-in-your-life-there-are-a-few-places-or-maybe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In your life there are a few places, or maybe only the one place, where something happened, and then there are all the other places." -- Alice Munro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231877-suppose-within-each-book-there-is-another-book-and-within</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 09:34:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231877-suppose-within-each-book-there-is-another-book-and-within]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suppose within each book there is another book, and within every letter on every page another volume constantly unfolding; but these volumes take no space on the desk. Suppose knowledge could be reduced to a quintessence, held within a picture, a sign, held within a place which is no place. Suppose the human skull were to become capacious, spaces opening inside it, humming chambers like beehives." -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252292-there-s-real-trouble-in-the-world-the-kind-that-can-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 09:59:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Barb Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252292-there-s-real-trouble-in-the-world-the-kind-that-can-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's real trouble in the world. The kind that can't be fixed. The kind we lie awake keeping vigil against. Love is not trouble. It's all we have to light our days, to bring music to the time we've been given." -- Barb Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71624-there-was-a-girl-and-her-uncle-sold-her-put</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 10:22:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71624-there-was-a-girl-and-her-uncle-sold-her-put]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was a girl, and her uncle sold her. Put like that it seems so simple.

No man, proclaimed Donne, is an island, and he was wrong. If we were not islands, we would be lost, drowned in each other's tragedies. We are insulated (a word that means, literally, remember, made into an island) from the tragedy of others, by our island nature and by the repetitive shape and form of the stories. The shape does not change: there was a human being who was born, lived and then by some means or other, died. There. You may fill in the details from your own experience. As unoriginal as any other tale, as unique as any other life. Lives are snowflakes- forming patterns we have seen before, as like one another as peas in a pod (and have you ever looked at peas in a pod? I mean, really looked at them? There's not a chance you'll mistake one for another, after a minute's close inspection) but still unique.

Without individuals we see only numbers, a thousand dead, a hundred thousand dead, &quot;casualties may rise to a million.&quot; With individual stories, the statistics become people- but even that is a lie, for the people continue to suffer in numbers that themselves are numbing and meaningless. Look, see the child's swollen, swollen belly and the flies that crawl at the corners of his eyes, this skeletal limbs: will it make it easier for you to know his name, his age, his dreams, his fears? To see him from the inside? And if it does, are we not doing a disservice to his sister, who lies in the searing dust beside him, a distorted distended caricature of a human child? And there, if we feel for them, are they now more important to us than a thousand other children touched by the same famine, a thousand other young lives who will soon be food for the flies' own myriad squirming children?

We draw our lines around these moments of pain, remain upon our islands, and they cannot hurt us. They are covered with a smooth, safe, nacreous layer to let them slip, pearllike, from our souls without real pain.

Fiction allows us to slide into these other heads, these other places, and look out through other eyes. And then in the tale we stop before we die, or we die vicariously and unharmed, and in the world beyond the tale we turn the page or close the book, and we resume our lives.

A life that is, like any other, unlike any other.

And the simple truth is this: There was a girl, and her uncle sold her." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456893-we-must-all-allow-ourselves-the-fantasy-of-projection</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 11:20:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Siri Hustvedt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456893-we-must-all-allow-ourselves-the-fantasy-of-projection]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["(... We must all allow ourselves the fantasy of projection from time to time, a chance to clothe ourselves in the imaginary gowns and tails of what has never been and never will be. This gives some polish to our tarnished lives, and sometimes we may choose one dream over another, and in the choosing find some respite from ordinary sadness. After all, we, none of us, can ever untangle the knot of fictions that make up that wobbly thing we call a self.)" -- Siri Hustvedt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/489919-they-can-print-statistics-and-count-the-populations-in-hundreds</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 09:41:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/489919-they-can-print-statistics-and-count-the-populations-in-hundreds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They can print statistics and count the populations in hundreds of thousands, but to each man a city consists of no more than a few streets, a few houses, a few people. Remove those few and a city exists no longer except as a pain in the memory, like a pain of an amputated leg no longer there." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/732952-i-can-be-by-myself-because-i-m-never-lonely-i-m</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 11:22:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Bohumil Hrabal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/732952-i-can-be-by-myself-because-i-m-never-lonely-i-m]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can be by myself because I'm never lonely; I'm simply alone, living in my heavily populated solitude, a harum-scarum of infinity and eternity, and Infinity and Eternity seem to take a liking to the likes of me." -- Bohumil Hrabal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137840-i-know-the-place-i-know-the-place-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2014 17:38:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teresa add a quote by Harold Pinter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137840-i-know-the-place-i-know-the-place-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;i&gt;I know the place&lt;/i&gt;

I know the place.
It is true.
Everything we do
Corrects the space
Between death and me
And you." -- Harold Pinter]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
