<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/541886-michelle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/541886-michelle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2011 13:36:25 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16962-sometimes-when-you-pick-up-your-child-you-can-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2011 13:36:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16962-sometimes-when-you-pick-up-your-child-you-can-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes when you pick up your child you can feel the map of your own bones beneath your hands, or smell the scent of your skin in the nape of his neck. This is the most extraordinary thing about motherhood - finding a piece of yourself separate and apart that all the same you could not live without." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119902-a-man-should-live-his-life-a-certain-way-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2011 13:37:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119902-a-man-should-live-his-life-a-certain-way-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man should live his life a certain way not because of some divine authority, but because of a personal moral obligation to himself and others." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37196-so-many-people-walk-around-with-a-meaningless-life-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 20:04:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37196-so-many-people-walk-around-with-a-meaningless-life-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many people walk around with a meaningless life. They seem half-asleep, even when they're busy doing things they think are important. This is because they're chasing the wrong things. The way you get meaning into your life is to devote yourself to loving others, devote yourself to your community around you, and devote yourself to creating something that gives you purpose and meaning." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105032-but-there-s-a-story-behind-everything-how-a-picture-got</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 20:05:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105032-but-there-s-a-story-behind-everything-how-a-picture-got]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But there's a story behind everything. How a picture got on a wall. How a scar got on your face. Sometimes the stories are simple, and sometimes they are hard and heartbreaking. But behind all your stories is always your mother's story, because hers is where yours begin." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200906-parents-rarely-let-go-of-their-children-so-children-let</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 20:07:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200906-parents-rarely-let-go-of-their-children-so-children-let]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Parents rarely let go of their children, so children let go of them. They move on. They move away. The moments that used to define them - a mother's approval, a father's nod - are covered by moments of their own accomplishments. It is not until much later, as the skin sags and the heart weakens, that children understand; their stories, and all their accomplishments, sit atop the stories of their mothers and fathers, stones upon stones, beneath the waters of their lives." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105031-i-also-believe-that-parents-if-they-love-you-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 20:09:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105031-i-also-believe-that-parents-if-they-love-you-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I also believe that parents, if they love you, will hold you up safely, above their swirling waters, and sometimes that means you'll never know what they endured, and you may treat them unkindly, in a way you otherwise wouldn't." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72490-the-big-things---how-we-think-what-we-value</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 20:11:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72490-the-big-things---how-we-think-what-we-value]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...the big things - how we think, what we value - those you must choose yourself.  You can't let anyone - or any society - determine those for you." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219271-if-we-tend-to-the-things-that-are-important-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 20:14:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219271-if-we-tend-to-the-things-that-are-important-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we tend to the things that are important in life, if we are right with those we love, and behave in line with our faith, our lives will not be cursed with the aching throb of unfulfilled business. Our words will always be sincere, our embraces will be tight. We will never wallow in the agony of ‘I could have, I should have’. We can sleep in a storm. And when its time, our goodbyes will be complete." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70581-people-always-think-that-happiness-is-a-faraway-thing-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 20:19:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Betty Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70581-people-always-think-that-happiness-is-a-faraway-thing-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People always think that happiness is a faraway thing,&quot; thought Francie, &quot;something complicated and hard to get.  Yet, what little things can make it up; a place of shelter when it rains - a cup of strong hot coffee when you're blue; for a man, a cigarette for contentment; a book to read when you're alone - just to be with someone you love.  Those things make happiness." -- Betty Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16454-you-re-going-to-come-across-people-in-your-life-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 20:24:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16454-you-re-going-to-come-across-people-in-your-life-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're going to come across people in your life who will say all the right words at all the right times. But in the end, it's always their actions you should judge them by. It's actions, not words, that matter." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94179-we-sit-silently-and-watch-the-world-around-us-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 20:26:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94179-we-sit-silently-and-watch-the-world-around-us-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We sit silently and watch the world around us. This has taken a lifetime to learn. It seems only the old are able to sit next to one another and not say anything and still feel content. The young, brash and impatient, must always break the silence. It is a waste, for silence is pure. Silence is holy. It draws people together because only those who are comfortable with each other can sit without speaking. This is the great paradox." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
