<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/542039-melissa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/542039-melissa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 13:55:23 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2032-there-is-nothing-to-writing-all-you-do-is-sit</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 13:55:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2032-there-is-nothing-to-writing-all-you-do-is-sit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing to writing. All you do is sit down at a typewriter and bleed." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10068-people-generally-suck</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 14:18:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Christopher Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10068-people-generally-suck]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People, generally, suck." -- Christopher Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26620-we-waste-time-looking-for-the-perfect-lover-instead-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 00:03:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26620-we-waste-time-looking-for-the-perfect-lover-instead-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We waste time looking for the perfect lover, instead of creating the perfect love." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44282-when-we-hold-each-other-in-the-darkness-it-doesn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 13:41:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44282-when-we-hold-each-other-in-the-darkness-it-doesn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we hold each other, in the darkness, it doesn't make the darkness go away. The bad things are still out there. The nightmares still walking. When we hold each other we feel not safe, but better. &quot;It's all right&quot; we whisper, &quot;I'm here, I love you.&quot; and we lie: &quot;I'll never leave you.&quot; For just a moment or two the darkness doesn't seem so bad." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 13:41:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9524-we-tell-ourselves-stories-in-order-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2011 17:50:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9524-we-tell-ourselves-stories-in-order-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We tell ourselves stories in order to live." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26452-i-didn-t-come-here-of-my-own-accord-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2011 17:50:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26452-i-didn-t-come-here-of-my-own-accord-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I didn't come here of my own accord, and I can't leave that way.
Whoever brought me here will have to take me home." -- Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6812-life-can-only-be-understood-backwards-but-it-must-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 00:33:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6812-life-can-only-be-understood-backwards-but-it-must-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life can only be understood backwards; but it must be lived forwards." -- Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105767-like-all-dreamers-i-confuse-disenchantment-with-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2011 15:20:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Jean Paul Sarte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105767-like-all-dreamers-i-confuse-disenchantment-with-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like all dreamers I confuse disenchantment with truth." -- Jean Paul Sarte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/368392-everyone-has-secrets-it-s-just-a-matter-of-finding-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 18:21:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Stieg Larsson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/368392-everyone-has-secrets-it-s-just-a-matter-of-finding-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone has secrets. It's just a matter of finding out what they are" -- Stieg Larsson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38448-above-all-be-the-heroine-of-your-life-not-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 13:38:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Nora Ephron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38448-above-all-be-the-heroine-of-your-life-not-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Above all, be the heroine of your life, not the victim." -- Nora Ephron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7511-i-saw-my-life-branching-out-before-me-like-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 20:55:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7511-i-saw-my-life-branching-out-before-me-like-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I saw my life branching out before me like the green fig tree in the story. From the tip of every branch, like a fat purple fig, a wonderful future beckoned and winked. One fig was a husband and a happy home and children, and another fig was a famous poet and another fig was a brilliant professor, and another fig was Ee Gee, the amazing editor, and another fig was Europe and Africa and South America, and another fig was Constantin and Socrates and Attila and a pack of other lovers with queer names and offbeat professions, and another fig was an Olympic lady crew champion, and beyond and above these figs were many more figs I couldn't quite make out. I saw myself sitting in the crotch of this fig tree, starving to death, just because I couldn't make up my mind which of the figs I would choose. I wanted each and every one of them, but choosing one meant losing all the rest, and, as I sat there, unable to decide, the figs began to wrinkle and go black, and, one by one, they plopped to the ground at my feet." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51108-emily-does-anyone-ever-realize-life-while-they-live-it-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 15:03:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Thornton Wilder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51108-emily-does-anyone-ever-realize-life-while-they-live-it-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["EMILY: &quot;Does anyone ever realize life while they live it...every, every minute?&quot;

STAGE MANAGER: &quot;No. Saints and poets maybe...they do some." -- Thornton Wilder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406726-only-it-seems-to-me-that-once-in-your-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 15:04:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Thornton Wilder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406726-only-it-seems-to-me-that-once-in-your-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only it seems to me that once in your life before you die you ought to see a country where they don't talk in English and don't even want to." -- Thornton Wilder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19563-from-the-backstabbing-co-worker-to-the-meddling-sister-in-law-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 21:03:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19563-from-the-backstabbing-co-worker-to-the-meddling-sister-in-law-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From the backstabbing co-worker to the meddling sister-in-law, you are in charge of how you react to the people and events in your life. You can either give negativity power over your life or you can choose happiness instead. Take control and choose to focus on what is important in your life. Those who cannot live fully often become destroyers of life." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189111-i-hate-men-who-are-afraid-of-women-s-strength</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 21:43:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189111-i-hate-men-who-are-afraid-of-women-s-strength]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hate men who are afraid of women's strength." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84169-anxiety-is-love-s-greatest-killer-it-makes-others-feel-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 21:43:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84169-anxiety-is-love-s-greatest-killer-it-makes-others-feel-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anxiety is love's greatest killer. It makes others feel as you might when a drowning man holds on to you. You want to save him, but you know he will strangle you with his panic." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200381-the-so-called-psychotically-depressed-person-who-tries-to-kill-herself</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 22:49:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200381-the-so-called-psychotically-depressed-person-who-tries-to-kill-herself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The so-called ‘psychotically depressed’ person who tries to kill herself doesn’t do so out of quote ‘hopelessness’ or any abstract conviction that life’s assets and debits do not square. And surely not because death seems suddenly appealing. The person in whom Its invisible agony reaches a certain unendurable level will kill herself the same way a trapped person will eventually jump from the window of a burning high-rise. Make no mistake about people who leap from burning windows. Their terror of falling from a great height is still just as great as it would be for you or me standing speculatively at the same window just checking out the view; i.e. the fear of falling remains a constant. The variable here is the other terror, the fire’s flames: when the flames get close enough, falling to death becomes the slightly less terrible of two terrors. It’s not desiring the fall; it’s terror of the flames. And yet nobody down on the sidewalk, looking up and yelling ‘Don’t!’ and ‘Hang on!’, can understand the jump. Not really. You’d have to have personally been trapped and felt flames to really understand a terror way beyond falling." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305581-i-m-the-girl-nobody-knows-until-she-commits-suicide-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 22:58:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Tom Leveen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305581-i-m-the-girl-nobody-knows-until-she-commits-suicide-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm the girl nobody knows until she commits suicide. Then suddenly everyone had a class with her." -- Tom Leveen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/790714-they-were-careless-people-they-smashed-up-things-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2013 09:13:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/790714-they-were-careless-people-they-smashed-up-things-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They were careless people ... they smashed up things and creatures and then retreated back into their money or their vast carelessness or whatever it was that kept them together, and let other people clean up the mess they had made . . . . " -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225267-every-man-has-his-secret-sorrows-which-the-world-knows</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2013 01:13:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Henry Wadsworth Longfellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225267-every-man-has-his-secret-sorrows-which-the-world-knows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every man has his secret sorrows which the world knows not; and often times we call a man cold when he is only sad." -- Henry Wadsworth Longfellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128439-some-friends-don-t-understand-this-they-don-t-understand-how-desperate</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2013 01:14:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128439-some-friends-don-t-understand-this-they-don-t-understand-how-desperate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some friends don't understand this. They don't understand how desperate I am to have someone say, I love you and I support you just the way you are because you're wonderful just the way you are. They don't understand that I can't remember anyone ever saying that to me. I am so demanding and difficult for my friends because I want to crumble and fall apart before them so that they will love me even though I am no fun, lying in bed, crying all the time, not moving. Depression is all about If you loved me you would." -- Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185907-when-you-re-surrounded-by-all-these-people-it-can-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2013 01:15:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Fiona Apple]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185907-when-you-re-surrounded-by-all-these-people-it-can-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you're surrounded by all these people, it can be lonelier than when you're by yourself.  You can be in a huge crowd, but if you don't feel like you can trust anyone or talk to anybody, you feel like you're really alone." -- Fiona Apple]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27468-if-i-can-t-feel-if-i-can-t-move-if-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2013 01:17:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Kay Redfield Jamison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27468-if-i-can-t-feel-if-i-can-t-move-if-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I can't feel, if I can't move, if I can't think, and I can't care, then what conceivable point is there in living?" -- Kay Redfield Jamison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172352-some-catastrophic-moments-invite-clarity-explode-in-split-moments-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2013 01:18:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172352-some-catastrophic-moments-invite-clarity-explode-in-split-moments-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some catastrophic moments invite clarity, explode in split moments: You smash your hand through a windowpane and then there is blood and shattered glass stained with red all over the place; you fall out a window and break some bones and scrape some skin. Stitches and casts and bandages and antiseptic solve and salve the wounds. But depression is not a sudden disaster. It is more like a cancer: At first its tumorous mass is not even noticeable to the careful eye, and then one day -- wham! -- there is a huge, deadly seven-pound lump lodged in your brain or your stomach or your shoulder blade, and this thing that your own body has produced is actually trying to kill you. Depression is a lot like that: Slowly, over the years, the data will accumulate in your heart and mind, a computer program for total negativity will build into your system, making life feel more and more unbearable. But you won't even notice it coming on, thinking that it is somehow normal, something about getting older, about turning eight or turning twelve or turning fifteen, and then one day you realize that your entire life is just awful, not worth living, a horror and a black blot on the white terrain of human existence. One morning you wake up afraid you are going to live.

In my case, I was not frightened in the least bit at the thought that I might live because I was certain, quite certain, that I was already dead. The actual dying part, the withering away of my physical body, was a mere formality. My spirit, my emotional being, whatever you want to call all that inner turmoil that has nothing to do with physical existence, were long gone, dead and gone, and only a mass of the most fucking god-awful excruciating pain like a pair of boiling hot tongs clamped tight around my spine and pressing on all my nerves was left in its wake.

That's the thing I want to make clear about depression: It's got nothing at all to do with life. In the course of life, there is sadness and pain and sorrow, all of which, in their right time and season, are normal -- unpleasant, but normal. Depression is an altogether different zone because it involves a complete absence: absence of affect, absence of feeling, absence of response, absence of interest. The pain you feel in the course of a major clinical depression is an attempt on nature's part (nature, after all, abhors a vacuum) to fill up the empty space. But for all intents and purposes, the deeply depressed are just the walking, waking dead.

And the scariest part is that if you ask anyone in the throes of depression how he got there, to pin down the turning point, he'll never know. There is a classic moment in The Sun Also Rises when someone asks Mike Campbell how he went bankrupt, and all he can say in response is, 'Gradually and then suddenly.' When someone asks how I love my mind, that is all I can say too" -- Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157533-antonin-artaud-wrote-on-one-of-his-drawings-never-real</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2013 01:23:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Andrew Solomon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157533-antonin-artaud-wrote-on-one-of-his-drawings-never-real]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Antonin Artaud wrote on one of his drawings, &quot;Never real and always true,&quot; and that is how depression feels.  You know that it is not real, that you are someone else, and yet you know that it is absolutely true." -- Andrew Solomon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/692246-when-you-re-an-introvert-like-me-and-you-ve-been-lonely</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2013 01:11:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Lana Del Rey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/692246-when-you-re-an-introvert-like-me-and-you-ve-been-lonely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you’re an introvert like me and you’ve been lonely for a while, and then you find someone who understands you, you become really attached to them. It’s a real release." -- Lana Del Rey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/687225-i-was-in-the-winter-of-my-life--and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2013 01:13:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Lana Del Rey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/687225-i-was-in-the-winter-of-my-life--and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was in the winter of my life- and the men I met along the road were my only summer. At night I fell sleep with visions of myself dancing and laughing and crying with them. Three years down the line of being on an endless world tour and memories of them were the only things that sustained me, and my only real happy times. I was a singer, not a very popular one, who once had dreams of becoming a beautiful poet- but upon an unfortunate series of events saw those dreams dashed and divided like a million stars in the night sky that I wished on over and over again- sparkling and broken. But I really didn’t mind because I knew that it takes getting everything you ever wanted and then losing it to know what true freedom is.

When the people I used to know found out what I had been doing, how I had been living- they asked me why. But there’s no use in talking to people who have a home, they have no idea what its like to seek safety in other people, for home to be wherever you lay your head.

I was always an unusual girl, my mother told me that I had a chameleon soul. No moral compass pointing me due north, no fixed personality. Just an inner indecisiveness that was as wide as wavering as the ocean. And if I said that I didn't plan for it to turn out this way I’d be lying- because I was born to be the other woman. I belonged to no one- who belonged to everyone, who had nothing- who wanted everything with a fire for every experience and an obsession for freedom that terrified me to the point that I couldn’t even talk about- and pushed me to a nomadic point of madness that both dazzled and dizzied me.

Every night I used to pray that I’d find my people- and finally I did- on the open road. We have nothing to lose, nothing to gain, nothing we desired anymore- except to make our lives into a work of art." -- Lana Del Rey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362920-time-just-gets-away-from-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 19:56:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Charles Portis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362920-time-just-gets-away-from-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time just gets away from us." -- Charles Portis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34716-suicide-is-a-form-of-murder---premeditated-murder-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 23:40:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34716-suicide-is-a-form-of-murder---premeditated-murder-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suicide is a form of murder - premeditated murder. It isn't something you do the first time you think of doing it. It takes getting used to. And you need the means, the opportunity, the motive. A successful suicide demands good organization and a cool head, both of which are usually incompatible with the suicidal state of mind." -- Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
