<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/54435-lindsey]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/54435-lindsey" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2009 14:54:56 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17243-many-years-later-as-he-faced-the-firing-squad-colonel</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2009 14:54:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17243-many-years-later-as-he-faced-the-firing-squad-colonel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many years later, as he faced the firing squad, Colonel Aureliano Buendía was to remember that distant afternoon when his father took him to discover ice..." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320128-to-see-someone-you-love-in-a-bad-setting-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2011 07:02:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Aimee Bender]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320128-to-see-someone-you-love-in-a-bad-setting-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To see someone you love, in a bad setting, is one of the great barometers of gratitude." -- Aimee Bender]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141195-to-think-of-the-midwest-as-a-whole-as-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 04:15:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141195-to-think-of-the-midwest-as-a-whole-as-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To think of the Midwest as a whole as anything other than beautiful is to ignore the extraordinary power of the land. The lushness of the grass and trees in August, the roll of the hills (far less of the Midwest is flat than outsiders seem to imagine), the rich smell of soil, the evening sunlight over a field of wheat, or the crickets chirping at dusk on a residential street: All of it, it has always made me feel at peace. There is room to breathe, there is a realness of place. The seasons are extreme, but they pass and return, pass and return, and the world seems far steadier than it does from the vantage point of a coastal city.

Certainly picturesque towns can be found in New England or California or the Pacific Northwest, but I can't shake the sense that they're too picturesque. On the East Coast, especially, these places seem to me aggressively quaint, unbecomingly smug, and even xenophobic, downright paranoid in their wariness of those who might somehow infringe upon the local charm. I suspect this wariness is tied to the high cost of real estate, the fear that there might not be enough space or money and what there is of both must be clung to and defended. The West Coast, I think, has a similar self-regard...and a beauty that I can't help seeing as show-offy. But the Midwest: It is quietly lovely, not preening with the need to have its attributes remarked on. It is the place I am calmest and most myself." -- Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346133-heart-weeps-head-tries-to-help-heart-head-tells-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 04:16:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Lydia Davis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346133-heart-weeps-head-tries-to-help-heart-head-tells-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Heart weeps.
Head tries to help heart.
Head tells heart how it is, again:
You will lose the ones you love. They will all go. But even the earth will go, someday.
Heart feels better, then.
But the words of head do not remain long in the ears of heart.
Heart is so new to this.
I want them back, says heart.
Head is all heart has.
Help, head. Help heart." -- Lydia Davis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7552-don-t-let-the-bastards-grind-you-down</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2011 12:39:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7552-don-t-let-the-bastards-grind-you-down]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't let the bastards grind you down." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474351-teenage-girls-please-don-t-worry-about-being-super-popular-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 06:17:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Mindy Kaling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474351-teenage-girls-please-don-t-worry-about-being-super-popular-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Teenage girls, please don’t worry about being super popular in high school, or being the best actress in high school, or the best athlete. Not only do people not care about any of that the second you graduate, but when you get older, if you reference your successes in high school too much, it actually makes you look kind of pitiful, like some babbling old Tennessee Williams character with nothing else going on in her current life. What I’ve noticed is that almost no one who was a big star in high school is also big star later in life. For us overlooked kids, it’s so wonderfully fair." -- Mindy Kaling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480759-i-don-t-want-to-hear-about-the-endless-struggles-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 06:18:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Mindy Kaling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480759-i-don-t-want-to-hear-about-the-endless-struggles-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't want to hear about the endless struggles to keep sex exciting, or the work it takes to plan a date night. I want to hear that you guys watch every episode of The Bachelorette together in secret shame, or that one got the other hooked on Breaking Bad and if either watches it without the other, they're dead meat. I want to see you guys high-five each other like teammates on a recreational softball team you both do for fun." -- Mindy Kaling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525604-i-was-reminded-of-the-four-immutable-laws-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2012 09:35:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525604-i-was-reminded-of-the-four-immutable-laws-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was reminded of the Four Immutable Laws of the Spirit: Whoever is present are the right people. Whenever it begins is the right time. Whatever happens is the only thing that could have happened. And when it's over, it's over." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525607-and-what-do-you-do-in-the-face-of-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2012 09:37:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525607-and-what-do-you-do-in-the-face-of-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And what do you do in the face of this powerlessness? As a parent?&quot;

&quot;You get to be obsessed and angry,&quot; Tom said. &quot;And they get to be the age they are, and act like teenagers if they want to. There is a zero-percent chance you will change them. So we breathe in, and out, talk to friends, as needed. We show up, wear clean underwear, say hello to strangers. We plant bulbs, and pick up litter, knowing there will be more in twenty minutes. We pray that we might cooperate with any flicker of light we can find in the world." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/528992-i-made-it-the-mantra-of-those-days-when-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2012 10:27:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/528992-i-made-it-the-mantra-of-those-days-when-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I made it the mantra of those days; when I paused before yet another series of switchbacks or skidded down knee-jarring slopes, when patches of flesh peeled off my feet along with my socks, when I lay alone and lonely in my tent at night I asked, often out loud: Who is tougher than me?

The answer was always the same, and even when I knew absolutely there was no way on this earth that it was true, I said it anyway: No one." -- Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/528994-what-if-i-forgave-myself-i-thought-what-if-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2012 10:29:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/528994-what-if-i-forgave-myself-i-thought-what-if-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What if I forgave myself? I thought. What if I forgave myself even though I'd done something I shouldn't have? What if I was a liar and a cheat and there was no excuse for what I'd done other than because it was what I wanted and needed to do? What if I was sorry, but if I could go back in time I wouldn't do anything differently than I had done? What if I'd actually wanted to fuck every one of those men? What if heroin taught me something? What if yes was the right answer instead of no? What if what made me do all those things everyone thought I shouldn't have done was what also had got me here? What if I was never redeemed? What if I already was?" -- Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/529002-widen-your-vision-of-what-beauty-is-realize-and-keep</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2012 10:51:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Lindsey Gates Markel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/529002-widen-your-vision-of-what-beauty-is-realize-and-keep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Widen your vision of what beauty is. Realize and keep close the fact that a beauty standard has been created by the very people who sell it, and that it is no accident that the accepted &quot;beauty standard&quot; can easily be described as &quot;perfect.&quot; Flaws are not tolerated if you want to be perfect. But the models that we see most often--even the tallest and thinnest and most doe-eyed--are still pinned and sprayed and pulled into place. Then they are manipulated digitally until, literally, everything that might be perceived as a &quot;flaw&quot; is erased. This is a way to sell product. It has nothing to do with real life. It has nothing to do with you. We are made of so-called &quot;flaws.&quot; They are the thread that stitches our parts together and keeps us from being generic cut-out paper dolls. You are beautiful. You are enough, now and always. You have always been enough." -- Lindsey Gates Markel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485702-some-people-don-t-understand-the-promises-they-re-making-when-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 09:55:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485702-some-people-don-t-understand-the-promises-they-re-making-when-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people don't understand the promises they're making when they make them,&quot; I said.

&quot;Right, of course. But you keep the promise anyway. That's what love is. Love is keeping the promise anyway." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/699788-if-i-were-going-to-begin-practicing-the-presence-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 12:14:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/699788-if-i-were-going-to-begin-practicing-the-presence-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I were going to begin practicing the presence of God for the first time today, it would help to begin by admitting the three most terrible truths of our existence: that we are so ruined, and so loved, and in charge of so little." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630699-the-highly-sensitive-introverted-tend-to-be-philosophical-or-spiritual</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 17:51:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Susan Cain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630699-the-highly-sensitive-introverted-tend-to-be-philosophical-or-spiritual]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The highly sensitive [introverted]  tend to be philosophical or spiritual in their orientation, rather than materialistic or hedonistic.  They dislike small talk.  They often describe themselves as creative or intuitive.  They dream vividly, and can often recall their dreams the next day.  They love music, nature, art, physical beauty. They feel exceptionally strong emotions--sometimes acute bouts of joy, but also sorrow, melancholy, and fear. Highly sensitive people also process information about their environments--both physical and emotional--unusually deeply.  They tend to notice subtleties that others miss--another person's shift in mood, say, or a lightbulb burning a touch too brightly." -- Susan Cain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2052-the-pleasure-of-all-reading-is-doubled-when-one-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 12:29:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsey add a quote by Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2052-the-pleasure-of-all-reading-is-doubled-when-one-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The pleasure of all reading is doubled when one lives with another who shares the same books." -- Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
