<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/545069-dasha]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/545069-dasha" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 16:55:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225108-while-i-can-t-have-you-i-long-for-you-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 16:55:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dasha add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225108-while-i-can-t-have-you-i-long-for-you-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["While I can’t have you, I long for you. I am the kind of person who would miss a train or a plane to meet you for coffee. I’d take a taxi across town to see you for ten minutes. I’d wait outside all night if I thought you would open the door in the morning. If you call me and say ‘Will you…’ my answer is ‘Yes’, before your sentence is out. I spin worlds where we could be together. I dream you. For me, imagination and desire are very close." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24313-time-that-withers-you-will-wither-me-we-will-fall</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 16:57:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dasha add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24313-time-that-withers-you-will-wither-me-we-will-fall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time that withers you will wither me.  We will fall like ripe fruit and roll down the grass together.  Dear friend, let me lie beside you watching the clouds until the earth covers us and we are gone." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194781-walk-with-me-hand-in-hand-through-the-neon-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 17:04:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dasha add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194781-walk-with-me-hand-in-hand-through-the-neon-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Walk with me, hand in hand through the neon and styrofoam. Walk the razor blades and the broken hearts. Walk the fortune and the fortune hunted. Walk the chop suey bars and the tract of stars.
I know I am a fool, hoping dirt and glory are both a kind of luminous paint; the humiliations and exaltations that light us up. I see like a bug, everything too large, the pressure of infinity hammering at my head. But how else to live, vertical that I am, pressed down and pressing up simultaneously? I cannot assume you will understand me. It is just as likely that as I invent what I want to say, you will invent what you want to hear. Some story we must have. Stray words on crumpled paper. A weak signal into the outer space of each other.
The probability of separate worlds meeting is very small. The lure of it is immense. We send starships. We fall in love." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237385-in-the-heat-of-her-hands-i-thought-this-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 17:07:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dasha add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237385-in-the-heat-of-her-hands-i-thought-this-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the heat of her hands I thought, This is the campfire that mocks the sun. This place will warm me, feed me and care for me. I will hold on to this pulse against other rhythms. The world will come and go in the tide of a day but here is her hand with my future in its palm." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/566955-i-ve-always-tried-to-make-a-home-for-myself-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 17:07:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dasha add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/566955-i-ve-always-tried-to-make-a-home-for-myself-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've always tried to make a home for myself, but I have not felt at home &lt;i&gt;in&lt;/i&gt; myself.  I've worked hard at being the hero of my own life.  But every time I checked the register of displaced persons, I was still on it.  I didn't know how to belong.  Longing?  Yes.  Belonging?  No." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
