<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/54512-marianne]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/54512-marianne" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 10:05:10 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106377-love-is-a-myth-love-is-a-myth-grandfather-trout</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 10:05:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marianne add a quote by John Crowley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106377-love-is-a-myth-love-is-a-myth-grandfather-trout]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a myth.'
'Love is a myth,' Grandfather Trout said. 'Like summer.'
'What?'
'In winter,'Grandfather Trout said, 'summer is a myth. A report, a rumor. Not to be believed in. Get it? Love is a myth. So is summer." -- John Crowley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/581826-it-felt-like-faith-like-revelation-that-things-went-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 20:49:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marianne add a quote by Iain Banks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/581826-it-felt-like-faith-like-revelation-that-things-went-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It felt like faith, like revelation: that things went on, that life ground on regardless, and mindless, and produced pain and pleasure and hope and fear and joy and despair, and you dodged some of it and you sought some of it and sometimes you were lucky
and sometimes you weren’t, and sometimes you could plan your way ahead and that would be the right thing to have done, but other times all you could do was forget about plans and just be ready to react, and sometimes the obvious was true and sometimes it
wasn’t, and sometimes experience helped but not always, and it was all luck, fate, in the end; you lived, and you waited to see what happened, and you would rarely ever be sure that what you had done was really the right thing or the wrong thing, because things can
always be better, and things can always be worse." -- Iain Banks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/768770-there-is-a-love-that-equals-in-its-power-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 02:02:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marianne add a quote by Mervyn Peake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/768770-there-is-a-love-that-equals-in-its-power-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a love that equals in its power the love of man for woman and reaches inwards as deeply. It is the love of a man or a woman for their world. For the world of their center where their lives burn genuinely and with a free flame.

The love of the diver for his world of wavering light. His world of pearls and tendrils and his breath at his breast. Born as a plunger into the deeps he is at one with every swarm of lime-green fish, with every colored sponge. As he holds himself to the ocean's faery floor, one hand clasped to a bedded whale's rib, he is complete and infinite. Pulse, power and universe sway in his body. He is in love.

The love of the painter standing alone and staring, staring at the great colored surface he is making. Standing with him in the room the rearing canvas stares back with tentative shapes halted in their growth, moving in a new rhythm from floor to ceiling. The twisted tubes, the fresh paint squeezed and smeared across the dry on his palette. The dust beneath the easel. The paint has edged along the brushes' handles. The white light in a northern sky is silent. The window gapes as he inhales his world. His world: a rented room, and turpentine. He moves towards his half-born. He is in Love.

The rich soil crumbles through the yeoman's fingers. As the pearl diver murmurs, 'I am home' as he moves dimly in strange water-lights, and as the painter mutters, 'I am me' on his lone raft of floorboards, so the slow landsman on his acre'd marl - says with dark Fuchsia on her twisting staircase, 'I am home." -- Mervyn Peake]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/790481-in-the-presence-of-real-tragedy-you-feel-neither-pain</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 02:04:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marianne add a quote by Mervyn Peake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/790481-in-the-presence-of-real-tragedy-you-feel-neither-pain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the presence of real tragedy you feel neither pain nor joy nor hatred, only a sense of enormous space and time suspended, the great doors open to black eternity, the rising across the terrible field of that last enormous, unanswerable question." -- Mervyn Peake]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/571951-a-reader-never-travels-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 14:29:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marianne add a quote by Michael McGirr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/571951-a-reader-never-travels-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A reader never travels alone." -- Michael McGirr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/581221-we-ve-got-to-believe-in-our-beautiful-impossible-blueprints</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 21:14:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marianne add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/581221-we-ve-got-to-believe-in-our-beautiful-impossible-blueprints]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We've got to believe in our beautiful impossible blueprints." -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3390-holding-hands-for-example-is-a-way-to-remember-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 09:25:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marianne add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3390-holding-hands-for-example-is-a-way-to-remember-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Holding hands, for example, is a way to remember how it feels to say nothing together." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620917-please-tell-me-a-story-about-a-girl-who-gets</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2013 02:41:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marianne add a quote by Helen Oyeyemi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620917-please-tell-me-a-story-about-a-girl-who-gets]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Please tell me a story about a girl who gets away.&quot;

I would, even if I had to adapt one, even if I had to make one up just for her. &quot;Gets away from what, though?&quot;

&quot;From her fairy godmother. From the happy ending that isn't really happy at all. Please have her get out and run off of the page altogether, to somewhere secret where words like 'happy' and 'good' will never find her.&quot;

&quot;You don't want her to be happy and good?&quot;

&quot;I'm not sure what's really meant by happy and good. I would like her to be free. Now. Please begin." -- Helen Oyeyemi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274775-she-isn-t-a-storm-or-a-leader-or-a-king</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2013 02:42:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marianne add a quote by Helen Oyeyemi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274775-she-isn-t-a-storm-or-a-leader-or-a-king]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She isn't a storm or a leader or a king or a war or anyone whose life and death makes noise. The problem is words. There is skin, yes. And then, inside that, there is your language, the casual, inherited magic spells taht make your skin real. It's too late now--even if we could say &quot;Shut up&quot; or &quot;Where's my dinner?&quot; in the first language, the real language, the words weren't born in us. And unless your skin and your language touch each other without interruption, there is no word strong enough to make you understand that it matters that you live. The things that really &quot;stay&quot; are an Orisha, a kind night, a pretended boy, a garden song that made no sense. Those come closer to being enough." -- Helen Oyeyemi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58841-you-ve-got-to-give-kids-really-beautiful-children-s-books-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 08:13:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marianne add a quote by Tony Millionaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58841-you-ve-got-to-give-kids-really-beautiful-children-s-books-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've got to give kids really beautiful children's books in order to turn them into revolutionaries. Because if they see these beautiful things when they're young, when they grow up they'll see the real world and say, 'Why is the world so ugly?! I remember when the world was beautiful.' And then they'll fight, and they'll have a revolution. They'll fight against all of our corruption in the world, they'll fight to try to make the world more beautiful. That's the job of a good children's book illustrator." -- Tony Millionaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/516419-read-the-great-stuff-but-read-the-stuff-that-isn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 23:16:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marianne add a quote by Edward Albee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/516419-read-the-great-stuff-but-read-the-stuff-that-isn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Read the great stuff, but read the stuff that isn't so great, too. Great stuff is very discouraging. If you read only Beckett and Chekhov, you'll go away and only deliver telegrams for Western Union." -- Edward Albee]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
