<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/549388-erin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/549388-erin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 21:04:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240693-isn-t-it-also-that-on-some-fundamental-level-we-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 21:04:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240693-isn-t-it-also-that-on-some-fundamental-level-we-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't it also that on some fundamental level we find it difficult to understand that other people are human beings in the same way that we are? We idealize them as gods or dismiss them as animals." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/379288-i-m-sorry-but-i-don-t-get-it-if-we-re-supposed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 21:45:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by A.S. King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/379288-i-m-sorry-but-i-don-t-get-it-if-we-re-supposed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm sorry, but I don't get it. If we're supposed to ignore everything that's wrong with our lives, then I can't see how we'll ever make things right." -- A.S. King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284483-every-life-has-a-watershed-moment-an-instant-when-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 04:43:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Mira Grant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284483-every-life-has-a-watershed-moment-an-instant-when-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every life has a watershed moment, an instant when you realize you're about to make a choice that will define everything else you ever do, and that if you choose wrong, there may not be that many things left to choose. Sometimes the wrong choice is the only one that lets you face the end with dignity, grace, and the awareness that you're doing the right thing.
I'm not sure we can recognize those moments until they've passed us." -- Mira Grant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425903-life-s-more-fun-when-you-take-the-chance-that-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 04:44:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Mira Grant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425903-life-s-more-fun-when-you-take-the-chance-that-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life's more fun when you take the chance that it might end." -- Mira Grant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464824-this-is-the-truth-we-are-a-nation-accustomed-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 21:03:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Mira Grant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464824-this-is-the-truth-we-are-a-nation-accustomed-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is the truth: We are a nation accustomed to being afraid. If I’m being honest, not just with you but with myself, it’s not just the nation, and it’s not just something we’ve grown used to. It’s the world, and it’s an addiction. People crave fear. Fear justifies everything. Fear makes it okay to have surrendered freedom after freedom, until our every move is tracked and recorded in a dozen databases the average man will never have access to. Fear creates, defines, and shapes our world, and without it, most of us would have no idea what to do with ourselves. Our ancestors dreamed of a world without boundaries, while we dream new boundaries to put around our homes, our children, and ourselves. We limit our potential day after day in the name of a safety that we refuse to ever achieve. We took a world that was huge with possibility, and we made it as small as we could." -- Mira Grant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121960-at-times-the-world-may-seem-an-unfriendly-and-sinister</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 19:38:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121960-at-times-the-world-may-seem-an-unfriendly-and-sinister]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At times the world may seem an unfriendly and sinister place, but believe that there is much more good in it than bad.  All you have to do is look hard enough.  and what might seem to be a series of unfortunate events may in fact be the first steps of a journey." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
