<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/550790-kim]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/550790-kim" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 14:00:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/336109-technological-change-is-discontinuous-the-monks-in-their-scriptoria-did</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 14:00:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Jason Epstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/336109-technological-change-is-discontinuous-the-monks-in-their-scriptoria-did]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Technological change is discontinuous. The monks in their scriptoria did not invent the printing press, horse breeders did not invent the motorcar, and the music industry did not invent the iPod or launch iTunes. Early in the new century book publishers, confined within their history and outflanked by unencumbered digital innovators, missed yet another critical opportunity, seized once again by Amazon, this time to build their own universal digital catalog, serving e-book users directly and on their own terms while collecting the names, e-mail addresses, and preferences of their customers. This strategic error will have large consequences." -- Jason Epstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34703-paranoid-probably-but-just-because-you-re-paranoid-doesn-t-mean-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 18:51:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Jim Butcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34703-paranoid-probably-but-just-because-you-re-paranoid-doesn-t-mean-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Paranoid? Probably. But just because you're paranoid doesn't mean there isn't an invisible demon about to eat your face." -- Jim Butcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11241-everyone-must-leave-something-behind-when-he-dies-my-grandfather</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 19:08:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11241-everyone-must-leave-something-behind-when-he-dies-my-grandfather]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone must leave something behind when he dies, my grandfather said. A child or a book or a painting or a house or a wall built or a pair of shoes made. Or a garden planted. Something your hand touched some way so your soul has somewhere to go when you die, and when people look at that tree or that flower you planted, you're there. 

It doesn't matter what you do, he said, so long as you change something from the way it was before you touched it into something that's like you after you take your hands away. The difference between the man who just cuts lawns and a real gardener is in the touching, he said. The lawn-cutter might just as well not have been there at all; the gardener will be there a lifetime." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/345382-these-days-vampires-gravitated-toward-particle-accelerators-projects-to-decode</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 13:50:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Deborah Harkness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/345382-these-days-vampires-gravitated-toward-particle-accelerators-projects-to-decode]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These days vampires gravitated toward particle accelerators, projects to decode the genome, and molecular biology.  Once they had flocked to alchemy, anatomy, and electricity.  If it went bang, involved blood, or promised to unlock the secrets of the universe, there was sure to be a vampire around." -- Deborah Harkness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/359150-and-so-many-of-the-indies-have-partnered-with-google</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 12:16:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Steve Weddle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/359150-and-so-many-of-the-indies-have-partnered-with-google]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And so many of the indies have partnered with Google to sell ebooks right from their own websites. These stores are embracing the “new technology” instead of hiding from it, because they realize it’s about the story, not the ink on paper. If you want ebooks, your local indie can sell you ebooks. If your local independent is hanging up posters saying that ebooks will kill everything, you should tag that bookstore as a favorite in your GPS doohickey. You’ll get great deals, because that store will have a going-out-of-business sale soon. Yes, even though you try to save it with a letter-writing campaign." -- Steve Weddle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144862-in-ireland-you-go-to-someone-s-house-and-she-asks</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 14:00:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by C.E. Murphy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144862-in-ireland-you-go-to-someone-s-house-and-she-asks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In Ireland, you go to someone's house, and she asks you if you want a cup of tea. You say no, thank you, you're really just fine. She asks if you're &lt;I&gt;sure&lt;/I&gt;. You say of course you're sure, really, you don't need a thing. Except they pronounce it &lt;I&gt;ting&lt;/I&gt;. You don't need a &lt;I&gt;ting&lt;/I&gt;. Well, she says then, I was going to get myself some anyway, so it would be no trouble. Ah, you say, well, if you were going to get yourself some, I wouldn't mind a spot of tea, at that, so long as it's no trouble and I can give you a hand in the kitchen. Then you go through the whole thing all over again until you both end up in the kitchen drinking tea and chatting. 

In America, someone asks you if you want a cup of tea, you say no, and then you don't get any damned tea.

I liked the Irish way better." -- C.E. Murphy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 11:28:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11177-we-cross-our-bridges-when-we-come-to-them-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 12:44:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11177-we-cross-our-bridges-when-we-come-to-them-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We cross our bridges when we come to them and burn them behind us, with nothing to show for our progress except a memory of the smell of smoke, and a presumption that once our eyes watered." -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
