<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/552179-elgaroo-brenza]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/552179-elgaroo-brenza" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 11:49:46 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/889-the-sky-above-the-port-was-the-color-of-television</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 11:49:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elgaroo add a quote by William Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/889-the-sky-above-the-port-was-the-color-of-television]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sky above the port was the color of television, tuned to a dead channel." -- William Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14885-any-sufficiently-advanced-technology-is-indistinguishable-from-magic</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 11:51:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elgaroo add a quote by Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14885-any-sufficiently-advanced-technology-is-indistinguishable-from-magic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any sufficiently advanced technology is indistinguishable from magic." -- Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115016-there-is-no-intensity-of-love-or-feeling-that-does</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 12:04:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elgaroo add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115016-there-is-no-intensity-of-love-or-feeling-that-does]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no intensity of love or feeling that does not involve the risk of crippling hurt. It is a duty to take this risk, to love and feel without defense or reserve." -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47436-the-whole-educational-and-professional-training-system-is-a-very</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 12:40:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elgaroo add a quote by Noam Chomsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47436-the-whole-educational-and-professional-training-system-is-a-very]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The whole educational and professional training system is a very elaborate filter, which just weeds out people who are too independent, and who think for themselves, and who don't know how to be submissive, and so on -- because they're dysfunctional to the institutions." -- Noam Chomsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114850-the-only-way-to-deal-with-an-unfree-world-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 04:35:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elgaroo add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114850-the-only-way-to-deal-with-an-unfree-world-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only way to deal with an unfree world is to become so absolutely free that your very existence is an act of rebellion." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/514216-admit-it-you-aren-t-like-them-you-re-not-even-close</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 11:51:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elgaroo add a quote by Timothy Leary]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/514216-admit-it-you-aren-t-like-them-you-re-not-even-close]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Admit it. You aren’t like them. You’re not even close. You may occasionally dress yourself up as one of them, watch the same mindless television shows as they do, maybe even eat the same fast food sometimes. But it seems that the more you try to fit in, the more you feel like an outsider, watching the “normal people” as they go about their automatic existences. For every time you say club passwords like “Have a nice day” and “Weather’s awful today, eh?”, you yearn inside to say forbidden things like “Tell me something that makes you cry” or “What do you think deja vu is for?”. Face it, you even want to talk to that girl in the elevator. But what if that girl in the elevator (and the balding man who walks past your cubicle at work) are thinking the same thing? Who knows what you might learn from taking a chance on conversation with a stranger? Everyone carries a piece of the puzzle. Nobody comes into your life by mere coincidence. Trust your instincts. Do the unexpected. Find the others…" -- Timothy Leary]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834719-the-whole-time-i-was-hoping-my-silence-would-fit</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 09:10:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elgaroo add a quote by Anna Akhmatova]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834719-the-whole-time-i-was-hoping-my-silence-would-fit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The whole time I was hoping my silence would fit yours and exclamation marks would gently float across time and space so that boundaries would be crossed; the whole time I was praying you would read my eyes and understand what I was never able to understand. See, we were never about butterflies. We’ve always been about burning stars. All about us is unearthly and radiant." -- Anna Akhmatova]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
