<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/552678-nate-howard]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/552678-nate-howard" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 13:33:47 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9920-the-heart-was-made-to-be-broken</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 13:33:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate add a quote by Oscar Wilde ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9920-the-heart-was-made-to-be-broken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The heart was made to be broken." -- Oscar Wilde ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174533-never-allow-someone-to-be-your-priority-while-allowing-yourself</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 13:34:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174533-never-allow-someone-to-be-your-priority-while-allowing-yourself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never allow someone to be your priority while allowing yourself to be their option." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102207-you-teach-me-now-how-cruel-you-ve-been---cruel</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 13:43:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102207-you-teach-me-now-how-cruel-you-ve-been---cruel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You teach me now how cruel you've been - cruel and false. Why did you despise me? Why did you betray your own heart, Cathy? I have not one word of comfort. You deserve this. You have killed yourself. Yes, you may kiss me, and cry; and wring out my kisses and tears: they'll blight you - they'll damn you. You loved me - what right had you to leave me? What right - answer me - for the poor fancy you felt for Linton? Because misery, and degradation, and death, and nothing that God or Satan could inflict would have parted us, you, of your own will did it. I have no broken your heart - you have broken it; and in breaking it, you have broken mine. So much the worse for me that I am strong. Do I want to live? What kind of living will it be when you - Oh, God! would you like to lie with your soul in the grave?" -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270950-this-life-is-what-you-make-it-no-matter-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 14:05:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270950-this-life-is-what-you-make-it-no-matter-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This life is what you make it. No matter what, you're going to mess up sometimes, it's a universal truth. But the good part is you get to decide how you're going to mess it up. Girls will be your friends - they'll act like it anyway. But just remember, some come, some go. The ones that stay with you through everything - they're your true best friends. Don't let go of them. Also remember, sisters make the best friends in the world. As for lovers, well, they'll come and go too. And baby, I hate to say it, most of them - actually pretty much all of them are going to break your heart, but you can't give up because if you give up, you'll never find your soulmate. You'll never find that half who makes you whole and that goes for everything. Just because you fail once, doesn't mean you're gonna fail at everything. Keep trying, hold on, and always, always, always believe in yourself, because if you don't, then who will, sweetie? So keep your head high, keep your chin up, and most importantly, keep smiling, because life's a beautiful thing and there's so much to smile about." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18322-one-does-not-become-enlightened-by-imagining-figures-of-light</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 20:38:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate add a quote by Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18322-one-does-not-become-enlightened-by-imagining-figures-of-light]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One does not become enlightened by imagining figures of light, but by making the darkness conscious." -- Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51154-where-love-rules-there-is-no-will-to-power-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 20:40:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate add a quote by Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51154-where-love-rules-there-is-no-will-to-power-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where love rules, there is no will to power, and where power predominates, love is lacking. The one is the shadow of the other." -- Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248440-through-pride-we-are-ever-deceiving-ourselves-but-deep-down</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 20:41:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate add a quote by Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248440-through-pride-we-are-ever-deceiving-ourselves-but-deep-down]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Through pride we are ever deceiving ourselves. But deep down below the surface of the average conscience a still, small voice says to us, something is out of tune. " -- Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67459-art-is-a-kind-of-innate-drive-that-seizes-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 20:43:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate add a quote by Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67459-art-is-a-kind-of-innate-drive-that-seizes-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Art is a kind of innate drive that seizes a human being and makes him its instrument. To perform this difficult office it is sometimes necessary for him to sacrifice happiness and everything that makes life worth living for the ordinary human being." -- Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61979-knowing-your-own-darkness-is-the-best-method-for-dealing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 20:44:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate add a quote by Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61979-knowing-your-own-darkness-is-the-best-method-for-dealing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Knowing your own darkness is the best method for dealing with the darknesses of other people." -- Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1716-travel-is-fatal-to-prejudice-bigotry-and-narrow-mindedness-and-many</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2013 04:53:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1716-travel-is-fatal-to-prejudice-bigotry-and-narrow-mindedness-and-many]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Travel is fatal to prejudice, bigotry, and narrow-mindedness, and many of our people need it sorely on these accounts. Broad, wholesome, charitable views of men and things cannot be acquired by vegetating in one little corner of the earth all one's lifetime." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169599-i-ve-never-been-lonely-i-ve-been-in-a-room---</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 17:27:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169599-i-ve-never-been-lonely-i-ve-been-in-a-room---]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've never been lonely. I've been in a room -- I've felt suicidal. I've been depressed. I've felt awful -- awful beyond all -- but I never felt that one other person could enter that room and cure what was bothering me...or that any number of people could enter that room. In other words, loneliness is something I've never been bothered with because I've always had this terrible itch for solitude. It's being at a party, or at a stadium full of people cheering for something, that I might feel loneliness. I'll quote Ibsen, &quot;The strongest men are the most alone.&quot; I've never thought, &quot;Well, some beautiful blonde will come in here and give me a fuck-job, rub my balls, and I'll feel good.&quot; No, that won't help. You know the typical crowd, &quot;Wow, it's Friday night, what are you going to do? Just sit there?&quot; Well, yeah. Because there's nothing out there. It's stupidity. Stupid people mingling with stupid people. Let them stupidify themselves. I've never been bothered with the need to rush out into the night. I hid in bars, because I didn't want to hide in factories. That's all. Sorry for all the millions, but I've never been lonely. I like myself. I'm the best form of entertainment I have. Let's drink more wine!" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11589-i-have-absolutely-no-pleasure-in-the-stimulants-in-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 17:28:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11589-i-have-absolutely-no-pleasure-in-the-stimulants-in-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have absolutely no pleasure in the stimulants in which I sometimes so madly indulge. It has not been in the pursuit of pleasure that I have periled life and reputation and reason. It has been the desperate attempt to escape from torturing memories, from a sense of insupportable loneliness and a dread of some strange impending doom." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108135-all-great-and-precious-things-are-lonely</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 17:28:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nate add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108135-all-great-and-precious-things-are-lonely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All great and precious things are lonely." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
