<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/554963-cheryl]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/554963-cheryl" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 09:26:46 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350-i-with-a-deeper-instinct-choose-a-man-who-compels</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 09:26:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cheryl add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350-i-with-a-deeper-instinct-choose-a-man-who-compels]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I, with a deeper instinct, choose a man who compels my strength, who makes enormous demands on me, who does not doubt my courage or my toughness, who does not believe me naïve or innocent, who has the courage to treat me like a woman." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2846-and-the-day-came-when-the-risk-to-remain-tight</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 09:26:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cheryl add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2846-and-the-day-came-when-the-risk-to-remain-tight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the day came when the risk to remain tight in a bud was more painful than the risk it took to blossom." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45328-there-are-two-ways-to-reach-me-by-way-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 09:29:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cheryl add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45328-there-are-two-ways-to-reach-me-by-way-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two ways to reach me: by way of kisses or by way of the imagination. But there is a hierarchy: the kisses alone don't work." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105928-you-live-like-this-sheltered-in-a-delicate-world-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 09:30:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cheryl add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105928-you-live-like-this-sheltered-in-a-delicate-world-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You live like this, sheltered, in a delicate world, and you believe you are living. Then you read a book… or you take a trip… and you discover that you are not living, that you are hibernating. The symptoms of hibernating are easily detectable: first, restlessness. The second symptom (when hibernating becomes dangerous and might degenerate into death): absence of pleasure. That is all. It appears like an innocuous illness. Monotony, boredom, death. Millions live like this (or die like this) without knowing it. They work in offices. They drive a car. They picnic with their families. They raise children. And then some shock treatment takes place, a person, a book, a song, and it awakens them and saves them from death. Some never awaken." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119899-i-do-not-want-to-be-the-leader-i-refuse</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 09:32:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cheryl add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119899-i-do-not-want-to-be-the-leader-i-refuse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not want to be the leader. I refuse to be the leader. I want to live darkly and richly in my femaleness. I want a man lying over me, always over me. His will, his pleasure, his desire, his life, his work, his sexuality the touchstone, the command, my pivot. I don’t mind working, holding my ground intellectually, artistically; but as a woman, oh, God, as a woman I want to be dominated. I don’t mind being told to stand on my own feet, not to cling, be all that I am capable of doing, but I am going to be pursued, fucked, possessed by the will of a male at his time, his bidding." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99661-the-truly-faithless-one-is-the-one-who-makes-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 09:33:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cheryl add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99661-the-truly-faithless-one-is-the-one-who-makes-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truly faithless one is the one who makes love to only a fraction of you. And denies the rest." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162491-do-you-know-what-i-would-answer-to-someone-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 09:36:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cheryl add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162491-do-you-know-what-i-would-answer-to-someone-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you know what I would answer to someone who asked me for a description of myself, in a hurry? This:

??  !!

For indeed my life is a perpetual question mark--my thirst for books, my observations of people, all tend to satisfy a great, overwhelming desire to know, to understand, to find an answer to a million questions. And gradually the answers are revealed, many things are explained, and above all, many things are given names and described, and my restlessness is subdued. Then I become an exclamatory person, clapping my hands to the immense surprises the world holds for me, and falling from one ecstasy into another. I have the habit of peeping and prying and listening and seeking--passionate curiosity and expectation. But I have also the habit of being surprised, the habit of being filled with wonder and satisfaction each time I stumble on some wondrous thing. The first habit could make me a philosopher or a cynic or perhaps a humorist. But the other habit destroys all the delicate foundations, and I find each day that I am still...only a Woman!" -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127077-there-is-not-one-big-cosmic-meaning-for-all-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 09:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cheryl add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127077-there-is-not-one-big-cosmic-meaning-for-all-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is not one big cosmic meaning for all; there is only the meaning we each give to our life, an individual meaning, an individual plot, like an individual novel, a book for each person." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151671-submission-is-not-about-authority-and-it-is-not-obedience</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 09:49:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cheryl add a quote by Wm. Paul Young]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151671-submission-is-not-about-authority-and-it-is-not-obedience]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Submission is not about authority and it is not obedience; it is all about relationships of love and respect." -- Wm. Paul Young]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
