<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/555726-philip]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/555726-philip" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2008 20:10:23 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13205-what-being-in-the-war-and-being-in-the-army</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2008 20:10:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philip add a quote by Marianne Wiggins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13205-what-being-in-the-war-and-being-in-the-army]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What being in the War and being in the Army had shown him was that people tend naturally toward light, toward its source, as sunflowers do in a field.  
People lean, either in their dreams or in their actions, toward that place where they suspect their inner lights are coming from.  Whether they call it God or conscience or the manual of Army protocol, people sublime toward where their inner fire burns, and given enough fuel for thought and a level playing field to dream on, anyone can leave a fingerprint on the blank of history.  That's what 
Fos believed." -- Marianne Wiggins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13208-you-fight-your-superficiality-your-shallowness-so-as-to-try</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2008 20:16:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philip add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13208-you-fight-your-superficiality-your-shallowness-so-as-to-try]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You fight your superficiality, your shallowness, so as to try to come at people without unreal expectations, without an overload of bias or hope or arrogance, as untanklike as you can be, sans cannon and machine guns and steel plating half a foot thick; you come at them unmenacingly on your own ten toes instead of tearing up the turf with your caterpillar treads, take them on with an open mind, as equals, man to man, as we used to say, and yet you never fail to get them wrong.  You might as well have the brain of a tank.  You get them wrong before you meet them, while you're anticipating meeting them; you get them wrong while you're with them; and then you go home to tell somebody else about the meeting and you get them all wrong again.  Since the same generally goes for them with you, the whole thing is really a dazzling illusion. ...  The fact remains that getting people right is not what living is all about anyway.  It's getting them wrong that is living, getting them wrong and wrong and wrong and then, on careful reconsideration, getting them wrong again.  That's how we know we're alive:  we're wrong.  Maybe the best thing would be to forget being right or wrong about people and just go along for the ride.  But if you can do that -- well, lucky you." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17884-and-as-lindbergh-s-election-couldn-t-have-made-clearer-to-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 18:56:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philip add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17884-and-as-lindbergh-s-election-couldn-t-have-made-clearer-to-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And as Lindbergh's election couldn't have made clearer to me, the unfolding of the unforeseen was everything. Turned wrong way round, the relentless unforeseen was what we schoolchildren studied as &quot;History,&quot; harmless history, where everything unexpected in its own time is chronicled on the page as inevitable.  The terror of the unforeseen is what the science of history hides, turning a disaster into an epic." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27356-other-freshmen-were-already-moving-into-their-dormitory-rooms-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 05:49:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philip add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27356-other-freshmen-were-already-moving-into-their-dormitory-rooms-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Other freshmen were already moving into their dormitory rooms when we arrived, with their parents helping haul. I saw boxes of paperbacks, stereo equipment, Dylan albums and varnished acoustic guitars, home-knitted afghans, none as brilliant as mine, Janis posters, Bowie posters, Day-Glo bedsheets, hacky sacks, stuffed bears. But as we carried my trunk up two flights of stairs terror invaded me. Although I was studying French because I dreamed of going to Paris, I actually dreaded leaving home, and in the end my parents did not want me to leave, either. But this is how children are sacrificed into their futures: I had to go, and here I was. We walked back down the stairs. I was too numb to cry, but I watched my mother and father as they stood beside the car and waved. That moment is a still image; I can call it up as if it were a photograph. My father, so thin and athletic, looked almost frail with shock, while my mother, whose beauty was still remarkable, and who was known on the reservation for her silence and reserve, had left off her characteristic gravity. Her face and my father's were naked with love. It wasn't something thatwe talked about—love. But they allowed me this one clear look at it. It blazed from them. And then they left." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28040-that-solar-hue-that-variegation-of-gleam-and-shade-made</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 15:35:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philip add a quote by Giuseppe Tomasi di Lampedusa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28040-that-solar-hue-that-variegation-of-gleam-and-shade-made]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That solar hue, that variegation of gleam and shade, made Don Fabrizio's heart ache as he stood black and stiff in a doorway:  this eminently patrician room reminded him of country things; the chromatic scale was the same as that of the vast wheat fields around Donnafugata, rapt, begging pity from the tyrannous sun; in this room, too, as on his estates in mid-August, the harvest had been gathered long before, stacked elsewhere, leaving, as here, a sole reminder in the color of the stubble burned and useless now.  The notes of the waltz in the warm air seemed to him but a stylization of the incessant winds harping their own sorrows on the parched surfaces, today, yesterday, tomorrow, forever and forever.  The crowd of dancers, among whom he could count so many near to him in blood if not in heart, began to seem unreal, made up of that material from which are woven lapsed memories, more elusive even than the stuff of disturbing dreams." -- Giuseppe Tomasi di Lampedusa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5850-human-speech-is-like-a-cracked-kettle-on-which-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 07:24:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philip add a quote by Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5850-human-speech-is-like-a-cracked-kettle-on-which-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human speech is like a cracked kettle on which we tap crude rhythms for bears to dance to, while we long to make music that will melt the stars." -- Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6856-if-one-cannot-enjoy-reading-a-book-over-and-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 19:05:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philip add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6856-if-one-cannot-enjoy-reading-a-book-over-and-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If one cannot enjoy reading a book over and over again, there is no use in reading it at all." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46272-ink-runs-from-the-corners-of-my-mouth-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 15:12:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philip add a quote by Mark Strand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46272-ink-runs-from-the-corners-of-my-mouth-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ink runs from the corners of my mouth.
There is no happiness like mine.
I have been eating poetry." -- Mark Strand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2008 19:20:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philip add a quote by William Nicholson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We read to know we're not alone." -- William Nicholson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108063-and-what-amazes-me-as-i-hit-the-motorway-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 14:36:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philip add a quote by Anne Enright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108063-and-what-amazes-me-as-i-hit-the-motorway-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And what amazes me as I hit the motorway is not the fact that everyone loses someone, but that everyone loves someone. It seems like such a massive waste of energy -- and we all do it, all the people beetling along between the white lines, merging, converging, overtaking. We each love someone, even though they will die. And we keep loving them, even when they are not there to love any more. And there is no logic or use to any of this, that I can see." -- Anne Enright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98507-it-is-certain-in-any-case-that-ignorance-allied-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2010 20:52:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philip add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98507-it-is-certain-in-any-case-that-ignorance-allied-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is certain, in any case, that ignorance, allied with power, is the most ferocious enemy justice can have." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277823-when-the-day-of-judgment-dawns-and-the-great-conquerers</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:38:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philip add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277823-when-the-day-of-judgment-dawns-and-the-great-conquerers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the Day of Judgment dawns and the great conquerers and lawyers and statesmen come to receive their rewards -- their crowns, their laurels, their names carved indelibly upon imperishable marble -- the Almighty will turn to Peter and will say, not without a certain envy when he sees us coming with our books under our arms, &quot;Look, these need no reward. We have nothing to give them here. They have loved reading." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143535-the-world-s-a-headmaster-who-works-on-your-faults-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 18:30:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philip add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143535-the-world-s-a-headmaster-who-works-on-your-faults-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world's a headmaster who works on your faults. I don't mean in a mystical or Jesus way. More how you'll keep tripping over a hidden step, over and over, till you finally understand: Watch out for that step! Everything that's wrong with us, if we're too selfish or too Yessir, Nosir, Three bags full sir or too anything, that's a hidden step. Either you suffer the consequences of not noticing your fault forever or, one day, you do notice it, and fix it. Joke is, once you get it into your brain about that hidden step and think, Hey, life isn't such a shithouse after all again, then BUMP! Down you go, a whole new flight of hidden steps.
There are always more." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/450835-from-p-40-of-signet-edition-of-thomas-wolfe-s-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 18:34:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Philip add a quote by Thomas Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/450835-from-p-40-of-signet-edition-of-thomas-wolfe-s-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From p. 40 of Signet Edition of Thomas Wolfe's _You Can't Go Home Again_ (1940):

Some things will never change. Some things will always be the same. Lean down your ear upon the earth and listen.

The voice of forest water in the night, a woman's laughter in the dark, the clean, hard rattle of raked gravel, the cricketing stitch of midday in hot meadows, the delicate web of children's voices in bright air--these things will never change.

The glitter of sunlight on roughened water, the glory of the stars, the innocence of morning, the smell of the sea in harbors, the feathery blur and smoky buddings of young boughs, and something there that comes and goes and never can be captured, the thorn of spring, the sharp and tongueless cry--these things will always be the same.

All things belonging to the earth will never change--the leaf, the blade, the flower, the wind that cries and sleeps and wakes again, the trees whose stiff arms clash and tremble in the dark, and the dust of lovers long since buried in the earth--all things proceeding from the earth to seasons, all things that lapse and change and come again upon the earth--these things will always be the same, for they come up from the earth that never changes, they go back into the earth that lasts forever. Only the earth endures, but it endures forever.

The tarantula, the adder, and the asp will also never change. Pain and death will always be the same. But under the pavements trembling like a pulse, under the buildings trembling like a cry, under the waste of time, under the hoof of the beast above the broken bones of cities, there will be something growing like a flower, something bursting from the earth again, forever deathless, faithful, coming into life again like April." -- Thomas Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
