<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/55815-yvette]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/55815-yvette" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 08:08:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88706-heinrich-heine-so-loosened-the-corsets-of-the-german-language</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 08:08:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvette add a quote by Karl Kraus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88706-heinrich-heine-so-loosened-the-corsets-of-the-german-language]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Heinrich Heine so loosened the corsets of the German language that today every little salesman can fondle her breasts." -- Karl Kraus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68727-don-t-use-words-too-big-for-the-subject-don-t-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 09:55:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvette add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68727-don-t-use-words-too-big-for-the-subject-don-t-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't use words too big for the subject. Don't say infinitely when you mean very; otherwise you'll have no word left when you want to talk about something really infinite." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126712-i-am-invisible-understand-simply-because-people-refuse-to-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 05:59:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvette add a quote by Ralph Ellison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126712-i-am-invisible-understand-simply-because-people-refuse-to-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am invisible, understand, simply because people refuse to see me. Like the bodiless heads you see sometimes in circus sideshows, it is as though I have been surrounded by mirrors of hard, distorting glass. When they approach me they see only my surroundings, themselves or figments of their imagination, indeed, everything and anything except me." -- Ralph Ellison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2294-for-beauty-is-nothing-but-the-beginning-of-terror-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 11:23:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvette add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2294-for-beauty-is-nothing-but-the-beginning-of-terror-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For beauty is nothing but the beginning of terror
which we are barely able to endure, and it amazes us so,
because it serenely disdains to destroy us.
Every angel is terrible." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155038-crying-is-all-right-in-its-way-while-it-lasts</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 10:27:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvette add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155038-crying-is-all-right-in-its-way-while-it-lasts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Crying is all right in its way while it lasts. But you have to stop sooner or later, and then you still have to decide what to do." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27486-what-draws-people-to-be-friends-is-that-they-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 10:28:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvette add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27486-what-draws-people-to-be-friends-is-that-they-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What draws people to be friends is that they see the same truth. They share it." -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241582-i-have-learned-now-that-while-those-who-speak-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 10:28:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvette add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241582-i-have-learned-now-that-while-those-who-speak-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have learned now that while those who speak about one's miseries usually hurt, those who keep silence hurt more." -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289205-love-is-never-any-better-than-the-lover-wicked-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2014 15:45:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvette add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289205-love-is-never-any-better-than-the-lover-wicked-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is never any better than the lover. Wicked people love wickedly, violent people love violently, weak people love weakly, stupid people love stupidly, but the love of a free man is never safe. There is no gift for the beloved. The lover alone possesses his gift of love. The loved one is shorn, neutralized, frozen in the glare of the lover’s inward eye." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100787-all-of-our-waste-which-we-dumped-on-her-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2014 15:45:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvette add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100787-all-of-our-waste-which-we-dumped-on-her-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All of our waste which we dumped on her and which she absorbed. And all of our beauty, which was hers first and which she gave to us. All of us--all who knew her--felt so wholesome after we cleaned ourselves on her. We were so beautiful when we stood astride her ugliness. her simplicity decorated us, her guilt sanctified us, her pain made us glow with health, her awkwardness made us think we has a sense of humor. Her inarticulateness made us believe we were eloquent. Her poverty kept us generous. Even her waking dreams we used--to silence our own nightmares. And she let us, and thereby deserved our contempt. We honed our egos on her, padded our characters with her frailty, and yawned in the fantasy of our strength.

And fantasy it was, for we were not strong, only aggressive; we were not free, merely licensed; we were not compassionate, we were polite; not good, but well behaved. We courted death in order to call ourselves brave, and hid like thieves from life. We substituted good grammar for intellect; we switched habits to simulate maturity; we rearranged lies and called it truth, seeing in the new pattern of an old idea the Revelation and the Word." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151615-anger-is-better-there-is-a-sense-of-being-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2014 15:46:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvette add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151615-anger-is-better-there-is-a-sense-of-being-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anger is better. There is a sense of being in anger. A reality and presence. An awareness of worth. It is a lovely surging." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27421-your-silence-will-not-protect-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 10:57:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvette add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27421-your-silence-will-not-protect-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your silence will not protect you." -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161176-after-the-egyptian-and-indian-the-greek-and-roman-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 16:24:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvette add a quote by W.E.B. DuBois]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161176-after-the-egyptian-and-indian-the-greek-and-roman-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After the Egyptian and Indian, the Greek and Roman, the Teuton and Mongolian, the Negro is a sort of seventh son, born with a veil, and gifted with second-sight in this American world,—a world which yields him no true self-consciousness, but only lets him see himself through the revelation of the other world. It is a peculiar sensation, this double-consciousness, this sense of always looking at one’s self through the eyes of others, of measuring one by the tape of a world that looks on in amused contempt and pity. One ever feels his two-ness,—an American, a Negro... two thoughts, two unreconciled strivings; two warring ideals in one dark body, whose dogged strength alone keeps it from being torn asunder.

The history of the American Negro is the history of this strife, — this longing to attain self-conscious manhood, to merge his double self into a better and truer self." -- W.E.B. DuBois]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/760755-i-sit-with-shakespeare-and-he-winces-not-across-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 16:25:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvette add a quote by W.E.B. Du Bois]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/760755-i-sit-with-shakespeare-and-he-winces-not-across-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I sit with Shakespeare, and he winces not. Across the color line I move arm and arm with Balzac and Dumas, where smiling men and welcoming women glide in gilded halls. From out of the caves of evening that swing between the strong-limbed Earth and the tracery of stars, I summon Aristotle and Aurelius and what soul I will, and they come all graciously with no scorn nor condescension. So, wed with Truth, I dwell above the veil. Is this the life you grudge us, O knightly America? Is this the life you long to change into the dull red hideousness of Georgia? Are you so afraid lest peering from this high Pisgah, between Philistine and Amalekite, we sight the Promised Land?" -- W.E.B. Du Bois]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12746-the-power-of-the-ballot-we-need-in-sheer-self-defense</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 16:25:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Yvette add a quote by W.E.B. Du Bois]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12746-the-power-of-the-ballot-we-need-in-sheer-self-defense]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The power of the ballot we need in sheer self-defense, - else what shall save us from a second slavery?" -- W.E.B. Du Bois]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
