<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/558368-deana]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/558368-deana" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 09:44:10 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278314-books-are-my-friends-where-it-s-okay-to-be-silent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 09:44:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Julie Gregory]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278314-books-are-my-friends-where-it-s-okay-to-be-silent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are my friends, where it's okay to be silent, where you're not a freak if you don't want to get drunk, peel out in the parking lot, tip cows." -- Julie Gregory]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277981-but-something-worse-can-happen-to-the-person-who-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2010 09:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Jane Jakeman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277981-but-something-worse-can-happen-to-the-person-who-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...But something worse can happen to the person who is betrayed.&quot;
&quot;What? What could possibly happen to me that is worse?&quot;
The older man stared at the younger, and then said pityingly, &quot;You may learn treachery from it." -- Jane Jakeman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136261-i-start-to-see-that-i-surround-myself-with-broken</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 09:37:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Julie Gregory]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136261-i-start-to-see-that-i-surround-myself-with-broken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I start to see that I surround myself with broken people; more broken than me. Ah, yes, let me count your cracks. Let's see, one hundred, two... yes, you'll do nicely. A cracked companion makes me look more whole, gives me something outside myself to care for. When I'm with whole, healed people I feel my own cracks, the shatters, the insanities of dislocation in myself." -- Julie Gregory]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278312-but-dad-you-were-a-grown-man-you-have-got</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 09:42:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Julie Gregory]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278312-but-dad-you-were-a-grown-man-you-have-got]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But Dad, you were a grown man, you have got to take responsibility for what you did, too! I mean, you made me eat [snotty] Kleenex, Dad! For Christ's sake, you can't do that to a little girl! You have got to say you're sorry for the stuff you did as a grown man!'
'Well,' Dad snorts, 'I musta done something right! 'Cause you never left any snot rags lying around the house again, now, did you?" -- Julie Gregory]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57729-nobody-around-here-had-ever-seen-a-lady-beekeeper-till</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2010 12:12:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57729-nobody-around-here-had-ever-seen-a-lady-beekeeper-till]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody around here had ever seen a lady beekeeper till her. She liked to tell everybody that women made the best beekeepers, 'cause they have a special ability built into them to love creatures that sting. It comes from years of loving children and husbands." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12290-we-are-so-limited-you-have-to-use-the-same</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2010 12:12:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12290-we-are-so-limited-you-have-to-use-the-same]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are so limited, you have to use the same word for loving Rosaleen as you do for loving Coke with peanuts. Isn't that a shame we don't have many more ways to say it?" -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280461-as-i-squatted-on-the-grass-at-the-edge-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2010 12:17:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280461-as-i-squatted-on-the-grass-at-the-edge-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As I squatted on the grass at the edge of the woods, the pee felt hot between my legs. I watched in puddle in the dirt, the smell of it rising into the night. There was no difference between my piss and June's. That's what i thought when I looked at the dark circle on the ground. Piss is Piss." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280462-my-mother-was-a-good-catholic----she-went-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2010 12:19:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280462-my-mother-was-a-good-catholic----she-went-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My mother was a good Catholic -- she went to mass twice a week at St. Mary's in Richmond, but my father was an Orthodox Eclectic." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13753-people-who-claim-that-they-re-evil-are-usually-no-worse</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 20:15:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13753-people-who-claim-that-they-re-evil-are-usually-no-worse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People who claim that they're evil are usually no worse than the rest of us... It's people who claim that they're good, or any way  better than the rest of us, that you have to be wary of." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299742-i-cannot-love-two-people-at-once-becky-told-william</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2010 19:11:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Nancy Clark]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299742-i-cannot-love-two-people-at-once-becky-told-william]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot love two people at once,&quot; Becky told William.
&quot;No. You can't,&quot; he said.
&quot;Well, then. That's all right, then. Of course one can't, I mean to say, I wasn't sure you hadn't mistaken any aspect of our friendship for something else.&quot; Her heart stood still and it raced, all at once.
&quot;Because you don't love him,&quot; William said." -- Nancy Clark]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299744-what-a-lucky-girl-you-are-to-have-this-opportunity</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2010 19:19:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Nancy Clark]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299744-what-a-lucky-girl-you-are-to-have-this-opportunity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a lucky girl you are to have this opportunity to live in one of the world's great cities at this most fascinating point in its long, rich history, they had said. Little Becky had known enough not to ask if there was going to be a Banana Republic or a Gap there, or a Tower Records or a Starbucks or a Tweeters or a Blockbuster or a Super CVS or a Saks. Her mother only mentioned museums and concert halls and churches and architecture, so Little Becky was quite sure there was no room left in Prague for anything good to be built." -- Nancy Clark]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299745-they-were-walking-along-a-roadway-of-great-slabs-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:38:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Nancy Clark]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299745-they-were-walking-along-a-roadway-of-great-slabs-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They were walking along a roadway of great slabs of stone set down one after another, the beginning and end of which they could take in at a glance, a road rising from and heading toward nowhere now.
&quot;You can't get there from here,&quot; William said, using a Down East accent. &quot;Anymore.&quot; Maine, they thought of Maine, then. Evidently this truncated road could still carry them as far away and as long ago as that." -- Nancy Clark]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313740-a-family-in-my-sister-s-neighborhood-was-recently-stricken-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 14:41:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313740-a-family-in-my-sister-s-neighborhood-was-recently-stricken-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A family in my sister's neighborhood was recently stricken with a double tragedy, when both the young mother and her three-year-old son were diagnosed with cancer. When Catherine told me about this, I could only say, shocked, &quot;Dear God, that family needs grace.&quot; She replied firmly, &quot;That family needs casseroles,&quot; and proceeded to organize the entire neighborhood into bringing that family dinner, in shifts, every single night, for an entire year. I do not know if my sister fully recognizes that this IS grace." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322009-the-pigeon-had-learned-something-about-women-from-his-eight</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 11:56:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Brigid Pasulka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322009-the-pigeon-had-learned-something-about-women-from-his-eight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[The Pigeon had learned something about [women] from his eight sisters, and if over the years he had absorbed only this one thing, it would stand as vindication that a boy does not suffer needlessly from growing up in a house with eight sisters. That thing was that a woman's heart is not bought by the currency of a man's emotion for her. A woman's heart is won over by her own feelings for herself when he just happens to be around ..." -- Brigid Pasulka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322010-normally-i-give-permission-to-take-my-daughter-for-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 11:58:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Brigid Pasulka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322010-normally-i-give-permission-to-take-my-daughter-for-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Normally I give permission to take my daughter for a walk after only the building of a wall and a stone pathway.' He smiled. 'For future reference.'

'But, Pan, I knew after the first week that a walk was not the only thing I would request,' the Pigeon said, smiling, 'and winter will be here soon." -- Brigid Pasulka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322011-if-everyone-knows-so-much-about-it-why-do-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 11:59:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Brigid Pasulka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322011-if-everyone-knows-so-much-about-it-why-do-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If everyone knows so much about it, why do they need to make a documentary?" -- Brigid Pasulka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 08:20:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44541-laws-and-principles-are-not-for-the-times-when-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 11:49:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44541-laws-and-principles-are-not-for-the-times-when-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Laws and principles are not for the times when there is no temptation: they are for such moments as this, when body and soul rise in mutiny against their rigour ... If at my convenience I might break them, what would be their worth?" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316159-what-i-really-fear-is-time-that-s-the-devil-whipping</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 20:17:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Tom Rachman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316159-what-i-really-fear-is-time-that-s-the-devil-whipping]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I really fear is time. That's the devil: whipping us on when we'd rather loll, so the present sprints by, impossible to grasp, and all is suddenly past, a past that won't hold still, that slides into these inauthentic tales. My past- it doesn't feel real in the slightest. The person who inhabited it is not me. It's as if the present me is constantly dissolving. There's that line from Heraclitus: 'No man steps in the same river twice, for it is not the same river and he is not the same man.' That's quite right. We enjoy this illusion of continuity, and we call it memory. Which explains, perhaps, why our worst fear isn't the end of life but the end of memories." -- Tom Rachman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316173-you-can-t-dread-what-you-can-t-experience-the-only-death</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 20:17:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Tom Rachman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316173-you-can-t-dread-what-you-can-t-experience-the-only-death]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can’t dread what you can’t experience. The only death we experience is that of other people. That’s as bad as it gets. And that’s bad enough, surely." -- Tom Rachman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331257-literally-this-word-should-be-deleted-all-too-often-actions</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 20:18:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Tom Rachman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331257-literally-this-word-should-be-deleted-all-too-often-actions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["literally: This word should be deleted. All too often, actions described as “literally” did not happen at all. As in, “He literally jumped out of his skin.” No, he did not. Though if he literally had, I’d suggest raising the element and proposing the piece for page one. Inserting “literally” willy-nilly reinforces the notion that breathless nitwits lurk within this newsroom. Eliminate on sight—the usage, not the nitwits. The nitwits are to be captured" -- Tom Rachman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/375815-i-have-to-wonder-if-you-re-not-being-slightly-naive</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 20:22:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Tom Rachman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/375815-i-have-to-wonder-if-you-re-not-being-slightly-naive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have to wonder if you're not being slightly naive here. I mean, are you saying that you want nothing for people? You have no motives? Everybody has motives. Name the person, the circumstances, I'll name the motive. Even saints have motives -- to feel like saints, probably. ... But still, the point of any relationship is obtaining something from another person." -- Tom Rachman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139297-everybody-is-so-terribly-sensitive-about-the-things-they-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 20:23:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Norton Juster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139297-everybody-is-so-terribly-sensitive-about-the-things-they-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody is so terribly sensitive about the things they know best." -- Norton Juster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25001-but-why-do-only-unimportant-things-asked-milo-who-suddenly</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 20:24:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Norton Juster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25001-but-why-do-only-unimportant-things-asked-milo-who-suddenly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But why do only unimportant things?&quot; asked Milo, who suddenly remembered how much time he spent each day doing them.

&quot;Think of all the trouble it saves,&quot; the man explained, and his face looked as if he'd be grinning an evil grin--if he could grin at all. &quot;If you only do the easy and useless jobs, you'll never have to worry about the important ones which are so difficult. You just won't have the time. For there's always something to do to keep you from what you really should be doing, and if it weren't for that dreadful magic staff, you'd never know how much time you were wasting." -- Norton Juster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377711-i-hate-all-electronic-toys-cell-phones-e-mail-palmpilots-handheld</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 09:31:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by David Skibbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377711-i-hate-all-electronic-toys-cell-phones-e-mail-palmpilots-handheld]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hate all electronic toys: cell phones, e-mail, PalmPilots, handheld Global Positioning System equipment, and the whole raft of gadgets that intrude on solitude.

When I was a kid I used to disappear into the woods all day. Now I can walk in the wilderness without wasting my valuable time. As I hike along I can call anyone in the world, schedule an appointment, take a picture of me standing next to a tree and then send the person a map so he or she can join me there. Solitude has been snuffed out." -- David Skibbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273399-that-s-the-good-part-of-dying-when-you-ve-nothing-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 21:23:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273399-that-s-the-good-part-of-dying-when-you-ve-nothing-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's the good part of dying; when you've nothing to lose, you run any risk you want." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121445-the-world-is-a-looking-glass-and-gives-back-to-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 09:25:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by William Makepeace Thackeray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121445-the-world-is-a-looking-glass-and-gives-back-to-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is a looking-glass, and gives back to every man the reflection of his own face. Frown at it, and it will in turn look sourly upon you; laugh at it and with it, and it is a jolly kind companion; and so let all young persons take their choice." -- William Makepeace Thackeray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258358-if-you-are-not-allowed-to-touch-the-heart-sometimes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 09:25:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by William Makepeace Thackeray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258358-if-you-are-not-allowed-to-touch-the-heart-sometimes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["if you are not allowed to touch the heart sometimes in spite of syntax, and are not to be loved until you all know the difference between trimeter and trameter, may all Poetry go to the deuce, and every schoolmaster perish miserably!" -- William Makepeace Thackeray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382708-indeed-for-my-own-part-though-i-have-been-repeatedly</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 09:30:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by William Makepeace Thackeray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382708-indeed-for-my-own-part-though-i-have-been-repeatedly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Indeed, for my own part, though I have been repeatedly told by persons for whom I have the greatest respect, that Miss Brown is an insignificant chit, and Mrs. White has nothing but her petit minois chiffonne, and Mrs. Black has not a word to say for herself; yet I know that I have had the most delightful conversations with Mrs. Black (of course, my dear Madam, they are inviolable): I see all the men in a cluster round Mrs. White's chair: all the young fellows battling to dance with Miss Brown; and so I am tempted to think that to be despised by her sex is a very great compliment to a woman." -- William Makepeace Thackeray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382709-i-regularly-frequent-st-george-s-hanover-square-during-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 09:34:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deana add a quote by William Makepeace Thackeray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382709-i-regularly-frequent-st-george-s-hanover-square-during-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["... I regularly frequent St. George';s, Hanover Square, during the genteel marriage season; and though I have never seen the bridegroom's male friends give way to tears, or the beadles and officiating clergy in any way affected, yet it is not at all uncommon to see women who are not in the least concerned in the operations going on -- old ladies who are long past marrying, stout middle-aged females with plenty of sons and daughters, let alone pretty young creatures in pink bonnets, who are on their promotion, and may naturally taken an interest in the ceremony -- I say it is quite common to see the women present piping, sobbing, sniffling; hiding their little faces in their little useless pocket-handkerchiefs; and heaving, old and young, with emotion." -- William Makepeace Thackeray]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
