<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/55890-sammie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/55890-sammie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 05:14:59 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19421-if-you-can-t-explain-it-to-a-six-year-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 05:14:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sammie add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19421-if-you-can-t-explain-it-to-a-six-year-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can't explain it to a six year old, you don't understand it yourself." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 05:16:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sammie add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3312-women-and-cats-will-do-as-they-please-and-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 05:17:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sammie add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3312-women-and-cats-will-do-as-they-please-and-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Women and cats will do as they please, and men and dogs should relax and get used to the idea." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140404-take-sides-always-take-sides-you-will-sometimes-be-wrong</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 05:23:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sammie add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140404-take-sides-always-take-sides-you-will-sometimes-be-wrong]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Take sides! Always take sides! You will sometimes be wrong - but the man who refuses to take sides must always be wrong." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171579-when-van-gogh-was-a-young-man-in-his-early</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 15:08:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sammie add a quote by Brenda Ueland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171579-when-van-gogh-was-a-young-man-in-his-early]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When Van Gogh was a young man in his early twenties, he was in London studying to be a clergyman. He had no thought of being an artist at all. he sat in his cheap little room writing a letter to his younger brother in Holland, whom he loved very much. He looked out his window at a watery twilight, a thin lampost, a star, and he said in his letter something like this: &quot;it is so beautiful I must show you how it looks.&quot; And then on his cheap ruled note paper, he made the most beautiful, tender, little drawing of it. 

When I read this letter of Van Gogh's it comforted me very much and seemed to throw a clear light on the whole road of Art. Before, I thought that to produce a work of painting or literature, you scowled and thought long and ponderously and weighed everything solemnly and learned everything that all artists had ever done aforetime, and what their influences and schools were, and you were extremely careful about *design* and *balance* and getting *interesting planes* into your painting, and avoided, with the most astringent severity, showing the faintest *acedemical* tendency, and were strictly modern. And so on and so on.

But the moment I read Van Gogh's letter I knew what art was, and the creative impulse. It is a feeling of love and enthusiasm for something, and in a direct, simple, passionate and true way, you try to show this beauty in things to others, by drawing it.

And Van Gogh's little drawing on the cheap note paper was a work of art because he loved the sky and the frail lamppost against it so seriously that he made the drawing with the most exquisite conscientiousness and care.  " -- Brenda Ueland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266621-practice-giving-things-away-not-just-things-you-don-t-care</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 15:13:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sammie add a quote by Huston Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266621-practice-giving-things-away-not-just-things-you-don-t-care]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Practice giving things away, not just things you don't care about, but things you do like.  Remember, it is not the size of a gift, it is its quality and the amount of mental attachment you overcome that count.  So don't bankrupt yourself on a momentary positive impulse, only to regret it later.  Give thought to giving.  Give small things, carefully, and observe the mental processes going along with the act of releasing the little thing you liked.  (53)
(Quote is actually Robert A F Thurman but Huston Smith, who only wrote the introduction to my edition, seems to be given full credit for this text.)" -- Huston Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/506156-it-is-desirable-that-a-man-live-in-all-respects</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 15:13:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sammie add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/506156-it-is-desirable-that-a-man-live-in-all-respects]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is desirable that a man live in all respects so simply and preparedly that if an enemy take the town... he can walk out the gate empty-handed and without anxiety." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5892-our-life-is-frittered-away-by-detail-simplify-simplify</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 15:15:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sammie add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5892-our-life-is-frittered-away-by-detail-simplify-simplify]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our life is frittered away by detail. Simplify, simplify." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318926-the-greatest-step-towards-a-life-of-simplicity-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 15:15:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sammie add a quote by Steve Maraboli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318926-the-greatest-step-towards-a-life-of-simplicity-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greatest step towards a life of simplicity is to learn to let go." -- Steve Maraboli]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
