<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/559715-rachel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/559715-rachel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 11:32:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32070-it-wasn-t-only-wickedness-and-scheming-that-made-people-unhappy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 11:32:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32070-it-wasn-t-only-wickedness-and-scheming-that-made-people-unhappy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It wasn't only wickedness and scheming that made people unhappy, it was confusion and misunderstanding; above all, it was the failure to grasp the simple truth that other people are as real as you." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11550-the-joys-of-possession-i-have-never-felt-acutely-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 11:33:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11550-the-joys-of-possession-i-have-never-felt-acutely-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The joys of possession I have never felt acutely. I find it hard to think of myself as the owner of anything. But I do tend to slip into the role of guardian and protector of the unloved and unlovable, of what other people disdain or spurn: bad-tempered old dogs, ugly pieces of furniture that have stubbornly stayed alive, cars on the edge of breakdown. It is a role I resist; but every now and then the mute appeal of the unwanted overwhelms my defences." -- J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9425-i-decline-to-accept-the-end-of-man-i-refuse</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 11:35:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9425-i-decline-to-accept-the-end-of-man-i-refuse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I decline to accept the end of man... I refuse to accept this.  I believe that man will not merely endure: he will prevail.  He is immortal, not because he alone among the creatures has an inexhaustible voice, but because he has a soul, a spirit capable of compassion and sacrifice and endurance.  The poet's, the writer's, duty is to write about these things.  It is his privilege to help man endure by lifting his heart, by reminding him of the courage and honor and hope and pride and compassion and pity and sacrifice which have been the glory of his past.  The poet's voice need not merely be the record of man, it can be one of the props, the pillars to help him endure and prevail." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38105-the-writer-should-never-be-ashamed-of-staring-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 14:59:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38105-the-writer-should-never-be-ashamed-of-staring-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The writer should never be ashamed of staring. There is nothing that does not require his attention." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
