<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/561013-lena]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/561013-lena" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2007 20:53:30 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5842-it-is-better-to-be-alone-than-in-bad-company</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2007 20:53:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by George Washington]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5842-it-is-better-to-be-alone-than-in-bad-company]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to be alone than in bad company." -- George Washington]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5845-people-are-always-shouting-they-want-to-create-a-better</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2007 20:57:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5845-people-are-always-shouting-they-want-to-create-a-better]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People are always shouting they want to create a better future. It's not true. The future is an apathetic void of no interest to anyone. The past is full of life, eager to irritate us, provoke and insult us, tempt us to destroy or repaint it. The only reason people want to be masters of the future is to change the past." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5846-everything-that-irritates-us-about-others-can-lead-us-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2007 20:57:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5846-everything-that-irritates-us-about-others-can-lead-us-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything that irritates us about others can lead us to an understanding of ourselves." -- Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9292-it-isn-t-what-you-have-or-who-you-are-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2007 20:59:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by Dale Carnegie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9292-it-isn-t-what-you-have-or-who-you-are-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It isn't what you have or who you are or where you are or what you are doing that makes you happy or unhappy. It is what you think about it." -- Dale Carnegie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5848-we-have-no-patience-with-other-people-s-vanity-because-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2007 21:15:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by Francois de La Rochefoucauld]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5848-we-have-no-patience-with-other-people-s-vanity-because-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have no patience with other people's vanity because it is offensive to our own." -- Francois de La Rochefoucauld]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5852-it-is-better-to-be-unhappy-in-love-than-unhappy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2007 21:38:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by Guy de Maupassant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5852-it-is-better-to-be-unhappy-in-love-than-unhappy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to be unhappy in love than unhappy in marriage, but some people manage to be both." -- Guy de Maupassant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48434-for-there-is-nothing-heavier-than-compassion-not-even-one-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 20:18:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48434-for-there-is-nothing-heavier-than-compassion-not-even-one-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["for there is nothing heavier than compassion. Not even one's own pain weighs so heavy as the pain one feels with someone, for someone, a pain intensified by the imagination and prolonged by a hundred echoes." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65833-we-all-need-someone-to-look-at-us-we-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 20:20:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65833-we-all-need-someone-to-look-at-us-we-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all need someone to look at us. we can be divided into four categories according to the kind of look we wish to live under. the first category longs for the look of an infinite number of anonymous eyes, in other words, for the look of the public. the second category is made up of people who have a vital need to be looked at by many known eyes. they are the tireless hosts of cocktail parties and dinners. they are happier than the people in the first category, who, when they lose their public, have the feeling that the lights have gone out in the room of their lives. this happens to nearly all of them sooner or later. people in the second category, on the other hand, can always come up with the eyes they need. then there is the third category, the category of people who need to be constantly before the eyes of the person they love. their situation is as dangerous as the situation of people in the first category. one day the eyes of their beloved will close, and the room will go dark. and finally there is the fourth category, the rarest, the category of people who live in the imaginary eyes of those who are not present. they are the dreamers." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37-anyone-whose-goal-is-something-higher-must-expect-someday-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 20:25:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37-anyone-whose-goal-is-something-higher-must-expect-someday-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone whose goal is 'something higher' must expect someday to suffer vertigo. What is vertigo? Fear of falling? No, Vertigo is something other than fear of falling. It is the voice of the emptiness below us which tempts and lures us, it is the desire to fall, against which, terrified, we defend ourselves." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19911-i-write-differently-from-what-i-speak-i-speak-differently</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 21:12:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19911-i-write-differently-from-what-i-speak-i-speak-differently]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I write differently from what I speak, I speak differently from what I think, I think differently from the way I ought to think, and so it all proceeds into deepest darkness." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62720-it-is-very-queer-that-the-unhappiness-of-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 08:12:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by Erich Maria Remarque]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62720-it-is-very-queer-that-the-unhappiness-of-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is very queer that the unhappiness of the world is so often brought on by small men." -- Erich Maria Remarque]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149506-i-did-not-want-to-think-so-much-about-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 08:13:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by Erich Maria Remarque]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149506-i-did-not-want-to-think-so-much-about-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I did not want to think so much about her.  I wanted to take her as an unexpected, delightful gift, that had come and would go again — nothing more.  I meant not to give room to the thought that it could ever be more.  I knew too well that all love has the desire for eternity and that therein lies its eternal torment.  Nothing lasts.  Nothing." -- Erich Maria Remarque]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402640-i-used-to-think-i-was-the-strangest-person-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 06:34:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by Frida Kahlo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402640-i-used-to-think-i-was-the-strangest-person-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I used to think I was the strangest person in the world but then I thought there are so many people in the world, there must be someone just like me who feels bizarre and flawed in the same ways I do.  I would imagine her, and imagine that she must be out there thinking of me too.  Well, I hope that if you are out there and read this and know that, yes, it's true I'm here, and I'm just as strange as you." -- Frida Kahlo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190660-isn-t-it-funny-how-the-memories-you-cherish-before-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 11:51:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by Allyson Braithwaite Condie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190660-isn-t-it-funny-how-the-memories-you-cherish-before-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't it funny how the memories you cherish before a breakup can become your worst enemies afterwards? The thoughts you loved to think about, the memories you wanted to hold up to the light and view from every angle--it suddenly seems a lot safer to lock them in a box, far from the light of day and throw away the key. It's not an act of bitterness. It's an act if self-preservation. It's not always a bad idea to stay behind the window and look out at life instead, is it?" -- Allyson Braithwaite Condie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175762-because-you-can-never-go-from-going-out-to-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 11:51:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175762-because-you-can-never-go-from-going-out-to-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because you can never go from going out to being friends, just like that. It's a lie. It's just something that people say they'll do to take the permanence out of a breakup. And someone always takes it to mean more than it does, and then is hurt even more when, inevitably, said ‘friendly' relationship is still a major step down from the previous relationship, and it's like breaking up all over again. But messier." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429117-if-i-m-sincere-today-what-does-it-matter-if-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 06:57:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by José Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429117-if-i-m-sincere-today-what-does-it-matter-if-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I'm sincere today, what does it matter if I regret it tomorrow?" -- José Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240657-i-don-t-think-we-did-go-blind-i-think-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 06:57:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lena add a quote by José Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240657-i-don-t-think-we-did-go-blind-i-think-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't think we did go blind, I think we are blind, Blind but seeing, Blind people who can see, but do not see." -- José Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
