<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/561200-holly]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/561200-holly" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 14:23:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512936-our-deeds-determine-us-as-much-as-we-determine-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 14:23:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Marian Evans]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512936-our-deeds-determine-us-as-much-as-we-determine-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deeds determine us, as much as we determine our deeds; and until we know what has been or will be the peculiar combination of outward with inward facts, which constitutes a man's critical actions, it will be better not to think ourselves wise about his character. There is a terrible coercion in our deeds wihich may first turn the honest man into a deceiver, and then reconcile him to the change; for this reason -- that the second wrong presents itself to him in the guise of the only practicable right. The action which before commission has been seen with that blended common-sense and fresh untarnished feeling which is the healthy eye of the soul, is looked at afterwards with the lens of apologetic ingenuity, through which all things that men call beautiful and ugly are seen to be made up of textures very much alike. - Adam Bede p. 359" -- Marian Evans]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512938-there-is-no-sort-of-wrong-deed-of-which-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 14:24:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Marian Evans]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512938-there-is-no-sort-of-wrong-deed-of-which-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no sort of wrong deed of which a man can bear the punishment alone: you can't isolate yourself, and say that the evil which is in you shall not spread. Men's lives are as thoroughly blended with each other as the air they breathe: evil spreads as necessarily as disease. I know, I feel the terrible extent of suffering this sin of Arthur's has caused to others; but so does every sin cause suffering to others besides those who commit it. An act of vengeance on your part against Arthur would simply be another evil added to those we are suffering under: you could not bear the punishment alone; you would entail the worst sorrows on every one who loves you. You would have committed an act of blind fury, that would leave all the present evils just as they were, and add worse evils to them. You may tell me that you meditate no fatal act of vengeance: but the feeling in your mind is what gives birth to such actions, and as long as you indulge it, as long as you do not see that to fix your mind on Arthur's punishment is revenge, and not justice, you are in danger of being led on to the commission of some great wrong." -- Marian Evans]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
