<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/563247-summer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/563247-summer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 20:40:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501463-this-is-meant-to-be-in-praise-of-the-interval</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 20:40:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by David Berman, “Cassette County”]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501463-this-is-meant-to-be-in-praise-of-the-interval]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is meant to be in praise of the interval called hangover,
a sadness not co-terminous with hopelessness,
and the North American doubling cascade
that (keep going) “this diamond lake is a photo lab”
and if predicates really do propel the plot
then you might see Jerusalem in a soap bubble
or the appliance failures on Olive Street
across these great instances,
because “the complex Italians versus the basic Italians”
because what does a mirror look like (when it´s not working)
but birds singing a full tone higher in the sunshine.

I´m going to call them Honest Eyes until I know if they are,
in the interval called slam clicker, Realm of Pacific,
because the second language wouldn´t let me learn it
because I have heard of you for a long time occasionally
because diet cards may be the recovery evergreen
and there is a new benzodiazepene called Distance,

anti-showmanship, anti-showmanship, anti-showmanship.

I suppose a broken window is not symbolic
unless symbolic means broken, which I think it sorta does,
and when the phone jangles
what´s more radical, the snow or the tires,
and what does the Bible say about metal fatigue
and why do mothers carry big scratched-up sunglasses
in their purses.

Hello to the era of going to the store to buy more ice
because we are running out.
Hello to feelings that arrive unintroduced.
Hello to the nonfunctional sprig of parsley
and the game of finding meaning in coincidence.

Because there is a second mind in the margins of the used book
because Judas Priest (source: Firestone Library)
sang a song called Stained Class,
because this world is 66% Then and 33% Now,

and if you wake up thinking “feeling is a skill now”
or “even this glass of water seems complicated now”
and a phrase from a men´s magazine (like single-district cognac)
rings and rings in your neck,
then let the consequent misunderstandings
(let the changer love the changed)
wobble on heartbreakingly nu legs
into this street-legal nonfiction,
into this good world,
this warm place
that I love with all my heart,

anti-showmanship, anti-showmanship, anti-showmanship." -- David Berman, “Cassette County”]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181-being-kissed-on-the-back-of-the-knee-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 18:10:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Anne Sexton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181-being-kissed-on-the-back-of-the-knee-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being kissed on the back 
of the knee is a moth 
at the windowscreen...." -- Anne Sexton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18403-children-of-her-type-contrive-the-purest-philosophies-ada-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 18:10:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18403-children-of-her-type-contrive-the-purest-philosophies-ada-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Children of her type contrive the purest philosophies. Ada had worked out her own little system. Hardly a week had elapsed since Van’s arrival when he was found worthy of being initiated in her web of wisdom. An individual’s life consisted of certain classified things: &quot;real things&quot; which were unfrequent and priceless, simply &quot;things&quot; which formed the routine stuff of life; and &quot;ghost things,&quot; also called &quot;fogs,&quot; such as fever, toothache, dreadful disappointments, and death. Three or more things occurring at the same time formed a &quot;tower,&quot; or, if they came in immediate succession, they made a &quot;bridge.&quot; &quot;Real towers&quot; and &quot;real bridges&quot; were the joys of life, and when the towers came in a series, one experienced supreme rapture; it almost never happened, though. In some circumstances, in a certain light, a neutral &quot;thing&quot; might look or even actually become &quot;real&quot; or else, conversely, it might coagulate into a fetid &quot;fog.&quot; When the joy and the joyless happened to be intermixed, simultaneously or along the ramp of duration, one was confronted with &quot;ruined towers&quot; and &quot;broken bridges." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118225-sometimes-a-strikeout-means-that-the-slugger-s-girlfriend-just-ran</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 18:10:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by David James Duncan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118225-sometimes-a-strikeout-means-that-the-slugger-s-girlfriend-just-ran]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes a strikeout means that the slugger’s girlfriend just ran off with the UPS driver. Sometimes a muffed ground ball means that the shortstop’s baby daughter has a pain in her head that won’t go away. And handicapping is for amateur golfers, not ballplayers. Pitchers don’t ease off on the cleanup hitter because of the lumps just discovered in his wife’s breast. Baseball is not life. It is a fiction, a metaphor. And a ballplayer is a man who agrees to uphold that metaphor as though lives were at stake. 

Perhaps they are. I cherish a theory I once heard propounded by G.Q. Durham that professional baseball is inherently antiwar. The most overlooked cause of war, his theory runs, is that it’s so damned interesting. It takes hard effort, skill, love and a little luck to make times of peace consistently interesting. About all it takes to make war interesting is a life. The appeal of trying to kill others without being killed yourself, according to Gale, is that it brings suspense, terror, honor, disgrace, rage, tragedy, treachery and occasionally even heroism within range of guys who, in times of peace, might lead lives of unmitigated blandness. But baseball, he says, is one activity that is able to generate suspense and excitement on a national scale, just like war. And baseball can only be played in peace. Hence G.Q.’s thesis that pro ball-players—little as some of them may want to hear it—are basically just a bunch of unusually well-coordinated guys working hard and artfully to prevent wars, by making peace more interesting." -- David James Duncan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18404-everything-with-me-is-either-worship-and-passion-or-pity</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 03:13:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18404-everything-with-me-is-either-worship-and-passion-or-pity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything with me is either worship and passion or pity and understanding. I hate rarely, though when I hate, I hate murderously. For example now, I hate the bank and everything connected with it. I also hate Dutch paintings, penis-sucking, parties, and cold rainy weather. But I am much more preoccupied with loving." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118216-all-men-have-parties-and-are-pals-who-never-let</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 17:10:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Tove Jansson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118216-all-men-have-parties-and-are-pals-who-never-let]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All men have parties and are pals who never let each other down. A pal can say terrible things which are forgotten the next day. A pal never forgives, he just forgets, and a woman forgives but never forgets. That's how it is. That's why women aren't allowed to have parties. Being forgiven is very unpleasant." -- Tove Jansson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110184-baseball-breaks-your-heart-it-is-designed-to-break-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 17:10:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by A. Bartlett Giamatti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110184-baseball-breaks-your-heart-it-is-designed-to-break-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Baseball] breaks your heart. It is designed to break your heart. The game begins in the spring, when everything else begins again, and it blossoms in the summer, filling the afternoons and evenings, and then as soon as the chill rains come, it stops and leaves you to face the fall all alone. You count on it, rely on it to buffer the passage of time, to keep the memory of sunshine and high skies alive, and then just when the days are all twilight, when you need it most, it stops." -- A. Bartlett Giamatti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353228-you-can-t-ever-be-really-free-if-you-admire-somebody</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 18:07:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Tove Jansson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353228-you-can-t-ever-be-really-free-if-you-admire-somebody]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can't ever be really free if you admire somebody too much." -- Tove Jansson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30407-first-of-all-love-is-a-joint-experience-between-two</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 18:07:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by carson mccullers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30407-first-of-all-love-is-a-joint-experience-between-two]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First of all, love is a joint experience between two persons — but the fact that it is a joint experience does not mean that it is a similar experience to the two people involved. There are the lover and the beloved, but these two come from different countries. Often the beloved is only a stimulus for all the stored-up love which had lain quiet within the lover for a long time hitherto. And somehow every lover knows this. He feels in his soul that his love is a solitary thing. He comes to know a new, strange loneliness and it is this knowledge which makes him suffer. So there is only one thing for the lover to do. He must house his love within himself as best he can; he must create for himself a whole new inward world — a world intense and strange, complete in himself. Let it be added here that this lover about whom we speak need not necessarily be a young man saving for a wedding ring — this lover can be man, woman, child, or indeed any human creature on this earth.

Now, the beloved can also be of any description. The most outlandish people can be the stimulus for love. A man may be a doddering great-grandfather and still love only a strange girl he saw in the streets of Cheehaw one afternoon two decades past. The preacher may love a fallen woman. The beloved may be treacherous, greasy-headed, and given to evil habits. Yes, and the lover may see this as clearly as anyone else — but that does not affect the evolution of his love one whit. A most mediocre person can be the object of a love which is wild, extravagant, and beautiful as the poison lilies of the swamp. A good man may be the stimulus for a love both violent and debased, or a jabbering madman may bring about in the soul of someone a tender and simple idyll. Therefore, the value and quality of any love is determined solely by the lover himself.

It is for this reason that most of us would rather love than be loved. Almost everyone wants to be the lover. And the curt truth is that, in a deep secret way, the state of being beloved is intolerable to many. The beloved fears and hates the lover, and with the best of reasons. For the lover is forever trying to strip bare his beloved. The lover craves any possible relation with the beloved, even if this experience can cause him only pain." -- carson mccullers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20853-this-was-a-new-recognition-that-perfection-is-admirable-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 20:40:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Roger Angell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20853-this-was-a-new-recognition-that-perfection-is-admirable-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This was a new recognition that perfection is admirable but a trifle inhuman, and that a stumbling kind of semi-success can be much more warming. Most of all, perhaps, these exultant yells for the Mets were also yells for ourselves, and came from a wry, half-understood recognition that there is more Met than Yankee in every one of us. I knew for whom that foghorn blew; it blew for me." -- Roger Angell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47334-a-cat-has-absolute-emotional-honesty-human-beings-for-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 12:36:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47334-a-cat-has-absolute-emotional-honesty-human-beings-for-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A cat has absolute emotional honesty: human beings, for one reason or another, may hide their feelings, but a cat does not." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/809964-and-i-see-that-not-touching-for-so-long-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 07:50:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Amy Hempel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/809964-and-i-see-that-not-touching-for-so-long-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I see that not touching for so long was a drive to the beach with the windows rolled up so the waves feel that much colder." -- Amy Hempel]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
