<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/564249-hasan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/564249-hasan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 11:50:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55036-the-foundation-of-irreligious-criticism-is-man-makes-religion-religion</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 11:50:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Karl Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55036-the-foundation-of-irreligious-criticism-is-man-makes-religion-religion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The foundation of irreligious criticism is: Man makes religion, religion does not make man. Religion is, indeed, the self-consciousness and self-esteem of man who has either not yet won through to himself, or has already lost himself again. But man is no abstract being squatting outside the world. Man is the world of man – state, society. This state and this society produce religion, which is an inverted consciousness of the world, because they are an inverted world...

Religious suffering is, at one and the same time, the expression of real suffering and a protest against real suffering. Religion is the sigh of the oppressed creature, the heart of a heartless world, and the soul of soulless conditions. It is the opium of the people.

The abolition of religion as the illusory happiness of the people is the demand for their real happiness. To call on them to give up their illusions about their condition is to call on them to give up a condition that requires illusions. The criticism of religion is, therefore, in embryo, the criticism of that vale of tears of which religion is the halo.

Criticism has plucked the imaginary flowers on the chain not in order that man shall continue to bear that chain without fantasy or consolation, but so that he shall throw off the chain and pluck the living flower. The criticism of religion disillusions man, so that he will think, act, and fashion his reality like a man who has discarded his illusions and regained his senses, so that he will move around himself as his own true Sun. Religion is only the illusory Sun which revolves around man as long as he does not revolve around himself." -- Karl Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169323-to-feel-most-beautifully-alive-means-to-be-reading-something</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 12:48:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Gaston Bachelard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169323-to-feel-most-beautifully-alive-means-to-be-reading-something]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To feel most beautifully alive means to be reading something beautiful, ready always to apprehend in the flow of language the sudden flash of poetry." -- Gaston Bachelard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41709-a-little-learning-is-a-dangerous-thing-drink-deep-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 12:48:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Alexander Pope]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41709-a-little-learning-is-a-dangerous-thing-drink-deep-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A little learning is a dangerous thing.
Drink deep, or taste not the Pierian Spring;
There shallow draughts intoxicate the brain,
and drinking largely sobers us again." -- Alexander Pope]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322267-what-a-piece-of-work-is-a-man-how-noble</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 12:49:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322267-what-a-piece-of-work-is-a-man-how-noble]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a piece of work is a man! How noble in
Reason! how infinite in faculties! in form and moving
how express and admirable! In action how like an Angel!
in apprehension how like a god! the beauty of the
world! the paragon of animals! and yet to me, what is
this quintessence of dust? Man delights not me; no,
nor Woman neither; though by your smiling you seeme
to say so" -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49389-everything-s-already-been-said-but-since-nobody-was-listening-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 11:50:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Andre Gide]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49389-everything-s-already-been-said-but-since-nobody-was-listening-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything's already been said, but since nobody was listening, we have to start again." -- Andre Gide]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12890-death-is-always-on-the-way-but-the-fact-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 11:50:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Paul Bowles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12890-death-is-always-on-the-way-but-the-fact-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death is always on the way, but the fact that you don't know when it will arrive seems to take away from the finiteness of life. It's that terrible precision that we hate so much. But because we don't know, we get to think of life as an inexhaustible well. Yet everything happens a certain number of times, and a very small number, really. How many more times will you remember a certain afternoon of your childhood, some afternoon that's so deeply a part of your being that you can't even conceive of your life without it? Perhaps four or five times more. Perhaps not even. How many more times will you watch the full moon rise? Perhaps twenty. And yet it all seems limitless." -- Paul Bowles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19682-all-of-humanity-s-problems-stem-from-man-s-inability-to-sit</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 07:23:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Blaise Pascal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19682-all-of-humanity-s-problems-stem-from-man-s-inability-to-sit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All of humanity's problems stem from man's inability to sit quietly in a room alone." -- Blaise Pascal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217194-kitap-okumakla-manav-n-beni-aldatmas-na-engel-olam-yorum-bir-t-rl-manava</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 07:23:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Oğuz Atay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217194-kitap-okumakla-manav-n-beni-aldatmas-na-engel-olam-yorum-bir-t-rl-manava]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kitap okumakla, manavın beni aldatmasına engel olamıyorum bir türlü. Manava inanmadığım halde beni aldatıyor namussuz." -- Oğuz Atay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79484-i-m-not-anti-social-i-m-just-not-social</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 07:23:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Woody Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79484-i-m-not-anti-social-i-m-just-not-social]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not anti-social. I'm just not social." -- Woody Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130692-people-often-say-that-the-english-are-very-cold-fish</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 06:35:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130692-people-often-say-that-the-english-are-very-cold-fish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People often say that the English are very cold fish, very reserved, that they have a way of looking at things – even tragedy – with a sense of irony. There’s some truth in it; it’s pretty stupid of them, though. Humor won’t save you; it doesn’t really do anything at all. You can look at life ironically for years, maybe decades; there are people who seem to go through most of their lives seeing the funny side, but in the end, life always breaks your heart. Doesn’t matter how brave you are, how reserved, or how much you’ve developed a sense of humor, you still end up with your heart broken. That’s when you stop laughing. In the end there’s just the cold, the silence and the loneliness. In the end, there’s only death." -- Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/564764-it-s-a-fact-that-in-societies-like-ours-sex-truly-represents</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 12:42:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/564764-it-s-a-fact-that-in-societies-like-ours-sex-truly-represents]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's a fact...that in societies like ours sex truly represents a second system of differentiation, completely independent of money; and as a system of differentiation it functions just as mercilessly. The effects of these two systems are, furthermore, strictly equivalent. Just like unrestrained economic liberalism, and for similar reasons, sexual liberalism produces phenomena of absolute pauperization . Some men make love every day; others five or six times in their life, or never. Some make love with dozens of women; others with none. It's what's known as 'the law of the market'...Economic liberalism is an extension of the domain of the struggle, its extension to all ages and all classes of society. Sexual liberalism is likewise an extension of the domain of the struggle, its extension to all ages and all classes of society." -- Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/568101-liberals-always-say-about-totalitarians-that-they-like-humanity-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 14:16:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Slavoj Žižek]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/568101-liberals-always-say-about-totalitarians-that-they-like-humanity-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Liberals always say about totalitarians that they like humanity, as such, but they have no empathy for concrete people, no? OK, that fits me perfectly. Humanity? Yes, it's OK – some great talks, some great arts. Concrete people? No, 99% are boring idiots." -- Slavoj Žižek]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16302-there-lives-more-faith-in-honest-doubt-believe-me-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 07:24:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Alfred, Lord Tennyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16302-there-lives-more-faith-in-honest-doubt-believe-me-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There lives more faith in honest doubt, believe me, than in half the creeds." -- Alfred, Lord Tennyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394542-let-each-of-us-examine-his-thoughts-he-will-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 07:24:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Blaise Pascal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394542-let-each-of-us-examine-his-thoughts-he-will-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let each of us examine his thoughts; he will find them wholly concerned with the past or the future.  We almost never think of the present, and if we do think of it, it is only to see what light is throws on our plans for the future.  The present is never our end.  The past and the present are our means, the future alone our end.  Thus we never actually live, but hope to live, and since we are always planning how to be happy, it is inevitable that we should never be so." -- Blaise Pascal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193944-the-most-merciful-thing-in-the-world-i-think-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 11:51:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193944-the-most-merciful-thing-in-the-world-i-think-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most merciful thing in the world, I think, is the inability of the human mind to correlate all its contents. We live on a placid island of ignorance in the midst of black seas of infinity, and it was not meant that we should voyage far. The sciences, each straining in its own direction, have hitherto harmed us little; but some day the piecing together of dissociated knowledge will open up such terrifying vistas of reality, and of our frightful position therein, that we shall either go mad from the revelation or flee from the light into the peace and safety of a new dark age." -- H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629951-the-more-i-learned-the-more-conscious-did-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 11:51:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629951-the-more-i-learned-the-more-conscious-did-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["... the more I learned, the more conscious did I become of the fact that I was ridiculous. So that for me my years of hard work at the university seem in the end to have existed for the sole purpose of demonstrating and proving to me, the more deeply engrossed I became in my studies, that I was an utterly absurd person" -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 11:51:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51878-knowledge-subverts-love-in-proportion-as-we-penetrate-our-secrets</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 11:51:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Emil Cioran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51878-knowledge-subverts-love-in-proportion-as-we-penetrate-our-secrets]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Knowledge subverts love: in proportion as we penetrate our secrets, we come to loathe our kind, precisely because they resemble us." -- Emil Cioran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620767-with-sociology-one-can-do-anything-and-call-it-work</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 11:51:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Malcolm Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620767-with-sociology-one-can-do-anything-and-call-it-work]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With sociology one can do anything and call it work" -- Malcolm Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28552-if-a-way-to-the-better-there-be-it-exacts</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 00:34:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Thomas Hardy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28552-if-a-way-to-the-better-there-be-it-exacts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a way to the Better there be, it exacts a full look at the Worst." -- Thomas Hardy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31315-education-is-a-progressive-discovery-of-our-own-ignorance</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 11:50:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Will Durant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31315-education-is-a-progressive-discovery-of-our-own-ignorance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Education is a progressive discovery of our own ignorance." -- Will Durant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255277-the-art-of-not-reading-is-a-very-important-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 05:50:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255277-the-art-of-not-reading-is-a-very-important-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The art of &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; reading is a very important one. It consists in not taking an interest in whatever may be engaging the attention of the general public at any particular time. When some political or ecclesiastical pamphlet, or novel, or poem is making a great commotion, you should remember that he who writes for fools always finds a large public. A precondition for reading good books is not reading bad ones: for life is short." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220095-a-book-is-a-suicide-postponed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 07:22:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Cioran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220095-a-book-is-a-suicide-postponed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book is a suicide postponed." -- Cioran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/355996-buying-books-would-be-a-good-thing-if-one-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 05:52:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/355996-buying-books-would-be-a-good-thing-if-one-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Buying books would be a good thing if one could also buy the time to read them; but as a rule the purchase of books is mistaken for the appropriation of their contents." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127797-i-love-reading-another-reader-s-list-of-favorites-even-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2013 04:11:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127797-i-love-reading-another-reader-s-list-of-favorites-even-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love reading another reader’s list of favorites. Even when I find I do not share their tastes or predilections, I am provoked to compare, contrast, and contradict. It is a most healthy exercise, and one altogether fruitful." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8791-sonnet-29-when-in-disgrace-with-fortune-and-men-s-eyes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 16:27:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8791-sonnet-29-when-in-disgrace-with-fortune-and-men-s-eyes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;b&gt;Sonnet 29&lt;/b&gt;

When, in disgrace with fortune and men's eyes,
I all alone beweep my outcast state 
And trouble deaf heaven with my bootless cries
And look upon myself and curse my fate, 
Wishing me like to one more rich in hope, 
Featured like him, like him with friends possess'd,
Desiring this man's art and that man's scope, 
With what I most enjoy contented least; 
Yet in these thoughts myself almost despising,
Haply I think on thee, and then my state, 
Like to the lark at break of day arising 
From sullen earth, sings hymns at heaven's gate;
For thy sweet love remember'd such wealth brings
That then I scorn to change my state with kings." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/682340-marry-and-you-will-regret-it-don-t-marry-you-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 03:40:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/682340-marry-and-you-will-regret-it-don-t-marry-you-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Marry, and you will regret it; don’t marry, you will also regret it; marry or don’t marry, you will regret it either way. Laugh at the world’s foolishness, you will regret it; weep over it, you will regret that too; laugh at the world’s foolishness or weep over it, you will regret it either way; laugh at the world’s foolishness or weep over it, you will regret both. Believe a woman, you will regret it; believe her not, you will also regret it; believe a woman or believe her not, you will regret it either way; believing a woman or not believing her, you will regret it both ways. Hang yourself, you will regret it; do not hang yourself, and you will regret that too; hang yourself or don’t hang yourself, you’ll regret it either way; whether you hang yourself or do not hang yourself, you will regret both. This, gentlemen, is the essence of all philosophy." -- Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21796-enjoy-every-sandwich</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 21:39:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by Warren Zevon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21796-enjoy-every-sandwich]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Enjoy every sandwich." -- Warren Zevon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1387-life-is-pain-highness-anyone-who-says-differently-is-selling</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 20:18:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1387-life-is-pain-highness-anyone-who-says-differently-is-selling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is pain, highness. Anyone who says differently is selling something." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111182-i-believe-in-aristocracy-though----if-that-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 16:43:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hasan add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111182-i-believe-in-aristocracy-though----if-that-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in aristocracy, though -- if that is the right word, and if a democrat may use it.  Not an aristocracy of power, based upon rank and influence, but an aristocracy of the sensitive, the considerate and the plucky.  Its members are to be found in all nations and classes, and all through the ages, and there is a secreat understanding between them when they meet.  They represent the true human tradition, the one permanent victory of our queer race over cruelty and chaos.  Thousands of them perish in obscurity, a few are great names.  They are sensitive for others as well as themselves, they are considerate without being fussy, their pluck is not swankiness but power to endure, and they can take a joke." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
