<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/565363-mark]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/565363-mark" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 13:08:08 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234344-if-you-can-t-be-happy-then-be-quiet-frm</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 13:08:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[mark add a quote by mark  Jabbour]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234344-if-you-can-t-be-happy-then-be-quiet-frm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["... if you can't be happy then be quiet!&quot; frm &quot;Silent Joe,&quot; by T Jefferson Parker.&quot; Silence is another form of lying.&quot; frm &quot;Attachment,&quot; by me. Take your pick ... words, &quot;writing freezes speech,&quot; Chris Hedges. &quot;Writing is thinking,&quot; me." -- mark  Jabbour]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52994-what-makes-you-think-human-beings-are-sentient-and-aware</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 17:57:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[mark add a quote by Michael Crichton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52994-what-makes-you-think-human-beings-are-sentient-and-aware]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What makes you think human beings are sentient and aware? There's no evidence for it. Human beings never think for themselves, they find it too uncomfortable. For the most part, members of our species simply repeat what they are told-and become upset if they are exposed to any different view. The characteristic human trait is not awareness but conformity, and the characteristic result is religious warfare. Other animals fight for territory or food; but, uniquely in the animal kingdom, human beings fight for their 'beliefs.' The reason is that beliefs guide behavior which has evolutionary importance among human beings. But at a time when our behavior may well lead us to extinction, I see no reason to assume we have any awareness at all. We are stubborn, self-destructive conformists. Any other view of our species is just a self-congratulatory delusion. Next question." -- Michael Crichton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118225-sometimes-a-strikeout-means-that-the-slugger-s-girlfriend-just-ran</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2010 09:04:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[mark add a quote by David James Duncan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118225-sometimes-a-strikeout-means-that-the-slugger-s-girlfriend-just-ran]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes a strikeout means that the slugger’s girlfriend just ran off with the UPS driver. Sometimes a muffed ground ball means that the shortstop’s baby daughter has a pain in her head that won’t go away. And handicapping is for amateur golfers, not ballplayers. Pitchers don’t ease off on the cleanup hitter because of the lumps just discovered in his wife’s breast. Baseball is not life. It is a fiction, a metaphor. And a ballplayer is a man who agrees to uphold that metaphor as though lives were at stake. 

Perhaps they are. I cherish a theory I once heard propounded by G.Q. Durham that professional baseball is inherently antiwar. The most overlooked cause of war, his theory runs, is that it’s so damned interesting. It takes hard effort, skill, love and a little luck to make times of peace consistently interesting. About all it takes to make war interesting is a life. The appeal of trying to kill others without being killed yourself, according to Gale, is that it brings suspense, terror, honor, disgrace, rage, tragedy, treachery and occasionally even heroism within range of guys who, in times of peace, might lead lives of unmitigated blandness. But baseball, he says, is one activity that is able to generate suspense and excitement on a national scale, just like war. And baseball can only be played in peace. Hence G.Q.’s thesis that pro ball-players—little as some of them may want to hear it—are basically just a bunch of unusually well-coordinated guys working hard and artfully to prevent wars, by making peace more interesting." -- David James Duncan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/528994-what-if-i-forgave-myself-i-thought-what-if-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 10:40:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[mark add a quote by Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/528994-what-if-i-forgave-myself-i-thought-what-if-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What if I forgave myself? I thought. What if I forgave myself even though I'd done something I shouldn't have? What if I was a liar and a cheat and there was no excuse for what I'd done other than because it was what I wanted and needed to do? What if I was sorry, but if I could go back in time I wouldn't do anything differently than I had done? What if I'd actually wanted to fuck every one of those men? What if heroin taught me something? What if yes was the right answer instead of no? What if what made me do all those things everyone thought I shouldn't have done was what also had got me here? What if I was never redeemed? What if I already was?" -- Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/423290-the-face-you-give-the-world-tells-the-world-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 13:17:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[mark add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/423290-the-face-you-give-the-world-tells-the-world-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The face you give the world tells the world how to treat you." -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
