<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/56540-stacey]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/56540-stacey" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2011 18:06:33 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341839-she-was-the-reason-i-was-a-reader-and-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2011 18:06:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacey add a quote by Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341839-she-was-the-reason-i-was-a-reader-and-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was the reason I was a reader, and being a reader was what had made me most myself; it had given me the gifts of curiosity and sympathy, an awareness of the world as an odd and vibrant contradictory place, and it had me unafraid of its oddness and vibrancy and contradictions." -- Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128793-i-did-not-care-if-ella-went-t-princeton-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2011 18:09:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacey add a quote by Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128793-i-did-not-care-if-ella-went-t-princeton-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I did not care if Ella went t Princeton, if she was exceptionally pretty, if she grew up to marry a rich man, or really if she married at all - there were many incarnations of her I felt confident I could embrace, a hippie or a housewife or a career woman.  But what I did care about, what I wanted most fervently, was for her to understand that hard work paid off, that decency begat decency, that humility was not a raincoat you occasionally pulled on when you thought conditions called for it, but rather a constant way of existing in the world, knowing that good luck and bad luck touched everyone and none of us was fully responsible for our fortunes or tragedies.  Above all, I wanted my daughter to understand that many people were guided by bitterness and that it was best to avoid these individuals - their moods and behavior were a hornet's nest you had no possible reason to do anything other than bypass and ignore." -- Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460624-history-is-that-certainty-produced-at-the-point-where-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 16:39:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacey add a quote by Julian Barnes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460624-history-is-that-certainty-produced-at-the-point-where-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["History is that certainty produced at the point where the imperfections of memory meet the inadequacies of documentation." -- Julian Barnes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124087-the-only-thing-that-came-close-was-how-he-felt</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 13:30:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacey add a quote by Junot Diaz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124087-the-only-thing-that-came-close-was-how-he-felt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only thing that came close was how he felt about his books; only the combined love he had for everything he'd read and everything he hoped to write came even close." -- Junot Diaz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341446-the-thing-about-champagne-you-say-unfoiling-the-cork-unwinding-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 18:19:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacey add a quote by David Levithan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341446-the-thing-about-champagne-you-say-unfoiling-the-cork-unwinding-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The thing about champagne,you say, unfoiling the cork, unwinding the wire restraint, is that is the ultimate associative object. Every time you open a bottle of champagne, it's a celebration, so there's no better way of starting a celebration than opening a bottle of champagne. Every time you sip it, you're sipping from all those other celebrations. The joy accumulates over time." -- David Levithan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 22:48:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacey add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/576982-after-those-four-years-he-returned-to-the-midwest-he-d</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 10:58:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacey add a quote by Chad Harbach]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/576982-after-those-four-years-he-returned-to-the-midwest-he-d]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After those four years, he returned to the Midwest. He'd turned twenty-five, the Age of Unfolding, and it was time to write a novel, the way his hero had. He moved to a cheap apartment in Chicago and set to work, but even as the pages accumulated, despair set in. It was easy enough to write a sentence, but if you were going to create a &lt;i&gt;work of art&lt;/i&gt;, the way Melville had, each sentence needed to fit perfectly with the one that preceded it, and the unwritten one that would follow. And each of those sentences needed to square with the ones on either side, so that three became five and five became seven, seven became nine, and whichever sentence he was writing became the slender fulcrum on which the whole precarious edifice depended. That sentence could contain anything, &lt;i&gt;anything&lt;/i&gt;, and so it promised the kind of absolute freedom that, to Affenlight's mind, belonged to the artist and the artist alone. And yet that sentence was also beholden to the book's very first one, and its last unwritten one, and ever sentence in between. Every phrase, every word, exhausted him." -- Chad Harbach]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/645395-after-that-the-book-will-fade-the-way-all-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 16:11:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacey add a quote by Robin Sloan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/645395-after-that-the-book-will-fade-the-way-all-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After that, the book will fade, the way all books fade in your mind. But I hope you will remember this:
A man walking fast down a dark lonely street. Quick steps and hard breathing, all wonder and need. A bell above a door and the tinkle it makes. A clerk and a ladder and warm golden light, and then: the right book exactly, at exactly the right time." -- Robin Sloan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1254180-the-ability-to-have-a-friend-and-to-be-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 13:46:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacey add a quote by Ann Patchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1254180-the-ability-to-have-a-friend-and-to-be-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The ability to have a friend, and to be a friend, is not unlike the ability to learn. Both are rooted in being accepting and open-minded with a talent for hard-work. If you are willing to stretch yourself, to risk yourself, if you are willing to love and honor and cherish the people who are important to you until one of you dies, then there will be great heartaches and even greater rewards." -- Ann Patchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
