<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/565487-tuck]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/565487-tuck" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 13:28:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214476-anyway-i-am-unfitted-to-hold-down-a-job-anywhere</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 13:28:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Joseph Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214476-anyway-i-am-unfitted-to-hold-down-a-job-anywhere]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyway, I am unfitted to hold down a job anywhere unless they were to pay me for getting angry at the world.&quot;  96" -- Joseph Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133868-be-sure-to-enjoy-language-experiment-with-ways-of-talking</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 14:37:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Deborah Levy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133868-be-sure-to-enjoy-language-experiment-with-ways-of-talking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be sure to enjoy language, experiment with ways of talking, be exuberant even when you don't feel like it because language can make your world a better place to live." -- Deborah Levy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51248-work-as-if-you-live-in-the-early-days-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 09:13:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Alasdair Gray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51248-work-as-if-you-live-in-the-early-days-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Work as if you live in the early days of a better nation." -- Alasdair Gray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413-are-there-many-people-without-illness-or-disability-who-sit</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 09:13:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Alasdair Gray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413-are-there-many-people-without-illness-or-disability-who-sit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Are there many people without illness or disability who sit at home in the evening with clenched fists, continually changing the channel of a television set and wishing they had the courage to roll over the parapet of a high bridge? I bet there are millions of us." -- Alasdair Gray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9776-to-the-question-how-do-the-authors-of-sketches-stories</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2010 11:52:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Robert Walser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9776-to-the-question-how-do-the-authors-of-sketches-stories]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To the question: How do the authors of sketches, stories and novels get along in life, the following answer can or must be given: They are stragglers and they are down at heel." -- Robert Walser]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138111-of-all-our-games-love-s-play-is-the-only-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 09:15:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Marguerite Yourcenar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138111-of-all-our-games-love-s-play-is-the-only-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of all our games, love's play is the only one which threatens to unsettle the soul..." -- Marguerite Yourcenar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121-passion-such-as-hers-is-all-consent-asking-little-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 09:15:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Marguerite Yourcenar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121-passion-such-as-hers-is-all-consent-asking-little-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Passion such as hers is all consent, asking little in return. I had merely to enter a room where she was to see her face take on that peaceful expression of one who is resting in bed. If I touched her, I had the impression that all the blood in her veins was turning to honey." -- Marguerite Yourcenar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114973-i-ve-been-frozen-solid-against-the-wall-in-mazzo-s-staring</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2011 14:18:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by John David Morley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114973-i-ve-been-frozen-solid-against-the-wall-in-mazzo-s-staring]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been frozen solid against the wall in Mazzo's, staring at my index finger for a couple of hours, when my dead brother Morton shows up. He does that literally. I mean, I look down on one side and see him coming up through the floor. Nothing special about that. People have been showing up through the floor all evening. They pop up and mushroom in bursts, clumps of people that explode and disappear. In the Mazzo theme park it's another of those acid nights." -- John David Morley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358842-i-cadged-a-complimentary-green-matchbook-with-a-gold-bird</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 08:33:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Ed Lynskey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358842-i-cadged-a-complimentary-green-matchbook-with-a-gold-bird]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cadged a complimentary green matchbook with a gold bird icon from the Bell canning jar. Later we'd use the matches to light our spliffs. My fingertips tapped the stem to the gizmo that dinged a bell. Nobody came out. Wrong signal, so I did two bell rings. No response prompted me to tap out a series of bell rings." -- Ed Lynskey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145232-and-i-got-a-strong-feeling-of-the-passage-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 09:26:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Merce Rodoreda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145232-and-i-got-a-strong-feeling-of-the-passage-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I got a strong feeling of the passage of time. Not the time of clouds and sun and rain and the moving stars that adorn the night, not spring when its time comes or fall, not the time that makes leaves bud on branches and then tears them off or folds and unfolds and colors the flowers, but the time inside me, the time you can't see but it molds us. The time that rolls on and on in people's hearts and makes them roll along with it and gradually changes us inside and out and makes us what we'll be on our dying day." -- Merce Rodoreda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176631-that-was-how-things-were-back-then-anything-that-grew</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 13:59:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Joseph Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176631-that-was-how-things-were-back-then-anything-that-grew]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That was how things were back then.  Anything that grew took its time growing, and anything that perished took a long time to be forgotten.  But everything that had once existed left its traces, and people lived on memories just as they now live on the ability to forget quickly and emphatically." -- Joseph Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/340261-ethics-that-focus-on-human-interactions-morals-that-focus-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 10:57:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Carl Safina]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/340261-ethics-that-focus-on-human-interactions-morals-that-focus-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ethics that focus on human interactions, morals that focus on humanity's relationship to a Creator, fall short of these things we've learned. They fail to encompass the big take-home message, so far, of a century and a half of biology and ecology: life is- more than anything else- a &lt;i&gt;process&lt;/i&gt;; it creates, and depends on, &lt;i&gt;relationships&lt;/i&gt; among energy, land, water, air, time and various living things. It's not just about human-to-human interaction; it's not just about spiritual interaction. It's about &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; interaction. We're bound with the rest of life in a network, a network including not just all living things but the energy and nonliving matter that flows through the living, making and keeping all of us alive as we make &lt;i&gt;it&lt;/i&gt; alive. We can keep debating ideologies and sending entreaties toward heaven. But unless we embrace the fuller reality we're in- and reality's implications- we'll face big problems." -- Carl Safina]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/340665-saving-the-world-requires-saving-democracy-that-requires-well-informed-citizens</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 10:57:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Carl Safina]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/340665-saving-the-world-requires-saving-democracy-that-requires-well-informed-citizens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Saving the world requires saving democracy. That requires well-informed citizens. Conservation, environment, poverty, community, education, family, health, economy- these combine to make one quest: liberty and justice for all. Whether one's special emphasis is global warming or child welfare, the cause is the same cause. And justice comes from the same place being human comes from: compassion." -- Carl Safina]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32094-during-my-sixteen-years-as-a-teacher-of-writing-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 13:12:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Gerald Murnane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32094-during-my-sixteen-years-as-a-teacher-of-writing-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["During my sixteen years as a teacher of writing, I removed many adverbs and adverbial phrases from students' writing. I decided long ago that a writer who needlessly modifies words is either a nervous writer who does not believe in the worth of what they are writing or a vain writer who wants to be seen as discriminating and sensitive to nuances or meaning." -- Gerald Murnane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32098-soon-after-i-left-university-i-came-up-with-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 13:12:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Gerald Murnane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32098-soon-after-i-left-university-i-came-up-with-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Soon after I left university, I came up with another definition of a literary critic or would be critic: someoone who uses &lt;i&gt;churlish&lt;/i&gt; towards the end of an article or review." -- Gerald Murnane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21573-i-am-only-responsible-for-my-own-heart-you-offered</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 09:39:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21573-i-am-only-responsible-for-my-own-heart-you-offered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am only responsible for my own heart, you offered yours up for the smashing my darling.  Only a fool would give out such a vital organ" -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358568-out-of-the-sad-sack-of-sad-shit-that-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 07:53:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Lidia Yuknavitch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358568-out-of-the-sad-sack-of-sad-shit-that-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Out of the sad sack of sad shit that was my life, I made a wordhouse." -- Lidia Yuknavitch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437818-she-was-awake-alive-full-of-ideas-like-branches-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2012 09:20:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Carolina De Robertis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437818-she-was-awake-alive-full-of-ideas-like-branches-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was awake, alive, full of ideas like branches in a greenhouse, growing thick and rife against the glass." -- Carolina De Robertis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620132-son-never-trust-a-man-who-doesn-t-drink-because-he-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 13:17:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by James Crumley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620132-son-never-trust-a-man-who-doesn-t-drink-because-he-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Son, never trust a man who doesn’t drink because he’s probably a self-righteous sort, a man who thinks he knows right from wrong all the time. Some of them are good men, but in the name of goodness, they cause most of the suffering in the world. They’re the judges, the meddlers. And, son, never trust a man who drinks but refuses to get drunk. They’re usually afraid of something deep down inside, either that they’re a coward or a fool or mean and violent. You can’t trust a man who’s afraid of himself. But sometimes, son, you can trust a man who occasionally kneels before a toilet. The chances are that he is learning something about humility and his natural human foolishness, about how to survive himself. It’s damned hard for a man to take himself too seriously when he’s heaving his guts into a dirty toilet bowl." -- James Crumley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131354-i-feel-like-a-lot-of-time-my-writing-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 09:11:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Carolyn Chute]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131354-i-feel-like-a-lot-of-time-my-writing-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I feel like a lot of time my writing is like having about twenty boxes of Christmas decorations.  But no tree.  You're going, Where do I put this?  Then they go, Okay, you can have a tree, but we'll blindfold you and you gotta cut it down with a spoon." -- Carolyn Chute]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118970-there-is-a-loneliness-in-this-world-so-great-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 10:47:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118970-there-is-a-loneliness-in-this-world-so-great-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["there is a loneliness in this world so great
that you can see it in the slow movement of
the hands of a clock.

people so tired
mutilated
either by love or no love.

people just are not good to each other
one on one.

the rich are not good to the rich
the poor are not good to the poor.

we are afraid.

our educational system tells us
that we can all be
big-ass winners.

it hasn't told us
about the gutters
or the suicides.

or the terror of one person
aching in one place
alone

untouched
unspoken to

watering a plant." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1193838-hacks-are-killing-our-national-literary-culture-america-treats-best-sellers</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2014 14:42:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by David B. Lentz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1193838-hacks-are-killing-our-national-literary-culture-america-treats-best-sellers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hacks are killing our national literary culture. America treats best-sellers like literary lions and literary lions worse than stray dogs." -- David B. Lentz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/400293-if-the-radical-right-had-its-way-we-d-all-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 10:05:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tuck add a quote by John Nichols]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/400293-if-the-radical-right-had-its-way-we-d-all-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the radical right had its way we’d all be church-going polyester heterosexuals driving around in white Cadillacs eating meatloaf and wax beans while mammoth bulldozers leveled all our forests and even hummingbirds were extinct.”

Charley, The Voice of the Butterfly" -- John Nichols]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
