<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/565580-nicola]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/565580-nicola" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 14:57:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39829-karl-marx-got-a-bum-rap-all-he-was-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 14:57:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicola add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39829-karl-marx-got-a-bum-rap-all-he-was-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Karl Marx got a bum rap. All he was trying to do was figure out how to take care of a whole lot of people. Of course, socialism is just “evil” now. It’s completely discredited, supposedly, by the collapse of the Soviet Union. I can’t help noticing that my grandchildren are heavily in hock to communist China now, which is evidently a whole lot better at business than we are. You talk about the collapse of communism or the Soviet Union. My goodness, this country collapsed in 1929. I mean it crashed, big time, and capitalism looked like a very poor idea." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4681-you-ve-got-to-sing-like-you-don-t-need-the-money</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 15:16:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicola add a quote by Richard  Leigh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4681-you-ve-got-to-sing-like-you-don-t-need-the-money]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You’ve got to sing like you don’t need the money,
Love like you’ll never get hurt.
You’ve got to dance like nobody’s watchin’." -- Richard  Leigh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17931-if-you-want-to-really-hurt-you-parents-and-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 15:16:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicola add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17931-if-you-want-to-really-hurt-you-parents-and-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to really hurt you parents, and you don't have the nerve to be gay, the least you can do is go into the arts. I'm not kidding. The arts are not a way to make a living. They are a very human way of making life more bearable. Practicing an art, no matter how well or badly, is a way to make your soul grow, for heaven's sake. Sing in the shower. Dance to the radio. Tell stories. Write a poem to a friend, even a lousy poem. Do it as well as you possible can. You will get an enormous reward. You will have created something." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15325-the-only-difference-between-hitler-and-bush-is-that-hitler</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 15:17:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicola add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15325-the-only-difference-between-hitler-and-bush-is-that-hitler]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only difference between Hitler and Bush is that Hitler was elected." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26979-as-for-literary-criticism-in-general-i-have-long-felt</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 15:20:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicola add a quote by kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26979-as-for-literary-criticism-in-general-i-have-long-felt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As for literary criticism in general: I have long felt that any reviewer who expresses rage and loathing for a novel or a play or a poem is preposterous. He or she is like a person who has put on full armor and attacked a hot fudge sundae or a banana split." -- kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/506799-well-it-s-a-good-life-and-a-good-world-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 15:35:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicola add a quote by Alan Sillitoe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/506799-well-it-s-a-good-life-and-a-good-world-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, it's a good life and a good world, all said and done, if you don't weaken." -- Alan Sillitoe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217308-on-his-first-parade-the-sergeant-major-exclaimed-that-he-couldn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 15:35:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicola add a quote by Alan Sillitoe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217308-on-his-first-parade-the-sergeant-major-exclaimed-that-he-couldn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On his first parade the sergeant-major exclaimed that he couldn't make out the shape of Arthur's head because there was so much hair on it, and Arthur jocularly agreed to get it cut, intending to forget about it until the fifteen days was over, which he did. 'You're a soldier now, not a Teddy-boy,' the sergeant-major said, but Arthur knew he was wrong in either case. He was nothing at all when people tried to tell him what he was. Not even his own name was enough, though it might be on on his pay-book. What am I? he wondered. A six-foot pit-prop that wants a pint of ale. That's what I am. And if any knowing bastard says that's what I am, I'm a dynamite-dealer, Sten-gun seller, hundred-ton tank trader, a capstan-lathe operator waiting to blow the army to Kingdom Cum. I'm me and nobody else; and what people think I am or say I am, that's what I'm not, because they don't know a bloody thing about me." -- Alan Sillitoe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217303-for-it-was-saturday-night-the-best-and-bingiest-glad-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 15:35:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicola add a quote by Alan Sillitoe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217303-for-it-was-saturday-night-the-best-and-bingiest-glad-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For it was Saturday night, the best and bingiest glad-time of the week, one of the fifty-two holidays in the slow-turning Big Wheel of the year, a violent preamble to a prostrate Sabbath. Piled up passions were exploded on Saturday night, and the effect of a week's monotonous graft in the factory was swilled out of your system in a burst of goodwill. You followed the motto of 'be drunk and be happy,' kept your crafty arms around female waists, and felt the beer going beneficially down into the elastic capacity of your guts." -- Alan Sillitoe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211580-all-i-m-out-for-is-a-good-time---all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 15:35:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicola add a quote by Alan Sillitoe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211580-all-i-m-out-for-is-a-good-time---all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All I'm out for is a good time - all the rest is propaganda." -- Alan Sillitoe]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
