<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/565533-katy-kennedy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/565533-katy-kennedy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2009 13:58:56 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121705-sonnet-xvii-i-do-not-love-you-as-if-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2009 13:58:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121705-sonnet-xvii-i-do-not-love-you-as-if-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sonnet XVII

I do not love you as if you were salt-rose, or topaz,
or the arrow of carnations the fire shoots off.
I love you as certain dark things are to be loved,
in secret, between the shadow and the soul.

I love you as the plant that never blooms
but carries in itself the light of hidden flowers;
thanks to your love a certain solid fragrance,
risen from the earth, lives darkly in my body.

I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where.
I love you straightforwardly, without complexities or pride;
so I love you because I know no other way than this: 

where I does not exist, nor you,
so close that your hand on my chest is my hand,
so close that your eyes close as I fall asleep. " -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154332-i-love-you-so-much-i-ll-never-be-able-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 15:54:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Dylan Thomas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154332-i-love-you-so-much-i-ll-never-be-able-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you so much I’ll never be able to tell you; I’m frightened to tell you. I can always feel your heart. Dance tunes are always right: I love you body and soul: —and I suppose body means that I want to touch you and be in bed with you, and i suppose soul means that i can hear you and see you and love you in every single, single thing in the whole world asleep or awake" -- Dylan Thomas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5504-once-you-have-tasted-flight-you-will-forever-walk-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 19:47:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Leonardo da Vinci]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5504-once-you-have-tasted-flight-you-will-forever-walk-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once you have tasted flight, you will forever walk the earth with your eyes turned skyward, for there you have been, and there you will always long to return." -- Leonardo da Vinci]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
