<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/565947-joanna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/565947-joanna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 12:22:53 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 12:22:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think your pain and your heartbreak are unprecedented in the history of the world, but then you read. It was books that taught me that the things that tormented me most were the very things that connected me with all the people who were alive, or who had ever been alive." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12041-true-rebels-after-all-are-as-rare-as-true-lovers-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 12:23:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12041-true-rebels-after-all-are-as-rare-as-true-lovers-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["True rebels after all, are as rare as true lovers,and in both cases, to mistake a fever for passion can destroy one's life" -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1872-the-paradox-of-education-is-precisely-this---that-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 12:23:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1872-the-paradox-of-education-is-precisely-this---that-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The paradox of education is precisely this - that as one begins to become conscious one begins to examine the society in which he is being educated. " -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6993-people-can-t-unhappily-invent-their-mooring-posts-their-lovers-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 12:23:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6993-people-can-t-unhappily-invent-their-mooring-posts-their-lovers-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People can't, unhappily, invent their mooring posts, their lovers and their friends, anymore than they can invent their parents.  Life gives these and also takes them away and the great difficulty is to say Yes to life." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1868-i-love-america-more-than-any-other-country-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 12:23:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1868-i-love-america-more-than-any-other-country-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love America more than any other country in the world and, exactly for this reason, I insist on the right to criticize her perpetually." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1104-the-doctor-peeked-into-the-trauma-room-and-saw-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 12:25:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Denis Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1104-the-doctor-peeked-into-the-trauma-room-and-saw-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[The doctor] peeked into the trauma room and saw the situation: the clerk - that is, me - standing next to the orderly, Georgie, both of us on drugs, looking down at a patient with a knife sticking up out of his face. 

'What seems to be the trouble?' he asked." -- Denis Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6122-i-feel-very-privileged-to-hear-how-somebody-used-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 12:26:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Denis Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6122-i-feel-very-privileged-to-hear-how-somebody-used-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I feel very privileged to hear how somebody used to run around stickin' people up and stealing cars, and now they're gettin' their life back together... I just love the stories. The stories of the fallen world, they excite us. That's the interesting stuff." -- Denis Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6724-does-everything-you-touch-turn-to-shit-does-this-happen</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 12:26:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Denis Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6724-does-everything-you-touch-turn-to-shit-does-this-happen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Does everything you touch turn to shit? Does this happen to you every time?&quot;

&quot;No wonder they call me Fuckhead.&quot;

It's a name that's going to stick.


" -- Denis Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1926-the-truth-is-always-an-insult-or-a-joke-lies</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 12:26:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Katherine Dunn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1926-the-truth-is-always-an-insult-or-a-joke-lies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is always an insult or a joke, lies are generally tastier. We love them. The nature of lies is to please. Truth has no concern for anyone's comfort" -- Katherine Dunn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1925-the-child-screaming-for-refuge-senses-how-feeble-a-shelter</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 12:26:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Katherine Dunn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1925-the-child-screaming-for-refuge-senses-how-feeble-a-shelter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The child, screaming for refuge, senses how feeble a shelter the twig hut of grown-up awareness is. They claim strength, these parents, and complete sanctuary. The weeping earth itself knows how desperate is the child's need for exactly that sanctuary. How deep and sticky is the darkness of childhood, how rigid the blades of infant evil, which is unadulterated, unrestrained by the convenient cushions of age and its civilizing anesthesia. 
Grownups can deal with scraped knees, dropped ice-cream cones, and lost dollies, but if they suspected the real reasons we cry they would fling us out of their arms in horrified revulsion. Yet we are small and as terrified as we are terrifying in our ferocious appetites." -- Katherine Dunn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 18:52:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Emotions, in my experience, aren't covered by single words. I don't believe in &quot;sadness,&quot; &quot;joy,&quot; or &quot;regret.&quot; Maybe the best proof that the language is patriarchal is that it oversimplifies feeling. I'd like to have at my disposal complicated hybrid emotions, Germanic train-car constructions like, say, &quot;the happiness that attends disaster.&quot; Or: &quot;the disappointment of sleeping with one's fantasy.&quot; I'd like to show how &quot;intimations of mortality brought on by aging family members&quot; connects with &quot;the hatred of mirrors that begins in middle age.&quot; I'd like to have a word for &quot;the sadness inspired by failing restaurants&quot; as well as for &quot;the excitement of getting a room with a minibar.&quot; I've never had the right words to describe my life, and now that I've entered my story, I need them more than ever. " -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10345-gone-mad-is-what-they-say-and-sometimes-run-mad</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 18:54:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10345-gone-mad-is-what-they-say-and-sometimes-run-mad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;i&gt;Gone mad&lt;/i&gt; is what they say, and sometimes &lt;i&gt;Run mad&lt;/i&gt;, as if mad is a different direction, like west; as if mad is a different house you could step into, or a separate country entirely. But when you go mad you don't go any other place, you stay where you are. And somebody else comes in." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13110-a-hip-looking-teen-watches-an-elderly-woman-hobble-across-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 18:55:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13110-a-hip-looking-teen-watches-an-elderly-woman-hobble-across-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A hip-looking teen watches an elderly woman hobble across the street on a walker.
&quot;Grammy's here!&quot; he shouts.
He puts some MacAttack Mac&amp;Cheese in the microwave and dons headphones and takes out a video game so he won't be bored during the forty seconds it takes his lunch to cook. A truck comes around the corner and hits Grammy, sending her flying over the roof into the backyard, where luckily she lands on a trampoline. Unluckily, she bounces back over the roof, into the front yard, landing on a rosebush." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10795-don-t-own-so-much-clutter-that-you-will-be-relieved</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 10:42:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10795-don-t-own-so-much-clutter-that-you-will-be-relieved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't own so much clutter that you will be relieved to see your house catch fire." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6363-when-despair-for-the-world-grows-in-me-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 10:43:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6363-when-despair-for-the-world-grows-in-me-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When despair for the world grows in me and I wake in the night at the least sound in fear of what my life and my children's lives may be, I go and lie down where the wood drake rests in his beauty on the water, and the great heron feeds. I come into the peace of wild things who do not tax their lives with forethought of grief. I come into the presence of still water. And I feel above me the day-blind stars waiting with their light. For a time I rest in the grace of the world, and am free." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53288-a-community-is-the-mental-and-spiritual-condition-of-knowing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 10:44:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53288-a-community-is-the-mental-and-spiritual-condition-of-knowing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A community is the mental and spiritual condition of knowing that the place is shared, and that the people who share the place define and limit the possibilities of each other's lives. It is the knowledge that people have of each other, their concern for each other, their trust in each other, the freedom with which they come and go among themselves." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21305-it-is-impossible-to-prefigure-the-salvation-of-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 10:44:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21305-it-is-impossible-to-prefigure-the-salvation-of-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is impossible to prefigure the salvation of the world in the same language by which the world has been dismembered and defaced." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29945-what-can-turn-us-from-this-deserted-future-back-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 10:46:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29945-what-can-turn-us-from-this-deserted-future-back-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What can turn us from this deserted future, back into the sphere of our being, the great dance that joins us to our home, to each other and to other creatures, to the dead and unborn? I think it is love. I am perforce aware how baldly and embarrassingly that word now lies on the page—for we have learned at once to overuse it, abuse it, and hold it in suspicion. But I do not mean any kind of abstract love (adolescent, romantic, or &quot;religious&quot;), which is probably a contradiction in terms, but particular love for particular things, places, creatures, and people, requiring stands, acts, showing its successes and failures in practical or tangible effects. And it implies a responsibility just as particular, not grim or merely dutiful, but rising out of generosity. I think that this sort of love defines the effective range of human intelligence, the range within its works can be dependably beneficent. Only the action that is moved by love for the good at hand has the hope of being responsible and generous. Desire for the future produces words that cannot be stood by. But love makes language exact, because one loves only what one knows." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63869-a-hope-fulfilled-is-already-half-a-disappointment</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 21:21:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63869-a-hope-fulfilled-is-already-half-a-disappointment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A hope fulfilled is already half a disappointment." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80383-i-cannot-be-awake-for-nothing-looks-to-me-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 10:40:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80383-i-cannot-be-awake-for-nothing-looks-to-me-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot be awake, for nothing looks to me as it did before, or else I am awake for the first time, and all before has been a mean sleep." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
