<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/567427-danalee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/567427-danalee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 08:38:26 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16840-the-issue-is-truth-my-dear-brothers-and-sisters-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 08:38:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Elder F. Enzio Busche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16840-the-issue-is-truth-my-dear-brothers-and-sisters-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The issue is truth, my dear brothers and sisters, and the only way to find truth is through uncompromising self-education toward self-honesty to see the original “real me,” the child of God, in its innocence and potential in contrast to the influence from the other part of me, “the flesh,” with its selfish desires and foolishness. Only in that state of pure honesty are we able to see truth in its complete dimension. Honesty may not be everything, but everything is nothing without honesty. In its final state, honesty is a gift of the Spirit through which the true disciples of Christ" -- Elder F. Enzio Busche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16841-with-time-and-perspective-we-recognize-that-such-problems-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 08:41:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Jeffery R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16841-with-time-and-perspective-we-recognize-that-such-problems-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With time and perspective we recognize that such problems in life do come for a purpose, if only to allow the one who faces such despair to be convinced that he really does need divine strength beyond himself, that she really does need the offer of heaven’s hand. Those who feel no need for mercy usually never seek it and almost never bestow it. Those who have never had a heartache or a weakness or felt lonely or forsaken never have had to cry unto heaven for relief of such personal pain. Surely it is better to find the goodness of God and the grace of Christ, even at the price of despair, than to risk living our lives in a moral or material complacency that has never felt any need for faith or forgiveness, any need for redemption or relief." -- Jeffery R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7768-i-hope-i-shall-possess-firmness-and-virtue-enough-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 08:52:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by George Washington]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7768-i-hope-i-shall-possess-firmness-and-virtue-enough-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hope I shall possess firmness and virtue enough to maintain what I consider the most enviable of all titles, the character of an honest man." -- George Washington]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16843-you-get-to-know-who-you-really-are-in-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 08:53:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Oprah Winfrey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16843-you-get-to-know-who-you-really-are-in-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You get to know who you really are in a crisis." -- Oprah Winfrey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16844-the-greater-the-difficulty-the-more-glory-in-surmounting-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 08:54:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Epictetus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16844-the-greater-the-difficulty-the-more-glory-in-surmounting-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greater the difficulty, the more glory in surmounting it. Skillful pilots gain their reputation from storms and tempests. " -- Epictetus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 23:28:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48160-struggle-is-the-food-from-which-change-is-made-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2008 20:25:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Danny Dreyer ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48160-struggle-is-the-food-from-which-change-is-made-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Struggle is the food from which change is made, and the best time to make the most of a struggle is when it's right in front of your face. 

Now, I know that might sound a bit simplistic. But, too often we're led to believe that struggling is a bad thing, or that we struggle because we're doing something wrong. 

I disagree. I look at struggle as an opportunity to grow. True struggle happens when you can sense what is not working for you and you're willing to take the appropriate action to correct the situation. Those who accomplish change are willing to engage the struggle." -- Danny Dreyer ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73356-if-thou-art-indeed-my-father-then-hast-thou-stained</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 23:17:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73356-if-thou-art-indeed-my-father-then-hast-thou-stained]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If thou art indeed my father, then hast thou stained thy sword in the life-blood of thy son. And thous didst it of thine obstinacy. For I sought to turn thee unto love, and I implored of thee thy name, for I thought to behold in thee the tokens recounted of my mother. But I appealed unto thy heart in vain, and now is the time gone for meeting." -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135540-now-you-wouldn-t-believe-me-if-i-told-you-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 22:39:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Winston Groom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135540-now-you-wouldn-t-believe-me-if-i-told-you-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now you wouldn't believe me if I told you, but I could run like the wind blows. From that day on, if I was ever going somewhere, I was running!" -- Winston Groom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 22:40:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Insanity is doing the same thing, over and over again, but expecting different results." -- Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 22:41:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many books, so little time." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 22:42:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opposite of love is not hate, it's indifference. The opposite of art is not ugliness, it's indifference. The opposite of faith is not heresy, it's indifference. And the opposite of life is not death, it's indifference." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 22:44:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1776-remember-if-the-time-should-come-when-you-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 22:44:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1776-remember-if-the-time-should-come-when-you-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember, if the time should come when you have to make a choice between what is right and what is easy, remember what happened to a boy who was good, and kind, and brave, because he strayed across the path of Lord Voldemort.  Remember Cedric Diggory." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 22:47:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 22:50:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 22:51:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is our choices, Harry, that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/660-i-believe-in-christianity-as-i-believe-that-the-sun</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 22:51:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/660-i-believe-in-christianity-as-i-believe-that-the-sun]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in Christianity as I believe that the sun has risen: not only because I see it, but because by it I see everything else." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6946-not-all-of-us-can-do-great-things-but-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 22:55:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6946-not-all-of-us-can-do-great-things-but-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not all of us can do great things. But we can do small things with great love." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12357-i-wish-it-need-not-have-happened-in-my-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 10:48:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12357-i-wish-it-need-not-have-happened-in-my-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish it need not have happened in my time,&quot; said Frodo.
&quot;So do I,&quot; said Gandalf, &quot;and so do all who live to see such times. But that is not for them to decide. All we have to decide is what to do with the time that is given us." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114306-how-do-you-pick-up-the-threads-of-an-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 10:51:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114306-how-do-you-pick-up-the-threads-of-an-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How do you pick up the threads of an old life? How do you go on, when in your heart, you begin to understand, there is no going back? There are some things that time cannot mend. Some hurts that go too deep...that have taken hold." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66815-if-i-love-you-i-will-carry-for-you-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 20:23:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66815-if-i-love-you-i-will-carry-for-you-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I love you, I will carry for you all your pain, I will assume for you all your debts (in every definition of the word), I will protect you from your own insecurity, I will protect upon you all sorts of good qualities that you have never actually cultivated in yourself and I will buy Christmas presents for your entire family. I will give you the sun and the rain, and if they are not available, I will give you a sun check and a rain check. I will give you all this and more, until I get so exhausted and depleted that the only way I can recover my energy is by becoming infatuated with someone else." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26192-i-had-rather-be-shut-up-in-a-very-modest</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 20:26:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26192-i-had-rather-be-shut-up-in-a-very-modest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had rather be shut up in a very modest cottage with my books, my family and a few old friends, dining on simple bacon, and letting the world roll on as it liked, than to occupy the most splendid post, which any human power can give." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74445-as-you-grow-older-you-ll-see-white-men-cheat-black</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 20:26:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74445-as-you-grow-older-you-ll-see-white-men-cheat-black]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As you grow older, you'll see white men cheat black men every day of your life, but let me tell you something and don't you forget it - whenever a white man does that to a black man, no matter who he is, how rich he is, or how fine a family he comes from, he is trash." -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227838-you-can-measure-the-happiness-of-a-marriage-by-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 20:27:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227838-you-can-measure-the-happiness-of-a-marriage-by-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can measure the happiness of a marriage by the number of scars that each partner carries on their tongues, earned from years of biting back angry words." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105031-i-also-believe-that-parents-if-they-love-you-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 20:29:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105031-i-also-believe-that-parents-if-they-love-you-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I also believe that parents, if they love you, will hold you up safely, above their swirling waters, and sometimes that means you'll never know what they endured, and you may treat them unkindly, in a way you otherwise wouldn't." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74796-friendship-is-everything-friendship-is-more-than-talent-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 20:29:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Mario Puzo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74796-friendship-is-everything-friendship-is-more-than-talent-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is everything. Friendship is more than talent. It is more than the government. It is almost the equal of family.- Don Corleone" -- Mario Puzo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23026-god-has-brought-us-together-as-families-to-bring-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 20:30:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23026-god-has-brought-us-together-as-families-to-bring-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God has brought us together as families to bring to pass His eternal purposes. We are part of this plan in this marriage relationship. let us love and respect and honor one another. We can do it, and we will be the better for it." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228961-it-is-easy-to-say-that-you-can-adopt-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 20:44:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Orson Scott Card]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228961-it-is-easy-to-say-that-you-can-adopt-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is easy to say that you can adopt the whole human race as your children, but it is not the same as living in a home with a child and shaping all you do to help him learn to be happy and whole and good.  Don't live your life without ever holding a child in your arms, on your lap, in your home, and feeling a child's arms around you and hearing his voice in your ear and seeing his smile, given to you because you put it into your heart." -- Orson Scott Card]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/458442-the-fact-is-there-is-no-foundation-no-secure-ground</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 20:54:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danalee add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/458442-the-fact-is-there-is-no-foundation-no-secure-ground]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fact is, there is no foundation, no secure ground, upon which people may stand today if it isn’t the family. If you don’t have the support and love and caring and concern that you get from a family, you don’t have much at all. Love is so supremely important. As our great poet Auden said, ‘Love each other or perish’." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
