<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/567518-bo-abeille]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/567518-bo-abeille" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 00:48:42 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19693-the-one-thing-that-everybody-wants-is-to-be-free-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 00:48:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Gertrude Stein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19693-the-one-thing-that-everybody-wants-is-to-be-free-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The one thing that everybody wants is to be free...not to be managed, threatened, directed, restrained, obliged, fearful, administered, they want none of these things they all want to feel free, the word discipline, and forbidden and investigated and imprisoned brings horror and fear into all hearts, they do not want to be afraid not more than is necessary in the ordinary business of living where one has to earn one's living and has to fear want and disease and death....The only thing that any one wants now is to be free, to be let alone, to live their life as they can, but not to be watched, controlled and scared, no no, not.

~ September, 1943" -- Gertrude Stein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19695-i-started-writing-because-of-a-terrible-feeling-of-powerlessness</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 00:58:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Wally Lamb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19695-i-started-writing-because-of-a-terrible-feeling-of-powerlessness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I started writing because of a terrible feeling of powerlessness,&quot; the novelist Anita Brookner has said. The National Book Award winner Alice McDermott noted that the most difficult thing about becoming a writer was convincing herself that she had anything to say that people would want to read. &quot;There's nothing to writing,&quot; the columnist Red Smith once commented.  &quot;All you do is sit down at a typewriter and open a vein." -- Wally Lamb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19696-the-hair-on-your-head-affects-people-and-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 01:00:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Wally Lamb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19696-the-hair-on-your-head-affects-people-and-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The hair on your head affects people and is a testament to the world about who you are.
- Bonnie Foreshaw (Tabatha Rowley's story)" -- Wally Lamb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1222-you-cannot-find-peace-by-avoiding-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 01:01:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1222-you-cannot-find-peace-by-avoiding-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You cannot find peace by avoiding life." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47211-dear-leonard-to-look-life-in-the-face-always-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 01:02:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Michael Cunningham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47211-dear-leonard-to-look-life-in-the-face-always-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dear Leonard. To look life in the face. Always to look life in the face and to know it for what it is. At last to know it. To love it for what it is, and then, to put it away. Leonard. Always the years between us. Always the years. Always the love. Always the hours." -- Michael Cunningham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19698-what-does-it-mean-to-regret-when-you-have-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 01:03:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Michael Cunningham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19698-what-does-it-mean-to-regret-when-you-have-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What does it mean to regret when you have no choice? It's what you can bear. And there it is... It was death. I chose life." -- Michael Cunningham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19699-clarissa-had-a-theory-in-those-days---they-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 01:04:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19699-clarissa-had-a-theory-in-those-days---they-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Clarissa had a theory in those days - they had heaps of theories, always theories, as young people have. It was to explain the feeling they had of dissatisfaction; not knowing people; not being known. For how could they know each other? You met every day; then not for six months, or years. It was unsatisfactory, they agreed, how little one knew people. But she said, sitting on the bus going up Shaftesbury Avenue, she felt herself everywhere; not 'here, here, here'; and she tapped the back of the seat; but everywhere. She waved her hand, going up Shaftesbury Avenue. She was all that. So that to know her, or any one, one must seek out the people who completed them; even the places. Odd affinities she had with people she had never spoke to, some women in the street, some man behind a counter - even trees, or barns. It ended in a transcendental theory which, with her horror of death, allowed her to believe, or say that she believed (for all her scepticism), that since our apparitions, the part of us which appears, are so momentary compared with the other, the unseen part of us, which spreads wide, the unseen might survive, be recovered somehow attached to this person or that, or even haunting certain places, after death. Perhaps - perhaps." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104400-from-daydreams-on-the-road-there-was-no-waking-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 02:44:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104400-from-daydreams-on-the-road-there-was-no-waking-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From daydreams on the road there was no waking. He plodded on. He could remember everything of her save her scent. Seated in a theatre with her beside him leaning forward listening to the music. Gold scrollwork and sconces and the tall columnar folds of the drapes at either side of the stage. She held his hand in her lap and he could feel the tops of her stockings through the thin stuff of her summer dress. Freeze this frame. Now call down your dark and your cold and be damned." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5138-people-were-always-getting-ready-for-tomorrow-i-didn-t-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 02:44:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5138-people-were-always-getting-ready-for-tomorrow-i-didn-t-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People were always getting ready for tomorrow. I didn't believe in that. Tomorrow wasn't getting ready for them. It didn't even know they were there." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124577-he-was-just-hungry-papa-he-s-going-to-die-he-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 02:45:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124577-he-was-just-hungry-papa-he-s-going-to-die-he-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was just hungry, Papa.  He's going to die.
He's going to die anyway.
He's so scared, Papa.
The man squatted and looked at him.  I'm scared, he said.  Do you understand?  I'm scared.
The boy didn't answer.  He just sat there with his head down, sobbing.
You're not the one who has to worry about everything.
The boy said something but he couldn't understand him.  What? He said.
He looked up, his wet and grimy face.  Yes I am, he said.  I am the one." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133400-when-you-ve-nothing-else-construct-ceremonies-out-of-the-air</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 02:46:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133400-when-you-ve-nothing-else-construct-ceremonies-out-of-the-air]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you've nothing else construct ceremonies out of the air and breathe upon them." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37700-he-thought-each-memory-recalled-must-do-some-violence-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 02:46:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37700-he-thought-each-memory-recalled-must-do-some-violence-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He thought each memory recalled must do some violence to its origins. As in a party game. Say the words and pass it on. So be sparing. What you alter in the remembering has yet a reality, known or not." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104406-no-lists-of-things-to-be-done-the-day-providential</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 02:47:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104406-no-lists-of-things-to-be-done-the-day-providential]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No lists of things to be done. The day providential to itself. The hour. There is no later. This is later. All things of grace and beauty such that one holds them to one's heart have a common provenance in pain. Their birth in grief and ashes." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120201-just-remember-that-the-things-you-put-into-your-head</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 02:47:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120201-just-remember-that-the-things-you-put-into-your-head]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just remember that the things you put into your head are there forever, he said." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18739-to-be-regularly-gay-was-to-do-every-day-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 06:28:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Gertrude Stein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18739-to-be-regularly-gay-was-to-do-every-day-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be regularly gay was to do every day the gay thing that they did every day. To be regularly gay was to end every day at the same time after they had been regularly gay. They were regularly gay. They were gay every day. They ended every day in the same way, at the same time, and they had been every day regularly gay." -- Gertrude Stein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20889-there-is-just-this-for-consolation-an-hour-here-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 00:59:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Michael Cunningham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20889-there-is-just-this-for-consolation-an-hour-here-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is just this for consolation: an hour here or there, when our lives seem, against all odds and expectations, to burst open and give us everything we've ever imagined , though everyone but children (and perhaps even they) knows these hours will inevitably be followed by others, far darker and more difficult. Still, we cherish the city, the morning, we hope, more than anything, for more. Heaven only knows why we love it so." -- Michael Cunningham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95737-we-throw-our-parties-we-abandon-our-families-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 01:00:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Michael Cunningham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95737-we-throw-our-parties-we-abandon-our-families-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We throw our parties; we abandon our families to live alone in Canada; we struggle to write books that do not change the world, despite our gifts and our unstinting efforts, our most extravagant hopes. We live our lives, do whatever we do, and then we sleep. It's as simple and ordinary as that. A few jump out windows, or drown themselves, or take pills; more die by accident; and most of us are slowly devoured by some disease, or, if we're very fortunate, by time itself. There's just this for consolation: an hour here or there when our lives seem, against all odds and expectations, to burst open and give us everything we've ever imagined, though everyone but children (and perhaps even they) know these hours will inevitably be followed by others, far darker and more difficult. Still, we cherish the city, the morning; we hope, more than anything, for more. Heaven only knows why we love it so..." -- Michael Cunningham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266857-silly-little-plastic-belt-made-for-a-skinny-pinny-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 21:15:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266857-silly-little-plastic-belt-made-for-a-skinny-pinny-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Silly little plastic belt, made for a skinny pinny; it could barely tie around her.  She managed, though - a tiny white bow.  Waiting, she folded her hands and realized how every single time she went by this hospital, the same two thoughts occurred to her:  that she'd been born here and that her father's body had been brought here after his suicide.  She'd been through some things, but never mind.  She straightened her back.  Other people had been through things, too." -- Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266858-there-were-days---she-could-remember-this---when</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 21:17:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266858-there-were-days---she-could-remember-this---when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There were days - she could remember this - when Henry would hold her hand as they walked home, middle-aged people, in their prime.  Had they known at these moments to be quietly joyful?  Most likely not.  People mostly did not know enough when they were living life that they were living it.  But she had that memory now, of something healthy and pure." -- Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135413-what-young-people-didn-t-know-she-thought-lying-down-beside</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 21:20:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135413-what-young-people-didn-t-know-she-thought-lying-down-beside]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What young people didn't know, she thought, lying down beside this man, his hand on her shoulder, her arm; oh, what young people did not know. They did not know that lumpy, aged, and wrinkled bodies were as needy as their own young, firm ones, that love was not to be tossed away carelessly . . . No, if love was available, one chose it, or didn't chose it. And if her platter had been full with the goodness of Henry and she had found it burdensome, had flicked it off crumbs at a time, it was because she had not know what one should know: that day after day was unconsciously squandered. . . . But here they were, and Olive pictured two slices of Swiss cheese pressed together, such holes they brought to this union--what pieces life took out of you." -- Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267373-you-really-can-t-go-through-life-wanting-to-be-liked</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2010 18:38:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Jimmy McDonough]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267373-you-really-can-t-go-through-life-wanting-to-be-liked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You really can't go through life wanting to be liked.  It's the hardest lesson to learn.  Once you say, &quot;Fuck it, I don't care,&quot; once you've got that attitude, then it's easy to relax, to talk, laugh, cry, whatever." -- Jimmy McDonough]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268281-i-have-now-traveled-so-far-south-that-i-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 00:45:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Geraldine Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268281-i-have-now-traveled-so-far-south-that-i-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have now traveled so far south that I find myself come to a place where our common expression “white as snow” has no useful meaning. Here, one who wishes his words to make plain sense had better say “white as cotton.” I will not say that I find the landscape lovely. We go on through Nature to God, and my Northern eye misses the grandeur that eases that ascent. I yearn for mountains, or at least for the gentle ridges of Massachusetts; the sweet folds and furrows that offer the refreshment of a new vista as each gap or summit is obtained. Here all is obvious, a song upon a single note. One wakes and falls asleep to a green sameness, the sun like a pale egg yolk, peering down from a white sky.
And the river! Water as unlike our clear fast-flowing freshets as a fat broody hen to a hummingbird. Brown as treacle, wider than a harbor, this is water sans sparkle or shimmer. In places, it roils as if heated below by a hidden furnace. In others, it sucks the light down and gives back naught but an inscrutable sheen that conceals both depth and shallows. It is a mountebank, this river. It feigns a gentle lassitude, yet coiled beneath are currents that have crushed the trunks of mighty trees, and swept men to swift drownings…" -- Geraldine Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268282-i-recognized-the-tokens-of-the-time-because-i-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 00:46:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Geraldine Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268282-i-recognized-the-tokens-of-the-time-because-i-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I recognized the tokens of the time, because I had lived through just such another uneasy season, when every day was tainted by the foul breath of a fear that could not be faced forthrightly, yet could not be ignored." -- Geraldine Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268283-i-did-note-this-and-set-it-down-as-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 00:46:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Geraldine Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268283-i-did-note-this-and-set-it-down-as-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I did note this, and set it down as yet one more of life’s injustices: that the man who has been wealthy is dunned more civilly than the fellow who has ever been poor. My creditors would come to me most graciously, diffident, if not downright apologetic, for asking what was theirs. It was as if I would be doing them a great, unlooked for kindness if only I would pay them a trifling sum on my outstanding debts. I would give them tea, and polite conversation, and, even when my answer to their just entreaty had to be a regretful, “Nothing, sir, ” my mortification was always entirely self-inflicted, for their civility never failed" -- Geraldine Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268285-i-could-feel-monika-nudging-me-furiously-at-this-point</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 00:47:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Zoe Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268285-i-could-feel-monika-nudging-me-furiously-at-this-point]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I could feel Monika nudging me furiously at this point, but I refused to look at her. I wasn’t feeling particularly reverent about my mother’s deadness, or about the vicar, but I do despise that ghastly, ‘You’ve got to laugh, haven’t you?’ approach to religious occasions. As a young man, I often goaded my believing friends with crudely logical questions about God. But as the years have passed, I have found myself hankering more and more for a little cosy voodoo in my life. Increasingly, I regard my atheism as a regrettable limitation. It seems to me that my lack of faith is not, as I once thought, a triumph of the rational mind, but rather, a failure of the imagination - an inability to tolerate mystery: a species, in fact, of neurosis. There is no chance of my being converted, of course - it is far too late for that. But I wish it wasn’t." -- Zoe Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268286-meir-let-me-ask-you-something-i-said-after-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 00:47:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Zoe Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268286-meir-let-me-ask-you-something-i-said-after-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Meir, let me ask you something,” I said after a while.
“Sure.”
“Do you think I’m a bad person?”
“Only God knows that for sure, Willy.”
“So you don’t have an opinion at all?”
“Not one that really matters.”
“Okay, let me ask you something else. If the Polish peasant who hid Jews from the Nazis is a hero, what is the Polish peasant who turned the Jews away? Is he a coward?”
Meir smiled, “Of course.”
“Really? A coward? A bad man?”
“A coward isn’t a bad man, necessarily. You can’t know if you’re a bad man until you die.”
“You’ve got to wait until you hear god’s decision?”
“Well, yes, that’s true. But I meant something else. Only when you die do you run out of chances to be good. Until then, there is always the possibility of turning yourself around." -- Zoe Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274889-my-self-is-all-to-me-i-don-t-have-any</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 21:09:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Joyce Carol Oates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274889-my-self-is-all-to-me-i-don-t-have-any]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My self is all to me. I don't have any need of you." -- Joyce Carol Oates]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274891-and-that-s-the-insult-of-it-how-always-it-comes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 21:11:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Joyce Carol Oates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274891-and-that-s-the-insult-of-it-how-always-it-comes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And that's the insult of it, how always it comes back to a woman being a &quot;good&quot; mother in the world's eyes or a &quot;bad&quot; mother, how everything in a woman's life is funneled through her body between her legs." -- Joyce Carol Oates]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274892-because-we-are-linked-by-blood-and-blood-is-memory</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 21:12:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Joyce Carol Oates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274892-because-we-are-linked-by-blood-and-blood-is-memory]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because we are linked by blood and blood is memory without language." -- Joyce Carol Oates]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274895-the-fact-was-that-the-woman-lived-the-life-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 21:16:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bo add a quote by Joyce Carol Oates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274895-the-fact-was-that-the-woman-lived-the-life-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fact was that the woman lived the life she chose, she was happy in that life and it was no one's business after all but her own, my uncle's face darkening with blood as he spoke, my mother's fair fine skin pink as if smarting yet still I persisted, for I thought it such a horror, such a grief, yes and an embarrassment too, I said, &quot;She's made a prison of this house, it's like she's a nun, it must be to punish herself,&quot; and my mother said quietly, angrily, &quot;You don't know - what do you know! People do what they want to do." -- Joyce Carol Oates]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
