<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/570393-crystal]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/570393-crystal" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 14:57:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390638-mr-bradford-she-said-i-m-not-going-to-propose-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 14:57:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by Heather Dixon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390638-mr-bradford-she-said-i-m-not-going-to-propose-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mr. Bradford,&quot; she said. &quot;I'm not going to propose to you.&quot;

The twinkle in Mr. Bradford's eyes faded. So did his smile. He managed to keep it on his face. It looked painful.

&quot;Oh,&quot; he said.

&quot;Mr. Bradford?&quot;

&quot;Yes?&quot;

&quot;Would you mind it so very much if...you know...you proposed to me?&quot;

The light in Mr. Bradford's eyes jumped to life. He beamed so largely it almost wasn't crooked.

&quot;If you want." -- Heather Dixon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390688-bramble-s-lips-were-tight-her-fists-still-shook-take-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 14:59:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by Heather Dixon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390688-bramble-s-lips-were-tight-her-fists-still-shook-take-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bramble's lips were tight. Her fists still shook.

&quot;Take it back,&quot; she said. She gazed at the floor, but the words whipped. &quot;We don't want the picture. We don't want your &lt;i&gt;charity&lt;/i&gt;. Take it back!&quot;

Teddie drew himself up to his full, towering taffy height.

&quot;N-dash it-O!&quot; he said. &quot;It's not &lt;i&gt;charity&lt;/i&gt; and I won't take it back! It's a gift! A &lt;i&gt;gift&lt;/i&gt;, dash it all! Because I liked your mum! And I like your sisters! And &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;, Bramble! I &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; you!&quot;

The words echoed. Everyone's hands clasped over their mouths, and they stared at Lord Teddie, who panted but kept a tight chin up. Bramble's lips were still pursed. They were white.

&quot;Young man,&quot; said the King gently. &quot;Your ship leaves soon?&quot;

Azalea guessed that, with the fiasco of everything, the King had annulled any arrangements between Bramble and Lord Teddie. Lord Teddie's entire taffylike form slumped. He turned to go, all bounciness dissolved.

&quot;Do you mean it?&quot;

Lord Teddie turned quickly. Bramble's lips remained tight, but her gaze was up, blazing yellow.

&quot;Gad, &lt;i&gt;yes&lt;/i&gt;,&quot; said Lord Teddie. &quot;I love you so much, my fingers hurt!&quot;

&quot;Oh!&quot; Bramble slapped he hand over her mouth and doubled over. &quot;Oh-oh-oh-&lt;i&gt;oh&lt;/i&gt;!&quot; She shook. It was hard to tell if she was crying, or coughing, or ill. &quot;&lt;i&gt;Oh!&lt;/i&gt;&quot;

In a billow of skirts, Bramble leaped. It was a grand jete worthy of the Delchastrian prima ballerina. She landed right on Lord Teddie, who had no choice but to catch her, and threw her arms around his neck. Then, to everyone's shock, she pressed her lips full on his.

&quot;Oh...my,&quot; said Clover.

No one seemed more surprised than Lord Teddie who stumbled back under Bramble's assault." -- Heather Dixon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
