<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/570506-tamara]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/570506-tamara" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 15:35:32 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4799-how-far-you-go-in-life-depends-on-your-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 15:35:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tamara add a quote by George Washington Carver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4799-how-far-you-go-in-life-depends-on-your-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How far you go in life depends on your being tender with the young, compassionate with the aged, sympathetic with the striving and tolerant of the weak and strong. Because someday in your life you will have been all of these. " -- George Washington Carver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28322-hold-everything-in-your-hands-lightly-otherwise-it-hurts-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 21:56:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tamara add a quote by Corrie Ten Boom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28322-hold-everything-in-your-hands-lightly-otherwise-it-hurts-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hold everything in your hands lightly, otherwise it hurts when God pries your fingers open." -- Corrie Ten Boom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18290-they-spoke-almost-as-loud-as-feeling-and-that-clamoured</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 21:58:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tamara add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18290-they-spoke-almost-as-loud-as-feeling-and-that-clamoured]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They spoke almost as loud as Feeling: and that clamoured wildly. &quot;Oh, comply!&quot; it said. &quot;Think of his misery; think of his danger — look at his state when left alone; remember his headlong nature; consider the recklessness following on despair — soothe him; save him; love him; tell him you love him and will be his. Who in the world cares for you? or who will be injured by what you do?&quot;

Still indomitable was the reply — &quot;I care for myself. The more solitary, the more friendless, the more unsustained I am, the more I will respect myself. I will keep the law given by God; sanctioned by man. I will hold to the principles received by me when I was sane, and not mad — as I am now. Laws and principles are not for the times when there is no temptation: they are for such moments as this, when body and soul rise in mutiny against their rigour; stringent are they; inviolate they shall be. If at my individual convenience I might break them, what would be their worth? They have a worth — so I have always believed; and if I cannot believe it now, it is because I am quite insane — quite insane: with my veins running fire, and my heart beating faster than I can count its throbs. Preconceived opinions, foregone determinations, are all I have this hour to stand by: there I plant my foot." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382192-it-always-is-harder-to-be-left-behind-than-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2014 08:39:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tamara add a quote by Bodie Thoene; Brock Thoene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382192-it-always-is-harder-to-be-left-behind-than-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It always is harder to be left behind than to be the one to go..." -- Bodie Thoene; Brock Thoene]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
