<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/570510-jan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/570510-jan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 22:24:49 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/867-his-laughter-echoed-through-my-mind-i-have-a-beautiful</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 22:24:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by Katie MacAlister]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/867-his-laughter-echoed-through-my-mind-i-have-a-beautiful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His laughter echoed through my mind. I have a beautiful woman in my arms, and am taking her back to my home, where she and I will be alone and able to indulge whatever fantasies we choose. What is there not to enjoy?" -- Katie MacAlister]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873-i-should-warn-you-i-m-an-expert-on-vampires-i-ve</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 23:03:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by Katie MacAlister]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873-i-should-warn-you-i-m-an-expert-on-vampires-i-ve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I should warn you, I’m an expert on vampires. I’ve seen every episode made of Buffy, Angel, and Forever Knight, so don’t think a little fang-flashing is going to scare me.” – Nell to Adrian

Oh, my God! You bit me on the leg! You drank my blood! I am not an appetizer!” You are much more then an appetizer. You are a twelve-course banquet. – Nell &amp; Adrian

I slid my tongue around the glossy enamel of his teeth, pausing to stroke down the length of an elongated canine tooth.
Yeah. I know. How stupid is it to French kiss a vampire and not expect sharp teeth? – Nell" -- Katie MacAlister]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/868-you-think-i-am-very-cute-you-think-me-sexy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 22:26:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by Katie MacAlister]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/868-you-think-i-am-very-cute-you-think-me-sexy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think I am very cute, you think me sexy, as well. I can read your thoughts, remember.” 

I hoisted myself up and slid across his body. You are conceited, arrogant, and domineering, everything I dislike in a man. 
And you are independent, stubborn, and heedless, everything I dislike in a women. 
I slid my hands under his back and kissed his dampened lips. So why is it that I love you so much? 

He smiled a smug, masculine little smile and captured my legs with his. 
Because I love you, and to be loved by a Dark One is enough for any woman.

I pinched him in a particularly vulnerable spot and allowed him to kiss me with all the sexy arrogance he had." -- Katie MacAlister]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/874-honest-to-god-clare-you-act-like-the-dress-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 23:10:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by Katie MacAlister]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/874-honest-to-god-clare-you-act-like-the-dress-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Honest to god, Clare, you act like the dress is more important than you being shot!”
Of course it is! It’s a Versace, you idiot! Bring help! I’m going to save this dress at all costs.” - Sam to Clare" -- Katie MacAlister]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52627-you-want-to-his-other-eye-popped-open-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 11:09:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by Katie MacAlister]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52627-you-want-to-his-other-eye-popped-open-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You want to …?” His other eye popped open as I started to slide down his body, intent on exploring that part of him which had given me so much pleasure.  He grabbed me before I was able to move four inches.  I looked up, worried that I had done something wrong.  A familiar strained, tense look was on his face, his eyes screwed up tight.  I looked down at his penis.  It was no longer in a resting state.  “I thought you were sated?”

I was. Until you went and mentioned doing that to me.  
No! Don’t touch me there, woman! For the love of – grk!”

A half hour later, Gabriel, his arm wrapped around me because my legs were unusually weak, hustled me toward the house with a grim look on his face.

I will beat this,” he muttered.  “I am a wyvern,  I am strong.  I will control my needs long enough to give you pleasure, and you will enjoy it, &lt;b&gt;dammit!&lt;/b&gt;”
I said nothing, but I smiled. &lt;b&gt;A&lt;i&gt; lot&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;   [May and Gabriel, pg. 307]" -- Katie MacAlister]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21490-owners-of-dogs-will-have-noticed-that-if-you-provide</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 07:34:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21490-owners-of-dogs-will-have-noticed-that-if-you-provide]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Owners of dogs will have noticed that, if you provide them with food and water and shelter and affection, they will think you are god. Whereas owners of cats are compelled to realize that, if you provide them with food and water and shelter and affection, they draw the conclusion that &lt;i&gt;they&lt;/i&gt; are gods." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74466-anything-will-give-up-it-s-secrets-if-you-love-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2008 13:06:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by George Washington Carver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74466-anything-will-give-up-it-s-secrets-if-you-love-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anything will give up it's secrets if you love it enough." -- George Washington Carver]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
