<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/571699-jenny]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/571699-jenny" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 12:49:20 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5945-so-do-we-pass-the-ghosts-that-haunt-us-later</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 12:49:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jenny add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5945-so-do-we-pass-the-ghosts-that-haunt-us-later]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So do we pass the ghosts that haunt us later in our lives; they sit undramatically by the roadside like poor beggars, and we see them only from the corners of our eyes, if we see them at all. The idea that they have been waiting there for us rarely crosses our minds. Yet they do wait, and when we have passed, they gather up their bundles of memory and fall in behind, treading in our footsteps and catching up, little by little." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15411-actual-happiness-always-looks-pretty-squalid-in-comparison-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 12:49:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jenny add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15411-actual-happiness-always-looks-pretty-squalid-in-comparison-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Actual happiness always looks pretty squalid in comparison with the overcompensations for misery. And, of course, stability isn't nearly so spectacular as instability. And being contented has none of the glamour of a good fight against misfortune, none of the picturesqueness of a struggle with temptation, or a fatal overthrow by passion or doubt. Happiness is never grand." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1576-there-is-a-time-in-every-man-s-education-when-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 12:51:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jenny add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1576-there-is-a-time-in-every-man-s-education-when-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a time in every man's education when he arrives at the conviction that envy is ignorance; that imitation is suicide; that he must take himself for better, for worse, as his portion; that though the wide universe is full of good, no kernel of nourishing corn can come to him but through his toil bestowed on that plot of ground which is given to him to till. The power which resides in him is new in nature, and none but he knows what that is which he can do, nor does he know until he has tried." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
