<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/572605-kelly]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/572605-kelly" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 05:09:58 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/708011-my-needlework-teacher-suffered-from-a-problem-of-vision-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 05:09:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/708011-my-needlework-teacher-suffered-from-a-problem-of-vision-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My needlework teacher suffered from a problem of vision.  She recognised things according to expectation and environment.  If you were in a particular place, you expected to see particular things.  Sheep and hills, sea and fish; if there was an elephant in the supermarket, she'd either not see it at all, or call it Mrs. Jones and talk about fishcakes.  But most likely, she's do what most people do when confronted with something they don't understand.  Panic." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/967689-as-long-as-there-are-fuses-no-walls-are-safe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 06:06:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/967689-as-long-as-there-are-fuses-no-walls-are-safe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As long as there are fuses, no walls are safe. As long as every wall is threatened, the world can happen. Outlaws are can openers in the supermarket of life." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/954513-there-are-essential-and-inessential-insanities-the-latter-are-solar</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 15:27:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/954513-there-are-essential-and-inessential-insanities-the-latter-are-solar]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are essential and inessential insanities. The latter are solar in character, the former are linked to the moon. Inessential insanities are a brittle amalgamation of ambition, aggression, and pre-adolescent anxiety - garbage that should have been dumped long ago. Essential insanities are those impulses one instinctively senses are virtuous and correct, even though peers may regard them as coo-coo. Inessential insanities get one in trouble with one's self. Essential insanities get one in trouble with others. In fact, it may be essential. Poetry, the best of it, is lunar and is concerned with the essential insanities.-" -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
