<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/572737-brian]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/572737-brian" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 11:59:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276790-her-name-was-maude-and-she-drank-whisky-all-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 11:59:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276790-her-name-was-maude-and-she-drank-whisky-all-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her name was Maude and she drank whisky all day from a fruit jar under the counter." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292607-as-a-rule-almost-all-of-them-are-midwesterners-this-area</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2010 10:00:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292607-as-a-rule-almost-all-of-them-are-midwesterners-this-area]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As a rule, almost all of them are Midwesterners...This area of the country, what are we to say of this area of the country, Ms. Beadsman?...Both in the middle and on the fringe. The physical heart and the cultural extremity. Corn, a steady waning complex of heavy industry, and sports.  What are we to say?  We feed and stoke and supply a nation much of which doesn't know we exist. A nation we tend to be decades behind, culturally and intellectually. What are we to say about it?" -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292608-the-really-desolate-areas-can-get-pretty-crowded-of-course</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2010 10:03:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292608-the-really-desolate-areas-can-get-pretty-crowded-of-course]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The really desolate areas can get pretty crowded, of course, sometimes, so it's good to get there early, get as much wandering as you can in before noon." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292609-we-re-a-family-that-takes-its-home-entertainment-very-seriously</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2010 10:04:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292609-we-re-a-family-that-takes-its-home-entertainment-very-seriously]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're a family that takes its home entertainment very seriously." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298224-almost-kien-was-tempted-to-believe-in-happiness-that-contemptible</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2010 13:49:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Elias Canetti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298224-almost-kien-was-tempted-to-believe-in-happiness-that-contemptible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Almost Kien was tempted to believe in happiness, that contemptible life-goal of illiterates. If it came of itself, without being hunted for, if you did not hold it fast by force and treated it with a certain condescension, it  was permissible to endure its presence for a few days" -- Elias Canetti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298232-another-woman-catches-sight-of-fischerle-s-hump-on-the-ground</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2010 14:13:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Elias Canetti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298232-another-woman-catches-sight-of-fischerle-s-hump-on-the-ground]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Another woman catches sight of Fischerle's hump on the ground and runs screaming into the street: 'Murder! Murder!' She takes the hump for a corpse. Further details - she knows none. The murderer is very thin, a poor sap, how he came to do it, you shouldn't have thought it of him. Shot may be, someone  suggests. Of course, everyone heard the shot. Three streets off, the shot had been heard. Not a bit of it, that was a motor tyre. No, it was a shot! The crowd won't be done out of its shot. A threatening attitude is assumed towards the doubters. Don't let him go. An accessory. Trying to confuse the trail! Out of the building comes more news. The woman's statements are revised. The thin man has been murdered. And the corpse on the floor? It's alive. It's the murderer, he had hidden himself. He was tring to creep away between the corpse's legs when he was caught. The more recent information is more detailed. The little man is a dwarf. What do you expect, a cripple! The blow was actually struck by another. A redheaded man. Ah, those redheads. The dwarf put him up to it. Lynch him! The woman gave the alarm. Cheers for the woman! She screamed and screamed. A Woman! Doesn't know what fear is. The murderer had threatened her. The redhead. It's always the Reds. He tore her collar off. No shooting. Of course not. What did he say? Someone must have invented the shot. The dwarf. Where is he? Inside. Rush the doors! No one else can get in. It's full up. What a murder! The woman had a plateful. Thrashed her every day. Half dead, she was. What did she marry a dwarf for? I wouldn't marry a dwarf. And you with a big man to yourself. All she could find. Too few men, that's what it is. The war! Young people to-day...Quite young he was too. Not eighteen. And a dwarf already. Clever! He was born that way. I know that. I've seen him. Went in there. Couldn't stand it. Too much blood. That's why he's so thin. An hour ago he was a great, fat man. Loss of blood, horrible! I tell you corpses swell. That's drowned ones. What do you know about corpses? Took all the jewellery off the corpse he did. Did it for the jewellery. Just outside the jewellery department it was. A pearl necklace. A baroness. He was her footman. No, the baron. Ten thousand pounds. Twenty thousand! A peer of the realm! Handsome too. Why did she send him? Should he have let his wife? It's for her to let him. Ah, men. She's alive though. He's the corpse. Fancy dying like that! A peer of the realm too Serve him right. The unemployed are starving. What's he want with a pearl necklace. String 'em up I say! Mean it too. The whole lot of them. And the Theresianum too. Burn it! Make a nice blaze." -- Elias Canetti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298233-understanding-as-we-understand-it-is-misunderstanding</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2010 14:14:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Elias Canetti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298233-understanding-as-we-understand-it-is-misunderstanding]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Understanding, as we understand it, is misunderstanding." -- Elias Canetti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/324033-permanence-has-been-swept-aside-by-the-rapidity-of-empty</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 15:39:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/324033-permanence-has-been-swept-aside-by-the-rapidity-of-empty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Permanence has been swept aside by the rapidity of empty images.  The pantheon, we discover to our astonishment, is the doghouse of the burning asylum...  We think our brain is a marble mausoleum, when in fact it's a house made of cardboard boxes, a shack stranded between an empty field and an endless dusk." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
