<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/573734-kristyn]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/573734-kristyn" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2009 00:23:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4952-everywhere-i-go-i-m-asked-if-i-think-the-university</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2009 00:23:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristyn add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4952-everywhere-i-go-i-m-asked-if-i-think-the-university]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everywhere I go I'm asked if I think the university stifles writers. My opinion is that they don't stifle enough of them. There's many a best-seller that could have been prevented by a good teacher." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7558-art-never-responds-to-the-wish-to-make-it-democratic</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2009 00:23:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristyn add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7558-art-never-responds-to-the-wish-to-make-it-democratic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Art never responds to the wish to make it democratic; it is not for everybody; it is only for those who are willing to undergo the effort needed to understand it." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13158-a-story-is-a-way-to-say-something-that-can-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2009 00:26:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristyn add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13158-a-story-is-a-way-to-say-something-that-can-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A story is a way to say something that can’t be said any other way, and it takes every word in the story to say what the meaning is." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53888-there-is-something-in-us-as-storytellers-and-as-listeners</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2009 00:26:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristyn add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53888-there-is-something-in-us-as-storytellers-and-as-listeners]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is something in us, as storytellers and as listeners to stories, that demands the redemptive act, that demands that what falls at least be offered the chance to be restored. The reader of today looks for this motion, and rightly so, but what he  has forgotten is the cost of it. His sense of evil is diluted or lacking altogether, and so he has forgotten the price of restoration. When he reads a novel, he wants either his sense tormented or his spirits raised. He wants to be transported, instantly, either to mock damnation or a mock innocence." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98539-there-is-so-little-to-remember-of-anyone---an</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 07:57:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristyn add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98539-there-is-so-little-to-remember-of-anyone---an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is so little to remember of anyone - an anecdote, a conversation at a table. But every memory is turned over and over again, every word, however chance, written in the heart in the hope that memory will fulfill itself, and become flesh, and that the wanderers will find a way home, and the perished, whose lack we always feel, will step through the door finally and stroke our hair with dreaming habitual fondness not having meant to keep us waiting long." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10795-don-t-own-so-much-clutter-that-you-will-be-relieved</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2011 14:21:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristyn add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10795-don-t-own-so-much-clutter-that-you-will-be-relieved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't own so much clutter that you will be relieved to see your house catch fire." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325712-we-would-be-worse-than-we-are-without-the-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 11:54:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristyn add a quote by Mario Vargas Llosa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325712-we-would-be-worse-than-we-are-without-the-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We would be worse than we are without the good books we have read, more conformist, not as restless, more submissive, and the critical spirit, the engine of progress, would not even exist. Like writing, reading is a protest against the insufficiencies of life. When we look in fiction for what is missing in life, we are saying, with no need to say it or even to know it, that life as it is does not satisfy our thirst for the absolute – the foundation of the human condition – and should be better. We invent fictions in order to live somehow the many lives we would like to lead when we barely have one at our disposal." -- Mario Vargas Llosa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476456-for-last-year-s-words-belong-to-last-year-s-language-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 06:34:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristyn add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476456-for-last-year-s-words-belong-to-last-year-s-language-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For last year's words belong to last year's language 
And next year's words await another voice." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240349-and-then-as-the-little-plane-climbed-higher-and-olive</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 12:08:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristyn add a quote by Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240349-and-then-as-the-little-plane-climbed-higher-and-olive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And then as the little plane climbed higher and Olive saw spread out below them fields of bright and tender green in this morning sun, farther out the coastline, the ocean shiny and almost flat, tiny white wakes behind a few lobster boats--then Olive felt something she had not expected to feel again: a sudden surging greediness for life. She leaned forward, peering out the window: sweet pale clouds, the sky as blue as your hat, the new green of the fields, the broad expanse of water--seen from up here it all appeared wondrous, amazing. She remembered what hope was, and this was it. That inner churning that moves you forward, plows you through life the way the boats below plowed the shiny water, the way the plane was plowing forward to a place new, and where she was needed." -- Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309485-nobody-tells-this-to-people-who-are-beginners-i-wish</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 06:12:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristyn add a quote by Ira Glass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309485-nobody-tells-this-to-people-who-are-beginners-i-wish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody tells this to people who are beginners, I wish someone told me. All of us who do creative work, we get into it because we have good taste. But there is this gap. For the first couple years you make stuff, it’s just not that good. It’s trying to be good, it has potential, but it’s not. But your taste, the thing that got you into the game, is still killer. And your taste is why your work disappoints you. A lot of people never get past this phase, they quit. Most people I know who do interesting, creative work went through years of this. We know our work doesn’t have this special thing that we want it to have. We all go through this. And if you are just starting out or you are still in this phase, you gotta know its normal and the most important thing you can do is do a lot of work. Put yourself on a deadline so that every week you will finish one story. It is only by going through a volume of work that you will close that gap, and your work will be as good as your ambitions. And I took longer to figure out how to do this than anyone I’ve ever met. It’s gonna take awhile. It’s normal to take awhile. You’ve just gotta fight your way through." -- Ira Glass]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
