<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/573827-sheila]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/573827-sheila" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 17:45:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106581-a-man-may-possess-a-profound-knowledge-of-history-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 17:45:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sheila add a quote by David O. McKay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106581-a-man-may-possess-a-profound-knowledge-of-history-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man may possess a profound knowledge of history and mathematics; he may be an authority in psychology, biology, or astronomy; he may know all the discovered truths pertaining to geology and natural science; but if he has not with this knowledge that nobility of soul which prompts him to deal justly with his fellow men, to practice virtue and holiness in personal life, he is not a truly educated man. &quot;Character is the aim of true education; and science, history, and literature are but means used to accomplish the desired end. Character is not the result of chance work but of continuous right thinking and right acting.

&quot;True education seeks, then, to make men and women not only good mathematicians, proficient linguists, profound scientists, or brilliant literary lights, but also honest men, combined with virtue, temperance, and brotherly love-men and women who prize truth, justice, wisdom, benevolence, and self-control as the choicest acquisitions of a successful life." -- David O. McKay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92246-i-think-it-must-be-apparent-to-every-thinking-mind</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 17:45:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sheila add a quote by David O. McKay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92246-i-think-it-must-be-apparent-to-every-thinking-mind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think it must be apparent to every thinking mind that the noblest of all professions is that of teaching, and that upon the effectiveness of that teaching hangs the destiny of nations." -- David O. McKay]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
