<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/574616-rachel-hawes]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/574616-rachel-hawes" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 02:22:29 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57-she-should-have-done-science-not-spent-all-her-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 02:22:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Kate Atkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57-she-should-have-done-science-not-spent-all-her-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She should have done science, not spent all her time with her head in novels.  Novels gave you a completely false idea about life, they told lies and they implied there were endings when in reality there were no endings, everything just went on and on and on." -- Kate Atkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58-it-is-a-cruel-ironical-art-photography-the-dragging-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 02:23:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Kate Morton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58-it-is-a-cruel-ironical-art-photography-the-dragging-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a cruel, ironical art, photography. The dragging of captured moments into the future; moments that should have been allowed to be evaporate into the past; should exist only in memories, glimpsed through the fog of events that came after. Photographs force us to see people before their future weighed them down...." -- Kate Morton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1336-piglet-sidled-up-to-pooh-from-behind-pooh-he-whispered</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:34:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1336-piglet-sidled-up-to-pooh-from-behind-pooh-he-whispered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Piglet sidled up to Pooh from behind. &quot;Pooh?&quot; he whispered.
&quot;Yes, Piglet?&quot;
&quot;Nothing,&quot; said Piglet, taking Pooh's hand. &quot;I just wanted to be sure of you." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30440-some-1-2-billion-people-in-the-world-still-have-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 01:26:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Felicity Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30440-some-1-2-billion-people-in-the-world-still-have-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some 1.2 billion people in the world still have too little to eat; the same number today suffer from being overweight…..For the first time in 100 years medical experts are predicting that life expectancy in developed countries will fall.  Thanks to obesity our children face the prospect of dying younger than us." -- Felicity Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62908-humans-if-nothing-else-have-the-good-sense-to-die</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2008 03:03:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62908-humans-if-nothing-else-have-the-good-sense-to-die]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humans, if nothing else, have the good sense to die." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102910-though-i-am-still-exceedingly-puzzled-as-to-why-our-murderer</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2008 04:36:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Colin Dexter ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102910-though-i-am-still-exceedingly-puzzled-as-to-why-our-murderer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...though I am still...exceedingly puzzled as to why our murderer should decide to draw almost inevitable attention to himself by wearing such a conspicuous pair of plimsolls and running around Burford for two and a half hours." -- Colin Dexter ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213783-the-internet-was-supposed-to-liberate-knowledge-but-in-fact</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 08:32:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Ben Elton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213783-the-internet-was-supposed-to-liberate-knowledge-but-in-fact]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The internet was supposed to liberate knowledge, but in fact it buried it, first under a vast sewer of ignorance, laziness, bigotry, superstition and filth and then beneath the cloak of political surveillance.  Now...cyberspace exists exclusively to promote commerce, gossip and pornography.  And of course to hunt down sedition.  Only paper is safe.  Books are the key.  A book cannot be accessed from afar, you have to hold it, you have to read it." -- Ben Elton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214439-fog-everywhere-fog-up-the-river-where-it-flows-among</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 03:45:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214439-fog-everywhere-fog-up-the-river-where-it-flows-among]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fog everywhere. Fog up the river where it flows among green airs and meadows; fog down the river, where it rolls defiled among the tiers of shipping, and the waterside pollutions of a great (and dirty) city.... Chance people on the bridges peeping over the parapets into a nether sky of fog, with fog all round them, as if they were up in a balloon and hanging in the misty clouds." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1404-if-you-don-t-have-time-to-read-you-don-t-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 09:56:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1404-if-you-don-t-have-time-to-read-you-don-t-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you don't have time to read, you don't have the time (or the tools) to write. Simple as that." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/543097-no-reader-has-any-obligation-to-an-author-whether-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 08:06:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Stacia Kane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/543097-no-reader-has-any-obligation-to-an-author-whether-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["NO reader has ANY obligation to an author, whether it be to leave a review or to write a &quot;constructive&quot; one. I put out a product. You are consumers of that product. Since when does that mean you have to kiss my ass? Hey, I like Pop-Tarts and eat them a few times a year; since when does that mean I'm obligated to support Kellogg's in any way except legally purchasing the Pop-Tarts before I eat them? I wasn't aware that purchasing and consuming a product meant I was under some sort of fucking thrall in which I'm only allowed to either praise the Pop-Tart (which to be honest isn't hard, especially the S'mores flavor) or, if I am going to criticize a flavor, offer a specific and detailed analysis as to why, phrased in as inoffensive and gentle a manner as possible so as not to upset the gentle people at Kellogg's.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;Something in the Water?&lt;/i&gt; (blog post; January 9, 2012)]" -- Stacia Kane]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
