<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/575389-nami]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/575389-nami" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 18:58:58 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78518-age-certainly-hadn-t-conferred-any-smarts-on-me-character-maybe</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 18:58:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nami add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78518-age-certainly-hadn-t-conferred-any-smarts-on-me-character-maybe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Age certainly hadn't conferred any smarts on me. Character maybe, but mediocrity is a constant, as one Russian writer put it. Russian writers have a way with aphorisms. They probably spend all winter thinking them up." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78519-so-for-all-that-we-might-speak-words-in-each</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 19:01:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nami add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78519-so-for-all-that-we-might-speak-words-in-each]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So for all that we might speak words in each other's vicinity, this could never develop into anything that could be called a conversation. It was as though we were speaking in different languages. If the Dalai Lama were on his deathbed and the jazz musician Eric Dolphy were to try to explain to him the importance of choosing one's engine oil in accordance with changes in the sound of the bass clarinet, that exchange might have been more worthwhile and effective than my conversations with Noboru Wataya." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85437-let-me-be-the-first-to-admit-that-the-naked</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2008 17:41:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nami add a quote by James Thurber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85437-let-me-be-the-first-to-admit-that-the-naked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me be the first to admit that the naked truth about me is to the naked truth about Salvador Dali as an old ukulele in the attic is to a piano in a tree, and I mean a piano with breasts.  Senor Dali has the jump on me from the beginning.  He remembers and describes in detail what it was like in the womb.  My own earliest memory is of accompanying my father to a polling booth in Columbus, Ohio, where he voted for William McKinley." -- James Thurber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103060-reading-and-writing-are-in-themselves-subversive-acts-what-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2008 17:32:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nami add a quote by Mark Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103060-reading-and-writing-are-in-themselves-subversive-acts-what-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reading and writing are in themselves subversive acts.  What they subvert is the notion that things have to be the way they are, that you are alone, that no one has ever felt the way you have.  What occurs to people when they read Kurt is that things are much more up for grabs than they thought they were.  The world is a slightly different place just because they read a damn book.  Imagine that." -- Mark Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103556-i-fall-upon-the-thorns-of-life-i-bleed-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 22:50:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nami add a quote by Saul Bellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103556-i-fall-upon-the-thorns-of-life-i-bleed-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I fall upon the thorns of life, I bleed. And then? I fall upon the thorns of life, I bleed. And what next? I get laid, I take a short holiday, but very soon after I fall upon those same thorns with gratification in pain, or suffering in joy - who knows what the mixture is! What good, what lasting good is there in me? Is there nothing else between birth and death but what I can get out of this perversity - only a favorable balance of disorderly emotions? No freedom? Only impulses? And what about all the good I have in my heart - does it mean anything? Is it simply a joke? A false hope that makes a man feel the illusion of worth? And so he goes on with his struggles. But this good is no phony. I know it isn't. I swear it." -- Saul Bellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
