<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/575430-charlie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/575430-charlie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 02:34:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156039-suppose-two-men-at-cards-with-nothing-to-wager-save</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 02:34:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlie add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156039-suppose-two-men-at-cards-with-nothing-to-wager-save]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suppose two men at cards with nothing to wager save their lives.  Who has not heard such a tale?  A turn of the card. The whole universe for such a player has labored clanking to his moment which will tell if he is to die at that man’s hand or that man at his.  What more certain validation of a man’s worth could there be?  This enhancement of the game to its ultimate state admits no argument concerning the notion of fate.  The selection of one man over another is a preference absolute and irrevocable and it is a dull man indeed who could reckon so profound a decision without agency or significance either one.  In such games as have for their stake the annihilation of the defeated the decisions are quite clear.  This man holding this particular arrangement of cards in his hand is thereby removed from existence.  This is the nature of war, whose stake is at once the game and the authority and the justification.  Seen so, war is the truest form of divination.  It is the testing of one’s will and the will of another within that larger will which because it binds them is therefore forced to select.  War is the ultimate game because war is at last a forcing of the unity of existence.  War is god." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129192-there-is-but-one-world-and-everything-that-is-imaginable</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 02:36:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlie add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129192-there-is-but-one-world-and-everything-that-is-imaginable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is but one world and everything that is imaginable is necessary to it. For this world also which seems to us a thing of stone and flower and blood is not a thing at all but is a tale. And all in it is a tale and each tale the sum of all lesser tales and yet these are also the selfsame tale and contain as well all else within them. So everything is necessary. Every least thing. This is the hard lesson. Nothing can be dispensed with. Nothing despised. Because the seams are hid from us, you see. The joinery. The way in which the world is made. We have no way to know what could be taken away. What omitted. We have no way to tell what might stand and what might fall. And those seams that are hid from us are of course in the tale itself and the tale has no abode or place of beind except in the telling only and there it lives and makes its home and therefore we can never be done with the telling. Of the telling there is no end. And . . . in whatever . . . place by whatever . . . name or by no name at all . . . all tales are one. Rightly heard all tales are one." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238695-masks-beneath-masks-until-suddenly-the-bare-bloodless-skull</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 13:49:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlie add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238695-masks-beneath-masks-until-suddenly-the-bare-bloodless-skull]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Masks beneath masks until suddenly the bare bloodless skull." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234312-everest-silences-you-when-you-come-down-nothing-seems-worth-saying</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 13:50:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlie add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234312-everest-silences-you-when-you-come-down-nothing-seems-worth-saying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everest silences you...when you come down, nothing seems worth saying, nothing at all.  You find the nothingness wrapping you up, like a sound.  Non-being.  You can't keep it up, of course.  the world rushes in soon enough.  What shuts you up is, I think, the sight you've had of perfection: why speak if you can't manage perfect thoughts, perfect sentences?  It feels like a betrayal of what you've been through.  But it fades; you accept that certain compromises, closures, are required if you're to continue." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182397-what-kind-of-idea-are-you-are-you-the-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 13:59:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlie add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182397-what-kind-of-idea-are-you-are-you-the-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What kind of idea are you? Are you the kind that compromises, does deals, accomodates itself to society, aims to find a niche, to survive; or are you the cussed, bloody-minded, ramrod-backed type of damnfool notion that would rather break than sway with the breeze? – The kind that will almost certainly, ninety-nine times out of hundred, be smashed to bits; but, the hundredth time, will change the world." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/716942-now-you-are-walking-in-paris-all-alone-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 14:48:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlie add a quote by Guillaume Apollinaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/716942-now-you-are-walking-in-paris-all-alone-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now you are walking in Paris all alone in the crowd
 
As herds of bellowing buses drive by
 
Love's anguish tightens your throat
 
As if you were never to be loved again
 
If you lived in the old days you would enter a monastery

You are ashamed when you discover yourself reciting a prayer

You make fun of yourself and like the fire of Hell your laughter crackles
 
The sparks of your laugh gild the depths of your life

It's a painting hanging in a dark museum

And sometimes you go and look at it close up" -- Guillaume Apollinaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136879-do-not-do-what-someone-else-could-do-as-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 14:54:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlie add a quote by André Gide]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136879-do-not-do-what-someone-else-could-do-as-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not do what someone else could do as well as you. Do not say, do not write what someone else could say, could write as well as you. Care for nothing in yourself but what you feel exists nowhere else. And, out of yourself create, impatiently or patiently, the most irreplaceable of beings." -- André Gide]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
