<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/575806-kressel-housman]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/575806-kressel-housman" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2010 09:52:30 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320253-who-has-inflicted-this-upon-us-who-has-made-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2010 09:52:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kressel add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320253-who-has-inflicted-this-upon-us-who-has-made-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who has inflicted this upon us? Who has made us Jews different from all other people? Who has allowed us to suffer so terribly up till now? It is God that has made us as we are, but it will be God, too, who will raise us up again. If we bear all this suffering and if there are still Jews left, when it is over, then Jews, instead of being doomed, will be held up as an example. Who knows, it might even be our religion from which the world and all peoples learn good, and for that reason and that reason alone do we have to suffer now. We can never become just Netherlanders, or just English, or representatives of any country for that matter; we will always remain Jews, but we want to, too." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44541-laws-and-principles-are-not-for-the-times-when-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 12:17:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kressel add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44541-laws-and-principles-are-not-for-the-times-when-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Laws and principles are not for the times when there is no temptation: they are for such moments as this, when body and soul rise in mutiny against their rigour ... If at my convenience I might break them, what would be their worth?" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66879-if-there-are-words-and-wrongs-like-knives-whose-deep</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 12:16:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kressel add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66879-if-there-are-words-and-wrongs-like-knives-whose-deep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there are words and wrongs like knives, whose deep inflicted lacerations never heal - cutting injuries and insults of serrated and poison-dripping edge - so, too, there are consolations of tone too fine for the ear not fondly and for ever to retain their echo: caressing kindnesses - loved, lingered over through a whole life, recalled with unfaded tenderness, and answering the call with undimmed shine, out of that raven cloud foreshadowing Death himself." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320036-and-anyway-it-s-not-as-though-i-ll-never-see-mum</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 12:16:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kressel add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320036-and-anyway-it-s-not-as-though-i-ll-never-see-mum]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And anyway, it’s not as though I’ll never see Mum again, is it?" -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66872-i-want-to-go-on-living-even-after-my-death</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 12:33:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kressel add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66872-i-want-to-go-on-living-even-after-my-death]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to go on living even after my death! And therefore I am grateful to God for this gift, this possibility of developing myself and of writing, of expressing all that is in me. I can shake off everything if I write; my sorrows disappear; my courage is reborn. But, and that is the great question, will I ever be able to write anything great, will I ever become a journalist or a writer?" -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37907-i-saw-that-success-failure-poverty-riches-were-price-tags</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 12:17:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kressel add a quote by Anzia Yezierska]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37907-i-saw-that-success-failure-poverty-riches-were-price-tags]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I saw that &quot;success,&quot; &quot;failure,&quot; &quot;poverty&quot;, &quot;riches,&quot; were price tags, money values of the market place which had mesmerized and sidetracked me for years." -- Anzia Yezierska]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66876-what-should-i-do-with-your-strong-manly-spirited-sketches</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 12:33:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kressel add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66876-what-should-i-do-with-your-strong-manly-spirited-sketches]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What should I do with your strong, manly, spirited sketches, full of variety and glow? How could I possibly join them on to the little bit (two inches wide) of ivory on which I work with so fine a brush, as produces little effect after much labour?" -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70731-when-pharoah-restored-the-chief-butler-to-his-position-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 12:33:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kressel add a quote by Rabbi Israel Spira, the Bluzhover Rebbe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70731-when-pharoah-restored-the-chief-butler-to-his-position-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When Pharoah restored the chief butler to his position as foretold by Joseph in his interpretation of the butler's dream, he forgot Joseph. &quot;Yet the chief butler did not remember Joseph but forgot him.&quot; (Genesis 40:23). Why does the Bible use this repetitive language? It is obvious that if the butler forgot Joseph, he did not remember him. Yet both verbs are used, &quot;not remembering&quot; and &quot;forgetting.&quot;  The Bible, in using this language, is teaching us a very important lesson. There are events of such overbearing magnitude that one ought not to remember them all the time, but one must not forget them either. Such an event is the Holocaust." -- Rabbi Israel Spira, the Bluzhover Rebbe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76813-if-you-are-not-sensitive-to-rejection-doesn-t-that-also</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 12:34:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kressel add a quote by Wendy Shalit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76813-if-you-are-not-sensitive-to-rejection-doesn-t-that-also]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are not sensitive to rejection, doesn't that also mean you're indifferent to love?" -- Wendy Shalit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159085-all-these-guys-picking-on-smart-kids-and-calling-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 12:34:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kressel add a quote by Bruce Coville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159085-all-these-guys-picking-on-smart-kids-and-calling-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All these guys picking on smart kids and calling them geeks and dweebs are going to grow up and want to know why &lt;i&gt;they&lt;/i&gt; don't &lt;i&gt;do something&lt;/i&gt; about the terrible state the world is in. I can tell you why. By the time they grow up, most of the kids who realy could have changed things are wrecked. " -- Bruce Coville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159087-i-have-begun-everything-with-the-idea-that-i-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 12:34:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kressel add a quote by Booker T. Washington]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159087-i-have-begun-everything-with-the-idea-that-i-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have begun everything with the idea that I could succeed, and I never had much patience with the multitudes of people who are always ready to explain why one cannot succeed." -- Booker T. Washington]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320025-the-most-powerful-movement-of-feeling-with-a-liturgy-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 12:34:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kressel add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320025-the-most-powerful-movement-of-feeling-with-a-liturgy-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most powerful movement of feeling with a liturgy is the prayer which seeks for nothing special, but is a yearning to escape from the limitations of our own weakness and an invocation of all Good to enter and abide with us." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320028-wang-lung-sat-smoking-thinking-of-the-silver-as-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 12:34:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kressel add a quote by Pearl S. Buck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320028-wang-lung-sat-smoking-thinking-of-the-silver-as-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wang Lung sat smoking, thinking of the silver as it had lain upon the table. It had come out of the earth, this silver, out of the earth that he ploughed and turned and spent himself upon. He took his life from the earth; drop by drop by his sweat he wrung food from it and from the food, silver. Each time before this that he had taken the silver out to give to anyone, it had been like taking a piece of his life and giving it to someone carelessly. But not for the first time, such giving was not pain. He saw, not the silver in the alien hand of a merchant in the town; he saw the silver transmuted into something worth even more than life itself - clothes upon the body of his son." -- Pearl S. Buck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37917-persuading-himself-that-he-was-a-most-conscientious-and-glorious</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 12:34:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kressel add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37917-persuading-himself-that-he-was-a-most-conscientious-and-glorious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["persuading himself that he was a most
conscientious and glorious martyr, [he] nobly resolved to do what, if he had examined his own heart a little more carefully, he would have found he could not resist. Such is the sleight of hand by which we juggle with ourselves, and change our very weaknesses into stanch
and most magnanimous virtues!" -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232857-i-think-it-religion-is-an-art-the-greatest-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2010 11:43:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kressel add a quote by Dodie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232857-i-think-it-religion-is-an-art-the-greatest-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think it [religion] is an art, the greatest one; an extension of the communion all the other arts attempt." -- Dodie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1149302-the-only-two-useful-art-forms-are-religion-and-stories</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 11:23:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kressel add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1149302-the-only-two-useful-art-forms-are-religion-and-stories]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only two useful art forms are religion and stories." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
