<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/578058-dominique-rakiec]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/578058-dominique-rakiec" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 10:21:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208939-here-she-is-all-mine-trying-her-best-to-give</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 10:21:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dominique add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208939-here-she-is-all-mine-trying-her-best-to-give]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["here she is, all mine, trying her best to give me all she can. How could I ever hurt her? But I didn’t understand then. That I could hurt somebody so badly she would never recover. That a person can, just by living, damage another human being beyond repair." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2012 11:00:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dominique add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I went to the woods because I wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and see if I could not learn what it had to teach, and not, when I came to die, discover that I had not lived. I did not wish to live what was not life, living is so dear; nor did I wish to practise resignation, unless it was quite necessary. I wanted to live deep and suck out all the marrow of life, to live so sturdily and Spartan-like as to put to rout all that was not life, to cut a broad swath and shave close, to drive life into a corner, and reduce it to its lowest terms." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161661-when-you-open-yourself-to-the-continually-changing-impermanent-dynamic</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 17:35:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dominique add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161661-when-you-open-yourself-to-the-continually-changing-impermanent-dynamic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you open yourself to the continually changing, impermanent, dynamic nature of your own being and of reality, you increase your capacity to love and care about other people and your capacity to not be afraid. You're able to keep your eyes open, your heart open, and your mind open. And you notice when you get caught up in prejudice, bias, and aggression. You develop an enthusiasm for no longer watering those negative seeds, from now until the day you die. And, you begin to think of your life as offering endless opportunities to start to do things differently." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
