<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/578242-john]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/578242-john" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2007 10:12:30 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5537-our-belief-in-a-world-external-to-ourselves-filled-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2007 10:12:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by James M. Corrigan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5537-our-belief-in-a-world-external-to-ourselves-filled-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our belief in a world external to ourselves, filled with things and people that are not us, is an overwhelming fact of our existence. But similarly, our absolute certainty that there is more to reality than just this physical world is a spiritual fact that bears more truth than any other in our lives. We seek to explain this spiritual nature as some metaphysical reality, accepting the constraint of Science that will not allow for any usurpation of the actuality of the physical universe. And we flounder trying. Once we allow our thoughts to be forced into some metaphysical realm, we find ourselves stripped of that single most important validation of spiritual truth – the undeniable presence at the heart of our existence. This is the spiritual truth that we seek, and it is not to be found in the physical reality of Science. The physical reality of Science is to be found in it! “An Introduction to Awareness” is a philosophical journey that takes the reader into the heart of this pure presence of nondual reality – a reality in which the spiritual is not metaphysical, but actual, in which physical reality is 'a machine in the ghost'. This pure presence that we cannot deny is the awareness that lies at the heart of our experiences and thoughts. This irrefutable truth is used as a starting point in a processual analysis of awareness, and of our ideas about existence and self, leading to a clear understanding of the nondual nature of reality as the pure presence of non-individuated Awareness." -- James M. Corrigan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2007 16:42:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5578-then-the-trembling-starts-to-get-worse-this-must-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2007 16:44:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ken Kesey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5578-then-the-trembling-starts-to-get-worse-this-must-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then the trembling starts to get worse. This must be how they begin, he thinks. Freak-outs. Breakdowns. Crack-ups. Eventually shut-ins and finally cross-offs. But first the cover-up . . ." -- Ken Kesey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89097-the-mutual-aid-tendency-in-man-has-so-remote-an-origin</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 18:34:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Peter Kropotkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89097-the-mutual-aid-tendency-in-man-has-so-remote-an-origin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The mutual-aid tendency in man has so remote an origin, and is so deeply interwoven with all the past evolution of the human race, that is has been maintained by mankind up to the present time, notwithstanding all vicissitudes of history." -- Peter Kropotkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/598747-the-learned-ignore-the-evidence-of-their-senses-to-preserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 17:55:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Adam Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/598747-the-learned-ignore-the-evidence-of-their-senses-to-preserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The learned ignore the evidence of their senses to preserve the coherence of the ideas of their imagination." -- Adam Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119283-life-is-a-series-of-natural-and-spontaneous-changes-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 08:47:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Lao Tzu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119283-life-is-a-series-of-natural-and-spontaneous-changes-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is a series of natural and spontaneous changes. Don't resist them; that only creates sorrow. Let reality be reality. Let things flow naturally forward in whatever way they like." -- Lao Tzu]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
