<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/578344-laura-stakelum]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/578344-laura-stakelum" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 11:12:41 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17177-those-who-believe-in-telekinetics-raise-my-hand</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 11:12:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17177-those-who-believe-in-telekinetics-raise-my-hand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who believe in telekinetics, raise my hand." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6691-if-i-should-ever-die-god-forbid-let-this-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 11:12:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by kurt vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6691-if-i-should-ever-die-god-forbid-let-this-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I should ever die, God forbid, let this be my epitaph:
THE ONLY PROOF HE NEEDED
FOR THE EXISTENCE OF GOD
WAS MUSIC" -- kurt vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31808-the-letter-said-that-they-were-two-feet-high-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 11:22:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31808-the-letter-said-that-they-were-two-feet-high-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The letter said that they were two feet high, and green., and shaped like plumber's friends. Their suction cups were on the ground, and their shafts, which were extremely flexible, usually pointed to the sky. At the top of each shaft was a little hand with a green eye in its palm. The creatures were friendly, and they could see in four dimensions. They pitied Earthlings for being able to see only three. They had many wonderful things to teach Earthlings, especially about time. Billy promised to tell what some of those wonderful things were in his next letter.
Billy was working on his second letter when the first letter was published. The second letter started out like this:
The most important thing I learned on Tralfamadore was that when a person dies he only appears to die. He is still very much alive in the past, so it is very silly for people to cry at his funeral. All moments, past, present and future, always have existed, always will exist. The Tralfamadorians can look at all the different moments just that way we can look at a stretch of the Rocky Mountains, for instance. They can see how permanent all the moments are, and they can look at any moment that interests them. It is just an illusion we have here on Earth that one moment follows another one, like beads on a string, and that once a moment is gone it is gone forever.
When a Tralfamadorian sees a corpse, all he thinks is that the dead person is in a bad condition in that particular moment, but that the same person is just fine in plenty of other moments. Now, when I myself hear that somebody is dead, I simply shrug and say what the Tralfamadorians say about dead people, which is &quot;so it goes." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13800-a-man-of-genius-makes-no-mistakes-his-errors-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 10:59:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13800-a-man-of-genius-makes-no-mistakes-his-errors-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man of genius makes no mistakes.  His errors are volitional and are the portals of discovery." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
