<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/58117-sky-chapin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/58117-sky-chapin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 07:48:10 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77660-what-on-earth-can-you-do-on-this-earth-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 07:48:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Tennessee Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77660-what-on-earth-can-you-do-on-this-earth-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What on earth can you do on this earth but catch at whatever comes near you, with both your fingers, until your fingers are broken?" -- Tennessee Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79906-do-you-have-doubts-about-life-are-you-unsure-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:32:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Miranda July]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79906-do-you-have-doubts-about-life-are-you-unsure-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you have doubts about life? Are you unsure if it's worth the trouble? Look at the sky: that is for you. Look at each person's face as you pass on the street: those faces are for you. And the street itself, and the ground under the street and the ball of fire underneath the ground: all these things are for you. They are as much for you as they are for other people. Remember this when you wake up in the morning and think you have nothing. Stand up and face the east. Now praise the sky and praise the light within each person under the sky. It's okay to be unsure. But praise, praise, praise." -- Miranda July]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:33:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finish each day and be done with it. You have done what you could.  Some blunders and absurdities no doubt crept in; forget them as soon as you can. Tomorrow is a new day.  You shall begin it serenely and with too high a spirit to be encumbered with your old nonsense." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26205-she-feels-in-italics-and-thinks-in-capitals</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:33:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26205-she-feels-in-italics-and-thinks-in-capitals]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She feels in italics and thinks in CAPITALS." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46994-sorrow-comes-in-great-waves-but-rolls-over-us-and-though</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:33:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46994-sorrow-comes-in-great-waves-but-rolls-over-us-and-though]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sorrow comes in great waves...but rolls over us, and though it may almost smother us, it leaves us.  And we know that if it is strong, we are stronger, inasmuch as it passes and we remain." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134645-lost-opportunities-lost-possibilities-feelings-we-can-never-get-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:34:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134645-lost-opportunities-lost-possibilities-feelings-we-can-never-get-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lost opportunities, lost possibilities, feelings we can never get back.  That's part of what it means to be alive.  But inside our heads - at least that's where I imagine it - there's a little room where we store those memories.  A room like the stacks in this library.  And to understand the workings of our own heart we have to keep on making new reference cards.  We have to dust things off every once in awhile, let in fresh air, change the water in the flower vases.  In other words, you'll live forever in your own private library." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2830-everything-was-beautiful-and-nothing-hurt</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:34:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2830-everything-was-beautiful-and-nothing-hurt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything was beautiful and nothing hurt." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:34:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hello babies. Welcome to Earth. It's hot in the summer and cold in the winter. It's round and wet and crowded. On the outside, babies, you've got a hundred years here. There's only one rule that I know of, babies-&quot;God damn it, you've got to be kind." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3172-and-i-urge-you-to-please-notice-when-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:34:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3172-and-i-urge-you-to-please-notice-when-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I urge you to please notice when you are happy, and exclaim or murmur or think at some point, 'If this isn't nice, I don't know what is." -- Kurt Vonnegut Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14471-many-people-need-desperately-to-receive-this-message-i-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:34:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14471-many-people-need-desperately-to-receive-this-message-i-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many people need desperately to receive this message: 'I feel and think much as you do, care about many of the things you care about, although most people do not care about them. You are not alone." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42717-and-lot-s-wife-of-course-was-told-not-to-look</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:34:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42717-and-lot-s-wife-of-course-was-told-not-to-look]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And Lot's wife, of course, was told not to look back where all those people and their homes had been. But she did look back, and I love her for that, because it was so human. So she was turned into a pillar of salt. So it goes." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53603-people-get-into-a-heavy-duty-sin-and-guilt-trip-feeling</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:34:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Pema Chodron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53603-people-get-into-a-heavy-duty-sin-and-guilt-trip-feeling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People get into a heavy-duty sin and guilt trip, feeling that if things are going wrong, that means that they did something bad and they are being punished. That's not the idea at all. The idea of karma is that you continually get the teachings that you need to open your heart. To the degree that you didn't understand in the past how to stop protecting your soft spot, how to stop armoring your heart, you're given this gift of teachings in the form of your life, to give you everything you need to open further." -- Pema Chodron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120721-feelings-like-disappointment-embarrassment-irritation-resentment-anger-jealousy-and-fear</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:35:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120721-feelings-like-disappointment-embarrassment-irritation-resentment-anger-jealousy-and-fear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…feelings like disappointment, embarrassment, irritation, resentment, anger, jealousy, and fear, instead of being bad news, are actually very clear moments that teach us where it is that we’re holding back. They teach us to perk up and lean in when we feel we’d rather collapse and back away. They’re like messengers that show us, with terrifying clarity, exactly where we’re stuck. This very moment is the perfect teacher, and, lucky for us, it’s with us wherever we are." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12617-i-like-living-i-have-sometimes-been-wildly-despairingly-acutely</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:35:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Agatha Christi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12617-i-like-living-i-have-sometimes-been-wildly-despairingly-acutely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like living.  I have sometimes been wildly, despairingly, acutely miserable, racked with sorrow; but through it all I still know quite certainly that just to be alive is a grand thing." -- Agatha Christi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172406-there-are-those-who-love-to-get-dirty-and-fix</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:35:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Gary Snyder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172406-there-are-those-who-love-to-get-dirty-and-fix]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are those who love to get dirty and fix things. They drink coffee at dawn, beer after work. And those who stay clean, just appreciate things. At breakfast they have milk and juice at night. There are those who do both, they drink tea." -- Gary Snyder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254693-stay-together-learn-the-flowers-go-light</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:36:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Gary Snyder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254693-stay-together-learn-the-flowers-go-light]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["stay together
learn the flowers
go light" -- Gary Snyder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16160-but-who-can-say-what-s-best-that-s-why-you-need</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:38:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16160-but-who-can-say-what-s-best-that-s-why-you-need]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But who can say what's best? That's why you need to grab whatever chance you have of happiness where you find it, and not worry about other people too much. My experience tells me that we get no more than two or three such chances in a life time, and if we let them go, we regret it for the rest of our lives." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1323-here-s-what-i-think-mr-wind-up-bird-said-may-kasahara</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:39:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1323-here-s-what-i-think-mr-wind-up-bird-said-may-kasahara]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's what I think, Mr. Wind-Up Bird,&quot; said May Kasahara. &quot;Everybody's born with some different thing at the core of their existence. And that thing, whatever it is, becomes like a heat source that runs each person from the inside. I have one too, of course. Like everybody else. But sometimes it gets out of hand. It swells or shrinks inside me, and it shakes me up. What I'd really like to do is find a way to communicate that feeling to another person. But I can't seem to do it. They just don't get it. Of course, the problem could be that I'm not explaining it very well, but I think it's because they're not listening very well. They pretend to be listening, but they're not, really. So I get worked up sometimes, and I do some crazy things." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129633-i-dream-sometimes-i-think-that-s-the-only-right-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:41:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129633-i-dream-sometimes-i-think-that-s-the-only-right-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I dream. Sometimes I think that's the only right thing to do." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371808-as-time-goes-on-you-ll-understand-what-lasts-lasts-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 23:46:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371808-as-time-goes-on-you-ll-understand-what-lasts-lasts-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As time goes on,  you'll understand. What lasts, lasts; what doesn't, doesn't. Time solves most things. And what time can't solve, you have to solve yourself." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44544-she-waited-for-the-train-to-pass-then-she-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 08:02:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44544-she-waited-for-the-train-to-pass-then-she-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She waited for the train to pass. Then she said, &quot;I sometimes think that people’s hearts are like deep wells. Nobody knows what’s at the bottom. All you can do is imagine by what comes floating to the surface every once in a while." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16893-but-even-so-every-now-and-then-i-would-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 08:03:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16893-but-even-so-every-now-and-then-i-would-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But even so, every now and then I would feel a violent stab of loneliness. The very water I drink, the very air I breathe, would feel like long, sharp needles. The pages of a book in my hands would take on the threatening metallic gleam of razor blades. I could hear the roots of loneliness creeping through me when the world was hushed at four o'clock in the morning." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140933-not-that-we-were-incompatible-we-just-had-nothing-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 12:21:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140933-not-that-we-were-incompatible-we-just-had-nothing-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not that we were incompatible: we just had nothing to talk about." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227153-i-really-like-you-midori-a-lot-how-much-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 12:22:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227153-i-really-like-you-midori-a-lot-how-much-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I really like you, Midori. A lot.”
“How much is a lot?”
“Like a spring bear,” I said.
“A spring bear?” Midori looked up again. “What’s that all about? A spring bear.”
“You’re walking through a field all by yourself one day in spring, and this sweet little bear cub with velvet fur and shiny little eyes comes walking along. And he says to you, “Hi, there, little lady. Want to tumble with me?’ So you and the bear cub spend the whole day in each other’s arms, tumbling down this clover-covered hill. Nice, huh?”
“Yeah. Really nice.”
“That’s how much I like you." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227157-don-t-you-see-it-s-just-not-possible-for-one-person</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 12:24:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227157-don-t-you-see-it-s-just-not-possible-for-one-person]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don’t you see? It’s just not possible for one person to watch over another person forever and ever. I mean, suppose we got married. You’d have to work during the day. Who’s going to watch over me while you’re away? Or if you go on a business trip, who’s going to watch over me then? Can I be glued to you every minute of our lives? What kind of equality would there be in that? What kind of relationship would that be? Sooner or later you’d get sick of me. You’d wonder what you were doing with your life, why you were spending all your time babysitting this woman. I couldn’t stand that. It wouldn’t solve any of my problems." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414647-tell-me-how-you-could-say-such-a-thing-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 19:08:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sky add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414647-tell-me-how-you-could-say-such-a-thing-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tell me how you could say such a thing, she said, staring down at the ground beneath her feet. You're not telling me anything I don't know already. 'Relax your body, and the rest of you will lighten up.' What's the point of saying that to me? If I relaxed my body now, I'd fall apart. I've always lived like this, and it's the only way I know how to go on living. If I relaxed for a second, I'd never find my way back. I'd go to pieces, and the pieces would be blown away. Why can't you see that? How can you talk about watching over me if you can't see that?" -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
