<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/582881-sneha]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/582881-sneha" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2008 14:31:45 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2253-live-as-if-you-were-to-die-tomorrow-learn-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2008 14:31:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sneha add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2253-live-as-if-you-were-to-die-tomorrow-learn-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2008 14:32:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sneha add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be yourself in a world that is constantly trying to make you something else is the greatest accomplishment." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2008 14:32:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sneha add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2008 14:32:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sneha add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 12:08:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sneha add a quote by Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't interest me what you do for a living. I want to know what you ache for, and if you dare to dream of meeting your heart's longing.
It doesn't interest me how old you are. I want to know if you will risk looking like a fool for love, for your dream, for the adventure of being alive. 
It doesn't interest me what planets are squaring your moon. I want to know if you have touched the center of your own sorrow, if you have been opened by life's betrayals or have become shriveled and closed from fear of further pain!I want to know if you can sit with pain, mine or your own, without moving to hide it or fade it, or fix it. 
I want to know if you can be with joy, mine or your own, if you can dance with wildness and let the ecstasy fill you to the tips of your fingers and toes without cautioning us to be careful, to be realistic, to remember the limitations of being human. 
It doesn't interest me if the story you are telling me is true. I want to know if you can disappoint another to be true to yourself; if you can bear the accusation of betrayal and not betray your own soul; if you can be faithlessand therefore trustworthy. 
I want to know if you can see beauty even when it's not pretty, every day,and if you can source your own life from its presence. 
I want to know if you can live with failure, yours and mine, and still stand on the edge of the lake and shout to the silver of the full moon, “Yes!”
It doesn't interest me to know where you live or how much money you have. I want to know if you can get up, after the night of grief and despair, weary and bruised to the bone, and do what needs to be done to feed the children. 
It doesn't interest me who you know or how you came to be here. I want to know if you will stand in the center of the fire with me and not shrink back. 
It doesn't interest me where or what or with whom you have studied. I want to know what sustains you, from the inside, when all else falls away. 
I want to know if you can be alone with yourself and if you truly like the company you keep in the empty moments." -- Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9401-do-not-think-that-love-in-order-to-be-genuine</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 05:09:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sneha add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9401-do-not-think-that-love-in-order-to-be-genuine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not think that love in order to be genuine has to be extraordinary. What we need is to love without getting tired. Be faithful in small things because it is in them that your strength lies." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30954-while-i-dance-i-cannot-judge-i-cannot-hate-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 12:10:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sneha add a quote by Hans Bos]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30954-while-i-dance-i-cannot-judge-i-cannot-hate-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["While I dance I cannot judge, I cannot hate, I cannot separate myself from life. I can only be joyful and whole. That is why I dance" -- Hans Bos]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30955-we-re-so-engaged-in-doing-things-to-achieve-purposes-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 12:11:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sneha add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30955-we-re-so-engaged-in-doing-things-to-achieve-purposes-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're so engaged in doing things to achieve purposes of outer value that we forget the inner value, the rapture that is associated with being alive, is what it is all about." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
