<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/584233-kristina]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/584233-kristina" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 12:53:13 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5194-it-s-not-what-you-look-at-that-matters-it-s-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 12:53:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5194-it-s-not-what-you-look-at-that-matters-it-s-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not what you look at that matters, it's what you see." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11123-there-is-no-remedy-for-love-but-to-love-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 12:54:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11123-there-is-no-remedy-for-love-but-to-love-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no remedy for love, but to love more." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28007-have-a-heart-that-never-hardens-and-a-temper-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2013 19:13:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28007-have-a-heart-that-never-hardens-and-a-temper-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have a heart that never hardens, and a temper that never tires, and a touch that never hurts." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/581661-it-s-said-it-takes-seven-years-to-grow-completely-new</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2013 20:20:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Brett E. Jenkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/581661-it-s-said-it-takes-seven-years-to-grow-completely-new]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s said it takes seven years to grow completely new skin cells.To think, this year I will grow into a body you never will have touched." -- Brett E. Jenkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253991-people-take-different-roads-seeking-fulfillment-and-happiness-just-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 17:01:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Dalai Lama XIV]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253991-people-take-different-roads-seeking-fulfillment-and-happiness-just-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People take different roads seeking fulfillment and happiness. Just because they’re not on your road doesn’t mean they’ve gotten lost." -- Dalai Lama XIV]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59284-the-longer-i-love-the-more-i-realize-the-impact</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 10:48:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Charles Swindoll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59284-the-longer-i-love-the-more-i-realize-the-impact]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The longer I love, the more I realize the impact of attitude on life.  Attitude, to me, is more important than facts.  It is more important than the past, than education, than money, than circumstances, than failures, than successes, than what other people think or say or do.  It is more important than appearance, giftedness or skill.  It will make or break a company...a church....a home.  The remarkable thing is we have a choice every day regarding the attitude we will embrace for that day.  We cannot change our past...we cannot change the fact that people will act in a certain way.  We cannot change the inevitable.  The only thing we can do is play on the one string we have, and that is our attitude...I am convinced that life is 10% what happens to me and 90% how I react to it.  And so it is with you...we are in charge of our attitudes." -- Charles Swindoll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286721-forgive-the-past-it-is-over-learn-from-it-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 07:23:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Brian Weiss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286721-forgive-the-past-it-is-over-learn-from-it-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Forgive the past. It is over. Learn from it and let go. People are constantly changing and growing. Do not cling to a limited, disconnected, negative image of a person in the past. See that person now. Your relationship is always alive and changing." -- Brian Weiss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139680-in-the-west-we-have-a-tendency-to-be-profit-oriented</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 10:13:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139680-in-the-west-we-have-a-tendency-to-be-profit-oriented]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the West we have a tendency to be profit-oriented, where everything is measured according to the results and we get caught up in being more and more active to generate results. In the East -- especially in India -- I find that people are more content to just be, to just sit around under a banyan tree for half a day chatting to each other. We Westerners would probably call that wasting time. But there is value to it. Being with someone, listening wihtout a clock and without anticipation of results, teaches us about love. The success of love is in the loving -- it is not in the result of loving. 

&lt;i&gt;These words, taken from the book A Simple Path, are the words of one of the Missionaries of Charity Sisters, &lt;b&gt;not&lt;/b&gt; of Mother Teresa.&lt;/i&gt;" -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/692427-i-still-think-that-the-greatest-suffering-is-being-lonely</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 10:18:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/692427-i-still-think-that-the-greatest-suffering-is-being-lonely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I still think that the greatest suffering is being lonely, feeling unloved, just having no one... That is the worst disease that any human being can ever experience." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295206-that-s-what-real-love-amounts-to---letting-a-person</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 15:25:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Jim Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295206-that-s-what-real-love-amounts-to---letting-a-person]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's what real love amounts to - letting a person be what he really is. Most people love you for who you pretend to be. To keep their love, you keep pretending - performing. You get to love your pretence. It's true, we're locked in an image, an act - and the sad thing is, people get so used to their image, they grow attached to their masks. They love their chains. They forget all about who they really are. And if you try to remind them, they hate you for it, they feel like you're trying to steal their most precious possession." -- Jim Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184013-i-don-t-trust-people-who-don-t-love-themselves-and-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 10:00:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184013-i-don-t-trust-people-who-don-t-love-themselves-and-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't trust people who don't love themselves and tell me, 'I love you.' ... There is an African saying which is: Be careful when a naked person offers you a shirt." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402967-deciding-whether-or-not-to-trust-a-person-is-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 10:05:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402967-deciding-whether-or-not-to-trust-a-person-is-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Deciding whether or not to trust a person is like deciding whether or not to climb a tree because you might get a wonderful view from the highest branch or you might simply get covered in sap and for this reason many people choose to spend their time alone and indoors where it is harder to get a splinter." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/778-it-is-not-a-lack-of-love-but-a-lack</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 21:19:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/778-it-is-not-a-lack-of-love-but-a-lack]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not a lack of love, but a lack of friendship that makes unhappy marriages." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 21:21:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18271-there-is-always-some-madness-in-love-but-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 21:30:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18271-there-is-always-some-madness-in-love-but-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is always some madness in love. But there is also always some reason in madness." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/773324-speaking-of-insecurity-it-s-broken-greater-spirits-than-ours-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2013 20:35:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/773324-speaking-of-insecurity-it-s-broken-greater-spirits-than-ours-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["(speaking of insecurity)
&quot;It's broken greater spirits than ours, and robbed the world of God knows how much beauty. I've seen it happen more times than I like to think about.&quot;
--&quot;$10,000 A Year, Easy" -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2013 20:57:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love never dies a natural death. It dies because we don't know how to replenish its source. It dies of blindness and errors and betrayals. It dies of illness and wounds; it dies of weariness, of witherings, of tarnishings." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230886-you-may-not-be-her-first-her-last-or-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2013 20:57:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230886-you-may-not-be-her-first-her-last-or-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may not be her first, her last, or her only. She loved before she may love again. But if she loves you now, what else matters? She's not perfect—you aren't either, and the two of you may never be perfect together but if she can make you laugh, cause you to think twice, and admit to being human and making mistakes, hold onto her and give her the most you can. She may not be thinking about you every second of the day, but she will give you a part of her that she knows you can break—her heart. So don't hurt her, don't change her, don't analyze and don't expect more than she can give. Smile when she makes you happy, let her know when she makes you mad, and miss her when she's not there." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28571-if-i-had-a-flower-for-every-time-i-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2013 20:58:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28571-if-i-had-a-flower-for-every-time-i-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I had a flower for every time I thought of you...I could walk through my garden forever." -- Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4964-love-is-that-condition-in-which-the-happiness-of-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 21:54:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4964-love-is-that-condition-in-which-the-happiness-of-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is that condition in which the happiness of another person is essential to your own." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 21:56:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26411-there-are-two-basic-motivating-forces-fear-and-love-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 21:59:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26411-there-are-two-basic-motivating-forces-fear-and-love-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two basic motivating forces: fear and love. When we are afraid, we pull back from life. When we are in love, we open to all that life has to offer with passion, excitement, and acceptance. We need to learn to love ourselves first, in all our glory and our imperfections. If we cannot love ourselves, we cannot fully open to our ability to love others or our potential to create. Evolution and all hopes for a better world rest in the fearlessness and open-hearted vision of people who embrace life." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49991-so-i-love-you-because-the-entire-universe-conspired-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 21:59:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49991-so-i-love-you-because-the-entire-universe-conspired-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So, I love you because the entire universe conspired to help me find you." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61787-i-would-always-rather-be-happy-than-dignified</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 22:00:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61787-i-would-always-rather-be-happy-than-dignified]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would always rather be happy than dignified." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175873-and-now-i-m-looking-at-you-he-said-and-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 22:00:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Cassandra Clare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175873-and-now-i-m-looking-at-you-he-said-and-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And now I’m looking at you,” he said, “and you’re asking me if I still want you, as if I could stop loving you. As if I would want to give up the thing that makes me stronger than anything else ever has. I never dared give much of myself to anyone before – bits of myself to the Lightwoods, to Isabelle and Alec, but it took years to do it – but, Clary, since the first time I saw you, I have belonged to you completely. I still do. If you want me." -- Cassandra Clare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114304-all-good-things-are-wild-and-free</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 13:00:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114304-all-good-things-are-wild-and-free]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All good things are wild and free." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3124-our-truest-life-is-when-we-are-in-dreams-awake</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 13:01:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3124-our-truest-life-is-when-we-are-in-dreams-awake]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our truest life is when we are in dreams awake." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8794-any-fool-can-make-a-rule-and-any-fool-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 13:03:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8794-any-fool-can-make-a-rule-and-any-fool-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any fool can make a rule
And any fool will mind it." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29754-as-a-single-footstep-will-not-make-a-path-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 13:03:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29754-as-a-single-footstep-will-not-make-a-path-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As a single footstep will not make a path on the earth, so a single thought will not make a pathway in the mind.  To make a deep physical path, we walk again and again.  To make a deep mental path, we must think over and over the kind of thoughts we wish to dominate our lives." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122440-i-do-believe-in-simplicity-it-is-astonishing-as-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 13:06:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristina add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122440-i-do-believe-in-simplicity-it-is-astonishing-as-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do believe in simplicity. It is astonishing as well as sad, how many trivial affairs even the wisest thinks he must attend to in a day; how singular an affair he thinks he must omit. When the mathematician would solve a difficult problem, he first frees the equation of all incumbrances, and reduces it to its simplest terms. So simplify the problem of life, distinguish the necessary and the real. Probe the earth to see where your main roots run. " -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
