<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/584564-ryan-b]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/584564-ryan-b" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 15:51:26 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94046-no-one-fights-dirtier-or-more-brutally-than-blood-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 15:51:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Whitney Otto]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94046-no-one-fights-dirtier-or-more-brutally-than-blood-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one fights dirtier or more brutally than blood; only family knows it’s own weaknesses, the exact placement of the heart. The tragedy is that one can still live with the force of hatred, feel infuriated that once you are born to another, that kinship lasts through life and death, immutable, unchanging, no matter how great the misdeed or betrayal. Blood cannot be denied, and perhaps that’s why we fight tooth and claw, because we cannot—being only human—put asunder what God has joined together." -- Whitney Otto]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920891-caring-too-much-for-objects-can-destroy-you-only-if-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 18:35:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920891-caring-too-much-for-objects-can-destroy-you-only-if-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Caring too much for objects can destroy you. Only—if you care for a thing enough, it takes on a life of its own, doesn’t it? And isn’t the whole point of things—beautiful things—that they connect you to some larger beauty?" -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/923278-i-look-at-the-blanked-out-faces-of-the-other-passengers--hoisting</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 18:36:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/923278-i-look-at-the-blanked-out-faces-of-the-other-passengers--hoisting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I look at the blanked-out faces of the other passengers--hoisting their briefcases, their backpacks, shuffling to disembark--and I think of what Hobie said: beauty alters the grain of reality.  And I keep thinking too of the more conventional wisdom: namely, that the pursuit of pure beauty is a trap, a fast track to bitterness and sorrow, that beauty has to be wedded to something more meaningful.

Only what is that thing?  Why am I made the way I am?  Why do I care about all the wrong things, and nothing at all for the right ones?  Or, to tip it another way: how can I see so clearly that everything I love or care about is illusion, and yet--for me, anyway--all that's worth living for lies in that charm?

A great sorrow, and one that I am only beginning to understand: we don't get to choose our own hearts.  We can't make ourselves want what's good for us or what's good for other people.  We don't get to choose the people we are.

Because--isn't it drilled into us constantly, from childhood on, an unquestioned platitude in the culture--?  From William Blake to Lady Gaga, from Rousseau to Rumi to Tosca to Mister Rogers, it's a curiously uniform message, accepted from high to low: when in doubt, what to do?  How do we know what's right for us?  Every shrink, every career counselor, every Disney princess knows the answer: &quot;Be yourself.&quot;  &quot;Follow your heart.&quot;

Only here's what I really, really want someone to explain to me.  What if one happens to be possessed of a heart that can't be trusted--?  What if the heart, for its own unfathomable reasons, leads one willfully and in a cloud of unspeakable radiance away from health, domesticity, civic responsibility and strong social connections and all the blandly-held common virtues and instead straight toward a beautiful flare of ruin, self-immolation, disaster?...If your deepest self is singing and coaxing you straight toward the bonfire, is it better to turn away?  Stop your ears with wax?  Ignore all the perverse glory your heart is screaming at you?  Set yourself on the course that will lead you dutifully towards the norm, reasonable hours and regular medical check-ups, stable relationships and steady career advancement the New York Times and brunch on Sunday, all with the promise of being somehow a better person?  Or...is it better to throw yourself head first and laughing into the holy rage calling your name?" -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/948911-stay-away-from-the-ones-you-love-too-much-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 18:36:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/948911-stay-away-from-the-ones-you-love-too-much-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stay away from the ones you love too much. Those are the ones who will kill you." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/938545-but-sometimes-unexpectedly-grief-pounded-over-me-in-waves-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 18:36:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/938545-but-sometimes-unexpectedly-grief-pounded-over-me-in-waves-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But sometimes, unexpectedly, grief pounded over me in waves that left me gasping; and when the waves washed back, I found myself looking out over a brackish wreck which was illumined in a light so lucid, so heartsick and empty, that I could hardly remember that the world had ever been anything but dead." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980938-because-i-don-t-care-what-anyone-says-or-how-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 18:37:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/980938-because-i-don-t-care-what-anyone-says-or-how-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because I don’t care what anyone says or how often or winningly they say it: no one will ever, ever be able to persuade me that life is some awesome, rewarding treat. Because, here’s the truth: life is a catastrophe. The basic fact of existence – of walking around trying to feed ourselves and find friends and whatever else we do – is a catastrophe. Forget all this ridiculous ‘Our Town’ nonsense everyone talks: the miracle of a newborn babe, the joy of one simple blossom, Life You Are Too Wonderful To Grasp, &amp;c. For me – and I’ll keep repeating it doggedly till I die, till I fall over on my ungrateful nihilistic face and am too weak to say it: better never born, than born into this cesspool. Sinkhole of hospital beds, coffins, and broken hearts. No release, no appeal, no “do-overs” to employ a favored phrase of Xandra’s, no way forward but age and loss, and no way out but death." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/985121-and-i-add-my-own-love-to-the-history-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 18:38:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/985121-and-i-add-my-own-love-to-the-history-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I add my own love to the history of people who have loved beautiful things, and looked out for them, and pulled them from the fire, and sought them when they were lost, and tried to preserve them and save them while passing them along literally from hand to hand, singing out brilliantly from the wreck of time to the next generation of lovers, and the next." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004077-if-a-painting-really-works-down-in-your-heart-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 18:38:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004077-if-a-painting-really-works-down-in-your-heart-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["—if a painting really works down in your heart and changes the way you see, and think, and feel, you don’t think, ‘oh, I love this picture because it’s universal.’ ‘I love this painting because it speaks to all mankind.’ That’s not the reason anyone loves a piece of art. It’s a secret whisper from an alleyway. Psst, you. Hey kid. Yes you." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/958463-every-new-event-everything-i-did-for-the-rest-of-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 18:38:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/958463-every-new-event-everything-i-did-for-the-rest-of-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every new event—everything I did for the rest of my life—would only separate us more and more: days she was no longer a part of, an ever-growing distance between us. Every single day for the rest of my life, she would only be further away." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/969507-and-in-the-midst-of-our-dying-as-we-rise</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 18:45:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/969507-and-in-the-midst-of-our-dying-as-we-rise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And in the midst of our dying, as we rise from the organic and sink back ignominiously into the organic, it is a glory and a privilege to love what Death doesn’t touch. For if disaster and oblivion have followed this painting down through time — so too has love. Insofar as it is immortal (and it is) I have a small, bright, immutable part in that immortality. It exists; and it keeps on existing. And I add my own love to the history of people who have loved beautiful things, and looked out for them, and pulled them from the fire, and sought them when they were lost, and tried to preserve them and save them while passing them along literally from hand to hand, singing out brilliantly from the wreck of time to the next generation of lovers, and the next." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004216-for-humans-trapped-in-biology-there-was-no-mercy-we-lived-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 18:46:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004216-for-humans-trapped-in-biology-there-was-no-mercy-we-lived-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For humans-trapped in biology-there was no mercy: we lived a while, we fussed around for a bit and died, we rotted in the ground like garbage. Time destroyed us all soon enough. But to destroy, or lose, a deathless thing-to break bonds stronger than the temporal-was a metaphysical uncoupling all its own, a startling new flavor of despair." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1023154-i-missed-her-so-much-i-wanted-to-die-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 18:48:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1023154-i-missed-her-so-much-i-wanted-to-die-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I missed her so much I wanted to die: a hard, physical longing, like a craving for air underwater. Lying awake, I tried to recall all my best memories of her—to freeze her in my mind so I wouldn’t forget her—but instead of birthdays and happy times I kept remembering things like how a few days before she was killed she’d stopped me halfway out the door to pick a thread off my school jacket. For some reason, it was one of the clearest memories I had of her: her knitted eyebrows, the precise gesture of her reaching out to me, everything. Several times too—drifting uneasily between dreaming and sleep—I sat up suddenly in bed at the sound of her voice speaking clearly in my head, remarks she might conceivably have made at some point but that I didn’t actually remember, things like Throw me an apple, would you? and I wonder if this buttons up the front or the back? and This sofa is in a terrible state of disreputableness." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/927807-well-i-have-to-say-i-personally-have-never-drawn-such</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 18:50:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/927807-well-i-have-to-say-i-personally-have-never-drawn-such]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well—I have to say I personally have never drawn such a sharp line between ‘good’ and ‘bad’ as you. For me: that line is often false. The two are never disconnected. One can’t exist without the other. As long as I am acting out of love, I feel I am doing best I know how. But you—wrapped up in judgment, always regretting the past, cursing yourself, blaming yourself, asking ‘what if,’ ‘what if.’ ‘Life is cruel.’ ‘I wish I had died instead of.’ Well—think about this. What if all your actions and choices, good or bad, make no difference to God? What if the pattern is pre-set? No no—hang on—this is a question worth struggling with. What if our badness and mistakes are the very thing that set our fate and bring us round to good? What if, for some of us, we can’t get there any other way?" -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/986550-when-we-are-sad-at-least-i-am-like-this-it-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 18:52:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/986550-when-we-are-sad-at-least-i-am-like-this-it-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we are sad—at least I am like this—it can be comforting to cling to familiar objects, to the things that don't change. Your descriptions of the desert—that oceanic, endless glare—are terrible but also very beautiful. Maybe there's something to be said for the rawness and emptiness of it all. The light of long ago is different from the light of today and yet here, in this house, I'm reminded of the past at every turn. But when I think of you, it's as if you've gone away to sea on a ship—out in a foreign brightness where there are no paths, only stars and sky." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/929096-but-depression-wasn-t-the-word-this-was-a-plunge-encompassing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 18:53:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/929096-but-depression-wasn-t-the-word-this-was-a-plunge-encompassing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But depression wasn't the word. This was a plunge encompassing sorrow and revulsion far beyond the personal: a sick, drenching nausea at all humanity and human endeavor from the dawn of time. The writhing loathsomeness of the biological order. Old age, sickness, death. No escape for anyone. Even the beautiful ones were like soft fruit about to spoil. And yet somehow people still kept fucking and breeding and popping out new fodder for the grave, producing more and more new beings to suffer like this was some kind of redemptive, or good, or even somehow morally admirable thing: dragging more innocent creatures into the lose-lose game. Squirming babies and plodding, complacent, hormone-drugged moms. Oh, isn't he cute? Awww. Kids shouting and skidding in the playground with no idea what future Hells await them: boring jobs and ruinous mortgages and bad marriages and hair loss and hip replacements and lonely cups of coffee in an empty house and a colostomy bag at the hospital. Most people seemed satisfied with the thin decorative glaze and the artful stage lighting that sometimes, made the bedrock atrocity of the human predicament look somewhat more mysterious or less abhorrent. People gambled and golfed and planted gardens and traded stocks and had sex and bought new cars and practiced yoga and worked and prayed and redecorated their homes and got worked up over the news and fussed over their children and gossiped about their neighbors and pored over restaurant reviews and founded charitable organizations and supported political candidates and attended the U.S. Open and dined and travelled and distracted themselves with all kinds of gadgets and devices, flooding themselves incessantly with information and texts and communication and entertainment from every direction to try to make themselves forget it: where we were, what we were. But in a strong light there was no good spin you could put on it. It was rotten from top to bottom." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/681493-nothing-had-changed-i-was-the-stupid-one-again-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 20:37:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Carol Rifka Brunt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/681493-nothing-had-changed-i-was-the-stupid-one-again-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing had changed. I was the stupid one again. I was the girl who never understood who she was to people." -- Carol Rifka Brunt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94042-she-had-always-wanted-words-she-loved-them-grew-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 20:48:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94042-she-had-always-wanted-words-she-loved-them-grew-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had always wanted words, she loved them; grew up on them. Words gave her clarity, brought reason, shape." -- Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21044-we-die-containing-a-richness-of-lovers-and-tribes-tastes</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 20:49:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21044-we-die-containing-a-richness-of-lovers-and-tribes-tastes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We die containing a richness of lovers and tribes, tastes we have swallowed, bodies we have plunged into and swum up as if rivers of wisdom, characters we have climbed into as if trees, fears we have hidden in as if caves. 

I wish for all this to be marked on by body when I am dead.  I believe in such cartography - to be marked by nature, not just to label ourselves on a map like the names of rich men and women on buildings.  We are communal histories, communal books.  We are not owned or monogamous in our taste or experience." -- Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214086-every-night-i-cut-out-my-heart-but-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 20:53:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214086-every-night-i-cut-out-my-heart-but-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every night I cut out my heart. But in the morning it was full again" -- Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/751791-do-you-understand-the-sadness-of-geography</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 20:54:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/751791-do-you-understand-the-sadness-of-geography]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you understand the sadness of geography?" -- Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135828-it-takes-a-minute-to-have-a-crush-on-someone</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 21:00:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Kahlil Gibran ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135828-it-takes-a-minute-to-have-a-crush-on-someone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It takes a minute to have a crush on someone, an hour to like someone, and a day to love someone... but it takes a lifetime to forget someone." -- Kahlil Gibran ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1219735-and-now-here-is-my-secret-a-very-simple-secret</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 13:55:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1219735-and-now-here-is-my-secret-a-very-simple-secret]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And now here is my secret, a very simple secret: It is only with the heart that one can see rightly; what is essential is invisible to the eye." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
