<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/58498-brook]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/58498-brook" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 08:27:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58988-o-lord-our-father-our-young-patriots-idols-of-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 08:27:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[brook add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58988-o-lord-our-father-our-young-patriots-idols-of-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["O Lord our Father, our young patriots, idols of our hearts, go forth to battle -- be Thou near them! With them -- in spirit -- we also go forth from the sweet peace of our beloved firesides to smite the foe. O Lord our God, help us to tear their soldiers to bloody shreds with our shells; help us to cover their smiling fields with the pale forms of their patriot dead; help us to drown the thunder of the guns with the shrieks of their wounded, writhing in pain; help us to lay waste their humble homes with a hurricane of fire; help us to wring the hearts of their unoffending widows with unavailing grief; help us to turn them out roofless with little children to wander unfriended the wastes of their desolated land in rags and hunger and thirst, sports of the sun flames of summer and the icy winds of winter, broken in spirit, worn with travail, imploring Thee for the refuge of the grave and denied it -- for our sakes who adore Thee, Lord, blast their hopes, blight their lives, protract their bitter pilgrimage, make heavy their steps, water their way with their tears, stain the white snow with the blood of their wounded feet! We ask it, in the spirit of love, of Him Who is the Source of Love, and Who is the ever-faithful refuge and friend of all that are sore beset and seek His aid with humble and contrite hearts. Amen." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58990-god-made-mud-god-got-lonesome-so-god-said-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 08:29:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[brook add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58990-god-made-mud-god-got-lonesome-so-god-said-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God made mud.
God got lonesome.
So God said to some of the mud, &quot;Sit up!&quot;
&quot;See all I've made,&quot; said God, &quot;the hills, the sea, the
sky, the stars.&quot;
And I was some of the mud that got to sit up and look
around.
Lucky me, lucky mud.
I, mud, sat up and saw what a nice job God had done.
Nice going, God.
Nobody but you could have done it, God! I certainly
couldn't have.
I feel very unimportant compared to You.
The only way I can feel the least bit important is to
think of all the mud that didn't even get to sit up and
look around.
I got so much, and most mud got so little.
Thank you for the honor!
Now mud lies down again and goes to sleep.
What memories for mud to have!
What interesting other kinds of sitting-up mud I met!
I loved everything I saw!
Good night.
I will go to heaven now.
I can hardly wait...
To find out for certain what my wampeter was...
And who was in my karass...
And all the good things our karass did for you.
Amen." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228308-you-may-not-control-all-the-events-that-happen-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 08:58:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[brook add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228308-you-may-not-control-all-the-events-that-happen-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may not control all the events that happen to you, but you can decide not to be reduced by them." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25301-i-believe-that-truth-has-only-one-face-that-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 14:45:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[brook add a quote by Georges Bataille]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25301-i-believe-that-truth-has-only-one-face-that-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that truth has only one face: that of a violent contradiction." -- Georges Bataille]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/631560-do-a-loony-goony-dance-cross-the-kitchen-floor-put-something</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 07:27:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[brook add a quote by Shel Silverstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/631560-do-a-loony-goony-dance-cross-the-kitchen-floor-put-something]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do a loony-goony dance 
'Cross the kitchen floor, 
Put something silly in the world 
That ain't been there before." -- Shel Silverstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
