<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/585911-eugene-van]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/585911-eugene-van" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 12:13:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110096-life-is-a-journey-time-is-a-river-the-door</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 12:13:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eugene add a quote by Jim Butcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110096-life-is-a-journey-time-is-a-river-the-door]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is a journey. Time is a river. The door is ajar" -- Jim Butcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66608-when-everything-goes-to-hell-the-people-who-stand-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 12:13:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eugene add a quote by Jim Butcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66608-when-everything-goes-to-hell-the-people-who-stand-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When everything goes to hell, the people who stand by you without flinching -- they are your family. " -- Jim Butcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408441-a-reader-lives-a-thousand-lives-before-he-dies-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 21:06:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eugene add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408441-a-reader-lives-a-thousand-lives-before-he-dies-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A reader lives a thousand lives before he dies, said Jojen. The man who never reads lives only one." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13641-imagine-yourself-as-a-living-house-god-comes-in-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 12:41:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eugene add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13641-imagine-yourself-as-a-living-house-god-comes-in-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine yourself as a living house. God comes in to rebuild that house. At first, perhaps, you can understand what He is doing. He is getting the drains right and stopping the leaks in the roof and so on; you knew that those jobs needed doing and so you are not surprised. But presently He starts knocking the house about in a way that hurts abominably and does not seem to make any sense. What on earth is He up to? The explanation is that He is building quite a different house from the one you thought of - throwing out a new wing here, putting on an extra floor there, running up towers, making courtyards. You thought you were being made into a decent little cottage: but He is building a palace. He intends to come and live in it Himself." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6979-i-am-trying-here-to-prevent-anyone-saying-the-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 12:44:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eugene add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6979-i-am-trying-here-to-prevent-anyone-saying-the-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am trying here to prevent anyone saying the really foolish thing that people often say about Him: I’m ready to accept Jesus as a great moral teacher, but I don’t accept his claim to be God. That is the one thing we must not say. A man who was merely a man and said the sort of things Jesus said would not be a great moral teacher. He would either be a lunatic — on the level with the man who says he is a poached egg — or else he would be the Devil of Hell. You must make your choice. Either this man was, and is, the Son of God, or else a madman or something worse. You can shut him up for a fool, you can spit at him and kill him as a demon or you can fall at his feet and call him Lord and God, but let us not come with any patronizing nonsense about his being a great human teacher. He has not left that open to us. He did not intend to." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
