<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/586195-siobhan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/586195-siobhan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 13:07:05 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1699-how-many-slams-in-an-old-screen-door-depends-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 13:07:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Siobhan add a quote by Shel Silverstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1699-how-many-slams-in-an-old-screen-door-depends-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How many slams in an old screen door? Depends how loud you shut it. How many slices in a bread? Depends how thin you cut it. How much good inside a day? Depends how good you live 'em. How much love inside a friend? Depends how much you give 'em." -- Shel Silverstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180253-what-s-the-first-sign-of-a-lurking-hidden-expectation-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2012 11:38:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Siobhan add a quote by Guy Finley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180253-what-s-the-first-sign-of-a-lurking-hidden-expectation-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What's the first sign of a lurking, hidden expectation you didn't know you had? Pain! People don't do what we want, things don't happen quickly enough, the weather doesn't cooperate, our bodies don't cooperate. Why are these moments so painful? Because our minds are focused on a static, unchanging, me-centric picture while the dynamic unfolding of a broader life continues around us. There is nothing wrong with expectations per se, as it's appropriate to set goals and work, properly, towards their fruition. But the instant we feel pain over life not going &quot;my way,&quot; our expectations have clearly taken an improper turn. Any moment you feel resistance or pain, look for -- and then let go of -- the hidden expectation. Practice giving yourself over to what &quot;you&quot; don't want. Let the line at the store be long. Let the other person interrupt you. Let the nervousness make you shake. Be where your body is, not where your mind is trying to take you." -- Guy Finley]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
