<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/586261-mo-tipton]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/586261-mo-tipton" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 13:35:36 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66180-traditional-hedonism-was-based-on-the-direct-experience-of-pleasure-wine</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 13:35:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66180-traditional-hedonism-was-based-on-the-direct-experience-of-pleasure-wine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Traditional hedonism...was based on the direct experience of pleasure: wine, women and song; sex, drugs and rock 'n' roll; or whatever the local variant. The problem, from a capitalist perspective, is that there are inherent limits to all this. People become sated, bored...Modern self-illusory hedonism solves this dilemma because here, what one is really consuming are fantasies and day-dreams about what having a certain product &lt;i&gt;would&lt;/i&gt; be like." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 13:03:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4610-the-difference-between-genius-and-stupidity-is-genius-has-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2008 14:25:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4610-the-difference-between-genius-and-stupidity-is-genius-has-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The difference between genius and stupidity is; genius has its limits." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8390-science-is-interesting-and-if-you-don-t-agree-you-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 13:05:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Richard Dawkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8390-science-is-interesting-and-if-you-don-t-agree-you-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Science is interesting, and if you don't agree you can fuck off.

&lt;b&gt;Note&lt;/b&gt;: Dawkins was quoting a former editor of New Scientist Magazine, who is as yet unidentified (possibly Jeremy Webb)" -- Richard Dawkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2499-there-are-two-motives-for-reading-a-book-one-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 13:05:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2499-there-are-two-motives-for-reading-a-book-one-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two motives for reading a book; one, that you enjoy it; the other, that you can boast about it." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15763-war-does-not-determine-who-is-right---only-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 13:06:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15763-war-does-not-determine-who-is-right---only-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["War does not determine who is right - only who is left." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2203-it-is-what-you-read-when-you-don-t-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2008 09:37:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2203-it-is-what-you-read-when-you-don-t-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is what you read when you don't have to that determines what you will be when you can't help it." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142250-at-this-point-in-history-our-society-tends-to-elevate</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2009 07:53:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Keith Stewart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142250-at-this-point-in-history-our-society-tends-to-elevate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At this point in history, our society tends to elevate and reward the specialist...This concentrated focus has brought some benefits...It may also be a modern malady. Specialization, when taken too far and allowed to define who and what we are, becomes limiting. It robs us of our wholeness and our self-sufficiency. It misses the big picture and confines us to a narrow zoom. And it leaves us at the mercy of experts." -- Keith Stewart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159145-we-seldom-consider-how-much-of-our-lives-we-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 15:02:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Ferenc Mate]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159145-we-seldom-consider-how-much-of-our-lives-we-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We seldom consider how much of our lives we must render in return for some object we barely want, seldom need, buy only because it was put before us...And this is understandable given the workings of our system where without a job we perish, where if we don't want a job and are happy to get by we are labeled irresponsible, non-contributing leeches on society. But if we hire a  fleet of bulldozers, tear up half the countryside and build some monstrous factory, casino or mall, we are called entrepreneurs, job-creators, stalwarts of the community. Maybe we should all be shut away on some planet for the insane. Then again, maybe that is where we are." -- Ferenc Mate]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175716-we-have-to-create-culture-don-t-watch-tv-don-t-read</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 13:35:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Terence McKenna]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175716-we-have-to-create-culture-don-t-watch-tv-don-t-read]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have to create culture, don't watch TV, don't read magazines, don't even listen to NPR. Create your own roadshow. The nexus of space and time where you are now is the most immediate sector of your universe, and if you're worrying about Michael Jackson or Bill Clinton or somebody else, then you are disempowered, you're giving it all away to icons, icons which are maintained by an electronic media so that you want to dress like X or have lips like Y. This is shit-brained, this kind of thinking. That is all cultural diversion, and what is real is you and your friends and your associations, your highs, your orgasms, your hopes, your plans, your fears. And we are told 'no', we're unimportant, we're peripheral. 'Get a degree, get a job, get a this, get a that.' And then you're a player, you don't want to even play in that game. You want to reclaim your mind and get it out of the hands of the cultural engineers who want to turn you into a half-baked moron consuming all this trash that's being manufactured out of the bones of a dying world." -- Terence McKenna]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3679-if-the-doors-of-perception-were-cleansed-every-thing-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 17:51:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by William Blake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3679-if-the-doors-of-perception-were-cleansed-every-thing-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the doors of perception were cleansed every thing would appear to man as it is, Infinite. For man has closed himself up, till he sees all things thro' narrow chinks of his cavern." -- William Blake]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
