<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/587402-loren-johnson]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/587402-loren-johnson" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2008 11:34:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4637-o-deep-thought-computer-he-said-the-task-we-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2008 11:34:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Loren add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4637-o-deep-thought-computer-he-said-the-task-we-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["O Deep Thought computer,&quot; he said, &quot;the task we have designed you to perform is this. We want you to tell us....&quot; he paused, &quot;The Answer.&quot;
&quot;The Answer?&quot; said Deep Thought. &quot;The Answer to what?&quot;
&quot;Life!&quot; urged Fook.
&quot;The Universe!&quot; said Lunkwill.
&quot;Everything!&quot; they said in chorus.
Deep Thought paused for a moment's reflection.
&quot;Tricky,&quot; he said finally.
&quot;But can you do it?&quot;
Again, a significant pause.
&quot;Yes,&quot; said Deep Thought, &quot;I can do it.&quot;
&quot;There is an answer?&quot; said Fook with breathless excitement.
&quot;Yes,&quot; said Deep Thought. &quot;Life, the Universe, and Everything. There is an answer. But, I'll have to think about it.&quot;
...
Fook glanced impatiently at his watch.
“How long?” he said.
“Seven and a half million years,” said Deep Thought.
Lunkwill and Fook blinked at each other.
“Seven and a half million years...!” they cried in chorus.
“Yes,” declaimed Deep Thought, “I said I’d have to think about it, didn’t I?&quot;

[Seven and a half million years later.... Fook and Lunkwill are long gone, but their ancestors continue what they started]

&quot;We are the ones who will hear,&quot; said Phouchg, &quot;the answer to the great question of Life....!&quot;
&quot;The Universe...!&quot; said Loonquawl.
&quot;And Everything...!&quot;
&quot;Shhh,&quot; said Loonquawl with a slight gesture. &quot;I think Deep Thought is preparing to speak!&quot;
There was a moment's expectant pause while panels slowly came to life on the front of the console. Lights flashed on and off experimentally and settled down into a businesslike pattern. A soft low hum came from the communication channel.

&quot;Good Morning,&quot; said Deep Thought at last.
&quot;Er..good morning, O Deep Thought&quot; said Loonquawl nervously, &quot;do you have...er, that is...&quot;
&quot;An Answer for you?&quot; interrupted Deep Thought majestically. &quot;Yes, I have.&quot;
The two men shivered with expectancy. Their waiting had not been in vain.
&quot;There really is one?&quot; breathed Phouchg.
&quot;There really is one,&quot; confirmed Deep Thought.
&quot;To Everything? To the great Question of Life, the Universe and everything?&quot;
&quot;Yes.&quot;
Both of the men had been trained for this moment, their lives had been a preparation for it, they had been selected at birth as those who would witness the answer, but even so they found themselves gasping and squirming like excited children.
&quot;And you're ready to give it to us?&quot; urged Loonsuawl.
&quot;I am.&quot;
&quot;Now?&quot;
&quot;Now,&quot; said Deep Thought.
They both licked their dry lips.
&quot;Though I don't think,&quot; added Deep Thought. &quot;that you're going to like it.&quot;
&quot;Doesn't matter!&quot; said Phouchg. &quot;We must know it! Now!&quot;
&quot;Now?&quot; inquired Deep Thought.
&quot;Yes! Now...&quot;
&quot;All right,&quot; said the computer, and settled into silence again. The two men fidgeted. The tension was unbearable.
&quot;You're really not going to like it,&quot; observed Deep Thought.
&quot;Tell us!&quot;
&quot;All right,&quot; said Deep Thought. &quot;The Answer to the Great Question...&quot;
&quot;Yes..!&quot;
&quot;Of Life, the Universe and Everything...&quot; said Deep Thought.
&quot;Yes...!&quot;
&quot;Is...&quot; said Deep Thought, and paused.
&quot;Yes...!&quot;
&quot;Is...&quot;
&quot;Yes...!!!...?&quot;
&quot;Forty-two,&quot; said Deep Thought, with infinite majesty and calm." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
