<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/588828-kim]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/588828-kim" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 13:47:06 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78375-my-name-used-to-be-in-the-papers-daily-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 13:47:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Edgar Lee Masters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78375-my-name-used-to-be-in-the-papers-daily-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My name used to be in the papers daily
As having dined somewhere,
Or traveled somewhere,
Or rented a house in Paris,
Where I entertained the nobility.
I was forever eating or traveling,
Or taking the cure at Baden-Baden.
Now I am here to do honor
To Spoon River, here beside the family whence I sprang.
No one cares now where I dined,
Or lived, or whom I entertained,
Or how often I took the cure at Baden-Baden!" -- Edgar Lee Masters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78381-the-first-words-that-are-read-by-seekers-of-enlightenment</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 13:51:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78381-the-first-words-that-are-read-by-seekers-of-enlightenment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first words that are read by seekers of enlightenment in the secret, gong-banging, yeti-haunted valleys near the hub of the world, are when they look into The Life of Wen the Eternally Surprised.

The first question they ask is: 'Why was he eternally surprised?'

And they are told: 'Wen considered the nature of time and understood that the universe is, instant by instant, recreated anew. Therefore, he understood, there is in truth no past, only a memory of the past. Blink your eyes, and the world you see next did not exist when you closed them. Therefore, he said, the only appropriate state of the mind is surprise. The only appropriate state of the heart is joy. The sky you see now, you have never seen before. The perfect moment is now. Be glad of it.'

The first words read by the young Lu-Tze when he sought perplexity in the dark, teeming, rain-soaked city of Ankh-Morpork were: 'Rooms For Rent, Very Reasonable.' And he was glad of it." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78382-if-there-s-a-child-on-the-south-side-of-chicago</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 13:52:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Barack Obama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78382-if-there-s-a-child-on-the-south-side-of-chicago]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there's a child on the south side of Chicago who can't read, that matters to me, even if it's not my child. If there's a senior citizen somewhere who can't pay for their prescription, who has to choose between medicine and the rent, that makes my life poorer - even if it's not my grandparent. If there's an Arab-American or Mexican-American family being rounded up by John Ashcroft without benefit of an attorney or due process, I know that that threatens my civil liberties. And I don't have to be a woman to be concerned that the Supreme Court is trying to take away a woman's right, because I know that my rights are next. It is that fundamental belief - I am my brother’s keeper, I am my sister’s keeper - that makes this country work." -- Barack Obama]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
