<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/589019-paul-wilner]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/589019-paul-wilner" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:11:23 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7942-the-belief-in-a-supernatural-source-of-evil-is-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:11:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paul add a quote by Joseph Conrad]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7942-the-belief-in-a-supernatural-source-of-evil-is-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The belief in a supernatural source of evil is not necessary; men alone are quite capable of every wickedness." -- Joseph Conrad]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119514-standing-on-a-street-corner-waiting-for-no-one-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 21:05:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paul add a quote by Gregory Corso]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119514-standing-on-a-street-corner-waiting-for-no-one-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Standing on a street corner waiting for no one is power." -- Gregory Corso]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79912-jazz-presumes-that-it-would-be-nice-if-the-four</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 23:15:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paul add a quote by Dave Hickey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79912-jazz-presumes-that-it-would-be-nice-if-the-four]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jazz presumes that it would be nice if the four of us--simpatico dudes that we are--while playing this complicated song together, might somehow be free and autonomous as well. Tragically, this never quite works out. At best, we can only be free one or two at a time--while the other dudes hold onto the wire. Which is not to say that no one has tried to dispense with wires. Many have, and sometimes it works--but it doesn't feel like &lt;i&gt;jazz&lt;/i&gt; when it does. The music simply drifts away into the stratosphere of formal dialectic, beyond our social concerns.

Rock-and-roll, on the other hand, presumes that the four of us--as damaged and anti-social as we are--might possibly get it &lt;i&gt;to-fucking-gether&lt;/i&gt;, man, and play this simple song. And play it right, okay? Just this once, in tune and on the beat. But we can't. The song's too simple, and we're too complicated and too excited. We try like hell, but the guitars distort, the intonation bends, and the beat just moves, imperceptibly, against our formal expectations, whetehr we want it to or not. Just because we're &lt;i&gt;breathing&lt;/i&gt;, man. Thus, in the process of trying to play this very simple song together, we create this hurricane of noise, this infinitely complicated, fractal filigree of delicate distinctions.

And you can thank the wanking eighties, if you wish, and digital sequencers, too, for proving to everyone that technologically &quot;perfect&quot; rock--like &quot;free&quot; jazz--sucks rockets. Because order sucks. I mean, look at the Stones. Keith Richards is &lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt; on top of the beat, and Bill Wyman, until he quit, was always behind it, because Richards is leading the band and Charlie Watts is listening to him and Wyman is listening to Watts. So the beat is sliding on those tiny neural lapses, not so you can tell, of course, but so you can feel it in your stomach. And the intonation is wavering, too, with the pulse in the finger on the amplified string. This is the delicacy of rock-and-roll, the bodily rhetoric of tiny increments, necessary imperfections, and contingent community. And it has its virtues, because jazz only works if we're trying to be free and are, in fact, together. Rock-and-roll works because we're all a bunch of flakes. That's something you can &lt;i&gt;depend&lt;/i&gt; on, and a good thing too, because in the twentieth century, that's all there is: jazz and rock-and-roll. The rest is term papers and advertising." -- Dave Hickey]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
