<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/589241-brittany]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/589241-brittany" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 16:19:19 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 16:19:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/633-i-have-found-the-paradox-that-if-you-love-until</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 16:08:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Daphne Rae]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/633-i-have-found-the-paradox-that-if-you-love-until]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have found the paradox, that if you love until it hurts, there can be no more hurt, only more love." -- Daphne Rae]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1342-goodbye-said-the-fox-and-now-here-is-my-secret</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 16:10:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1342-goodbye-said-the-fox-and-now-here-is-my-secret]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Goodbye,&quot; said the fox. &quot;And now here is my secret, a very simple secret: It is only with the heart that one can see rightly; what is essential is invisible to the eye." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60855-i-am-looking-for-friends-what-does-that-mean---</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 16:13:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60855-i-am-looking-for-friends-what-does-that-mean---]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am looking for friends. What does that mean -- tame?&quot;

&quot;It is an act too often neglected,&quot; said the fox. &quot;It means to establish ties.&quot; 

&quot;To establish ties?&quot; 

&quot;Just that,&quot; said the fox. &quot;To me, you are still nothing more than a little boy who is just like a hundred thousand other little boys. And I have no need of you. And you, on your part, have no need of me. To you I am nothing more than a fox like a hundred thousand other foxes. But if you tame me, then we shall need each other. To me, you will be unique in all the world. To you, I shall be unique in all the world...." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240508-i-want-there-to-be-a-place-in-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 13:49:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240508-i-want-there-to-be-a-place-in-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want there to be a place in the world where people can engage in one another’s differences in a way that is redemptive, full of hope and possibility. Not this “In order to love you, I must make you something else”. That’s what domination is all about, that in order to be close to you, I must possess you, remake and recast you." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291-we-all-do-better-when-we-work-together-our-differences</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 13:49:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Bill Clinton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291-we-all-do-better-when-we-work-together-our-differences]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all do better when we work together. Our differences do matter, but our common humanity matters more." -- Bill Clinton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362421-it-is-when-we-think-we-can-act-like-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 13:50:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362421-it-is-when-we-think-we-can-act-like-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is when we think we can act like God, that all respect is lost, and I think this is the downfall of peace. We lie if we say we do not see color and culture and difference. We fool ourselves and cheat ourselves when we say that all of us are the same. We should not want to be the same as others and we should not want others to be the same as us. Rather, we ought to glory and shine in all of our differences, flaunting them fabulously for all to see! It is never a conformity that we need! We need not to conform! What we need is to burst out into all these beautiful colors!" -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362424-the-downfall-of-the-attempts-of-governments-and-leaders-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 13:52:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362424-the-downfall-of-the-attempts-of-governments-and-leaders-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The downfall of the attempts of governments and leaders to unite mankind is found in this- in the wrong message that we should see everyone as the same. This is the root of the failure of harmony. Because the truth is, we should not all see everyone as the same! We are not the same! We are made of different colours and we have different cultures. We are all different! But the key to this door is to look at these differences, respect these differences, learn from and about these differences, and grow in and with these differences. We are all different. We are not the same. But that's beautiful. And that's okay.In the quest for unity and peace, we cannot blind ourselves and expect to be all the same. Because in this, we all have an underlying belief that everyone should be the same as us at some point. We are not on a journey to become the same or to be the same. But we are on a journey to see that in all of our differences, that is what makes us beautiful as a human race, and if we are ever to grow, we ought to learn and always learn some more." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/666904-i-ve-never-sung-anywhere-without-giving-the-people-listening-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 23:26:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Pete Seeger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/666904-i-ve-never-sung-anywhere-without-giving-the-people-listening-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’ve never sung anywhere without giving the people listening to me a chance to join in - as a kid, as a lefty, as a man touring the U.S.A. and the world, as an oldster. I guess it’s kind of a religion with me. Participation. That’s what’s going to save the human race." -- Pete Seeger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/666905-once-upon-a-time-wasn-t-singing-a-part-of-everyday</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 23:27:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Pete Seeger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/666905-once-upon-a-time-wasn-t-singing-a-part-of-everyday]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time, wasn’t singing a part of everyday life as much as talking, physical exercise, and religion? Our distant ancestors, wherever they were in this world, sang while pounding grain, paddling canoes, or walking long journeys. Can we begin to make our lives once more all of a piece? Finding the right songs and singing them over and over is a way to start. And when one person taps out a beat, while another leads into the melody, or when three people discover a harmony they never knew existed, or a crowd joins in on a chorus as though to raise the ceiling a few feet higher, then they also know there is hope for the world." -- Pete Seeger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484974-sometimes-you-read-a-book-and-it-fills-you-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 23:18:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484974-sometimes-you-read-a-book-and-it-fills-you-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, you read a book and it fills you with this weird evangelical zeal, and you become convinced that the shattered world will never be put back together unless and until all living humans read the book. And then there are books like An Imperial Affliction, which you can't tell people about, books so special and rare and yours that advertising your affection feels like betrayal" -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 22:07:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Kent M. Keith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Paradoxical Commandments

People are illogical, unreasonable, and self-centered.
Love them anyway.

If you do good, people will accuse you of selfish ulterior motives.
Do good anyway.

If you are successful, you will win false friends and true enemies.
Succeed anyway.

The good you do today will be forgotten tomorrow.
Do good anyway.

Honesty and frankness make you vulnerable.
Be honest and frank anyway.

The biggest men and women with the biggest ideas can be shot down by the smallest men and women with the smallest minds.
Think big anyway.

People favor underdogs but follow only top dogs.
Fight for a few underdogs anyway.

What you spend years building may be destroyed overnight.
Build anyway.

People really need help but may attack you if you do help them.
Help people anyway.

Give the world the best you have and you'll get kicked in the teeth.
Give the world the best you have anyway." -- Kent M. Keith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299816-one-ought-not-to-judge-her-all-children-are-heartless</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2013 22:39:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299816-one-ought-not-to-judge-her-all-children-are-heartless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One ought not to judge her: all children are Heartless. They have not grown a heart yet, which is why they can climb high trees and say shocking things and leap so very high grown-up hearts flutter in terror. Hearts weigh quite a lot. That is why it takes so long to grow one. But, as in their reading and arithmetic and drawing, different children proceed at different speeds. (It is well known that reading quickens the growth of a heart like nothing else.) Some small ones are terrible and fey, Utterly Heartless. Some are dear and sweet and Hardly Heartless At All. September stood very generally in the middle on the day the Green Wind took her, Somewhat Heartless, and Somewhat Grown." -- Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430977-the-thing-about-changing-the-world-once-you-do-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 07:58:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430977-the-thing-about-changing-the-world-once-you-do-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The thing about changing the world... Once you do it, the world's all different." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28811-i-have-been-and-still-am-a-seeker-but-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2013 13:40:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28811-i-have-been-and-still-am-a-seeker-but-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have been and still am a seeker, but I have ceased to question stars and books; I have begun to listen to the teaching my blood whispers to me." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280025-knowledge-is-a-weapon-i-intend-to-be-formidably-armed</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2013 14:05:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Terry Goodkind]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280025-knowledge-is-a-weapon-i-intend-to-be-formidably-armed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Knowledge is a weapon. I intend to be formidably armed." -- Terry Goodkind]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10579-you-know-one-of-the-tragedies-of-real-life-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 13:01:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Annie Proulx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10579-you-know-one-of-the-tragedies-of-real-life-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know, one of the tragedies of real life is that there is no background music." -- Annie Proulx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/611382-in-the-future-you-make-for-yourselves-anything-is-possible</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 16:57:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by R.J. Palacio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/611382-in-the-future-you-make-for-yourselves-anything-is-possible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...in the future you make for yourselves, anything is possible. If every single person in this room made it a rule that wherever you are, whenever you can, you will try to act a little kinder than is necessary - the world really would be a better place. And if you do this, if you act just a little kinder than is necessary, someone else, somewhere, someday, may recognize in you, in every single one of you, the face of God." -- R.J. Palacio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/921532-just-as-i-have-insisted-on-his-worth-he-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 14:58:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Veronica Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/921532-just-as-i-have-insisted-on-his-worth-he-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just as I have insisted on his worth, he has always insisted on my strength, insisted that my capacity is greater than I believe.  And I know, without being told, that's what love does, when it's right-it makes you more than you were, more than you thought you could be.
This is right." -- Veronica Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920793-i-was-so-afraid-that-we-would-just-keep-colliding</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 15:03:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Veronica Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920793-i-was-so-afraid-that-we-would-just-keep-colliding]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was so afraid that we would just keep colliding over and over again if we stayed together, and that eventually the impact would break me. But now I know I am like the blade and he is like the whetstone-
I am too strong to break so easily, and I become better, sharper, every time I touch him." -- Veronica Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160972-she-thought-there-were-no-gods-no-one-was-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 19:30:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160972-she-thought-there-were-no-gods-no-one-was-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She thought there were no Gods; no one was to blame; and so she evolved this atheist's religion of doing good for the sake of goodness." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 18:27:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what you shall do; Love the earth and sun and the animals, despise riches, give alms to every one that asks, stand up for the stupid and crazy, devote your income and labor to others, hate tyrants, argue not concerning God, have patience and indulgence toward the people, take off your hat to nothing known or unknown or to any man or number of men, go freely with powerful uneducated persons and with the young and with the mothers of families, read these leaves in the open air every season of every year of your life, re-examine all you have been told at school or church or in any book, dismiss whatever insults your own soul, and your very flesh shall be a great poem and have the richest fluency not only in its words but in the silent lines of its lips and face and between the lashes of your eyes and in every motion and joint of your body." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26346-stop-this-day-and-night-with-me-and-you-shall</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 23:07:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26346-stop-this-day-and-night-with-me-and-you-shall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stop this day and night with me and you shall possess the origin of all poems,
You shall possess the good of the earth and sun.... there are millions of suns left,
You shall no longer take things at second or third hand.... nor look through the eyes of the dead.... nor feed on the spectres in books,
You shall not look through my eyes either, nor take things from me,
You shall listen to all sides and filter them from yourself." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/972628-have-you-heard-that-it-was-good-to-gain-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 23:49:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/972628-have-you-heard-that-it-was-good-to-gain-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you heard that it was good to gain the day?
I also say it is good to fall, battles are lost in the same spirit
in which they are won." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44400-forever-is-composed-of-nows</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 16:54:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Emily Dickinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44400-forever-is-composed-of-nows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Forever is composed of nows." -- Emily Dickinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/973323-i-hope-that-in-this-year-to-come-you-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 18:31:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/973323-i-hope-that-in-this-year-to-come-you-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hope that in this year to come, you make mistakes. Because if you are making mistakes...you're Doing Something." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/918994-of-course-i-ll-hurt-you-of-course-you-ll-hurt-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 19:44:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/918994-of-course-i-ll-hurt-you-of-course-you-ll-hurt-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of course I’ll hurt you. Of course you’ll hurt me. Of course we will hurt each other. But this is the very condition of existence. To become spring, means accepting the risk of winter. To become presence, means accepting the risk of absence." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299192-not-all-those-who-wander-are-lost</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 19:47:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299192-not-all-those-who-wander-are-lost]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not all those who wander are lost." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/691583-but-maybe-happiness-isn-t-in-the-choosing-maybe-it-s-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 19:51:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Lauren Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/691583-but-maybe-happiness-isn-t-in-the-choosing-maybe-it-s-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But maybe happiness isn't in the choosing.  Maybe it's in the fiction, in the pretending: that wherever we have ended up is where we intended to be all along." -- Lauren Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246188-i-tramp-the-perpetual-journey-my-signs-are-a-rain-proof</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 21:03:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246188-i-tramp-the-perpetual-journey-my-signs-are-a-rain-proof]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I tramp the perpetual journey
My signs are a rain-proof coat, good shoes, and a staff cut from the 
woods, 
No friend of mine takes his ease in my chair, 
I have no chair, no philosophy, 
I lead no man to a dinner-table, library, exchange, 
But each man and each woman of you I lead upon a knoll, 
My left hand hooking you round the waist, 
My right hand pointing to landscapes of continents and the public 
road. 

Not I, not any one else can travel that road for you, 
You must travel it for yourself. 

It is not far, it is within reach, 
Perhaps you have been on it since you were born and did not know, 
Perhaps it is everywhere on water and on land. 

Shoulder your duds dear son, and I will mine, and let us hasten 
forth, 
Wonderful cities and free nations we shall fetch as we go. 

If you tire, give me both burdens, and rest the chuff of your hand 
on my hip, 
And in due time you shall repay the same service to me, 
For after we start we never lie by again. 

This day before dawn I ascended a hill and look'd at the crowded 
heaven, 
And I said to my spirit When we become the enfolders of those orbs, 
and the pleasure and knowledge of every thing in them, shall we 
be fill'd and satisfied then? 
And my spirit said No, we but level that lift to pass and continue 
beyond. 

You are also asking me questions and I hear you, 
I answer that I cannot answer, you must find out for yourself. 

Sit a while dear son, 
Here are biscuits to eat and here is milk to drink, 
But as soon as you sleep and renew yourself in sweet clothes, I kiss 
you with a good-by kiss and open the gate for your egress 
hence. 

Long enough have you dream'd contemptible dreams, 
Now I wash the gum from your eyes, 
You must habit yourself to the dazzle of the light and of every 
moment of your life. 

Long have you timidly waded holding a plank by the shore, 
Now I will you to be a bold swimmer, 
To jump off in the midst of the sea, rise again, nod to me, shout, 
and laughingly dash with your hair." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
