<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/58945-sarah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/58945-sarah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 08:27:50 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/342624-if-only-shiroyama-dreams-human-beings-were-not-masks-behind</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 08:27:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/342624-if-only-shiroyama-dreams-human-beings-were-not-masks-behind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If only,’ Shiroyama dreams, ‘human beings were not masks behind masks behind masks. If only this world was a clean board of lines and intersections. If only time was a sequence of considered moves and not a chaos of slippages and blunders." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/513095-scientists-estimate-the-universe-unfolded-from-its-state-of-infinite</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 20:47:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/513095-scientists-estimate-the-universe-unfolded-from-its-state-of-infinite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Scientists estimate the universe unfolded from its state of infinite destiny* - a moment commonly referred to as &quot;the big bang&quot; - approximately 1.3-2 x 10^10 years ago.

*Typo: &quot;destiny&quot; should read &quot;density." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/513102-in-the-end-navidson-is-left-with-one-page-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 20:53:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/513102-in-the-end-navidson-is-left-with-one-page-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the end Navidson is left with one page and one match. For a long time he waits in darkness and cold, postponing this final bit of illumination. At last though, he grips the match by the neck and after locating the friction strip sparks to life a final ball of light.

First, he reads a few lines by match light and then as the heat bites his fingertips he applies the flame to the page. Here then is one end: a final act of reading, a final act of consumption. And as the fire rapidly devours the paper, Navidson's eyes frantically sweep down over the text, keeping just ahead of the necessary immolation, until as he reaches the last few words, flames lick around his hands, ash peels off into the surrounding emptiness, and then as the fire retreats, dimming, its light suddenly spent, the book is gone leaving nothing behind but invisible traces already dismantled in the dark." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108834-there-are-so-many-fragile-things-after-all-people-break</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 21:00:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108834-there-are-so-many-fragile-things-after-all-people-break]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are so many fragile things, after all.  People break so easily, and so do dreams and hearts." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18285-wit-beyond-measure-is-a-man-s-greatest-treasure</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 21:02:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18285-wit-beyond-measure-is-a-man-s-greatest-treasure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wit beyond measure is a man's greatest treasure." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121457-a-book-you-finish-reading-is-not-the-same-book</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 07:11:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121457-a-book-you-finish-reading-is-not-the-same-book]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book you finish reading is not the same book it was before you read it." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 22:28:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I say is, a town isn't a town without a bookstore. It may call itself a town, but unless it's got a bookstore it knows it's not fooling a soul." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11285-god-does-not-play-dice-with-the-universe-he-plays</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 22:28:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11285-god-does-not-play-dice-with-the-universe-he-plays]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God does not play dice with the universe; He plays an ineffable game of His own devising, which might be compared, from the perspective of any of the other players [i.e. everybody], to being involved in an obscure and complex variant of poker in a pitch-dark room, with blank cards, for infinite stakes, with a Dealer who won't tell you the rules, and who &lt;i&gt;smiles all the time&lt;/i&gt;." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474350-you-should-know-i-disagree-with-a-lot-of-traditional</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 22:37:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Mindy Kaling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474350-you-should-know-i-disagree-with-a-lot-of-traditional]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You should know I disagree with a lot of traditional advice. For instance, they say the best revenge is living well. I say it’s acid in the face—who will love them now?" -- Mindy Kaling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3063-a-half-read-book-is-a-half-finished-love-affair</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 07:39:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3063-a-half-read-book-is-a-half-finished-love-affair]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A half-read book is a half-finished love affair." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218971-it-is-just-an-illusion-here-on-earth-that-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 07:46:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218971-it-is-just-an-illusion-here-on-earth-that-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is just an illusion here on Earth that one moment follows another one, like beads on a string, and that once a moment is gone, it is gone forever." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158384-billy-looked-at-the-clock-on-the-gas-stove-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 07:47:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158384-billy-looked-at-the-clock-on-the-gas-stove-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Billy looked at the clock on the gas stove. He had an hour to kill before the saucer came. He went into the living room, swinging the bottle like a dinner bell, turned on the television. He came slightly unstuck in time, saw the late movie backwards, then forwards again. It was a movie about American bombers in the Second World War and the gallant men who flew them. Seen backwards by Billy, the story went like this: American planes, full of holes and wounded men and corpses took off backwards from an airfield in England. Over France a few German fighter planes flew at them backwards, sucked bullets and shell fragments from some of the planes and crewmen. They did the same for wrecked American bombers on the ground, and those planes flew up backwards to join the formation.
The formation flew backwards over a German city that was in flames. The bombers opened their bomb bay doors, exerted a miraculous magnetism which shrunk the fires, gathered them into cylindrical steel containers, and lifted the containers into the bellies of the planes. The containers were stored neatly in racks. The Germans below had miraculous devices of their own, which were long steel tubes. They used them to suck more fragments from the crewmen and planes. But there were still a few wounded Americans, though, and some of the bombers were in bad repair. Over France, though, German fighters came up again, made everything and everybody as good as new.
When the bombers got back to their base, the steel cylinders were taken from the racks and shipped back to the United States of America, where factories were operating night and day, dismantling the cylinders, separating the dangerous contents into minerals. Touchingly, it was mainly women who did this work. The minerals were then shipped to specialists in remote areas. It was their business to put them into the ground., to hide them cleverly, so they would never hurt anybody ever again.
The American fliers turned in their uniforms, became high school kids. And Hitler turned into a baby, Billy Pilgrim supposed. That wasn't in the movie. Billy was extrapolating. Everybody turned into a baby, and all humanity, without exception, conspired biologically to produce two perfect people named Adam and Eve, he supposed." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242666-holding-this-soft-small-living-creature-in-my-lap-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 23:33:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242666-holding-this-soft-small-living-creature-in-my-lap-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Holding this soft, small living creature in my lap this way, though, and seeing how it slept with complete trust in me, I felt a warm rush in my chest. I put my hand on the cat's chest and felt his heart beating. The pulse was faint and fast, but his heart, like mine, was ticking off the time allotted to his small body with all the restless earnestness of my own." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154758-i-don-t-know----maybe-the-world-has-two-different</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 23:33:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154758-i-don-t-know----maybe-the-world-has-two-different]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know -- maybe the world has two different kinds of people, and for one kind the world is this completely logical, rice pudding place, and for the other it's all hit-or-miss macaroni gratin." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127314-i-m-going-to-take-you-out-of-here-i-m</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 23:35:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127314-i-m-going-to-take-you-out-of-here-i-m]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm going to take you out of here ... I'm going to take you home, to the world where you belong, where cats with bent tails live, and there are little backyards, and alarm clocks ring in the morning." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/373001-to-say-i-m-an-overrated-troll-when-you-have-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 22:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/373001-to-say-i-m-an-overrated-troll-when-you-have-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To say I’m an overrated troll, when you have never even seen me guard a bridge, is patently unfair." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 18:32:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hello babies. Welcome to Earth. It's hot in the summer and cold in the winter. It's round and wet and crowded. On the outside, babies, you've got a hundred years here. There's only one rule that I know of, babies-&quot;God damn it, you've got to be kind." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
