<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/59029-emily]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/59029-emily" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 11:32:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41284-she-had-lost-all-our-memories-for-ever-and-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 11:32:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41284-she-had-lost-all-our-memories-for-ever-and-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had lost all our memories for ever, and it was as though by dying she had robbed me of part of myself. I was losing my individuality. It was the first stage of my own death, the memories dropping off like gangrened limbs." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71296-when-she-packed-up-to-leave-she-knew-that-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 11:32:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Lorrie Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71296-when-she-packed-up-to-leave-she-knew-that-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When she packed up to leave, she knew that she was saying goodbye to something important, which was not that bad, in a way, because it meant that at least you had said hello to it to begin with..." -- Lorrie Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15887-what-is-the-meaning-of-life-that-was-all--a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2010 09:01:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15887-what-is-the-meaning-of-life-that-was-all--a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is the meaning of life? That was all- a simple question; one that tended to close in on one with years, the great revelation had never come. The great revelation perhaps never did come. Instead, there were little daily miracles, illuminations, matches struck unexpectedly in the dark; here was one." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7692-if-there-is-no-love-in-the-world-we-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 19:50:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7692-if-there-is-no-love-in-the-world-we-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there is no love in the world, we will make a new world, and we will give it walls, and we will furnish it with soft, red interiors, from the inside out, and give it a knocker that resonates like a diamond falling to a jeweller's felt so that we should never hear it. Love me, because love doesn't exist, and I have tried everything that does." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7903-draw-your-chair-up-close-to-the-edge-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2010 08:46:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7903-draw-your-chair-up-close-to-the-edge-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Draw your chair up close to the edge of the precipice and I’ll tell you a story." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9415-she-took-her-hand-and-raised-her-brush-for-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2010 09:01:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9415-she-took-her-hand-and-raised-her-brush-for-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...she took her hand and raised her brush. For a moment it stayed trembling in a painful but exciting ecstacy in the air. Where to begin?--that was the question at what point to make the first mark? One line placed on the canvas committed her to innumerable risks, to frequent and irrevocable decisions. All that in idea seemed simple became in practice immediately complex; as the waves shape themselves symmetrically from the cliff top, but to the swimmer among them are divided by steep gulfs, and foaming crests. Still the risk must run; the mark made." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13799-to-say-i-love-you-one-must-know-first-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 11:32:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13799-to-say-i-love-you-one-must-know-first-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To say &quot;I love you&quot; one must know first how to say the &quot;I&quot;." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15417-when-a-child-first-catches-adults-out----when-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 11:37:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15417-when-a-child-first-catches-adults-out----when-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a child first catches adults out -- when it first walks into his grave little head that adults do not always have divine intelligence, that their judgments are not always wise, their thinking true, their sentences just -- his world falls into panic desolation. The gods are fallen and all safety gone. And there is one sure thing about the fall of gods: they do not fall a little; they crash and shatter or sink deeply into green muck. It is a tedious job to build them up again; they never quite shine. And the child's world is never quite whole again. It is an aching kind of growing." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36026-if-you-don-t-know-the-thing-to-do-is-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 11:39:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36026-if-you-don-t-know-the-thing-to-do-is-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you don't know, the thing to do is not to get scared, but to learn." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16805-for-the-sake-of-a-few-lines-one-must-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 11:43:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16805-for-the-sake-of-a-few-lines-one-must-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the sake of a few lines one must see many cities, men and things. One must know the animals, one must feel how the birds fly and know the gesture with which the small flowers open in the morning. One must be able to think back to roads in unknown regions, to unexpected meetings and to partings which one had long seen coming; to days of childhood that are still unexplained, to parents that one had to hurt when they brought one some joy and one did not grasp it (it was joy for someone else); to childhood illness that so strangely began with a number of profound and grave transformations, to days in rooms withdrawn and quiet and to mornings by the sea, to the sea itself, to seas, to nights of travel that rushed along on  high and flew with all the stars-and it is not enough if one may think all of this. One must have memories of many nights of love, none of which was like the others, of the screams of women in labor, and of light, white, sleeping women in childbed, closing again. But one must also have been beside the dying, one must have sat beside the dead in the room with the open window and the fitful noises. And still it is not enough to have memories. One must be able to forget them when they are many, and one must have the great patience to wait until they come again. For it is not yet the memories themselves. Not until they have turned to blood within us, to glance, to gesture, nameless and no longer to be distinguished from ourselves-not until then can it happen that in a most rare hour the first word of a verse arises in their midst and goes forth from them." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71213-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-who-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 11:44:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71213-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-who-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time there was a boy who loved a girl, and her laughter was a question he wanted to spend his whole life answering." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95327-one-realizes-that-even-in-harmonious-families-there-is-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 15:41:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Willa Cather]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95327-one-realizes-that-even-in-harmonious-families-there-is-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One realizes that even in harmonious families there is this  double life:  the group life, which is the one we  can observe in our neighbour’s household, and, underneath, another – secret and  passionate and intense – which is the real life that stamps the  faces and gives character to the voices of our friends.  Always in his mind each member of these social units is escaping, running away, trying to break the net which circumstances and his own affections have woven about him. One realizes that human relationships are the tragic necessity of human life; that they can never be wholly satisfactory, that every ego is half the time greedily seeking them, and half the time pulling away from them.  In those simple relationships of loving husband and wife, affectionate sisters, children and grandmother, there are  innumerable shades of sweetness and anguish which make up the pattern of  our lives day by day . . ." -- Willa Cather]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308416-sometimes-as-now-her-heart-twisted-and-broke-under-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2010 09:29:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Shirley Hazzard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308416-sometimes-as-now-her-heart-twisted-and-broke-under-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, as now, her heart twisted and broke under his determination to wound her.  At others, she was almost convinced that she felt nothing more for him, that he had overdrawn on her endurance: then she would stay silent for awhile, almost at peace, beyond his reach, not knowing whether she had been utterly vanquished or become completely invincible.  However, it required merely some slight attention on his part to restore all her apprehensions - for these extremes of feeling only existed within the compass of her love.&quot;

&lt;i&gt;&quot;In One's Own House&lt;/i&gt;" -- Shirley Hazzard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270590-agnes-shay-had-the-true-spirit-of-a-maid-moistened</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 13:57:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by John Cheever]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270590-agnes-shay-had-the-true-spirit-of-a-maid-moistened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Agnes Shay had the true spirit of a maid. Moistened with dishwater and mild eau de cologne, reared in narrow and sunless bedrooms, in back passages, back stairs, laundries, linen closets, and in those servants' halls that remind one of a prison, her soul had grown docile and bleak...Agnes loved the ceremonies of a big house. She drew the curtains in the living room at dark, lighted the candles on the table, and struck the dinner chimes like an eager altar boy. On fine evenings, when she sat on the back porch between the garbage pails and the woodbins, she liked to recall the faces of all the cooks she had known. It made her life seem rich." -- John Cheever]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8635-that-is-what-is-wrong-with-cold-people-not-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2010 23:33:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Lorrie Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8635-that-is-what-is-wrong-with-cold-people-not-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That is what is wrong with cold people. Not that they have ice in their souls - we all have a bit of that - but that they insist every word and deed mirror that ice. They never learn the beauty or value of gesture. The emotional necessity. For them, it is all honesty before kindness, truth before art. Love is art, not truth. It's like painting scenery." -- Lorrie Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140032-there-were-moments-bristling-with-deadness-when-she-looked-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 15:46:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Lorrie Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140032-there-were-moments-bristling-with-deadness-when-she-looked-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There were moments bristling with deadness, when she looked out at her life and went, &quot;&lt;i&gt;What?&lt;/i&gt;&quot; Or worse, feeling interrupted and tired, &quot;Wha—?" -- Lorrie Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8145-it-s-a-strange-thing-to-discover-and-to-believe-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 19:59:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8145-it-s-a-strange-thing-to-discover-and-to-believe-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's a strange thing to discover and to believe that you are loved when you know that there is nothing in you for anybody but a parent or a God to love." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41291-the-sense-of-unhappiness-is-so-much-easier-to-convey</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 19:59:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41291-the-sense-of-unhappiness-is-so-much-easier-to-convey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sense of unhappiness is so much easier to convey than that of happiness. In misery we seem aware of our own existence, even though it may be in the form of a monstrous egotism: this pain of mine is individual, this nerve that winces belongs to me and to no other. But happiness annihilates  us: we lose our identity." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331545-quite-simply-i-was-in-love-with-new-york-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 12:12:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331545-quite-simply-i-was-in-love-with-new-york-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…quite simply, I was in love with New York. I do not mean &quot;love&quot; in any colloquial way, I mean that I was in love with the city, the way you love the first person who ever touches you and you never love anyone quite that way again. I remember walking across Sixty-second Street one twilight that first spring, or the second spring, they were all alike for a while. I was late to meet someone but I stopped at Lexington Avenue and bought a peach and stood on the corner eating it and knew that I had come out out of the West and reached the mirage. I could taste the peach and feel the soft air blowing from a subway grating on my legs and I could smell lilac and garbage and expensive perfume and I knew that it would cost something sooner or later—because I did not belong there, did not come from there" -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333751-the-impulse-to-write-things-down-is-a-peculiarly-compulsive</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 12:16:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333751-the-impulse-to-write-things-down-is-a-peculiarly-compulsive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The impulse to write things down is a peculiarly compulsive one, inexplicable to those who do not share it, useful only accidentally, only secondarily, in the way that any compulsion tries to justify itself. I suppose that it begins or does not begin in the cradle. Although I have felt compelled to write things down since I was five years old, I doubt that my daughter ever will, for she is a singularly blessed and accepting child, delighted with life exactly as life presents itself to her, unafraid to go to sleep and unafraid to wake up. Keepers of private notebooks are a different breed altogether, lonely and resistant rearrangers of things, anxious malcontents, children afflicted apparently at birth with some presentiment of loss." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316159-what-i-really-fear-is-time-that-s-the-devil-whipping</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 09:04:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Tom Rachman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316159-what-i-really-fear-is-time-that-s-the-devil-whipping]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I really fear is time. That's the devil: whipping us on when we'd rather loll, so the present sprints by, impossible to grasp, and all is suddenly past, a past that won't hold still, that slides into these inauthentic tales. My past- it doesn't feel real in the slightest. The person who inhabited it is not me. It's as if the present me is constantly dissolving. There's that line from Heraclitus: 'No man steps in the same river twice, for it is not the same river and he is not the same man.' That's quite right. We enjoy this illusion of continuity, and we call it memory. Which explains, perhaps, why our worst fear isn't the end of life but the end of memories." -- Tom Rachman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
