<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/590916-brianna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/590916-brianna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 04:01:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21108-am-i-mad-to-see-what-others-do-not-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 04:01:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brianna add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21108-am-i-mad-to-see-what-others-do-not-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Am I mad, to see what others do not see, or are they mad who are responsible for all that I am seeing?" -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147602-feel-feel-i-say---feel-for-all-you-re-worth</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2009 07:15:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brianna add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147602-feel-feel-i-say---feel-for-all-you-re-worth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Feel, feel, I say - feel for all you're worth, and even if it half kills you, for that is the only way to live" -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105928-you-live-like-this-sheltered-in-a-delicate-world-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2012 04:52:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brianna add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105928-you-live-like-this-sheltered-in-a-delicate-world-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You live like this, sheltered, in a delicate world, and you believe you are living. Then you read a book… or you take a trip… and you discover that you are not living, that you are hibernating. The symptoms of hibernating are easily detectable: first, restlessness. The second symptom (when hibernating becomes dangerous and might degenerate into death): absence of pleasure. That is all. It appears like an innocuous illness. Monotony, boredom, death. Millions live like this (or die like this) without knowing it. They work in offices. They drive a car. They picnic with their families. They raise children. And then some shock treatment takes place, a person, a book, a song, and it awakens them and saves them from death. Some never awaken." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878738-the-elm-log-by-alexander-solzhenitsyn-we-were-sawing-firewood</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 14:14:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brianna add a quote by Alexander Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878738-the-elm-log-by-alexander-solzhenitsyn-we-were-sawing-firewood]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Elm Log
By Alexander Solzhenitsyn

We were sawing firewood when we picked up an elm log and gave a cry of amazement. It was a full year since we had chopped down the trunk, dragged it along behind a tractor and sawn it up into logs, which we had then thrown on to barges and wagons, rolled into stacks and piled up on the ground - and yet this elm log had still not given up! A fresh green shoot had sprouted from it with a promise of a thick, leafy branch, or even a whole new elm tree.

We placed the log on the sawing-horse, as though on an executioner's block, but we could not bring ourselves to bite into it with our saw. How could we? That log cherished life as dearly as we did; indeed, its urge to live was even stronger than ours." -- Alexander Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/663835-the-mantle-of-spinsterhood-was-definitely-on-her-shoulders-now</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 11:21:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brianna add a quote by Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/663835-the-mantle-of-spinsterhood-was-definitely-on-her-shoulders-now]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The mantle of spinsterhood was definitely on her shoulders now. She was twenty-five and looked it, and so there as no longer any need to try to be attractive." -- Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
