<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/592631-bronwyn]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/592631-bronwyn" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 07:28:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315932-once-a-little-boy-sent-me-a-charming-card-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 07:28:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bronwyn add a quote by Maurice Sendak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315932-once-a-little-boy-sent-me-a-charming-card-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once a little boy sent me a charming card with a little drawing on it. I loved it. I answer all my children’s letters — sometimes very hastily — but this one I lingered over. I sent him a card and I drew a picture of a Wild Thing on it. I wrote, “Dear Jim: I loved your card.” Then I got a letter back from his mother and she said, “Jim loved your card so much he ate it.” That to me was one of the highest compliments I’ve ever received. He didn’t care that it was an original Maurice Sendak drawing or anything. He saw it, he loved it, he ate it." -- Maurice Sendak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1159587-in-1913-when-anthony-patch-was-twenty-five-two-years-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 12:58:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bronwyn add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1159587-in-1913-when-anthony-patch-was-twenty-five-two-years-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In 1913, when Anthony Patch was twenty-five, two years were already gone since irony, the Holy Ghost of this later day, had, theoretically at least, descended upon him. Irony was the final polish of the shoe, the ultimate dab of the clothes-brush, a sort of intellectual &quot;There!&quot;—yet" -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1159597-as-you-first-see-him-he-wonders-frequently-whether-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 13:04:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bronwyn add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1159597-as-you-first-see-him-he-wonders-frequently-whether-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As you first see him he wonders frequently whether he is not without honor and slightly mad, a shameful and obscene thinness glistening on the surface of the world like oil on a clean pond, these occasions being varied, of course, with those in which he thinks himself rather an exceptional young man, thoroughly sophisticated, well adjusted to his environment, and somewhat more significant than any one else he knows." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
