<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/592796-anurekha]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/592796-anurekha" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 09:18:51 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19778-the-secret-of-the-great-stories-is-that-they-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 09:18:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anurekha add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19778-the-secret-of-the-great-stories-is-that-they-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...the secret of the Great Stories is that they &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; no secrets. The Great Stories are the ones you have heard and want to hear again. The ones you can enter anywhere and inhabit comfortably. They don’t deceive you with thrills and trick endings. They don’t surprise you with the unforeseen. They are as familiar as the house you live in. Or the smell of your lover’s skin. You know how they end, yet you listen as though you don’t. In the way that although you know that one day you will die, you live as though you won’t. In the Great Stories you know who lives, who dies, who finds love, who doesn’t. And yet you want to know again.

&lt;i&gt;That&lt;/i&gt; is their mystery and their magic." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19791-to-him-she-seemed-so-beautiful-so-seductive-so-different</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 09:33:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anurekha add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19791-to-him-she-seemed-so-beautiful-so-seductive-so-different]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To him she seemed so beautiful, so seductive, so different from ordinary people, that he could not understand why no one was as disturbed as he by the clicking of her heels on the paving stones, why no one else's heart was wild with the breeze stirred by the sighs of her veils, why everyone did not go mad with the movements of her braid, the flight of her hands, the gold of her laughter. He had not missed a single one of her gestures, not one of the indications of her character, but he did not dare approach her for fear of destroying the spell." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19794-is-there-in-the-whole-world-a-being-who-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 09:41:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anurekha add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19794-is-there-in-the-whole-world-a-being-who-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is there in the whole world a being who would have the right to forgive and could forgive? I don't want harmony. From love for humanity I don't want it. I would rather be left with the unavenged suffering. I would rather remain with my unavenged suffering and unsatisfied indignation, even if I were wrong. Besides, too high a price is asked for harmony; it's beyond our means to pay so much to enter on it. And so I hasten to give back my entrance ticket, and if I am an honest man I am bound to give it back as soon as possible. And that I am doing. It's not God that I don't accept, Alyosha, only I most respectfully return him the ticket." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
