<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/593228-margie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/593228-margie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 11:54:56 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38280-eat-food-not-much-mostly-plants</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 11:54:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Michael Pollen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38280-eat-food-not-much-mostly-plants]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eat Food. Not Much. Mostly plants." -- Michael Pollen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220098-call-on-god-but-row-away-from-the-rocks</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 11:55:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220098-call-on-god-but-row-away-from-the-rocks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Call on God, but row away from the rocks." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4138-it-s-no-good-pretending-that-any-relationship-has-a-future</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 11:55:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4138-it-s-no-good-pretending-that-any-relationship-has-a-future]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's no good pretending that any relationship has a future if your record collections disagree violently or if your favorite films wouldn't even speak to each other if they met at a party." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10839-music-has-always-been-a-matter-of-energy-to-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 11:55:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10839-music-has-always-been-a-matter-of-energy-to-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Music has always been a matter of Energy to me, a question of Fuel.  Sentimental people call it Inspiration, but what they really mean is Fuel.  I have always needed Fuel. I am a serious consumer.  On some nights I still believe that a car with the gas needle on empty can run about fifty more miles if you have the right music very loud on the radio." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100028-on-my-fifth-trip-to-france-i-limited-myself-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 08:52:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100028-on-my-fifth-trip-to-france-i-limited-myself-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On my fifth trip to France I limited myself to the words and phrases that people actually use. From the dog owners I learned &quot;Lie down,&quot; &quot;Shut up,&quot; and &quot;Who shit on this carpet?&quot; The couple across the road taught me to ask questions correctly, and the grocer taught me to count. Things began to come together, and I went from speaking like an evil baby to speaking like a hillbilly. &quot;Is thems the thoughts of cows?&quot; I'd ask the butcher, pointing to the calves' brains displayed in the front window. &quot;I want me some lamb chop with handles on 'em." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18953-each-person-leaves-a-legacy--a-single-small-piece-of-herself</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 11:50:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by John Nichols]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18953-each-person-leaves-a-legacy--a-single-small-piece-of-herself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each person leaves a legacy--a single, small piece of herself, which makes richer each individual life and the collective life of humanity as a whole. But do not despair, for despair is a despicable and bourgeois affectation; we must not allow it.  As for what happens next, well, as the Cuban poet Regino Pedroso once said, &quot;como forjamos el hierro, forjaremos días nuevos&quot;: as we hammer out iron, we shall hammer out new days." -- John Nichols]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1944-a-woman-is-like-a-tea-bag-you-never-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 11:51:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1944-a-woman-is-like-a-tea-bag-you-never-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A woman is like a tea bag; you never know how strong it is until it's in hot water." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10840-your-memory-is-a-monster-you-forget-it-doesn-t-it-simply</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 09:11:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10840-your-memory-is-a-monster-you-forget-it-doesn-t-it-simply]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your memory is a monster; you forget—it doesn't. It simply files things away. It keeps things for you, or hides things from you—and summons them to your recall with will of its own. You think you have a memory; but it has you!" -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6708-the-statistics-on-sanity-are-that-one-out-of-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 09:11:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Rita Mae Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6708-the-statistics-on-sanity-are-that-one-out-of-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The statistics on sanity are that one out of every four people is suffering from a mental illness. Look at your 3 best friends. If they're ok, then it's you." -- Rita Mae Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1538-but-all-she-wanted-to-do-was-lie-in-bed</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 09:26:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Rebecca Wells]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1538-but-all-she-wanted-to-do-was-lie-in-bed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But all she wanted to do was lie in bed, eat Kraft macaroni and cheese, and hide from the alligators." -- Rebecca Wells]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19375-humanity-has-advanced-when-it-has-advanced-not-because-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 09:26:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by tom robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19375-humanity-has-advanced-when-it-has-advanced-not-because-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humanity has advanced, when it has advanced, not because it has been sober, responsible, and cautious, but because it has been playful, rebellious, and immature." -- tom robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113300-what-keeps-you-going-isn-t-some-fine-destination-but-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 09:26:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113300-what-keeps-you-going-isn-t-some-fine-destination-but-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What keeps you going isn't some fine destination but just the road you're on, and the fact that you know how to drive. You keep your eyes open, you see this damned-to-hell world you got born into, and you ask yourself, 'What life can I live that will let me breathe in &amp; out and love somebody or something and not run off screaming into the woods?" -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40146-human-beings-are-remarkable---at-what-we-can-learn</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 09:26:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40146-human-beings-are-remarkable---at-what-we-can-learn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human beings are remarkable - at what we can learn to live with. If we couldn't get strong from what we lose, and what we miss, and what we want and can't have, then we couldn't ever get strong enough, could we? What else makes us strong?" -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3659-people-of-ze-wurl-relax</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 09:25:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3659-people-of-ze-wurl-relax]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People of ze wurl, relax!" -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113306-so-you-make-this-deal-with-the-gods-you-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 09:24:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113306-so-you-make-this-deal-with-the-gods-you-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So you make this deal with the gods. You do these dances and they'll send rain and good crops and the whole works? And nothing bad will ever happen. Right.' Prayer had always struck me as more or less a glorified attempt at a business transaction. A rain dance even more so.
I thought I might finally have offended Loyd past the point of no return, like stealing the lobster from frozen foods that time, to get myself fired. But Loyd was just thinking. After a minute he said, 'No, it's not like that. It's not making a deal, bad things can still happen, but you want to try not to &lt;i&gt;cause&lt;/i&gt; them to happen. It has to do with keeping things in balance.'
In balance.'
Really, it's like the spirits have made a deal with &lt;i&gt;us&lt;/i&gt;.'
And what is the deal?' I asked.
We're on our own. The spirits have been good enough to let us live here and use the utilities, and we're saying: We know how nice you're being. We appreciate the rain, we appreciate the sun, we appreciate the deer we took. Sorry if we messed up anything. You've gone to a lot of trouble, and we'll try to be good guests.'
Like a note you'd send somebody after you stayed in their house?'
Exactly like that. 'Thanks for letting me sleep on your couch. I took some beer out of the refrigerator, and I broke a coffee cup. Sorry, I hope it wasn't your favorite one." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236585-he-unzipped-his-pants-and-his-brains-fell-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 11:48:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Rita Mae Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236585-he-unzipped-his-pants-and-his-brains-fell-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He unzipped his pants and his brains fell out." -- Rita Mae Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6499-evelyn-was-an-insomniac-so-when-they-say-she-died</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 11:54:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Garrison Keillor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6499-evelyn-was-an-insomniac-so-when-they-say-she-died]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Evelyn was an insomniac so when they say she died in her sleep, you have to question that." -- Garrison Keillor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4352-how-do-people-like-not-curse-how-is-it-possible</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 11:53:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4352-how-do-people-like-not-curse-how-is-it-possible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How do people, like, not curse? How is it possible? There are these gaps in speech where you just have to put a &quot;fuck.&quot; I'll tell you who the most admirable people in the world are: newscasters. If that was me, I'd be like, &quot;And the motherfuckers flew the fucking plane right into the Twin Towers.&quot; How could you not, if you're a human being? Maybe they're not so admirable. Maybe they're robot zombies." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15849-make-a-radical-change-in-your-lifestyle-and-begin-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 11:53:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15849-make-a-radical-change-in-your-lifestyle-and-begin-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["make a radical change in your lifestyle and begin to boldly do things which you may previously never have thought of doing, or been too hesitant to attempt. So many people live within unhappy circumstances and yet will not take the initiative to change their situation because they are conditioned to a life of security, conformity, and conservation, all of which may appear to give one peace of mind, but in reality nothing is more damaging to the adventurous spirit within a man than a secure future. The very basic core of a man's living spirit is his passion for adventure. The joy of life comes from our encounters with new experiences, and hence there is no greater joy than to have an endlessly changing horizon, for each day to have a new and different sun. If you want to get more out of life, you must lose your inclination for monotonous security and adopt a helter-skelter style of life that will at first appear to you to be crazy. But once you become accustomed to such a life you will see its full meaning and its incredible beauty." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126095-silence-is-a-mirror-so-faithful-and-yet-so-unexpected</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 11:52:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126095-silence-is-a-mirror-so-faithful-and-yet-so-unexpected]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Silence is a mirror.  So faithful, and yet so unexpected, is the relection it can throw back at men that they will go to almost any length to avoid seeing themselves in it, and if ever its duplicating surface is temporarily wiped clean of modern life's ubiquitous hubbub, they will hasten to fog it over with such desperate personal noise devices as polite conversation, hummin, whistling, imaginary dialogue, schizophrenic babble, or, should it come to that, the clandestine cannonry of their own farting.  Only in sleep is silence tolerated, and even there, most dreams have soundtracks.  Since meditation is a deliberate descent into deep internal hush, a mute stare into the ultimate looking glass, it is regarded with suspicion by the nattering masses; with hostility by buisness interests (people sitting in silent serenity are seldom consuming goods); and with spite by a clergy whose windy authority it is seen to undermine and whose bombastic livelihood it is perceived to threaten." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6019-i-wanted-you-to-see-what-real-courage-is-instead</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 11:52:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6019-i-wanted-you-to-see-what-real-courage-is-instead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted you to see what real courage is, instead of getting the idea that courage is a man with a gun in his hand. It's when you know you're licked before you begin, but you begin anyway and see it through no matter what.
- Atticus Finch" -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10856-every-now-and-then-when-your-life-gets-complicated-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 11:51:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10856-every-now-and-then-when-your-life-gets-complicated-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every now and then when your life gets complicated and the weasels start closing in, the only cure is to load up on heinous chemicals and then drive like a bastard from Hollywood to Las Vegas ... with the music at top volume and at least a pint of ether." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15325-the-only-difference-between-hitler-and-bush-is-that-hitler</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 11:51:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15325-the-only-difference-between-hitler-and-bush-is-that-hitler]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only difference between Hitler and Bush is that Hitler was elected." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190500-when-a-state-trooper-passes-me-on-the-highway-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 11:50:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Diana Joseph]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190500-when-a-state-trooper-passes-me-on-the-highway-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a state trooper passes me on the highway, I grit my teeth, check my speed, and hope nobody put a dead guy in the trunk while I was in Wal-Mart last night at two a.m." -- Diana Joseph]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213614-never-turn-your-back-on-fear-it-should-always-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 11:50:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213614-never-turn-your-back-on-fear-it-should-always-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never turn your back on fear. It should always be in front of you, like a thing that might have to be killed." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45178-music-is-the-only-religion-that-delivers-the-goods</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 09:34:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45178-music-is-the-only-religion-that-delivers-the-goods]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Music is the only religion that delivers the goods." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62365-i-m-vile-and-perverted-i-m-obsessed-and-deranged-i-ve-existed</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 09:38:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62365-i-m-vile-and-perverted-i-m-obsessed-and-deranged-i-ve-existed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm vile and perverted. 
I'm obsessed and deranged.
I've existed for years but very little has changed.
I'm the tool of the government and industry too.
For I'm destined to rule and regulate you.
You may think I'm pernicious, but you can't look away.
I'll make you think I'm delicious with the stuff that I say.
I'm the best you can get... have you guessed me yet?
I'm the slime oozing out of your TV set...." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67017-operation-self-esteem--day-fucking-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 09:43:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margie add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67017-operation-self-esteem--day-fucking-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Operation Self-Esteem--Day Fucking One." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
