<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/59506-patrick]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/59506-patrick" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 20:53:44 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237922-its-big-men-are-mostly-little-men-with-fancy-offices</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 20:53:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patrick add a quote by Raymond Chandler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237922-its-big-men-are-mostly-little-men-with-fancy-offices]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Its big men are mostly little men with fancy offices and a lot of money. A great many of them are stupid little men, with reach-me-down brains, small-town arrogance and a sort of animal knack of smelling out the taste of the stupidest part of the public. They have played in luck so long that they have come to mistake luck for enlightenment.&quot; - on Hollywood" -- Raymond Chandler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76171-to-be-truly-challenging-a-voyage-like-a-life-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 12:35:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patrick add a quote by Sterling Hayden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76171-to-be-truly-challenging-a-voyage-like-a-life-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be truly challenging, a voyage, like a life, must rest on a firm foundation of financial unrest. Otherwise, you are doomed to a routine traverse, the kind known to yachtsmen who play with their boats at sea... &quot;cruising&quot; it is called. Voyaging belongs to seamen, and to the wanderers of the world who cannot, or will not, fit in. If you are contemplating a voyage and you have the means, abandon the venture until your fortunes change. Only then will you know what the sea is all about.

&quot;I've always wanted to sail to the south seas, but I can't afford it.&quot; What these men can't afford is not to go. They are enmeshed in the cancerous discipline of &quot;security.&quot; And in the worship of security we fling our lives beneath the wheels of routine - and before we know it our lives are gone.

What does a man need - really need? A few pounds of food each day, heat and shelter, six feet to lie down in - and some form of working activity that will yield a sense of accomplishment. That's all - in the material sense, and we know it. But we are brainwashed by our economic system until we end up in a tomb beneath a pyramid of time payments, mortgages, preposterous gadgetry, playthings that divert our attention for the sheer idiocy of the charade.

The years thunder by, The dreams of youth grow dim where they lie caked in dust on the shelves of patience. Before we know it, the tomb is sealed.

Where, then, lies the answer? In choice. Which shall it be: bankruptcy of purse or bankruptcy of life? " -- Sterling Hayden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/453415-he-supposed-he-was-only-one-of-several-million-persons</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 15:02:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patrick add a quote by Charles Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/453415-he-supposed-he-was-only-one-of-several-million-persons]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He supposed he was only one of several million persons of his generation who had grown up and, somewhere around thirty, made the upsetting discovery that life wasn't going to pan out the way you'd always expected it would; and why this realization should have thrown him and not them&amp;mdash;or not too many of them&amp;mdash;was something he couldn't fathom. Life offered none of those prizes you'd been looking forward to since adolescence (he less than others, but looking forward to them all the same, if only out of curiosity). Adulthood came through with none of the pledges you'd been led somehow to believe in; the future still remained the future-illusion; a non-existent period of constantly-receding promise, hinting fulfillment, yet forever withholding the rewards. All the things that had never happened yet were never going to happen after all. It was a mug's game and there ought to be a law. But there wasn't any law, there was no rhyme or reason; and with the sour-grapes attitude of “Why the hell should there be”&amp;mdash;which is as near as you ever came to sophistication&amp;mdash;you retired within yourself and compensated for the disappointment by drink, by subsisting on daydreams, by living in a private world of your own making (hell or heaven, what did it matter?), by accomplishing or becoming in fancy what you could never bring about in fact." -- Charles Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
