<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/596333-heather-hofmaster]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/596333-heather-hofmaster" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 09:44:11 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2643-so-long-and-thanks-for-all-the-fish</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 09:44:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2643-so-long-and-thanks-for-all-the-fish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So long, and thanks for all the fish." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1-the-story-so-far-in-the-beginning-the-universe-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 09:45:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1-the-story-so-far-in-the-beginning-the-universe-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The story so far:
In the beginning the Universe was created.
This has made a lot of people very angry and been widely regarded as a bad move." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 09:45:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many books, so little time." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 09:45:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 09:45:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Groucho Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Outside of a dog, a book is man's best friend. Inside of a dog it's too dark to read." -- Groucho Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362-if-you-don-t-stand-for-something-you-will-fall-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 09:45:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Gordon A. Eadie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362-if-you-don-t-stand-for-something-you-will-fall-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you don't stand for something you will fall for anything." -- Gordon A. Eadie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 09:45:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 09:46:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Darkness cannot drive out darkness: only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate: only love can do that." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240-reality-is-merely-an-illusion-albeit-a-very-persistent-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 09:46:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240-reality-is-merely-an-illusion-albeit-a-very-persistent-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reality is merely an illusion, albeit a very persistent one." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 09:47:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finish each day and be done with it. You have done what you could.  Some blunders and absurdities no doubt crept in; forget them as soon as you can. Tomorrow is a new day.  You shall begin it serenely and with too high a spirit to be encumbered with your old nonsense." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1816-you-may-say-i-m-a-dreamer-but-i-m-not-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 09:47:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1816-you-may-say-i-m-a-dreamer-but-i-m-not-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may say I'm a dreamer, but I'm not the only one. I hope someday you'll join us. And the world will live as one." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13132-believe-nothing-no-matter-where-you-read-it-or-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 12:58:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Buddha Siddhartha Guatama Shakyamuni]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13132-believe-nothing-no-matter-where-you-read-it-or-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Believe nothing, no matter where you read it, or who said it, no matter if I have said it, unless it agrees with your own reason and your own common sense." -- Buddha Siddhartha Guatama Shakyamuni]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1269-all-that-we-are-is-the-result-of-what-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 12:58:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Gautama Buddha]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1269-all-that-we-are-is-the-result-of-what-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that we are is the result of what we have thought: it is founded on our thoughts and made up of our thoughts. If a man speak or act with an evil thought, suffering follows him as the wheel follows the hoof of the beast that draws the wagon....  If a man speak or act with a good thought, happiness follows him like a shadow that never leaves him." -- Gautama Buddha]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9770-i-cannot-live-without-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 12:58:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9770-i-cannot-live-without-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot live without books." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2312-i-have-observed-indeed-generally-that-while-in-protestant-countries</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 12:59:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2312-i-have-observed-indeed-generally-that-while-in-protestant-countries]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have observed, indeed, generally, that while in protestant countries the defections from the Platonic Christianity of the priests is to Deism, in catholic countries they are to Atheism. [author:Diderot|11004], [author:D'Alembert|3295333], [author:D’Holbach|1228712], [author:Condorcet|6420223], are known to have been among the most virtuous of men. Their virtue, then, must have had some other foundation than the love of God.

[&lt;i&gt;Letter to Thomas Law, 13 June 1814&lt;/i&gt;]" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4056-a-government-big-enough-to-give-you-everything-you-want</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 12:59:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Gerald R. Ford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4056-a-government-big-enough-to-give-you-everything-you-want]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A government big enough to give you everything you want is a government big enough to take from you everything you have." -- Gerald R. Ford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5958-we-in-america-do-not-have-government-by-the-majority</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 12:59:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5958-we-in-america-do-not-have-government-by-the-majority]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We in America do not have government by the majority. We have government by the majority who participate." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10730-4-religion-your-reason-is-now-mature-enough-to-examine</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 13:01:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10730-4-religion-your-reason-is-now-mature-enough-to-examine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["4. Religion. Your reason is now mature enough to examine this object. In the first place, divest yourself of all bias in favor of novelty &amp; singularity of opinion... shake off all the fears &amp; servile prejudices, under which weak minds are servilely crouched. &lt;b&gt;Fix reason firmly in her seat, and call to her tribunal every fact, every opinion. Question with boldness even the existence of a God; because, if there be one, he must more approve of the homage of reason, than that of blindfolded fear&lt;/b&gt;. You will naturally examine first, the religion of your own country. Read the Bible, then as you would read [author:Livy|2840091] or [author:Tacitus|2936846]. The facts which are within the ordinary course of nature, you will believe on the authority of the writer, as you do those of the same kind in [author:Livy|2840091] and [author:Tacitus|2936846]. The testimony of the writer weighs in their favor, in one scale, and their not being against the laws of nature, does not weigh against them. But those facts in the Bible which contradict the laws of nature, must be examined with more care, and under a variety of faces. Here you must recur to the pretensions of the writer to inspiration from God. Examine upon what evidence his pretensions are founded, and whether that evidence is so strong, as that its falsehood would be more improbable than a change in the laws of nature, in the case he relates. For example in the book of Joshua we are told the sun stood still several hours. Were we to read that fact in [author:Livy|2840091] or [author:Tacitus|2936846] we should class it with their showers of blood, speaking of statues, beasts, &amp;c. But it is said that the writer of that book was inspired. Examine therefore candidly what evidence there is of his having been inspired. The pretension is entitled to your inquiry, because millions believe it. On the other hand you are astronomer enough to know how contrary it is to the law of nature that a body revolving on its axis as the earth does, should have stopped, should not by that sudden stoppage have prostrated animals, trees, buildings, and should after a certain time have resumed its revolution, &amp; that without a second general prostration. Is this arrest of the earth's motion, or the evidence which affirms it, most within the law of probabilities? You will next read the New Testament. It is the history of a personage called Jesus. Keep in your eye the opposite pretensions: 1, of those who say he was begotten by God, born of a virgin, suspended &amp; reversed the laws of nature at will, &amp; ascended bodily into heaven; and 2, of those who say he was a man of illegitimate birth, of a benevolent heart, enthusiastic mind, who set out without pretensions to divinity, ended in believing them, and was punished capitally for sedition, by being gibbeted, according to the Roman law, which punished the first commission of that offence by whipping, &amp; the second by exile, or death &lt;i&gt;in fureâ&lt;/i&gt;.

...Do not be frightened from this inquiry by any fear of its consequences. If it ends in a belief that there is no God, you will find incitements to virtue in the comfort and pleasantness you feel in its exercise, and the love of others which it will procure you... In fine, I repeat, you must lay aside all prejudice on both sides, and neither believe nor reject anything, because any other persons, or description of persons, have rejected or believed it... I forgot to observe, when speaking of the New Testament, that you should read all the histories of Christ, as well of those whom a council of ecclesiastics have decided for us, to be Pseudo-evangelists, as those they named Evangelists. Because these Pseudo-evangelists pretended to inspiration, as much as the others, and you are to judge their pretensions by your own reason, and not by the reason of those ecclesiastics. Most of these are lost...

[&lt;i&gt;Letter to his nephew, Peter Carr, advising him in matters of religion, 1787&lt;/i&gt;]" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23222-let-us-tenderly-and-kindly-cherish-therefore-the-means-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 13:01:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by John Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23222-let-us-tenderly-and-kindly-cherish-therefore-the-means-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let us tenderly and kindly cherish therefore, the means of knowledge. Let us dare to read, think, speak, and write ." -- John Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40821-a-constitution-of-government-once-changed-from-freedom-can-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 13:02:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by John Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40821-a-constitution-of-government-once-changed-from-freedom-can-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A Constitution of Government once changed from Freedom, can never be restored. Liberty, once lost, is lost forever." -- John Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 13:03:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be yourself in a world that is constantly trying to make you something else is the greatest accomplishment." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 13:03:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4339-is-it-so-bad-then-to-be-misunderstood-pythagoras-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 13:04:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4339-is-it-so-bad-then-to-be-misunderstood-pythagoras-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is it so bad, then, to be misunderstood? Pythagoras was misunderstood, and Socrates, and Jesus, and Luther, and Copernicus, and Galileo, and Newton, and every pure and wise spirit that ever took flesh. To be great is to be misunderstood." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4601-if-everyone-demanded-peace-instead-of-another-television-set-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 13:17:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4601-if-everyone-demanded-peace-instead-of-another-television-set-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If everyone demanded peace instead of another television set, then there'd be peace." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2381-when-the-power-of-love-overcomes-the-love-of-power</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 13:17:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Jimi Hendrix ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2381-when-the-power-of-love-overcomes-the-love-of-power]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the power of love overcomes the love of power, the world will know peace." -- Jimi Hendrix ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7379-if-someone-thinks-that-peace-and-love-are-just-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 13:17:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7379-if-someone-thinks-that-peace-and-love-are-just-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If someone thinks that peace and love are just a cliche that must have been left behind in the 60s, that's a problem.  Peace and love are eternal." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22892-it-s-only-after-we-ve-lost-everything-that-we-re-free-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 13:18:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22892-it-s-only-after-we-ve-lost-everything-that-we-re-free-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's only after we've lost everything that we're free to do anything." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2068-the-things-you-used-to-own-now-they-own-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 13:18:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2068-the-things-you-used-to-own-now-they-own-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The things you used to own, now they own you." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16041-the-only-difference-between-a-suicide-and-a-martyrdom-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 13:18:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16041-the-only-difference-between-a-suicide-and-a-martyrdom-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only difference between a suicide and a martyrdom really is the amount of press coverage." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16072-the-unreal-is-more-powerful-than-the-real-because-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 13:18:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16072-the-unreal-is-more-powerful-than-the-real-because-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The unreal is more powerful than the real. Because nothing is as perfect as you can imagine it. Because its only intangible ideas, concepts, beliefs, fantasies that last. Stone crumbles. Wood rots. People, well, they die. But things as fragile as a thought, a dream, a legend, they can go on and on. If you can change the way people think. The way they see themselves. The way they see the world. You can change the way people live their lives. That's the only lasting thing you can create." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
