<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/597552-prashanth-nuggehalli-srinivas]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/597552-prashanth-nuggehalli-srinivas" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 03:33:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374972-this-was-yet-another-colonial-fascination-to-create-the-conditions</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 03:33:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Prashanth add a quote by Siddhartha Mukherjee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374972-this-was-yet-another-colonial-fascination-to-create-the-conditions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This was yet another colonial fascination: to create the conditions of misery in a population, then subject it to social or medical experimentation." -- Siddhartha Mukherjee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/622342-that-was-why-later-on-he-began-to-lose-interest</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 06:17:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Prashanth add a quote by J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/622342-that-was-why-later-on-he-began-to-lose-interest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That was why, later on, he began to lose interest in photography: first when colour took over, then when it became plain that the old magic of light-sensitive emulsions was waning, that to the rising generation the enchantment lay in a &lt;i&gt;techne&lt;/i&gt; of images without substance, images that could flash through the ether without residing anywhere, that could be sucked into a machine and emerge from it doctored, untrue. He gave up recording the world in photographs then, and transferred his energies to saving the past." -- J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21490-owners-of-dogs-will-have-noticed-that-if-you-provide</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 13:20:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Prashanth add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21490-owners-of-dogs-will-have-noticed-that-if-you-provide]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Owners of dogs will have noticed that, if you provide them with food and water and shelter and affection, they will think you are god. Whereas owners of cats are compelled to realize that, if you provide them with food and water and shelter and affection, they draw the conclusion that &lt;i&gt;they&lt;/i&gt; are gods." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/509469-every-day-the-new-york-times-carries-a-motto-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2013 12:09:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Prashanth add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/509469-every-day-the-new-york-times-carries-a-motto-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every day, the New York Times carries a motto in a box on its front page. &quot;All the News That's Fit to Print,&quot; it says. It's been saying it for decades, day in and day out. I imagine most readers of the canonical sheet have long ceased to notice this bannered and flaunted symbol of its mental furniture. I myself check every day to make sure that the bright, smug, pompous, idiotic claim is still there. Then I check to make sure that it still irritates me. If I can still exclaim, under my breath, why do they insult me and what do they take me for and what the hell is it supposed to mean unless it's as obviously complacent and conceited and censorious as it seems to be, then at least I know I still have a pulse. You may wish to choose a more rigorous mental workout but I credit this daily infusion of annoyance with extending my lifespan." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487577-in-an-average-day-you-may-well-be-confronted-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2013 12:15:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Prashanth add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487577-in-an-average-day-you-may-well-be-confronted-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In an average day, you may well be confronted with some species of bullying or bigotry, or some ill-phrased appeal to the general will, or some petty abuse of authority. If you have a political loyalty, you may be offered a shady reason for agreeing to a lie or a half-truth that serves some short-term purpose. Everybody devises tactics for getting through such moments; try behaving &quot;as if&quot; they need not be tolerated and are not inevitable." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
