<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/598789-nathan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/598789-nathan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2008 09:30:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36593-you-think-of-yourself-as-an-individual-person-with-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2008 09:30:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Douglas Preston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36593-you-think-of-yourself-as-an-individual-person-with-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think of yourself as an &quot;individual person&quot;, with a unique and separate mind.  You think you are born and you think you die.  All your life you feel separate and alone.  Sometimes desperately so.  You fear death because you fear the loss of individuality.  All this is an illusion.  You, he, she, those things around you living or not, the stars and galaxies, the empty space in between- these are not distinct, separate objects.  All is fundamentally entangled." -- Douglas Preston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36594-a-human-being-creates-complexity-by-writing-a-novel-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2008 09:32:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Douglas Preston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36594-a-human-being-creates-complexity-by-writing-a-novel-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A human being creates complexity by writing a novel on the surface of paper; a weather system creates complexity by writing waves on the surface of an ocean.  What is the difference between the information carried in the words of a novel and the information carried on the waves of the sea?  Listen, and the waves will speak, and someday, I tell you, you will write your thoughts on the surface of the sea." -- Douglas Preston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36599-every-time-she-saw-a-videotape-of-the-planes-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2008 09:59:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36599-every-time-she-saw-a-videotape-of-the-planes-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every time she saw a videotape of the planes she moved a finger toward the power button on the remote.  Then she kept on watching.  The second plane coming out of that ice blue sky, this was the footage that entered the body, that seemed to run beneath her skin, the fleeting sprint that carried lives and histories, theirs and hers, everyone's, into some distance, out beyond the towers." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
