<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/600738-coralee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/600738-coralee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 19:29:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 19:29:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I can hear my bones straining under the weight of all the lives I'm not living." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43334-i-love-you-also-means-i-love-you-more-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 19:29:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43334-i-love-you-also-means-i-love-you-more-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you also means I love you more than anyone loves you, or has loved you, or will love you, and also, I love you in a way that no one loves you, or has loved you, or will love you, and also, I love you in a way that I love no one else, and never have loved anyone else, and never will love anyone else." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177358-we-must-be-free-not-because-we-claim-freedom-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 19:30:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177358-we-must-be-free-not-because-we-claim-freedom-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must be free not because we claim freedom, but because we practice it." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31063-never-be-afraid-to-raise-your-voice-for-honesty-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 19:31:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31063-never-be-afraid-to-raise-your-voice-for-honesty-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never be afraid to raise your voice for honesty and truth and compassion against injustice and lying and greed. If people all over the world...would do this, it would change the earth." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381-to-die-would-be-an-awfully-big-adventure</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381-to-die-would-be-an-awfully-big-adventure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To die would be an awfully big adventure." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 04:23:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22392-nothing-in-the-world-is-more-common-than-unsuccessful-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2013 07:00:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by Banksy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22392-nothing-in-the-world-is-more-common-than-unsuccessful-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing in the world is more common than unsuccessful people with talent, leave the house before you find something worth staying in for. " -- Banksy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163503-the-people-who-run-our-cities-dont-understand-graffiti-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2013 07:05:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by Banksy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163503-the-people-who-run-our-cities-dont-understand-graffiti-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the people who run our cities dont understand graffiti because they think nothing has the right to exist unless it makes a profit...
the people who truly deface our neighborhoods are the companies that scrawl giant slogans across buildings and buses trying to make us feel inadequate unless we buy their stuff....
any advertisement in public space that gives you no choice whether you see it or not is yours, it belongs to you ,, its yours to take, rearrange and re use.Asking for permission is like asking to keep a rock someone just threw at your head.." -- Banksy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51731-i-d-been-painting-rats-for-three-years-before-someone-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2013 07:05:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by Banksy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51731-i-d-been-painting-rats-for-three-years-before-someone-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd been painting rats for three years before someone said 'that's clever it's an
anagram of art' and I had to pretend I'd known that all along." -- Banksy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10839-music-has-always-been-a-matter-of-energy-to-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 04:52:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10839-music-has-always-been-a-matter-of-energy-to-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Music has always been a matter of Energy to me, a question of Fuel.  Sentimental people call it Inspiration, but what they really mean is Fuel.  I have always needed Fuel. I am a serious consumer.  On some nights I still believe that a car with the gas needle on empty can run about fifty more miles if you have the right music very loud on the radio." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28811-i-have-been-and-still-am-a-seeker-but-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 13:50:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28811-i-have-been-and-still-am-a-seeker-but-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have been and still am a seeker, but I have ceased to question stars and books; I have begun to listen to the teaching my blood whispers to me." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59085-i-was-once-reproved-by-a-minister-who-was-driving</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 13:51:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59085-i-was-once-reproved-by-a-minister-who-was-driving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was once reproved by a minister who was driving a poor beast to some meeting-house horse-sheds among the hills of New Hampshire, because I was bending my steps to a mountain-top on the Sabbath, instead of a church, when I would have gone farther than he to hear a true word spoken on that or any day. He declared that I was 'breaking the Lord's fourth commandment,' and proceeded to enumerate, in a sepulchral tone, the disasters which had befallen him whenever he had done any ordinary work on the Sabbath. He really thought that a god was on the watch to trip up those men who followed any secular work on this day, and did not see that it was the evil conscience of the workers that did it. &lt;b&gt;The country is full of this superstition, so that when one enters a village, the church, not only really but from association, is the ugliest looking building in it, because it is the one in which human nature stoops the lowest and is most disgraced. Certainly, such temples as these shall erelong cease to deform the landscape&lt;/b&gt;. There are few things more disheartening and disgusting than when you are walking the streets of a strange village on the Sabbath, to hear a preacher shouting like a boatswain in a gale of wind, and thus harshly profaning the quiet atmosphere of the day." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24729-there-are-it-seems-two-muses-the-muse-of-inspiration</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 13:53:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24729-there-are-it-seems-two-muses-the-muse-of-inspiration]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are, it seems, two muses: the Muse of Inspiration, who gives us inarticulate visions and desires, and the Muse of Realization, who returns again and again to say &quot;It is yet more difficult than you thought.&quot; This is the muse of form. It may be then that form serves us best when it works as an obstruction, to baffle us and deflect our intended course. It may be that when we no longer know what to do, we have come to our real work and when we no longer know which way to go, we have begun our real journey. The mind that is not baffled is not employed. The impeded stream is the one that sings." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58485-few-people-know-how-to-take-a-walk-the-qualifications</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 13:59:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58485-few-people-know-how-to-take-a-walk-the-qualifications]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Few people know how to take a walk. The qualifications are endurance, plain clothes, old shoes, an eye for nature, good humor, vast curiosity, good speech, good silence and nothing too much." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248896-so-comes-snow-after-fire-and-even-dragons-have-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 14:04:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248896-so-comes-snow-after-fire-and-even-dragons-have-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So comes snow after fire, and even dragons have their endings." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31920-i-am-the-most-tired-woman-in-the-world-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2013 18:53:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31920-i-am-the-most-tired-woman-in-the-world-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the most tired woman in the world. I am tired when I get up. Life requires an effort I cannot make. Please give me that heavy book. I need to put something heavy like that on top of my head. I have to place my feet under the pillows always, so as to be able to stay on earth. Otherwise I feel myself going away, going away at a tremendous speed, on account of my lightness. I know that I am dead. As soon as I utter a phrase my sincerity dies, becomes a lie whose coldness chills me. Don't say anything, because I see that you understand me, and I am afraid of your understanding. I have such a fear of finding another like myself, and such a desire to find one! I am so utterly lonely, but I also have such a fear that my isolation be broken through, and I no longer be the head and ruler of my universe. I am in great terror of your understanding by which you penetrate into my world; and then I stand revealed and I have to share my kingdom with you." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/881297-i-want-to-love-you-wildly-i-don-t-want-words</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2013 19:00:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Coralee add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/881297-i-want-to-love-you-wildly-i-don-t-want-words]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to love you wildly. I don’t want words, but inarticulate cries, meaningless, from the bottom of my most primitive being, that flow from my belly like honey. A piercing joy, that leaves me empty, conquered, silenced." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
