<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/60311-micaela]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/60311-micaela" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 08:59:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32900-when-we-both-experienced-the-love-that-consumes-we-shared</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 08:59:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Micaela add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32900-when-we-both-experienced-the-love-that-consumes-we-shared]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we both experienced the love that consumes, we shared in the Absolute. The Absolute shows each of us who we really are; it is an enormous web of cause and effect, where every small gesture made by one person affects the life of someone else. This morning, that slice of the Absolute was still very much alive in my soul. I was seeing not only you but everything there is in the world, unlimited by space or time." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37449-it-would-be-best-if-this-obscure-chapter-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 21:29:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Micaela add a quote by J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37449-it-would-be-best-if-this-obscure-chapter-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It would be best if this obscure chapter in the history of the world were terminated at once, if these ugly people were obliterated from the face of the earth and we swore to make a new start, to run an empire in which there would be no more injustice, no more pain." -- J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48591-aureliano-segundo-was-deep-in-the-reading-of-a-book</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 07:08:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Micaela add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48591-aureliano-segundo-was-deep-in-the-reading-of-a-book]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Aureliano Segundo was deep in the reading of a book. Although it had no cover and the title did not appear anywhere, the boy enjoyed the story of a woman who sat at a table and ate nothing but kernels of rice, which she picked up with a pin, and the story of the fisherman who borrowed a weight for his net from a neighbor and when he gave him a fish in payment later it had a diamond in its stomach, and the one about the lamp that fulfilled wishes and about flying carpets. Surprised, he asked Ursula if all that was true and she answered him that it was, that many years ago the gypsies had brought magic lamps and flying mats to Macondo.
&quot;What's happening,&quot; she sighed, &quot;is that the world is slowly coming to an end and those things don't come here any more." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
