<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/603539-itzmyguys]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/603539-itzmyguys" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 14:03:18 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113048-lunatics-are-similar-to-designated-hitters-often-an-entire-family</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 14:03:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Itzmyguys add a quote by Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113048-lunatics-are-similar-to-designated-hitters-often-an-entire-family]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lunatics are similar to designated hitters.  Often an entire family is crazy, but since an entire family can't go into the hospital, one person is designated as crazy and goes inside.  Then, depending on how the rest of the family is feeling that person is kept inside or snatched out, to prove something about the family's mental health." -- Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69032-reading-one-book-is-like-eating-one-potato-chip</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 10:50:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Itzmyguys add a quote by Diane Duane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69032-reading-one-book-is-like-eating-one-potato-chip]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reading one book is like eating one potato chip." -- Diane Duane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2013 05:25:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Itzmyguys add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/596387-love-can-make-even-nice-people-do-awful-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2013 05:27:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Itzmyguys add a quote by Jude Deveraux]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/596387-love-can-make-even-nice-people-do-awful-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love can make even nice people do awful things." -- Jude Deveraux]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204193-i-live-in-my-own-little-world-but-its-ok</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 08:32:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Itzmyguys add a quote by Lauren Myracle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204193-i-live-in-my-own-little-world-but-its-ok]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I live in my own little world. But its ok, they know me here." -- Lauren Myracle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/502419-i-was-trying-to-explain-my-situation-to-myself-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 20:30:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Itzmyguys add a quote by Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/502419-i-was-trying-to-explain-my-situation-to-myself-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was trying to explain my situation to myself. My situation was that I was in pain and nobody knew it, even I had trouble knowing it. So I told myself, over and over, You are in pain. It was the only way I could get through to myself. I was demonstrating externally and irrefutably an inward condition." -- Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491448-i-told-her-once-i-wasn-t-good-at-anything-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 20:32:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Itzmyguys add a quote by Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491448-i-told-her-once-i-wasn-t-good-at-anything-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I told her once I wasn’t good at anything. She told me survival is a talent." -- Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126463-why-did-she-do-it-nobody-dared-to-ask-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 20:33:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Itzmyguys add a quote by Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126463-why-did-she-do-it-nobody-dared-to-ask-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why did she do it? Nobody dared to ask. Because - what courage! Who had the courage to burn herself? Twenty aspirin, a little slit alongside the veins of the arm, maybe even a bad half hour standing on a roof: We've all had those. And somewhat more dangerous things, like putting a gun in your mouth. But you put it there, you taste it, it's cold and greasy, your finger is on the trigger, and you find that a whole world lies between this moment and the moment you've been planning, when you'll pull the trigger. That world defeats you. You put the gun back in the drawer. You'll have to find another way.

What was that moment like for her? The moment she lit the match. Had she already tried roofs and guns and aspirins? Or was it just an inspiration?

I had an inspiration once. I woke up one morning and I knew that today I had to swallow fifty aspirin. It was my task: my job for the day. I lined them up on my desk and took them one by one, counting. But it's not the same as what she did. I could have stopped, at ten, or at thirty. And I could have done what I did do, which was go onto the street and faint. Fifty aspirin is a lot of aspirin, but going onto the street and fainting is like putting the gun back in the drawer.

She lit the match." -- Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/530020-in-the-parallel-universe-the-laws-of-physics-are-suspended</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 18:36:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Itzmyguys add a quote by Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/530020-in-the-parallel-universe-the-laws-of-physics-are-suspended]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the parallel universe the laws of physics are suspended.
What goes up does not necessarily come down, a body at rest does not tend to stay at
rest and not every action can be counted on to provoke an equal and opposite reaction.
Time, 'too, is different.  It may run in circles, flow backward, skip about from now to
then.  The very arrangement of molecules is fluid: Tables can be clocks, faces,
flowers." -- Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172352-some-catastrophic-moments-invite-clarity-explode-in-split-moments-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 18:42:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Itzmyguys add a quote by Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172352-some-catastrophic-moments-invite-clarity-explode-in-split-moments-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some catastrophic moments invite clarity, explode in split moments: You smash your hand through a windowpane and then there is blood and shattered glass stained with red all over the place; you fall out a window and break some bones and scrape some skin. Stitches and casts and bandages and antiseptic solve and salve the wounds. But depression is not a sudden disaster. It is more like a cancer: At first its tumorous mass is not even noticeable to the careful eye, and then one day -- wham! -- there is a huge, deadly seven-pound lump lodged in your brain or your stomach or your shoulder blade, and this thing that your own body has produced is actually trying to kill you. Depression is a lot like that: Slowly, over the years, the data will accumulate in your heart and mind, a computer program for total negativity will build into your system, making life feel more and more unbearable. But you won't even notice it coming on, thinking that it is somehow normal, something about getting older, about turning eight or turning twelve or turning fifteen, and then one day you realize that your entire life is just awful, not worth living, a horror and a black blot on the white terrain of human existence. One morning you wake up afraid you are going to live.

In my case, I was not frightened in the least bit at the thought that I might live because I was certain, quite certain, that I was already dead. The actual dying part, the withering away of my physical body, was a mere formality. My spirit, my emotional being, whatever you want to call all that inner turmoil that has nothing to do with physical existence, were long gone, dead and gone, and only a mass of the most fucking god-awful excruciating pain like a pair of boiling hot tongs clamped tight around my spine and pressing on all my nerves was left in its wake.

That's the thing I want to make clear about depression: It's got nothing at all to do with life. In the course of life, there is sadness and pain and sorrow, all of which, in their right time and season, are normal -- unpleasant, but normal. Depression is an altogether different zone because it involves a complete absence: absence of affect, absence of feeling, absence of response, absence of interest. The pain you feel in the course of a major clinical depression is an attempt on nature's part (nature, after all, abhors a vacuum) to fill up the empty space. But for all intents and purposes, the deeply depressed are just the walking, waking dead.

And the scariest part is that if you ask anyone in the throes of depression how he got there, to pin down the turning point, he'll never know. There is a classic moment in The Sun Also Rises when someone asks Mike Campbell how he went bankrupt, and all he can say in response is, 'Gradually and then suddenly.' When someone asks how I love my mind, that is all I can say too" -- Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/486456-i-wanted-so-much-to-forget-the-past-but-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 22:41:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Itzmyguys add a quote by Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/486456-i-wanted-so-much-to-forget-the-past-but-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted so much to forget the past, but it wouldn't go away, it hung around like an open wound that refused to scar over, an open window that no amount of muscle could shut." -- Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
