<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/603749-kay]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/603749-kay" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 09:09:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33583-religion-is-a-culture-of-faith-science-is-a-culture</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 09:09:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Richard P. Feynman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33583-religion-is-a-culture-of-faith-science-is-a-culture]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Religion is a culture of faith; science is a culture of doubt." -- Richard P. Feynman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19080-once-upon-a-time-in-the-dead-of-winter-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 20:13:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by David McCullough]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19080-once-upon-a-time-in-the-dead-of-winter-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time in the dead of winter in the Dakota Territory, Theodore Roosevelt took off in a makeshift boat down the Little Missouri River in pursuit of a couple of thieves who had stolen his prized rowboat.  After several days on the river, he caught up and got the draw on them with his trusty Winchester, at which point they surrendered.  Then Roosevelt set off in a borrowed wagon to haul the thieves cross-country to justice.  They headed across the snow-covered wastes of the Badlands to the railhead at Dickinson, and Roosevelt walked the whole way, the entire 40 miles.  It was an astonishing feat, what might be called a defining moment in Roosevelt’s eventful life.  But what makes it especially memorable is that during that time, he managed to read all of &lt;i&gt;Anna Karenina&lt;/i&gt;.  I often think of that when I hear people say they haven’t time to read." -- David McCullough]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6564-stories-never-really-end-even-if-the-books-like-to-pretend</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 20:13:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Cornelia Funke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6564-stories-never-really-end-even-if-the-books-like-to-pretend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories never really end...even if the books like to pretend they do. Stories always go on. They don't end on the last page, any more than they begin on the first page." -- Cornelia Funke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76908-get-out-of-my-way-you-cakesniffers-said-a-rude</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 20:13:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76908-get-out-of-my-way-you-cakesniffers-said-a-rude]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Get out of my way, you cakesniffers!” said a rude, violent, and filthy little girl, shoving the Baudelaire orphans aside as she dashed by." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11907-i-hate-quotations-tell-me-what-you-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 16:01:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11907-i-hate-quotations-tell-me-what-you-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hate quotations. Tell me what you know." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143175-i-can-live-with-doubt-and-uncertainty-and-not-knowing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 18:02:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Richard P. Feynman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143175-i-can-live-with-doubt-and-uncertainty-and-not-knowing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can live with doubt and uncertainty and not knowing. I think it is much more interesting to live not knowing than to have answers that might be wrong. If we will only allow that, as we progress, we remain unsure, we will leave opportunities for alternatives. We will not become enthusiastic for the fact, the knowledge, the absolute truth of the day, but remain always uncertain … In order to make progress, one must leave the door to the unknown ajar." -- Richard P. Feynman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26494-and-in-my-classes-i-will-talk-most-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 18:02:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26494-and-in-my-classes-i-will-talk-most-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And in my classes, I will talk most of the time, and you will listen most of the time. Because you may be smart, but I've been smart longer." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266843-the-rabbit-of-easter-he-bring-of-the-chocolate</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 18:02:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266843-the-rabbit-of-easter-he-bring-of-the-chocolate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The rabbit of Easter. He bring of the chocolate." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77513-fall-in-love-with-some-activity-and-do-it-nobody</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 16:02:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Richard P. Feynman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77513-fall-in-love-with-some-activity-and-do-it-nobody]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fall in love with some activity, and do it! Nobody ever figures out what life is all about, and it doesn't matter. Explore the world. Nearly everything is really interesting if you go into it deeply enough. Work as hard and as much as you want to on the things you like to do the best. Don't think about what you want to be, but what you want to do. Keep up some kind of a minimum with other things so that society doesn't stop you from doing anything at all." -- Richard P. Feynman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51179-the-korean-man-nodded-the-way-you-do-when-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 16:05:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51179-the-korean-man-nodded-the-way-you-do-when-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Korean man nodded, the way you do when you’re a foreigner and understand that someone has finished a sentence." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215483-we-re-each-of-us-our-own-chiaroscuro-our-own-bit</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 16:09:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215483-we-re-each-of-us-our-own-chiaroscuro-our-own-bit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're each of us our own chiaroscuro, our own bit of illusion trying to emerge into something solid, something real. We've got to forgive ourselves that. I must remember to forgive myself. Because there's an awful lot of gray to work with. No one can live in the light all the time." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309485-nobody-tells-this-to-people-who-are-beginners-i-wish</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 21:46:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Ira Glass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309485-nobody-tells-this-to-people-who-are-beginners-i-wish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody tells this to people who are beginners, I wish someone told me. All of us who do creative work, we get into it because we have good taste. But there is this gap. For the first couple years you make stuff, it’s just not that good. It’s trying to be good, it has potential, but it’s not. But your taste, the thing that got you into the game, is still killer. And your taste is why your work disappoints you. A lot of people never get past this phase, they quit. Most people I know who do interesting, creative work went through years of this. We know our work doesn’t have this special thing that we want it to have. We all go through this. And if you are just starting out or you are still in this phase, you gotta know its normal and the most important thing you can do is do a lot of work. Put yourself on a deadline so that every week you will finish one story. It is only by going through a volume of work that you will close that gap, and your work will be as good as your ambitions. And I took longer to figure out how to do this than anyone I’ve ever met. It’s gonna take awhile. It’s normal to take awhile. You’ve just gotta fight your way through." -- Ira Glass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75967-but-if-it-matters-to-you-you-ll-be-able-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 09:08:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75967-but-if-it-matters-to-you-you-ll-be-able-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But if it matters to you, you'll be able to choose Gryffindor over Slytherin. The Sorting Hat takes your choice into account.&quot;
&quot;Really?&quot;
&quot;It did for me,&quot; said Harry.
He had never told any of his children that before, and he saw the wonder in Albus's face when he said it." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225104-and-we-spectators-always-everywhere-looking-at-never-out-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 09:09:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225104-and-we-spectators-always-everywhere-looking-at-never-out-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And we, spectators always, everywhere,
looking at, never out of, everything!
It fills us. We arrange it. It collapses.
We re-arrange it, and collapse ourselves.

Who's turned us round like this, so that we always,
do what we may, retain the attitude
of someone who's departing? Just as he,
on the last hill, that shows him all his valley
for the last time, will turn and stop and linger,
we live our lives, for ever taking leave." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/423977-though-all-three-men-faced-the-same-hardship-their-differing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 18:32:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Laura Hillenbrand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/423977-though-all-three-men-faced-the-same-hardship-their-differing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Though all three men faced the same hardship, their differing perceptions of it appeared to be shaping their fates.  Louie and Phil's hope displaced their fear and inspired them to work toward their survival, and each success renewed their physical and emotional vigor.  Mac's resignation seemed to paralyze him and the less he participated in their efforts to survive, the more he slipped. Though he did the least, as the days passed, it was he who faded the most.  Louie and Phil's optimism, and Mac's hopelessness, were becoming self-fulfilling." -- Laura Hillenbrand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/439757-i-loved-my-brother-but-relying-on-him-was-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 07:18:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Aimee Bender]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/439757-i-loved-my-brother-but-relying-on-him-was-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I loved my brother, but relying on him was like closing a hand around air." -- Aimee Bender]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230027-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2012 10:46:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230027-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look again at that dot. That's here. That's home. That's us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every &quot;superstar,&quot; every &quot;supreme leader,&quot; every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there-on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam.

The Earth is a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena.  Think of the endless cruelties visited by the inhabitants of one corner of this pixel on the scarcely distinguishable inhabitants of some other corner, how frequent their misunderstandings, how eager they are to kill one another, how fervent their hatreds.  Think of the rivers of blood spilled by all those generals and emperors so that, in glory and triumph, they could become the momentary masters of a fraction of a dot.

Our posturings, our imagined self-importance, the delusion that we have some privileged position in the Universe, are challenged by this point of pale light. Our planet is a lonely speck in the great enveloping cosmic dark. In our obscurity, in all this vastness, there is no hint that help will come from elsewhere to save us from ourselves.

The Earth is the only world known so far to harbor life. There is nowhere else, at least in the near future, to which our species could migrate. Visit, yes. Settle, not yet.  Like it or not, for the moment the Earth is where we make our stand.

It has been said that astronomy is a humbling and character-building experience. There is perhaps no better demonstration of the folly of human conceits than this distant image of our tiny world. To me, it underscores our responsibility to deal more kindly with one another, and to preserve and cherish the pale blue dot, the only home we've ever known." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371653-first-lord-no-tattoos-may-neither-chinese-symbol-for-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 05:45:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371653-first-lord-no-tattoos-may-neither-chinese-symbol-for-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First, Lord: No tattoos. May neither Chinese symbol for truth nor Winnie-the-Pooh holding the FSU logo stain her tender haunches.

May she be Beautiful but not Damaged, for it’s the Damage that draws the creepy soccer coach’s eye, not the Beauty.

When the Crystal Meth is offered, May she remember the parents who cut her grapes in half And stick with Beer.

Guide her, protect her

When crossing the street, stepping onto boats, swimming in the ocean, swimming in pools, walking near pools, standing on the subway platform, crossing 86th Street, stepping off of boats, using mall restrooms, getting on and off escalators, driving on country roads while arguing, leaning on large windows, walking in parking lots, riding Ferris wheels, roller-coasters, log flumes, or anything called “Hell Drop,” “Tower of Torture,” or “The Death Spiral Rock ‘N Zero G Roll featuring Aerosmith,” and standing on any kind of balcony ever, anywhere, at any age.

Lead her away from Acting but not all the way to Finance. Something where she can make her own hours but still feel intellectually fulfilled and get outside sometimes And not have to wear high heels.

What would that be, Lord? Architecture? Midwifery? Golf course design? I’m asking You, because if I knew, I’d be doing it, Youdammit.

May she play the Drums to the fiery rhythm of her Own Heart with the sinewy strength of her Own Arms, so she need Not Lie With Drummers.

Grant her a Rough Patch from twelve to seventeen. Let her draw horses and be interested in Barbies for much too long, For childhood is short – a Tiger Flower blooming Magenta for one day – And adulthood is long and dry-humping in cars will wait.

O Lord, break the Internet forever, That she may be spared the misspelled invective of her peers And the online marketing campaign for Rape Hostel V: Girls Just Wanna Get Stabbed.

And when she one day turns on me and calls me a Bitch in front of Hollister, Give me the strength, Lord, to yank her directly into a cab in front of her friends, For I will not have that Shit. I will not have it.

And should she choose to be a Mother one day, be my eyes, Lord, that I may see her, lying on a blanket on the floor at 4:50 A.M., all-at-once exhausted, bored, and in love with the little creature whose poop is leaking up its back.

“My mother did this for me once,” she will realize as she cleans feces off her baby’s neck. “My mother did this for me.” And the delayed gratitude will wash over her as it does each generation and she will make a Mental Note to call me. And she will forget. But I’ll know, because I peeped it with Your God eyes." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/557819-having-lost-his-mother-father-brother-an-grandfather-the-friends</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 12:54:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/557819-having-lost-his-mother-father-brother-an-grandfather-the-friends]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Having lost his mother, father, brother, an grandfather, the friends and foes of his youth, his beloved teacher Bernard Kornblum, his city, his history—his home—the usual charge leveled against comic books, that they offered merely an escape from reality, seemed to Joe actually to be a powerful argument on their behalf…

The escape from reality was, he felt—especially right after the war—a worthy challenge… The pain of his loss—though he would never have spoken of it in those terms—was always with him in those days, a cold smooth ball lodged in his chest, just behind his sternum. For that half hour spent in the dappled shade of the Douglas firs, reading Betty and Veronica, the icy ball had melted away without him even noticing. That was the magic—not the apparent magic of a silk-hatted card-palmer, or the bold, brute trickery of the escape artist, but the genuine magic of art. It was a mark of how fucked-up and broken was the world—the reality—that had swallowed his home and his family that such a feat of escape, by no means easy to pull off, should remain so universally despised." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127811-i-m-not-saying-that-everything-is-survivable-just-that-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 20:26:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127811-i-m-not-saying-that-everything-is-survivable-just-that-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not saying that everything is survivable. Just that everything except the last thing is." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166714-the-way-i-figure-it-everyone-gets-a-miracle-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 20:27:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166714-the-way-i-figure-it-everyone-gets-a-miracle-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The way I figure it, everyone gets a miracle. Like, I will probably never be struck by lightening, or win a Nobel Prize, or become the dictator of a small nation in the Pacific Islands, or contract terminal ear cancer, or spontaneously combust.  But if you consider all the unlikely things together, at least one of them will probably happen to each of us.  I could have seen it rain frogs.  I could have stepped foot on Mars.  I could have been eaten by a whale.  I could have married the Queen of England or survived months at sea.  But my miracle was different.  My miracle was this: out of all the houses in all the subdivisions in all of Florida, I ended up living next door to Margo Roth Spiegelman." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/822701-technically-it-s-a-family-restaurant-but-it-will-only-remind</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 09:32:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Sarah Vowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/822701-technically-it-s-a-family-restaurant-but-it-will-only-remind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Technically, it's a family restaurant, but it will only remind you of your family if your mom chain-smoked menthols." -- Sarah Vowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1051481-flakes-of-snow-swirled-and-danced-across-the-porch-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 21:03:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1051481-flakes-of-snow-swirled-and-danced-across-the-porch-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Flakes of snow swirled and danced across the porch. The Overlook faced it as it had for nearly three-quarters of a century, its darkened windows now bearded with snow, indifferent to the fact it was now cut off from the world… Inside its shell the three of them went about their early evening routine, like microbes trapped in the intestine of a monster." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/831432-a-flash-of-resentment-it-s-hard-enough-being-alive-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 10:23:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kay add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/831432-a-flash-of-resentment-it-s-hard-enough-being-alive-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A flash of resentment.  It's hard enough being alive, trying to survive in the world and find your place in it, to do the things you need to do to get by, without wondering if the thing you just did, whatever it was, was worth someone having...if not died, then having given up her life.  It wasn't fair. &quot;Life's not fair,&quot; said Ginnie, as if I had spoken aloud." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
