<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/60371-julia]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/60371-julia" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 15:24:56 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9226-i-sink-down-into-my-body-as-into-a-swamp</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 15:24:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9226-i-sink-down-into-my-body-as-into-a-swamp]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I sink down into my body as into a swamp, fenland, where only I know the footing….
I’m a cloud, congealed around a central object, the shape of a pear, which is hard and more real than I am and glows red within its translucent wrapping. Inside it is a space, huge as the sky at night and dark and curved like that, though black-red rather than black." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 19:09:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417319-we-all-make-vows-jimmy-and-there-is-something-very</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 09:46:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Mary Doria Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417319-we-all-make-vows-jimmy-and-there-is-something-very]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...&quot;we all make vows, Jimmy.  And there is something very beautiful and touching and noble about wanting good impulses to be permanent and true forever,&quot; she said.  &quot;Most of us stand up and vow to love, honor and cherish someone.  And we truly mean it, at the time.  But two or twelve or twenty years down the road, the lawyers are negotiating the property settlement.&quot;
    &quot;You and George didn't go back on your promises.&quot;
    She laughed.  &quot;Lemme tell ya something, sweetface.  I have been married at least four times, to four different men.&quot;  She watched him chew that over for a moment before continuing, &quot;They've all been named George Edwards but, believe me, the man who is waiting for me down the hall is a whole lot different animal from the boy I married, back before there was dirt.  Oh, there are continuities.  He has always been fun and he has never been able to budget his time properly and - well, the rest is none of your business.&quot;
    &quot;But people change,&quot; he said quietly.
    &quot;Precisely.  People change.  Cultures change.  Empires rise and fall.  Shit.  Geology changes!  Every ten years or so, George and I have faced the fact that we have changed and we've had to decide if it makes sense to create a new marriage between these two new people.&quot;  She flopped back against her chair.  &quot;Which is why vows are such a tricky business.  Because nothing stays the same forever.  Okay.  Okay!  I'm figuring something out now.&quot;  She sat up straight, eyes focused somewhere outside the room, and Jimmy realized that even Anne didn't have all the answers and that was either the most comforting thing he'd learned in a long time or the most discouraging.  &quot;Maybe because so few of us would be able to give up something so fundamental for something so abstract, we protect ourselves from the nobility of a priest's vows by jeering at him when he can't live up to them, always and forever.&quot;  She shivered and slumped suddenly, &quot;But, Jimmy!  What unnatural words.  Always and forever!  Those aren't human words, Jim.  Not even stones are always and forever." -- Mary Doria Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261599-boys-are-idiots-girls-are-idiots-too-of-course-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 16:28:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Josh Lieb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261599-boys-are-idiots-girls-are-idiots-too-of-course-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Boys are idiots.

Girls are idiots, too, of course, but boys are a special kind of idiot.

A girl, for instance, will vote for a boy in an election, or go to a movie that's about a boy, or buy a book that features a boy hero (or villain).  Boys are much less likely to return the favor.  They can't wrap their feeble minds around the idea that this &lt;i&gt;girl&lt;/i&gt; might have anything in common with them.  It's like they can't recognize girls as human beings." -- Josh Lieb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/457385-everyone-has-something-of-beauty-about-them-but-loving-let-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2011 20:16:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by Ally Condie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/457385-everyone-has-something-of-beauty-about-them-but-loving-let-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone has something of beauty about them. But loving let's you look, and look, and look again. You notice the back of a hand, the turn of a head, the way of a walk. When you first love, you look blind and you see it all as the glorious, beloved whole, or a beautiful sum of beautiful parts. But when you see the one you love as pieces, as why's, you can love those parts too, and it's a love at once more complicated and more complete." -- Ally Condie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9227-time-for-you-and-time-for-me-and-time-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2011 20:17:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julia add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9227-time-for-you-and-time-for-me-and-time-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time for you and time for me,	
And time yet for a hundred indecisions,	
And for a hundred visions and revisions,	
Before the taking of a toast and tea." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
