<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/605984-mene-tekel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/605984-mene-tekel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 15:25:53 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/993770-simplicity-is-a-kind-of-transparency-in-which-subtle-nuances</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 15:25:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mene add a quote by David Byrne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/993770-simplicity-is-a-kind-of-transparency-in-which-subtle-nuances]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Simplicity is a kind of transparency in which subtle nuances can have outsize effects. When everything is visible and appears to be dumb, that’s when the details take on larger meanings." -- David Byrne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/775551-something-about-music-urges-us-to-engage-with-its-larger</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 15:25:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mene add a quote by David Byrne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/775551-something-about-music-urges-us-to-engage-with-its-larger]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Something about music urges us to engage with its larger context, beyond the piece of plastic it came on-it seems to be part of our genetic makeup that we can be so deeply moved by this art form.  Music resonates in so many parts of the brain that we can't conceive of it being an isolated thing." -- David Byrne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/967539-the-act-of-making-music-clothes-art-or-even-food</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 15:25:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mene add a quote by David Byrne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/967539-the-act-of-making-music-clothes-art-or-even-food]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The act of making music, clothes, art, or even food has a very different, and possibly more beneficial effect on us than simply consuming those things. And yet for a very long time, the attitude of the state toward teaching and funding the arts has been in direct opposition to fostering creativity among the general population. It can often seem that those in power don’t want us to enjoy making things for ourselves—they’d prefer to establish a cultural hierarchy that devalues our amateur efforts and encourages consumption rather than creation. This might sound like I believe there is some vast conspiracy at work, which I don’t, but the situation we find ourselves in is effectively the same as if there were one. The way we are taught about music, and the way it’s socially and economically positioned, affect whether it’s integrated (or not) into our lives, and even what kind of music might come into existence in the future. Capitalism tends toward the creation of passive consumers, and in many ways this tendency is counterproductive." -- David Byrne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1152166-but-at-times-words-can-be-a-dangerous-addition-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 15:25:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mene add a quote by David Byrne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1152166-but-at-times-words-can-be-a-dangerous-addition-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But at times words can be a dangerous addition to music — they can pin it down. Words imply that the music is about what the words say, literally, and nothing more. If done poorly, they can destroy the pleasant ambiguity that constitutes much of the reason we love music. That ambiguity allows listeners to psychologically tailor a song to suit their needs, sensibilities, and situations, but words can limit that, too. There are plenty of beautiful tracks that I can’t listen to because they’ve been “ruined” by bad words — my own and others. In Beyonce's song &quot;Irreplaceable,&quot; she rhymes &quot;minute&quot; with &quot;minute,&quot; and I cringe every time I hear it (partly because by that point I'm singing along). On my own song &quot;Astronaut,&quot; I wrap up with the line &quot;feel like I'm an astronaut,&quot; which seems like the dumbest metaphor for alienation ever. Ugh." -- David Byrne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/887201-my-favorite-term-for-a-new-kind-of-performance-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 15:26:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mene add a quote by David Byrne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/887201-my-favorite-term-for-a-new-kind-of-performance-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My favorite term for a new kind of performance is &quot;security theater.&quot;  In this genre, we watch as ritualized inspections and patdowns create the illusion of security.  It's a form that has become common since 9/11, and even the government agencies that participate in this activity acknowledge,off the record, that it is indeed a species of theater." -- David Byrne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/659936-as-music-becomes-less-of-a-thing--a-cylinder-a-cassette</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 15:26:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mene add a quote by David Byrne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/659936-as-music-becomes-less-of-a-thing--a-cylinder-a-cassette]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As music becomes less of a thing--a cylinder, a cassette, a disc--and more ephemeral, perhaps we will begin to assign an increasing value to live performances again." -- David Byrne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/746831-music-isn-t-fragile</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 15:26:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mene add a quote by David Byrne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/746831-music-isn-t-fragile]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Music isn't fragile." -- David Byrne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/721090-it-can-often-seem-that-those-in-power-don-t-want</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 15:26:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mene add a quote by David Byrne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/721090-it-can-often-seem-that-those-in-power-don-t-want]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It can often seem that those in power don't want us to enjoy making things for ourselves - they'd prefer to establish a cultural hierarchy that devalues our amateur efforts and encourages consumption rather than creation." -- David Byrne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/663874-i-like-a-good-story-and-i-also-like-staring</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 15:26:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mene add a quote by David Byrne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/663874-i-like-a-good-story-and-i-also-like-staring]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like a good story and I also like staring at the sea-- do I have to choose between the two?" -- David Byrne]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
