<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/607804-sophie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/607804-sophie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 21:57:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 21:57:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be patient toward all that is unsolved in your heart and try to love the questions themselves, like locked rooms and like books that are now written in a very foreign tongue. Do not now seek the answers, which cannot be given you because you would not be able to live them. And the point is, to live everything. Live the questions now. Perhaps you will then gradually, without noticing it, live along some distant day into the answer." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141479-why-do-you-want-to-shut-out-of-your-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 22:17:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141479-why-do-you-want-to-shut-out-of-your-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why do you want to shut out of your life any uneasiness, any misery, any depression, since after all you don't know what work these conditions are doing inside you? Why do you want to persecute yourself with the question of where all this is coming from and where it is going? Since you know, after all, that you are in the midst of transitions and you wished for nothing so much as to change. If there is anything unhealthy in your reactions, just bear in mind that sickness is the means by which an organism frees itself from what is alien; so one must simply help it to be sick, to have its whole sickness and to break out with it, since that is the way it gets better." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 22:46:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.

So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173437-this-being-human-is-a-guest-house-every-morning-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 10:40:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173437-this-being-human-is-a-guest-house-every-morning-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This being human is a guest house. Every morning is a new arrival. A joy, a depression, a meanness, some momentary awareness comes as an unexpected visitor...Welcome and entertain them all. Treat each guest honorably. The dark thought, the shame, the malice, meet them at the door laughing, and invite them in. Be grateful for whoever comes, because each has been sent as a guide from beyond." -- Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113974-radar-threw-his-books-into-his-locker-and-shut-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 18:04:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113974-radar-threw-his-books-into-his-locker-and-shut-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Radar threw his books into his locker and shut it. Then the din of conversation around us quieted just a bit as he turned his eyes toward the heavens and shouted, &quot;IT IS NOT MY FAULT THAT MY PARENTS OWN THE WORLD'S LARGEST COLLECTION OF BLACK SANTAS." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72745-the-reason-that-the-rich-were-so-rich-vimes-reasoned</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 14:54:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72745-the-reason-that-the-rich-were-so-rich-vimes-reasoned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The reason that the rich were so rich, Vimes reasoned, was because they managed to spend less money.

Take boots, for example. He earned thirty-eight dollars a month plus allowances. A really good pair of leather boots cost fifty dollars. But an affordable pair of boots, which were sort of OK for a season or two and then leaked like hell when the cardboard gave out, cost about ten dollars. Those were the kind of boots Vimes always bought, and wore until the soles were so thin that he could tell where he was in Ankh-Morpork on a foggy night by the feel of the cobbles.

But the thing was that good boots lasted for years and years. A man who could afford fifty dollars had a pair of boots that'd still be keeping his feet dry in ten years' time, while the poor man who could only afford cheap boots would have spent a hundred dollars on boots in the same time and would still have wet feet.

This was the Captain Samuel Vimes 'Boots' theory of socioeconomic unfairness." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159730-you-read-a-book-for-the-story-for-each-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 00:55:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159730-you-read-a-book-for-the-story-for-each-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You read a book for the story, for each of its words,&quot; Gordy said, &quot;and you draw your cartoons for the story, for each of the words and images. And, yeah, you need to take that seriously, but you should also read and draw because really good books and cartoons give you a boner.&quot;

I was shocked:

&quot;Did you just say books should give me a boner?&quot;

&quot;Yes, I did.&quot;

&quot;Are you serious?&quot;

&quot;Yeah... don't you get excited about books?&quot;

&quot;I don't think that you're supposed to get THAT excited about books.&quot;

&quot;You should get a boner! You have to get a boner!&quot; Gordy shouted. &quot;Come on!&quot;

We ran into the Reardan High School Library.

&quot;Look at all these books,&quot; he said.

&quot;There aren't that many,&quot; I said. It was a small library in a small high school in a small town.

&quot;There are three thousand four hundred and twelve books here,&quot; Gordy said. &quot;I know that because I counted them.&quot;

&quot;Okay, now you're officially a freak,&quot; I said.

&quot;Yes, it's a small library. It's a tiny one. But if you read one of these books a day, it would still take you almost ten years to finish.&quot;

&quot;What's your point?&quot;

&quot;The world, even the smallest parts of it, is filled with things you don't know.&quot;

Wow. That was a huge idea.

Any town, even one as small as Reardan, was a place of mystery. And that meant Wellpinit, the smaller, Indian town, was also a place of mystery.

&quot;Okay, so it's like each of these books is a mystery. Every book is a mystery. And if you read all of the books ever written, it's like you've read one giant mystery. And no matter how much you learn, you keep on learning so much more you need to learn.&quot;

&quot;Yes, yes, yes, yes,&quot; Gordy said. &quot;Now doesn't that give you a boner?&quot;

&quot;I am rock hard,&quot; I said." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137546-peter-she-asked-trying-to-speak-firmly-what-are-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 00:55:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137546-peter-she-asked-trying-to-speak-firmly-what-are-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Peter,' she asked, trying to speak firmly, 'what are your exact feelings for me?'
Those of a devoted son, Wendy.'
I thought so,' she said, and went and sat by herself at the extreme end of the room.
You are so queer,' he said, frankly puzzled, 'and Tiger Lily is just the same. There is something she wants to be to me, but she says it is not my mother.'
No, indeed, it is not,' Wendy replied with frightful emphasis." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137506-gordie-the-white-boy-genius-gave-me-this-book-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 00:55:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137506-gordie-the-white-boy-genius-gave-me-this-book-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Gordie, the white boy genius, gave me this book by a Russian dude named Tolstoy, who wrote, 'Happy families are all alike; every unhappy family is unhappy in its own way.' Well, I hate to argue with a Russian genius, but Tolstoy didn't know Indians, and he didn't know that all Indian families are unhappy for the same exact reasons: the frikkin' booze." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137549-my-father-took-one-hundred-and-thirty-two-minutes-to-die</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 20:23:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137549-my-father-took-one-hundred-and-thirty-two-minutes-to-die]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My father took one hundred and thirty-two minutes to die.

I counted.

It happened on the Jellicoe Road. The prettiest road I’d ever seen, where trees made breezy canopies like a tunnel to Shangri-La. We were going to the ocean, hundreds of miles away, because I wanted to see the ocean and my father said that it was about time the four of us made that journey. I remember asking, 'What’s the difference between a trip and a journey?' and my father said, 'Narnie, my love, when we get there, you’ll understand,' and that was the last thing he ever said." -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94993-it-takes-long-practice-yes-you-have-to-work-did</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 20:34:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94993-it-takes-long-practice-yes-you-have-to-work-did]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It takes long practice, yes. You have to work. Did you think you could snap your fingers, and have it as a gift? What is worth having is worth working for." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136007-it-is-my-first-morning-of-high-school-i-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 20:40:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136007-it-is-my-first-morning-of-high-school-i-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is my first morning of high school. I have seven new notebooks, a skirt I hate, and a stomachache." -- Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140840-there-are-members-of-our-body-politic-who-tell-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 14:50:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Alexander Meiklejohn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140840-there-are-members-of-our-body-politic-who-tell-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are members of our body politic who tell us that the public interest is best served when government action is reduced to a minimum and especially when it is kept negative in character. But just now, the nation as a whole seems to be moving rather swiftly and decisively—as is the world as a whole—in the opposite direction. More and more, we Americans are initiating new forms of positive government action for the common good. Between these two tendencies the struggle becomes every day more open and more intense. And as we wage that conflict it is well to remember that the logic of the Constitution gives no backing to either of the two combatants, as against the other. We are left free, as any self-governing people must leave itself free, to determine by specific decisions what our economy shall be. It would be ludicrous to say that we are committed by the Constitution to the economic cooperations of socialism. But equally ludicrous are those appeals by which, in current debate, we are called upon to defend the practices of capitalism, of &quot;free enterprise,&quot; so-called, as essential to the freedom of the American Way of Life. The American Way of Life is free because it is what we Americans freely choose—from time to time—that it shall be." -- Alexander Meiklejohn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7394-he-couldn-t-see-why-people-made-such-a-fuss-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 14:57:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7394-he-couldn-t-see-why-people-made-such-a-fuss-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He couldn’t see why people made such a fuss about people eating their silly old fruit anyway, but life would be a lot less fun if they didn’t.  And there was never an apple, in Adam’s opinion, that wasn’t worth the trouble you got into for eating it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413047-everybody-has-a-secret-world-inside-of-them-i-mean</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 14:29:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413047-everybody-has-a-secret-world-inside-of-them-i-mean]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody has a secret world inside of them. I mean everybody. All of the people in the whole world, I mean everybody — no matter how dull and boring they are on the outside. Inside them they've all got unimaginable, magnificent, wonderful, stupid, amazing worlds... Not just one world. Hundreds of them. Thousands, maybe." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133159-the-colonel-led-all-the-cheers-cornbread-he-screamed-chicken</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 09:58:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133159-the-colonel-led-all-the-cheers-cornbread-he-screamed-chicken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Colonel led all the cheers.
Cornbread!&quot; he screamed.
CHICKEN!&quot; the crowd responded.
Rice!&quot;
PEAS!&quot;
And then, all together: &quot;WE GOT HIGHER SATs.&quot;
Hip Hip Hip Hooray!&quot; the Colonel cried.
YOU'LL BE WORKIN' FOR US SOMEDAY!" -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105972-what-a-treacherous-thing-to-believe-that-a-person-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 10:02:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105972-what-a-treacherous-thing-to-believe-that-a-person-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a treacherous thing to believe that a person is more than a person." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127811-i-m-not-saying-that-everything-is-survivable-just-that-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 16:20:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127811-i-m-not-saying-that-everything-is-survivable-just-that-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not saying that everything is survivable. Just that everything except the last thing is." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123639-do-you-understand-how-amazing-it-is-to-hear-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 16:41:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123639-do-you-understand-how-amazing-it-is-to-hear-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you understand how amazing it is to hear that from an adult?  Do you know how amazing it is to hear that from anybody?  It's one of the simplest sentences in the world, just four words, but they're the four hugest words in the world when they're put together.

You can do it." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66881-the-only-thing-known-to-go-faster-than-ordinary-light</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 17:09:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66881-the-only-thing-known-to-go-faster-than-ordinary-light]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only thing known to go faster than ordinary light is monarchy, according to the philosopher Ly Tin Wheedle. He reasoned like this: you can't have more than one king, and tradition demands that there is no gap between kings, so when a king dies the succession must therefore pass to the heir &lt;i&gt;instantaneously&lt;/i&gt;. Presumably, he said, there must be some elementary particles -- kingons, or possibly queons -- that do this job, but of course succession sometimes fails if, in mid-flight, they strike an anti-particle, or republicon. His ambitious plans to use his discovery to send messages, involving the careful torturing of a small king in order to modulate the signal, were never fully expanded because, at that point, the bar closed." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99696-i-comma-square-bracket-recruit-s-name-square-bracket-comma-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 17:15:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99696-i-comma-square-bracket-recruit-s-name-square-bracket-comma-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I comma square bracket recruit's name square bracket comma do solemnly swear by square bracket recruit's deity of choice square bracket to uphold the Laws and Ordinances of the City of Ankh-Morpork comma serve the public truƒt comma and defend the ƒubjects of his ƒtroke her bracket delete whichever is inappropriate bracket Majeƒty bracket name of reigning monarch bracket without fear comma favour comma or thought of perƒonal ƒafety semi-colon to purƒue evildoers and protect the innocent comma comma laying down my life if neceƒsary in the cauƒe of said duty comma so help me bracket aforeƒaid deity bracket full stop Gods Save the King stroke Queen bracket delete whichever is inappropriate bracket full stop." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152650-the-monks-of-cool-whose-tiny-and-exclusive-monastery-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 17:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152650-the-monks-of-cool-whose-tiny-and-exclusive-monastery-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Monks of Cool, whose tiny and exclusive monastery is hidden in a really cool and laid-back valley in the lower Ramtops, have a passing-out test for a novice. He is taken into a room full of all types of clothing and asked: Yo, my son, which of these is the most stylish thing to wear? And the correct answer is: Hey, whatever I select." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166423-i-hated-that-the-soldier-doll-had-my-name-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2009 12:06:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by James Howe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166423-i-hated-that-the-soldier-doll-had-my-name-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hated that the soldier doll had my name. I mean, please. I didn't play with him much. He was another Christmas present from my clueless grandparents. One time when they were visiting, my grandpa asked me if G.I. Joe had been in any wars lately. I said, &quot;No, but he and Ken got married last week.&quot; Every Christmas since then, my grandparents have sent me a check." -- James Howe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129153-a-little-kid-asks-my-dad-why-that-man-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2009 12:09:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129153-a-little-kid-asks-my-dad-why-that-man-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A little kid asks my dad why that man is chopping down the tree.

Dad: He's not chopping it down. He's saving it. Those branches were long dead from disease. All plants are like that. By cutting off the damage you make it possible for the tree to grow again. You watch - by the end of summer, this tree will be the strongest on the block." -- Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106112-and-all-at-once-i-knew-how-margo-roth-spiegelman</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2009 20:12:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106112-and-all-at-once-i-knew-how-margo-roth-spiegelman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And all at once I knew how Margo Roth Spiegelman felt when she wasn't being Margo Roth Spiegelman: she felt empty. She felt the unscaleable wall surrounding her. I thought of her asleep on the carpet with only that jagged sliver of sky above her. Maybe Margo felt comfortable there because Margo the person lived like that all the time: in an abandoned room with blocked-out windows, the only light pouring in through holes in the roof. Yes. The fundamental mistake I had always made—and that she had, in fairness, always led me to make—was this: Margo was not a miracle. She was not an adventure. She was not a fine and precious thing. She was a girl." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24015-you-do-not-have-to-be-good-you-do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 23:05:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24015-you-do-not-have-to-be-good-you-do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You do not have to be good.
You do not have to walk on your knees
for a hundred miles through the desert, repenting.
You only have to let the soft animal of your body 
love what it loves.
Tell me about despair, yours, and I will tell you mine.
Meanwhile the world goes on.
Meanwhile the sun and the clear pebbles of the rain
are moving across the landscapes,
over the prairies and the deep trees,
the mountains and the rivers.
Meanwhile the wild geese, high in the clean blue air,
are heading home again.
Whoever you are, no matter how lonely,
the world offers itself to your imagination,
calls to you like the wild geese, harsh and exciting –
over and over announcing your place
in the family of things." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2633-it-is-said-that-your-life-flashes-before-your-eyes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2010 01:16:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2633-it-is-said-that-your-life-flashes-before-your-eyes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is said that your life flashes before your eyes just before you die. That is true, it's called Life." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155019-i-flip-ahead-in-the-textbook-there-s-an-interesting-chapter</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2010 01:25:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155019-i-flip-ahead-in-the-textbook-there-s-an-interesting-chapter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I flip ahead in the textbook. There's an interesting chapter about acid rain. Nothing about sex. We aren't scheduled to learn about that until eleventh grade." -- Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256664-we-can-never-be-gods-after-all--but-we-can-become</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 07:21:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by N.K. Jemisin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256664-we-can-never-be-gods-after-all--but-we-can-become]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can never be gods, after all--but we can become something less than human with frightening ease." -- N.K. Jemisin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14636-albert-grunted-do-you-know-what-happens-to-lads-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 11:38:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sophie add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14636-albert-grunted-do-you-know-what-happens-to-lads-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Albert grunted. &quot;Do you know what happens to lads who ask too many questions?&quot;
Mort thought for a moment.
&quot;No,&quot; he said eventually, &quot;what?&quot;
There was silence.
Then Albert straightened up and said, &quot;Damned if I know. Probably they get answers, and serve 'em right." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
