<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/608614-l]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/608614-l" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 21:38:31 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123384-the-art-of-living-is-more-like-wrestling-than-dancing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 21:38:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[L add a quote by Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123384-the-art-of-living-is-more-like-wrestling-than-dancing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The art of living is more like wrestling than dancing, in so far as it stands ready against the accidental and the unforeseen, and is not apt to fall." -- Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123386-i-hate-a-song-that-makes-you-think-that-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 22:04:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[L add a quote by Woody Guthrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123386-i-hate-a-song-that-makes-you-think-that-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hate a song that makes you think that you are not any good. I hate a song that makes you think that you are just born to lose. Bound to lose. No good to nobody. No good for nothing. Because you are too old or too young or too fat or too slim or too ugly or too this or too that. Songs that run you down or poke fun at you on account of your bad luck or hard travelling. I am out to fight those songs to my very last breath of air and my last drop of blood. I am out to sing songs that will prove to you that this is your world and that if it has hit you pretty hard and knocked you for a dozen loops, no matter what color, what size you are, how you are built, I am out to sing the songs that make you take pride in yourself and in your work. And the songs that I sing are made up for the most part by all sorts of folks just about like you. I could hire out to the other side, the big money side, and get several dollars every week just to quit singing my own kind of songs and to sing the kind that knock you down still farther and the ones that poke fun at you even more and the ones that make you think that you've not got any sense at all. But I decided a long time ago that I'd starve to death before I'd sing any such songs as that. The radio waves and your movies and your jukeboxes and your songbooks are already loaded down and running over with such no good songs as that anyhow." -- Woody Guthrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24712-how-is-it-that-one-day-life-is-orderly-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 12:52:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[L add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24712-how-is-it-that-one-day-life-is-orderly-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How is it that one day life is orderly and you are content, a little cynical perhaps but on the whole just so, and then without warning you find the solid floor is a trapdor and you are now in another place whose geography is uncertain and whose customs are strange?
Travellers at least have a chose.  Those who set sail know know that things will not be the same as at home.  Explorers are perpared.  But for us, who travel to cities of the interior by chance, there is no preparaton.  We who are fluent find liffe is a foreign language.  Somewhere beween the swamp and the mountains.  Somewhere beween fear and sex.  Somewere beween God and the Devil passion is and the way there is sudden and the way back worse." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161371-for-i-was-as-you-have-already-guessed-a-collaborator</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 12:59:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[L add a quote by Robertson Davies]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161371-for-i-was-as-you-have-already-guessed-a-collaborator]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For I was, as you have already guessed, a collaborator with Destiny, not one who put a pistol to its head and demanded particular treasures.  The only thing for me to do was to keep on keeping on, to have faith in my whim, and remember that for me, as for the saints, illumination when it came would probably come from some unexpected source." -- Robertson Davies]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185571-never-did-get-my-curiosity-cured-she-said-some-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2009 10:09:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[L add a quote by William Least Heat-Moon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185571-never-did-get-my-curiosity-cured-she-said-some-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never did get my curiosity cured,' she said.  'Some people sit around and wait for the world to poke them.  Right here in this old curiosity shop of a world, they say, 'Poke me, world,' Well, you have to keep the challenges coming on.  Make them up if necessary." -- William Least Heat-Moon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
