<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/608861-laura]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/608861-laura" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 10:11:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11066-in-our-deepest-moments-we-say-the-most-inadequate-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 10:11:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Edna O'Brien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11066-in-our-deepest-moments-we-say-the-most-inadequate-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In our deepest moments we say the most inadequate things.&quot;

&lt;i&gt;(Sister Imelda)&lt;/i&gt;" -- Edna O'Brien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7480-real-isn-t-how-you-are-made-said-the-skin-horse</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 10:11:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7480-real-isn-t-how-you-are-made-said-the-skin-horse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Real isn't how you are made,' said the Skin Horse. 'It's a thing that happens to you. When a child loves you for a long, long time, not just to play with, but REALLY loves you, then you become Real.'

'Does it hurt?' asked the Rabbit. 

'Sometimes,' said the Skin Horse, for he was always truthful. 'When you are Real you don't mind being hurt.' 

'Does it happen all at once, like being wound up,' he asked, 'or bit by bit?' 

'It doesn't happen all at once,' said the Skin Horse. 'You become. It takes a long time. That's why it doesn't happen often to people who break easily, or have sharp edges, or who have to be carefully kept. Generally, by the time you are Real, most of your hair has been loved off, and your eyes drop out and you get loose in the joints and very shabby. But these things don't matter at all, because once you are Real you can't be ugly, except to people who don't understand." -- Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5535-i-culled-poetry-from-odors-sounds-faces-and-ordinary-events</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 10:11:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Jimmy Santiago Baca]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5535-i-culled-poetry-from-odors-sounds-faces-and-ordinary-events]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I culled poetry from odors, sounds, faces, and ordinary events occurring around me.  Breezes bulged me as if I were cloth; sounds nicked their marks on my nerves; objects made impressions on my sight as if in clay.  There, in the soft language, life centered and ground itself in me and I was flowing with the grain of the universe.  Language placed my life experiences in a new context, freeing me for the moment to become with air as air, with clouds as clouds, from which new associations arose to engage me in present life in a more purposeful way.  " -- Jimmy Santiago Baca]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309919-watching-them-harmony-felt-too-shaken-to-take-a-step</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 10:11:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Larry McMurtry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309919-watching-them-harmony-felt-too-shaken-to-take-a-step]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Watching them, Harmony felt too shaken to take a step.  Eddie and Sheba were young; but she herself had become old.  Even if she wasn’t particularly old if you just counted years, the fact was years were no way to count.  Happenings were the way to count, the big happening that separated her from youth or even middle age was the death of her daughter, Pepper.  That death made her realize that life, once you got around to producing children, was no longer about being pretty or having boyfriends or making money – it was about protecting children; getting them raised to the point where they could try life as adults.  It didn’t have to be just children that come out of your body, either.  It could be anyone young who needed something you had to give.  Some grown men were children; some grown women, too.  Harmony knew that she had spent a good part of her life, taking care of just such men.  But now that she felt old she didn’t think she wanted to spend much more of her energy protecting men who had had a good chance to grow up, but had blown it.  If she never had another boyfriend – something she had been worrying about, on the plane – it might be a little dull in some areas, like sexual areas, but it wouldn’t be the end of the world.  
            What would be the end of the world would be to let some little girl like Sheba get in the car with a bad man who would make a U-turn across the street and kill her right there in front of the pay phones, where pimps and crack dealers were making their calls." -- Larry McMurtry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/655-i-believe-entertainment-can-aspire-to-be-art-and-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 10:11:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by steve martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/655-i-believe-entertainment-can-aspire-to-be-art-and-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe entertainment can aspire to be art, and can become art, but if you set out to make art you're an idiot." -- steve martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/86621-were-they-beautiful-we-were-all-beautiful-we-were-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 10:11:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/86621-were-they-beautiful-we-were-all-beautiful-we-were-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Were they beautiful?  We were all beautiful. We were in our twenties." -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312535-we-all-leave-one-another-we-die-we-change--</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 12:17:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Edna O'Brien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312535-we-all-leave-one-another-we-die-we-change--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all leave one another.  We die, we change - it's mostly change - we outgrow our best friends; but even if I do leave you, I will have passed on to you something of myself; you will be a different person because of knowing me; it's inescapable..." -- Edna O'Brien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756706-there-are-many-things-that-can-only-be-seen-through</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2014 10:58:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Oscar A. Romero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756706-there-are-many-things-that-can-only-be-seen-through]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are many things that can only be seen through eyes that have cried" -- Oscar A. Romero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/389382-i-don-t-want-to-be-an-anti-against-anybody-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2014 10:58:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Oscar A. Romero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/389382-i-don-t-want-to-be-an-anti-against-anybody-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don’t want to be an anti, against anybody. I simply want to be the builder of a great affirmation: the affirmation of God,who loves us and who wants to save us." -- Oscar A. Romero]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
