<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/609661-melissa-krabbe]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/609661-melissa-krabbe" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2012 15:21:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34253-are-you-born-again-he-asked-as-we-taxied-down</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2012 15:21:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Anne LaMott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34253-are-you-born-again-he-asked-as-we-taxied-down]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Are you born again?&quot; he asked, as we taxied down the runway. He was rather prim and tense, maybe a little like David Eisenhower with a spastic colon. I did not know how to answer for a moment.
&quot;Yes,&quot; I said. &quot;I am.&quot;
My friends like to tell each other that I am not really a born-again Christian. They think of me more along the lines of that old Jonathan Miller routine, where he said, &quot;I'm not really a Jew -- I'm Jew-ish.&quot; They think I am Christian-ish. But I'm not. I'm just a bad Christian. A bad born-again Christian. And certainly, like the apostle Peter, I am capable of denying it, of presenting myself as a sort of leftist liberation-theology enthusiast and maybe sort of a vaguely Jesusy bon vivant. But it's not true. And I believe that when you get on a plane, if you start lying you are totally doomed.
So I told the truth; that I am a believer, a convert. I'm probably about three months away from slapping an aluminum Jesus-fish on the back of my car, although I first want to see if the application or stickum in any way interferes with my lease agreement. And believe me, all this boggles even *my* mind. But it's true. I could go to a gathering of foot-wash Baptists and, except for my dreadlocks, fit right in. I would wash their feet; I would let them wash mine." -- Anne LaMott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298526-a-tree-gives-glory-to-god-by-being-a-tree</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 11:02:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Thomas Merton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298526-a-tree-gives-glory-to-god-by-being-a-tree]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A tree gives glory to God by being a tree. For in being what God means it to be it is obeying [God]. It “consents,” so to speak, to [God's] creative love. It is expressing an idea which is in God and which is not distinct from the essence of God, and therefore a tree imitates God by being a tree" -- Thomas Merton]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
