<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/610815-renee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/610815-renee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 22:21:42 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59816-i-channel-the-rote-and-the-new-and-unseen-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 22:21:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Jim Shepard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59816-i-channel-the-rote-and-the-new-and-unseen-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I channel the rote and the new and unseen. My head has always been the busiest of crossroads, a festival of happy and unhappy arrivals. In the hours before daybreak when I was a boy, god sent me words as visitors." -- Jim Shepard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15-as-my-mother-once-said-the-boys-throw-stones-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2009 11:04:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Joanna Russ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15-as-my-mother-once-said-the-boys-throw-stones-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As my mother once said: The boys throw stones at the frog in jest. But the frogs die in earnest." -- Joanna Russ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14-i-m-not-a-girl-i-m-a-genius</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2007 20:42:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Joanna Russ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14-i-m-not-a-girl-i-m-a-genius]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not a girl. I'm a genius. " -- Joanna Russ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18-3-there-are-bears-and-there-are-small-dogs-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2007 20:44:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18-3-there-are-bears-and-there-are-small-dogs-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["3. There are bears and there are small dogs. Be strong like bear! If they take out your teeth, sit on the dogs. Bears always forget they can just sit on the dogs. Sit on the dogs." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23-my-soul-is-ten-thousand-miles-wide-and-extremely-invisibly</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2007 20:47:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23-my-soul-is-ten-thousand-miles-wide-and-extremely-invisibly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My soul is ten thousand miles wide and extremely invisibly deep. It is the same size as the sea, and you cannot, you cannot cram it into beer cans and fingernails and stake it out in lots and own it. It will drown you all and never even notice." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35-deliver-my-soul-from-the-sword-my-darling-from-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2007 21:05:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Thomas Savage]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35-deliver-my-soul-from-the-sword-my-darling-from-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Deliver my soul from the sword,
my darling from the power of the dog." -- Thomas Savage]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25870-on-the-wall-next-to-the-table-next-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2008 19:01:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Haven Kimmel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25870-on-the-wall-next-to-the-table-next-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the wall next to the table, next to the scones that provided each table with its own circle of lamplight were quotations about reading, her favorite of which was from Kafka: 'A book must be the axe for the frozen sea within us." -- Haven Kimmel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52277-and-the-joys-i-ve-felt-have-not-always-been-joyous</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 23:39:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52277-and-the-joys-i-ve-felt-have-not-always-been-joyous]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the joys I've felt have not always been joyous. I could have lived differently. When I was your age, my grandfather bought me a ruby bracelet. It as too big for me an would slide up and down my arm. It was almost a necklace. He later told me that he had asked the jeweler make that way. Its size was supposed to be a symbol of his love. More rubies, more love. But I could not wear it comfortably. I could not wear it at all. So here is the point of everything I have been trying to say. IF I were to give a bracelet to you, now, I would measure your wrist twice" -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60003-sometimes-i-feel-like-a-tree-on-a-hill-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2008 23:00:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60003-sometimes-i-feel-like-a-tree-on-a-hill-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I feel like a tree on a hill, at the place where all the wind blows and the hail hits the tree the hardest. All the people I love are down the side aways, sheltered under a great rock, and I am out of the fold, standing alone in the sun and the snow. I feel like I am not part of the rest somehow, although they welcome me and are kind. I see my family as they sit together and it is like theyh ave a certain way between them that is beyond me. I wonder if other folks ever feel included yet alone." -- Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63569-i-am-circling-around-god-around-the-ancient-tower-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2008 22:49:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63569-i-am-circling-around-god-around-the-ancient-tower-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am circling around God, around the ancient tower, and I have been circling for a thousand years, and I still don't know if I am a falcon, or a storm, or a great song." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63878-i-looked-at-her-and-a-voice-inside-me-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2008 18:40:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Steven Hall]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63878-i-looked-at-her-and-a-voice-inside-me-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I looked at her and a voice inside me said, &lt;i&gt;we only see starlight because all the stars are bleeding.&lt;/i&gt;" -- Steven Hall]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63880-a-cat-is-a-responsibility-after-all-and-feeding-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2008 18:43:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Steven Hall]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63880-a-cat-is-a-responsibility-after-all-and-feeding-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A cat is a responsibility after all. And feeding and keeping and caring about a stupid fat cat isn't much, isn't much in the entirety of what counts for being a person and the huge range of &lt;i&gt;what people do,&lt;/i&gt;but it is something. It is something and it's something that's warm and that I still have." -- Steven Hall]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126662-and-again-the-dark-street-the-dark-dark-street-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 21:37:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Kobo Abe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126662-and-again-the-dark-street-the-dark-dark-street-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And again, the dark street. The dark, dark street. The women out shopping for the evening meal of course, and baby carriage and the silver bicycle were already painted out by the darkness; most of the commuters too were already in place in their filing-drawer houses. A half-forsaken chasm of time .... " -- Kobo Abe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126663-we-have-missed-him-in-the-sunshine-in-the-storm</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 21:39:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Paul Auster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126663-we-have-missed-him-in-the-sunshine-in-the-storm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have missed him in the sunshine, in the storm, in the twilight, ever since. " -- Paul Auster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129573-we-suffer-the-threat-of-breathing-in-water-we-fight</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 20:01:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Lynne Hugo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129573-we-suffer-the-threat-of-breathing-in-water-we-fight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We suffer the threat of breathing in water; we fight the nightmares that would drown us. And just as we feel the deceptive joy of floating, we flex our muscles and learn to kick, propelling ourselves into deeper waters where we can't see the bottom or touch the side.

There, in the deep, we stroke. 

Then, surprising ourselves, saving ourselves, we swim. " -- Lynne Hugo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79741-nothing-is-very-strong-strong-enough-to-steal-away-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 13:46:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79741-nothing-is-very-strong-strong-enough-to-steal-away-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing is very strong: strong enough to steal away a man's best years not in sweet sins but in a dreary flickering of the mind over it knows not what and knows not why, in the gratification of curiosities so feeble that the man is only half aware of them, in drumming of fingers and kicking of heels, in whistling tunes that he does not like, or in the long, dim labyrinth of reveries that have not even lust or ambition to give them a relish, but which, once chance association has started them, the creature is took weak and fuddled to shake off." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165908-i-heard-the-opening-bar-of-help-as-i-headed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2009 15:22:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Oscar Zeta Acosta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165908-i-heard-the-opening-bar-of-help-as-i-headed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I heard the opening bar of 'Help' as I headed down Polk Street. Every single time I've heard that tune I've taken it as some message from God, a warning of things to come, a perfect description of my mashed-potato character" -- Oscar Zeta Acosta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169986-and-yet-standing-behind-her-son-waiting-for-the-traffic</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 21:37:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169986-and-yet-standing-behind-her-son-waiting-for-the-traffic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And yet, standing behind her son, waiting for the traffic light change, she remembered how in the midst of it all there had been a time when she'd felt a loneliness so deep that once, not so many years ago, having a cavity filled, the dentist's gentle turning of her chin with his soft fingers had felt to her like a tender kindness of almost excruciating depth, and she had swallowed with a groan of longing, tears springing to her eyes." -- Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169988-this-because-it-is-never-really-very-cold-in-england</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 21:40:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169988-this-because-it-is-never-really-very-cold-in-england]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This because it is never really very cold in England. It is drizzly, and the wind will blow; hail happens, and there is a breed of Tuesday in January in which time creeps and no light comes and the air is full of water and nobody really loves anybody, but still a decent jumper and a waxen jacket lined with wool is sufficient for every weather England's got to give." -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169989-he-was-having-an-odd-paternal-rush-a-blood-surge</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 21:43:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169989-he-was-having-an-odd-paternal-rush-a-blood-surge]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was having an odd paternal rush, a blood surge that was also &lt;i&gt;about&lt;/i&gt; blood and was presently hunting through Howard's expansive intelligence to find words that would more effectively express something like &lt;i&gt;don't walk in front of cars take care and be good and don't hurt or be hurt and don't live in a way that makes you feel dead and don't betray anybody or yourself and take care of what matters and please don't and please remember and make sure&lt;/i&gt;" -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178929-because-i-have-willed-it-and-i-am-not-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 21:54:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Susan Power]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178929-because-i-have-willed-it-and-i-am-not-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because I have willed it. And I am not a fairy tale." -- Susan Power]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173801-as-i-stood-outside-in-cow-lane-it-occurred-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 21:54:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Alan Bradley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173801-as-i-stood-outside-in-cow-lane-it-occurred-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As I stood outside in Cow Lane, it occurred to me that Heaven must be a place where the library is open twenty-four hours a day, seven days a week.

No ... eight days a week." -- Alan Bradley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187599-my-ideal-life-is-a-quiet-one-i-like-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2009 14:02:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Charles D'Ambrosio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187599-my-ideal-life-is-a-quiet-one-i-like-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My ideal life is a quiet one. I like to read, to sit still in the same chair, with the lampshade at a certain angle, alone, or with Meagan nearby, and now and then, if I'm lucky, I'll come across a lovely phrase or fine sentiment, look up from my book, and feel the harmony of some notion, the justice of it, and know that everything is there. That's life to me, those privately discovered moments. " -- Charles D'Ambrosio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187603-in-a-split-second-of-eternity-everything-is-changed-transfigured</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2009 14:11:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Muriel Barbery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187603-in-a-split-second-of-eternity-everything-is-changed-transfigured]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a split second of eternity, everything is changed, transfigured. A few bars of music, rising from an unfamiliar place, a touch of perfection in the flow of human dealings--I lean my head slowly to one side, reflect on the camellia on the moss on the temple, reflect on a cup of tea, while outside the wind is rustling foliage, the forward rush of life is crystalized in a brilliant jewel of a moment that knows neither projects nor future, human destiny is rescued from the pale succession of days, glows with light at last and, surpassing time, warms my tranquil heart. " -- Muriel Barbery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187604-madame-michel-has-the-elegance-of-the-hedgehog-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2009 14:14:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Muriel Barbery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187604-madame-michel-has-the-elegance-of-the-hedgehog-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Madame Michel has the elegance of the hedgehog: on the outside she is covered in quills, a real fortress, but my gut feeling is that on the inside, she has the same simple refinement as the hedgehog: a deceptively indolent little creature, fiercely solitary--and terrible elegant. " -- Muriel Barbery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265181-i-looked-like-a-woman-in-glasses-but-i-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 13:12:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Lydia Davis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265181-i-looked-like-a-woman-in-glasses-but-i-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I looked like a woman in glasses, but I had dreams of leading a very different kind of life, the life of a woman who would not wear glasses, the kind of woman I saw from a distance now and then in a bar." -- Lydia Davis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265183-nearly-every-morning-a-certain-woman-in-our-community-comes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 13:17:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Lydia Davis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265183-nearly-every-morning-a-certain-woman-in-our-community-comes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nearly every morning, a certain woman in our community comes running out of her house with her face white and her overcoat flapping wildly. She cries out, &quot;Emergency, emergency,&quot; and one of us runs to her and holds her until her fears are calmed. We know she is making it up; nothing is has really happened to her. But we understand, because there is hardly one of us who has no been moved at some time to do just what she has done, and every time, it has taken all our strength, and even the strength of our friends and families, too, to keep us quiet." -- Lydia Davis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267301-i-want-to-take-away-your-sunshine-lukas-not-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2010 12:51:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Peter H. Fogtdal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267301-i-want-to-take-away-your-sunshine-lukas-not-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to take away your sunshine, Lukas. Not because I'm evil but because the sun can't exist without shadows. I want to examine the lie that keeps you afloat--the idea that it's wonderful to be Lukas, that it's splendid to be the tsar's favorite dwarf, that there's nothing better to do than bring crackers to Menshikov like some kind of dog. When does it hurt the most, Lukas? That's what I'd like to know. What hurts you more than anything else? Is it when the tsar mocks you? Or is it when he can't remember your name? Is it when he forgets all about your for a year or two? When are you going to curse Peter Alexeyevich to Hell, Lukas? That's what I'd like to know. I want to get behind that smile of yours, and your clown's heart. And then I'll console you when you fall apart--I'll console you when you realize that you are infinitely unloved. 
    At that moment I'll be at your side, but no before.
    Not a moment before." -- Peter H. Fogtdal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293101-it-is-i-suppose-the-common-grief-of-children-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 21:21:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by Katherine Dunn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293101-it-is-i-suppose-the-common-grief-of-children-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is, I suppose, the common grief of children at having to protect their parents from reality. It is bitter for the young to see what awful innocence adults grow into, that terrible vulnerability that must be sheltered from the rodent mire of childhood.
Can we blame the child for resenting the fantasy of largeness? Big, soft arms and deep voices in the dark saying, &quot;Tell Papa, tell Mama, and we'll make it right.&quot; The child, screaming for refuge, senses how feeble a shelter the twig hut of grown-up awareness is. They claim strength, these parents, and complete sanctuary. The weeping earth itself knows how desperate is the child's need for exactly that sanctuary. How deep and sticky is the darkness of childhood, how rigid the blades of infant evil, which is unadulterated, unrestrained by the convenient cushions of age and its civilizing anesthesia.
Grownups can deal with scraped knees, dropped ice-cream cones, and lost dollies, but if they suspected the real reasons we cry they would fling us out of their arms in horrified revulsion. Yet we are small and as terrified as we are terrifying in our ferocious appetites.
We need that warm adult stupidity. Even knowing the illusion, we cry and hide in their laps, speaking only of defiled lollipops or lost bears, and getting lollipop or a toy bear'd worth of comfort. We make do with it rather than face alone the cavernous reaches of our skull for which there is no remedy, no safety, no comfort at all. We survive until, by sheer stamina, we escape into the dim innocence of our own adulthood and its forgetfulness." -- Katherine Dunn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/281593-i-cannot-believe-such-monstrous-energy-of-grief-can-lead</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 21:37:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renee add a quote by John Champlin Gardner Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/281593-i-cannot-believe-such-monstrous-energy-of-grief-can-lead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot believe such monstrous energy of grief can lead to nothing!" -- John Champlin Gardner Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
