<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/610982-sarah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/610982-sarah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 19:28:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98490-evil-can-be-undone-but-it-cannot-develop-into-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 19:28:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98490-evil-can-be-undone-but-it-cannot-develop-into-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Evil can be undone, but it cannot 'develop' into good. Time does not heal it. The spell must be unwound, bit by bit, 'with backward mutters of dissevering power' - or else not. " -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71113-son-he-said-ye-cannot-in-your-present-state-understand-eternity-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 19:30:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71113-son-he-said-ye-cannot-in-your-present-state-understand-eternity-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Son,'he said,' ye cannot in your present state understand eternity...That is what mortals misunderstand. They say of some temporal suffering, &quot;No future bliss can make up for it,&quot; not knowing that Heaven, once attained, will work backwards and turn even that agony into a glory. And of some sinful pleasure they say &quot;Let me have but this and I'll take the consequences&quot;: little dreaming how damnation will spread back and back into their past and contaminate the pleasure of the sin. Both processes begin even before death. The good man's past begins to change so that his forgiven sins and remembered sorrows take on the quality of Heaven: the bad man's past already conforms to his badness and is filled only with dreariness. And that is why...the Blessed will say &quot;We have never lived anywhere except in Heaven, : and the Lost, &quot;We were always in Hell.&quot; And both will speak truly." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98493-there-have-been-some-who-were-so-occupied-in-spreading</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 19:31:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C. S.  Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98493-there-have-been-some-who-were-so-occupied-in-spreading]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There have been some who were so occupied in spreading Christianity that they never gave a thought to Christ. Man! Ye see it in smaller matters. Did ye never know a lover of books that with all his first editions and signed copies had lost the power to read them? Or an organiser of charities that had lost all love for the poor? It is the subtlest of all snares." -- C. S.  Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64681-and-yet-all-loneliness-angers-hatreds-envies-and-itchings-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 19:35:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64681-and-yet-all-loneliness-angers-hatreds-envies-and-itchings-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And yet all loneliness, angers, hatreds, envies, and itchings that it contains, if rolled into one single experience and put into the scale against the least moment of the joy that is felt by the least in Heaven, would have no weight that could be registered at all.  Bad cannot succeed even in being bad as truly as good is good." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101397-in-my-experience-god-rarely-makes-our-fear-disappear-instead</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2008 13:06:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Bruce Wilkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101397-in-my-experience-god-rarely-makes-our-fear-disappear-instead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In my experience, God rarely makes our fear disappear. Instead, He asks us to be strong and take courage. What is courage? As Ordinary discovered, courage is not the absence of fear; rather, it's choosing to act in spite of the fear. You could say that without fear, you can't have genuine courage." -- Bruce Wilkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101398-the-single-best-way-to-develop-leaders</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2008 13:08:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Bruce Wilkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101398-the-single-best-way-to-develop-leaders]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The single best way to develop leaders . . . is to take people out of their safe environment and away from the people they know, and throw them into a new arena they know little about. Way over their head, preferably. In fact, the more demanding their challenges, the more pressure and risk they face, the more likely a dynamic leader will emerge." -- Bruce Wilkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101399-not-surprisingly-the-place-we-re-most-likely-to-experience-testing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2008 13:08:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Bruce Wilkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101399-not-surprisingly-the-place-we-re-most-likely-to-experience-testing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not surprisingly, the place we're most likely to experience testing is exactly where we struggle most to trust God." -- Bruce Wilkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/337363-whenever-you-find-a-man-who-says-he-doesn-t-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 18:13:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/337363-whenever-you-find-a-man-who-says-he-doesn-t-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever you find a man who says he doesn't believe in a real Right and Wrong, you will find the same man going back on this a moment later.&quot;

--The Case for Christianity" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105875-it-seems-then-we-are-forced-to-believe-in-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 18:15:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105875-it-seems-then-we-are-forced-to-believe-in-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seems, then, we are forced to believe in a real Right and Wrong. People may be sometimes mistaken about them, just as people sometimes get their sums wrong, but they are not a matter of mere taste and opinion any more than the multiplication table." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105878-supposing-you-hear-a-cry-for-help-from-a-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 18:39:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105878-supposing-you-hear-a-cry-for-help-from-a-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Supposing you hear a cry for help from a man in danger. You will probably feel two desires - one a desire to give help (due to your herd instinct), the other a desire to keep out of danger (due to the instinct for self-preservation). But you will find inside you, in addition to these two impulses, a third thing which tells you that you ought to follow the impulse to help, and suppress the impulse to run away. Now this thing that judges between two instincts, that decides which should be encouraged, cannot itself be either of them. You might as well say that the sheet of music which tells you, at a given moment, to play one note on the piano and not another, is itself one of the notes on the keyboard. The Moral Law tells us the tune we have to play: our instincts are merely the keys." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105881-strictly-speaking-there-are-no-such-things-as-good-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 18:41:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105881-strictly-speaking-there-are-no-such-things-as-good-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Strictly speaking, there are no such things as good and bad impulses. Think...of a piano. It has not got two kinds of notes on it, the 'right' notes and the 'wrong' ones. Every single note is right at one time and wrong at another. The Moral Law is not any one instinct or set of instincts: it is something which makes a kind of tune (the tune we call goodness or right conduct) by directing the instincts." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318481-we-all-want-progress-but-progress-means-getting-nearer-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 18:07:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318481-we-all-want-progress-but-progress-means-getting-nearer-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all want progress. But progress means getting nearer to the place where you want to be. And if you have taken a wrong turning, then to go forward does not get you any nearer. If you are on the wrong road, progress means doing an about-turn and walking back to the right road; and in that case the man who turns back soonest is the most progressive man." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106183-this-is-the-fix-we-are-in-if-the-universe</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 18:09:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106183-this-is-the-fix-we-are-in-if-the-universe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is the fix we are in. If the universe is not governed by an absolute goodness, then all our efforts are in the long run hopeless. But if it is, then we are making ourselves enemies to that goodness every day, and are not in the least likely to do any better tomorrow, and so our case is hopeless again. We cannot do without it, and we cannot do with it. God is the only comfort, He is also the supreme terror: the thing we most need and the thing we most want to hide from. He is our only possible ally, and we have made ourselves His enemies. Some people talk as if meeting the gaze of absolute goodness would be fun. They need to think again. They are still only playing with religion." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5054-if-you-look-for-truth-you-may-find-comfort-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 18:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5054-if-you-look-for-truth-you-may-find-comfort-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you look for truth, you may find comfort in the end; if you look for comfort you will not get either comfort or truth only soft soap and wishful thinking to begin, and in the end, despair." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106826-if-you-do-not-take-the-distinction-between-good-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 18:07:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106826-if-you-do-not-take-the-distinction-between-good-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you do not take the distinction between good and bad very seriously, then it is easy to say that anything you find in this world is a part of God. But, of course, if you think some things really bad, and God really good, then you cannot talk like that. You must believe that God is separate from the world and that some of the things we see in it are contrary to His will." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10152-reality-in-fact-is-usually-something-you-could-not-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 20:10:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10152-reality-in-fact-is-usually-something-you-could-not-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reality, in fact, is usually something you could not have guessed. That is one of the reasons I believe Christianity. It is a religion you could not have guessed. If it offered us just the kind of universe we had always expected, I should feel we were making it up. But, in fact, it is not the sort of thing anyone would have made up. It has just that queer twist about it that real things have. So let us leave behind all these boys' philosophies--these over simple answers. The problem is not simple and the answer is not going to be simple either." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106854-christianity-agrees-with-dualism-that-this-universe-is-at-war</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 20:11:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106854-christianity-agrees-with-dualism-that-this-universe-is-at-war]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Christianity agrees with Dualism that this universe is at war. But it does not think this is a war between independent powers. It thinks it is a civil war, a rebellion, and that we are living in a part of the universe occupied by the rebel." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106874-god-made-us-invented-us-as-a-man-invents-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 21:10:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106874-god-made-us-invented-us-as-a-man-invents-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God made us: invented us as a man invents an engine. A car is made to run on petrol, and it would not run properly on anything else. Now God designed the human machine to run on Himself. He Himself is the fuel our spirits were designed to burn, or the food our spirits were designed to feed on. There is no other. That is why it is just no good asking God to make us happy in our own way without bothering about religion. God cannot give us a happiness and peace apart from Himself, because it is not there." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173488-in-the-same-way-a-christian-is-not-a-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 20:53:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173488-in-the-same-way-a-christian-is-not-a-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the same way a Christian is not a man who never goes wrong, but a man is enabled to repent and pick himself up and begin over again after each stumble--because the Christ-life is inside him, repairing him all the time, enabling him to repeat (in some degree) the kind of voluntary death which Christ Himself carried out.&quot; - Mere Christianity" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113376-a-christian-society-is-not-going-to-arrive-until-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 15:33:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113376-a-christian-society-is-not-going-to-arrive-until-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A Christian society is not going to arrive until most of us really want it: and we are not going to want it until we become fully Christian. I may repeat &quot;Do as you would be done by&quot; till I am black in the fact, but I cannot really carry it out till I love my neighbour as myself: and I cannot learn to love my neighbour as myself till I learn to love God: and I cannot learn to love God except by learning to obey Him. And so, as I warned you, we are driven on to something more inward - driven on from social matters to religious matters." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113377-that-is-why-christians-are-told-not-to-judge-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 15:33:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113377-that-is-why-christians-are-told-not-to-judge-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That is why Christians are told not to judge. We see only the results which a man's choices make out of his raw material. But God does not judge him on the raw material at all, but on what he has done with it." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113378-one-man-may-be-so-placed-that-his-anger-sheds</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 15:35:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113378-one-man-may-be-so-placed-that-his-anger-sheds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One man may be so placed that his anger sheds the blood of thousands, and another so placed that however angry he gets he will only be laughed at. But the little mark on the soul may be much the same in both. Each has done something to himself which, unless he repents, will make it harder for him to keep out of the rage next time he is tempted, and will make the rage worse when he does fall into it. Each of them, if he seriously turns to God, can have that twist in the central man straightened out again: each is, in the long run, doomed if he will not. The bigness or smallness of the thing, seen from the outside, is not what really matters." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139094-when-a-man-is-getting-better-he-understands-more-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 14:20:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139094-when-a-man-is-getting-better-he-understands-more-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a man is getting better he understands more and more clearly the evil that is still left in him. When a man is getting worse he understands his own badness less and less." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139095-if-anyone-says-that-sex-in-itself-is-bad-christianity</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 14:22:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139095-if-anyone-says-that-sex-in-itself-is-bad-christianity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If anyone says that sex, in itself, is bad, Christianity contradicts him at once. But, of course, when people say, 'Sex is nothing to be ashamed of,' they may mean 'the state into which the sexual instinct has now got is nothing to be ashamed of'. If they mean that, I think they are wrong. I think it is everything to be ashamed of. There is nothing to be ashamed of in enjoying your food: there would be everything to be ashamed of if half the world made food the main interest of their lives and spent their time looking at pictures of food and dribbling and smacking their lips." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139096-christian-principles-are-admittedly-stricter-than-the-others-but-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 14:22:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139096-christian-principles-are-admittedly-stricter-than-the-others-but-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Christian principles are, admittedly, stricter than the others; but then we think you will get help towards obeying them which you will not get towards obeying the others." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139097-the-christian-idea-of-marriage-is-based-on-christ-s-words</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 14:24:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139097-the-christian-idea-of-marriage-is-based-on-christ-s-words]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Christian idea of marriage is based on Christ's words that a man and wife are to be regarded as a single organism - for that is what the words 'one flesh' would be in modern English. And the Christians believe that when He said this He was not expressing a sentiment but stating a fact - just as one is stating a fact when one says that a lock and its key are one mechanism, or that a violin and a bow are one musical instrument." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139098-if-people-do-not-believe-in-permanent-marriage-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 14:26:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139098-if-people-do-not-believe-in-permanent-marriage-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If people do not believe in permanent marriage, it is perhaps better that they should live together unmarried than that they should make vows they do not mean to keep. It is true that by living together without marriage they will be guilty (in Christian eyes) of fornication. But one fault is not mended by adding another; unchastity is not improved by adding perjury. The idea that 'being in love' is the only reason for remaining married really leaves no room for marriage as a contract or promise at all. If love is the whole thing, then the promise can add nothing; and if it adds nothing, then it should not be made." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139099-the-promise-made-when-i-am-in-love-and-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 14:27:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139099-the-promise-made-when-i-am-in-love-and-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The promise, made when I am in love and because I am in love, to be true to the beloved as long as I live, commits me to being true even if I cease to be in love. A promise must be about things that I can do, about actions: no one can promise to go on feeling in a certain way. He might as well promise to never have a headache or always to feel hungry." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139100-ceasing-to-be-in-love-need-not-mean-ceasing-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 14:29:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139100-ceasing-to-be-in-love-need-not-mean-ceasing-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ceasing to be 'in love' need not mean ceasing to love. Love in this second sense - love as distinct from 'being in love' - is not merely a feeling. It is a deep unity, maintained by the will and deliberately strengthened by habit; reinforced by (in Christian marriages) the grace which both partners ask, and receive, from God. They can have this love for each other even at those moments when they do not like each other; as you love yourself even when you do not like yourself. They can retain this love even when each would easily, if they allowed themselves, be 'in love' with someone else. 'Being in love' first moved them to promise fidelity: this quieter love enables them to keep the promise." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139101-christianity-does-not-want-us-to-reduce-by-one-atom</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 14:32:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139101-christianity-does-not-want-us-to-reduce-by-one-atom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Christianity does not want us to reduce by one atom the hatred we feel for cruelty and treachery. We ought to hate them. Not one word of what we have said about them needs to be unsaid. But it does want us to hate them in the same way in which we hate things in ourselves: being sorry that the man should have done such things, and hoping, if it is anyway possible, that somehow, sometime, somewhere he can be cured and made human again." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
