<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/611813-melinda]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/611813-melinda" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 05:20:04 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132157-the-pessimist-resembles-a-man-who-observes-with-fear-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 05:20:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132157-the-pessimist-resembles-a-man-who-observes-with-fear-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The pessimist resembles a man who observes with fear and sadness that his wall calendar, from which he daily tears a sheet, grows thinner with each passing day.  On the other hand, the person who attacks the problems of life actively is like a man who removes each successive leaf from his calendar and files it neatly and carefully away with its predecessors, after first having jotted down a few diary notes on the back.  He can reflect with pride and joy on all the richness set down in these notes, on all the life he has already lived to the fullest.  What will it matter to him if he notices that he is growing old?  Has he any reason to envy the young people whom he sees, or wax nostalgic over his own lost youth?  What reasons has he to envy a young person?  For the possibilities that a young person has, the future which is in store for him?

No, thank you,' he will think.  'Instead of possibilities, I have realities in my past, not only the reality of work done and of love loved, but of sufferings bravely suffered.  These sufferings are even the things of which I am most proud, although these are things which cannot inspire envy.' &quot;

From &quot;Logotherapy in a Nutshell&quot;, an essay" -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214795-i-enjoy-doing-housework-ironing-washing-cooking-dishwashing-whenever-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 05:19:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Tasha Tudor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214795-i-enjoy-doing-housework-ironing-washing-cooking-dishwashing-whenever-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I enjoy doing housework, ironing, washing, cooking, dishwashing.  Whenever I get one of those questionaires and they ask what is your profession, I always put down housewife.  It's an admirable profession, why apologize for it.  You aren't stupid because you're a housewife.  When you're stirring the jam you can read Shakespeare." -- Tasha Tudor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28623-read-not-to-contradict-and-confute-nor-to-believe-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 09:31:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Francis Bacon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28623-read-not-to-contradict-and-confute-nor-to-believe-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Read not to contradict and confute; nor to believe and take for granted; nor to find talk and discourse; but to weigh and consider.  Some books are to be tasted, others to be swallowed, and some few to be chewed and digested: that is, some books are to be read only in parts, others to be read, but not curiously, and some few to be read wholly, and with diligence and attention." -- Francis Bacon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2919-he-is-no-fool-who-gives-what-he-cannot-keep</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 09:35:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Jim Elliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2919-he-is-no-fool-who-gives-what-he-cannot-keep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He is no fool who gives what he cannot keep to gain that which he cannot lose." -- Jim Elliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9178-chance-favors-the-prepared-mind</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 09:37:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Louis Pasteur]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9178-chance-favors-the-prepared-mind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chance favors the prepared mind." -- Louis Pasteur]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135079-the-lord-s-mercy-often-rides-to-the-door-of-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 09:38:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Charles Spurgeon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135079-the-lord-s-mercy-often-rides-to-the-door-of-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Lord's mercy often rides to the door of our heart upon the black horse of affliction." -- Charles Spurgeon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27510-the-hottest-places-in-hell-are-reserved-for-those-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 09:39:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by John F. Kennedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27510-the-hottest-places-in-hell-are-reserved-for-those-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The hottest places in hell are reserved for those who, in times of great moral crisis, maintain their neutrality." -- John F. Kennedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34863-the-heights-by-great-men-reached-and-kept-were-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 09:40:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Henry Wadsworth Longfellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34863-the-heights-by-great-men-reached-and-kept-were-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The heights by great men reached and kept were not attained in sudden flight but, they while their companions slept, they were toiling upwards in the night." -- Henry Wadsworth Longfellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37597-you-never-know-how-much-you-really-believe-anything-until</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 09:42:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37597-you-never-know-how-much-you-really-believe-anything-until]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You never know how much you really believe anything until its truth or falsehood becomes a matter of life and death to you." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135082-where-god-tears-great-gaps-we-should-not-try-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 09:44:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Dietrich Bonhoeffer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135082-where-god-tears-great-gaps-we-should-not-try-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where God tears great gaps we should not try to fill them with human words." -- Dietrich Bonhoeffer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141025-i-see-you-are-in-a-dilemma-and-one-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 09:54:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141025-i-see-you-are-in-a-dilemma-and-one-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I see you are in a dilemma, and one of a peculiar and difficult nature.  Two paths lie before you; you conscientiously wish to choose the right one, even though it be the most steep, straight, and rugged; but you do not know which is the right one; you cannot decide whether duty and religion command you to go out into the cold and friendless world, and there to earn your living by governess drudgery, or whether they enjoin your continued stay with your aged mother, neglecting, for the present, every prospect of independency for yourself, and putting up with the daily inconvenience, sometimes even with privations.  I can well imagine, that it is next to impossible for you to decide for yourself in this matter, so I will decide it for you. 

At least, I will tell you what is my earnest conviction on the subject; I will show you candidly how the question strikes me.  The right path is that which necessitates the greatest sacrifice of self-interest -- which implies the greatest good to others; and this path, steadily followed, will lead, I believe, in time, to prosperity and to happiness; though it may seem, at the outset, to tend quite in a contrary direction.  Your mother is both old and infirm; old and infirm people have but few resources of happiness -- fewer almost than the comparatively young and healthy can conceive; to deprive them of one of these is cruel.  If your mother is more composed when you are with her, stay with her.  If she would be unhappy in case you left her, stay with her.  It will not apparently, as far as short-sighted humanity can see, be for your advantage to remain at XXX, nor will you be praised and admired for remaining at home to comfort your mother; yet, probably, your own conscience will approve, and if it does, stay with her.  I recommend you to do what I am trying to do myself.

[Quoted from a letter to a friend, referenced in the last chapter of Vol 1. &quot;The Life of Charlotte Bronte&quot; by Elizabeth Gaskell ]" -- Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162173-first-came-bright-spirits-not-the-spirits-of-men-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2009 08:33:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162173-first-came-bright-spirits-not-the-spirits-of-men-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First came bright Spirits, not the Spirits of men, who danced and scattered flowers.  Then, on the left and right, at each side of the forest avenue, came youthful shapes, boys upon one hand, and girls upon the other.  If I could remember their singing and write down the notes, no man who read that score would ever grow sick or old.  Between them went musicians: and after these a lady in whose honour all this was being done.  

	I cannot now remember whether she was naked or clothed.  If she were naked, then it must have been the almost visible penumbra of her courtesy and joy which produces in my memory the illusion of a great and shining train that followed her across the happy grass.  If she were clothed, then the illusion of nakedness is doubtless due to the clarity with which her inmost spirit shone through the clothes.  For clothes in that country are not a disguise: the spiritual body lives along each thread and turns them into living organs.  A robe or a crown is there as much one of the wearer's features as a lip or an eye. 
 
	But I have forgotten.  And only partly do I remember the unbearable beauty of her face.  

	“Is it?...is it?” I whispered to my guide.
	“Not at all,” said he.  “It's someone ye'll never have heard of.  Her name on earth was Sarah Smith and she lived at Golders Green.”
	“She seems to be...well, a person of particular importance?”
	“Aye.  She is one of the great ones.  Ye have heard that fame in this country and fame on Earth are two quite different things.”
	“And who are these gigantic people...look!  They're like emeralds...who are dancing and throwing flowers before here?”
	“Haven't ye read your Milton? A thousand liveried angels lackey her.”
	“And who are all these young men and women on each side?”
	“They are her sons and daughters.”
	“She must have had a very large family, Sir.”
	“Every young man or boy that met her became her son – even if it was only the boy that brought the meat to her back door.  Every girl that met her was her daughter.”
	“Isn't that a bit hard on their own parents?”
	“No.  There are those that steal other people's children.  But her motherhood was of a different kind.  Those on whom it fell went back to their natural parents loving them more.  Few men looked on her without becoming, in a certain fashion, her lovers.  But it was the kind of love that made them not less true, but truer, to their own wives.”
	“And how...but hullo!  What are all these animals?  A cat-two cats-dozens of cats.  And all those dogs...why, I can't count them.  And the birds.  And the horses.”
	“They are her beasts.”
	“Did she keep a sort of zoo?  I mean, this is a bit too much.”
	“Every beast and bird that came near her had its place in her love.  In her they became themselves.  And now the abundance of life she has in Christ from the Father flows over into them.”
	I looked at my Teacher in amazement.
	“Yes,” he said.  “It is like when you throw  a stone into a pool, and the concentric waves spread out further and further.  Who knows where it will end?  Redeemed humanity is still young, it has hardly come to its full strength.  But already there is joy enough int the little finger of a great saint such as yonder lady to waken all the dead things of the universe into life." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10152-reality-in-fact-is-usually-something-you-could-not-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 20:03:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10152-reality-in-fact-is-usually-something-you-could-not-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reality, in fact, is usually something you could not have guessed. That is one of the reasons I believe Christianity. It is a religion you could not have guessed. If it offered us just the kind of universe we had always expected, I should feel we were making it up. But, in fact, it is not the sort of thing anyone would have made up. It has just that queer twist about it that real things have. So let us leave behind all these boys' philosophies--these over simple answers. The problem is not simple and the answer is not going to be simple either." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19964-i-didn-t-go-to-religion-to-make-me-happy-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 20:05:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19964-i-didn-t-go-to-religion-to-make-me-happy-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I didn’t go to religion to make me happy. I always knew a bottle of Port would do that. If you want a religion to make you feel really comfortable, I certainly don’t recommend Christianity." -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23974-it-is-a-good-rule-after-reading-a-new-book</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 20:05:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23974-it-is-a-good-rule-after-reading-a-new-book]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a good rule after reading a new book, never to allow yourself another new one till you have read an old one in between." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26465-christianity-if-false-is-of-no-importance-and-if-true</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 20:06:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26465-christianity-if-false-is-of-no-importance-and-if-true]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Christianity, if false, is of no importance, and if true, of infinite importance, the only thing it cannot be is moderately important." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28923-next-to-the-blessed-sacrament-itself-your-neighbor-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 20:07:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28923-next-to-the-blessed-sacrament-itself-your-neighbor-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Next to the Blessed Sacrament itself, your neighbor is the holiest object presented to your senses." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30083-literature-adds-to-reality-it-does-not-simply-describe-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 20:07:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30083-literature-adds-to-reality-it-does-not-simply-describe-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Literature adds to reality, it does not simply describe it. It enriches the necessary competencies that daily life requires and provides; and in this respect, it irrigates the deserts that our lives have already become." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6439-if-we-find-ourselves-with-a-desire-that-nothing-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 20:08:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6439-if-we-find-ourselves-with-a-desire-that-nothing-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we find ourselves with a desire that nothing in this world can satisfy, the most probable explanation is that we were made for another world." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6979-i-am-trying-here-to-prevent-anyone-saying-the-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 05:19:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6979-i-am-trying-here-to-prevent-anyone-saying-the-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am trying here to prevent anyone saying the really foolish thing that people often say about Him: I’m ready to accept Jesus as a great moral teacher, but I don’t accept his claim to be God. That is the one thing we must not say. A man who was merely a man and said the sort of things Jesus said would not be a great moral teacher. He would either be a lunatic — on the level with the man who says he is a poached egg — or else he would be the Devil of Hell. You must make your choice. Either this man was, and is, the Son of God, or else a madman or something worse. You can shut him up for a fool, you can spit at him and kill him as a demon or you can fall at his feet and call him Lord and God, but let us not come with any patronizing nonsense about his being a great human teacher. He has not left that open to us. He did not intend to." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42142-there-are-no-ordinary-people-you-have-never-talked-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 05:19:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42142-there-are-no-ordinary-people-you-have-never-talked-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are no ordinary people. You have never talked to a mere mortal. Nations, cultures, arts, civilizations - these are mortal, and their life is to ours as the life of a gnat. But it is immortals whom we joke with, work with, marry, snub and exploit - immortal horrors or everlasting splendors. This does not mean that we are to be perpetually solemn. We must play. But our merriment must be of that kind (and it is, in fact, the merriest kind) which exists between people who have, from the outset, taken each other seriously - no flippancy, no superiority, no presumption." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214792-i-salute-you-there-is-nothing-i-can-give-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 05:18:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Father Giovanni]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214792-i-salute-you-there-is-nothing-i-can-give-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I salute you!  There is nothing I can give you which you have not; but there is much, that, while I cannot give, you can take.
No heaven can come to us unless our hearts find rest in it today.  Take Heaven.
No peace lies in the future which is not hidden in this present instant.  Take Peace.
The gloom of the world is but a shadow, behind it, yet, within our reach, is joy.  Take Joy.
And so, at this Christmas time, I greet you, with the prayer that for  you, now and forever, the day breaks and the shadows flee away." -- Father Giovanni]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137336-we-no-longer-dare-to-believe-in-beauty-and-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 19:00:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by Hans Urs von Balthasar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137336-we-no-longer-dare-to-believe-in-beauty-and-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We no longer dare to believe in beauty and we make of it a mere appearance in order the more easily to dispose of it. Our situation today shows that beauty demands for itself at least as much courage and decision as do truth and goodness, and she will not allow herself to be separated and banned from her two sisters without taking them along with herself in an act of mysterious vengeance. We can be sure that whoever sneers at her name as if she were the ornament of a bourgeois past -- whether he admits it or not -- can no longer pray and soon will no longer be able to love." -- Hans Urs von Balthasar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/746558-it-is-in-our-own-daily-life-that-we-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 12:37:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/746558-it-is-in-our-own-daily-life-that-we-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is in our own daily life that we are to look for the portents and the prodigies.... Compared with this life, all public life, all fame, all wisdom, is by its nature cramped and cold and small.  For on that defined and lighted public stage men are of necessity forced to profess one set of accomplishments, to rise to one rigid standard.  It is the utterly unknown people, who can grow in all directions like an exuberant tree." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/562011-the-greatest-service-we-can-do-to-education-today-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 14:35:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/562011-the-greatest-service-we-can-do-to-education-today-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…the greatest service we can do to education today is to teach fewer subjects. No one has time to do more than a very few things well before he is twenty, and when we force a boy to be a mediocrity in a dozen subjects, we destroy his standards, perhaps for life." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310462-for-every-one-pupil-who-needs-to-be-guarded-against</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 14:05:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310462-for-every-one-pupil-who-needs-to-be-guarded-against]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For every one pupil who needs to be guarded against a weak excess of sensibility there are three who need to be awakened from the slumber of cold vulgarity.  The task of the modern educator is not to cut down jungles but to irrigate deserts. The right defence against false sentiments is to inculcate just sentiments. By starving the sensibility of our pupils we only make them easier prey to the propagandist when he comes. For famished nature will be avenged and a hard heart is no infallible protection against a soft head." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/881778-aristotle-says-that-the-aim-of-education-is-to-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 14:09:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/881778-aristotle-says-that-the-aim-of-education-is-to-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Aristotle says that the aim of education is to make the pupil like and dislike what he ought." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/702-it-would-seem-that-our-lord-finds-our-desires-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 05:15:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/702-it-would-seem-that-our-lord-finds-our-desires-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It would seem that Our Lord finds our desires not too strong, but too weak. We are half-hearted creatures, fooling about with drink and sex and ambition when infinite joy is offered us, like an ignorant child who wants to go on making mud pies in a slum because he cannot imagine what is meant by the offer of a holiday at the sea. We are far too easily pleased." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231487-we-live-in-fact-in-a-world-starved-for-solitude</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 05:16:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231487-we-live-in-fact-in-a-world-starved-for-solitude]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We live, in fact, in a world starved for solitude, silence, and private: and therefore starved for meditation and true friendship." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282593-it-is-a-serious-thing-to-live-in-a-society</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 05:16:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melinda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282593-it-is-a-serious-thing-to-live-in-a-society]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a serious thing to live in a society of possible gods and goddesses, to remember that the dullest most uninteresting person you talk to may one day be a creature which,if you say it now, you would be strongly tempted to worship, or else a horror and a corruption such as you now meet, if at all, only in a nightmare. All day long we are, in some degree helping each other to one or the other of these destinations. It is in the light of these overwhelming possibilites, it is with the awe and the circumspection proper to them, that we should conduct all of our dealings with one another, all friendships, all loves, all play, all politics. There are no ordinary people. You have never  talked to a mere mortal. nations, cultures, arts, civilizations - These are mortal, and their life is to ours as the life of a gnat. But it is immortals whom we joke with, work with, marry, snub, and exploit - immortal horrors or everlasting splendors." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
