<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/612723-deb-davis]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/612723-deb-davis" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 22:55:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24447-laughter-isn-t-even-the-other-side-of-tears-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 22:55:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24447-laughter-isn-t-even-the-other-side-of-tears-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Laughter isn't even the other side of tears. It is tears turned inside out. Truly the suffering is great, here on earth. We blunder along, shredded by our mistakes, bludgeoned by our faults. Not having a clue where the dark path leads us. But on the whole, we stumble along bravely, don't you think?" -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 22:52:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 22:52:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 22:52:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198-i-am-so-clever-that-sometimes-i-don-t-understand-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 23:55:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198-i-am-so-clever-that-sometimes-i-don-t-understand-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am so clever that sometimes I don't understand a single word of what I am saying." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 23:55:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1958-whenever-i-feel-the-need-to-exercise-i-lie-down</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 23:56:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Paul   Terry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1958-whenever-i-feel-the-need-to-exercise-i-lie-down]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever I feel the need to exercise, I lie down until it goes away." -- Paul   Terry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362-if-you-don-t-stand-for-something-you-will-fall-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 23:56:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Gordon A. Eadie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362-if-you-don-t-stand-for-something-you-will-fall-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you don't stand for something you will fall for anything." -- Gordon A. Eadie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2580-never-put-off-till-tomorrow-what-may-be-done-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 23:57:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2580-never-put-off-till-tomorrow-what-may-be-done-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never put off till tomorrow what may be done day after tomorrow just as well&quot;. 

From: &quot;More Maxims of Mark" -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder-and-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 23:57:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Miss Piggy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder-and-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beauty is in the eye of the beholder and it may be necessary from time to time to give a stupid or misinformed beholder a black eye." -- Miss Piggy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16949-a-friend-is-someone-who-knows-all-about-you-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 23:57:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16949-a-friend-is-someone-who-knows-all-about-you-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A friend is someone who knows all about you and still loves you." -- Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11090-the-truth-will-set-you-free-but-first-it-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 23:58:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Gloria Steinem]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11090-the-truth-will-set-you-free-but-first-it-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth will set you free, but first it will piss you off." -- Gloria Steinem]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17452-let-children-read-whatever-they-want-and-then-talk-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 23:59:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Judy Blume]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17452-let-children-read-whatever-they-want-and-then-talk-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let children read whatever they want and then talk about it with them. If parents and kids can talk together, we won't have as much censorship because we won't have as much fear." -- Judy Blume]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18115-those-who-deny-freedom-to-others-deserve-it-not-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 00:00:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18115-those-who-deny-freedom-to-others-deserve-it-not-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who deny freedom to others deserve it not for themselves." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108645-f-reedom-isn-t-free-it-shouldn-t-be-a-bragging-point-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 00:01:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Bill Maher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108645-f-reedom-isn-t-free-it-shouldn-t-be-a-bragging-point-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[F]reedom isn't free. It shouldn't be a bragging point that &quot;Oh, I don't get involved in politics,&quot; as if that makes you somehow cleaner.  No, that makes you derelict of duty in a republic.  Liars and panderers in government would have a much harder time of it if so many people didn't insist on their right to remain ignorant and blindly agreeable." -- Bill Maher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6356-many-of-us-are-slaves-to-our-minds-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 22:50:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Sakyong Mipham Rinpoche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6356-many-of-us-are-slaves-to-our-minds-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[" Many of us are slaves to our minds. Our own mind is our worst enemy. We try to focus, and our mind wanders off. We try to keep stress at bay, but anxiety keeps us awake at night. We try to be good to the people we love, but then we forget them and put ourselves first. And when we want to change our life, we dive into spiritual practice and expect quick results, only to lose focus after the honeymoon has worn off. We return to our state of bewilderment. We're left feeling helpless and discouraged. It seems we all agree that training the body through exercise, diet, and relaxation is a good idea, but why don't we think about training our minds?" -- Sakyong Mipham Rinpoche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112407-exercise-is-a-dirty-word-every-time-i-hear-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 22:50:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Charles Schulz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112407-exercise-is-a-dirty-word-every-time-i-hear-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Exercise is a dirty word. Every time I hear it  I wash my mouth out with chocolate." -- Charles Schulz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20743-buy-or-borrow-self-improvement-books-but-don-t-read-them-stack</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 19:20:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by SARK]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20743-buy-or-borrow-self-improvement-books-but-don-t-read-them-stack]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Buy or borrow self-improvement books, but don't read them.  Stack them around your bedroom and use them as places to rest bowls of cookies.

Watch exercise shows on television, but don't do the exercises.  Practice believing that the benefit lies in imagining yourself doing the exercises.

Don't power walk.  Saunter slowly in the sun, eating chocolate, and carry a blanket so you can take a nap." -- SARK]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3661-there-is-always-something-to-do-there-are-hungry-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 19:26:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Nikki Giovanni]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3661-there-is-always-something-to-do-there-are-hungry-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is always something to do. There are hungry people to feed, naked people to clothe, sick people to comfort and make well. And while I don't expect you to save the world I do think it's not asking too much for you to love those with whom you sleep, share the happiness of those whom you call friend, engage those among you who are visionary and remove from your life those who offer you depression, despair and disrespect." -- Nikki Giovanni]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2125-did-you-ever-want-to-set-someone-s-head-on-fire</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 19:27:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Warren Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2125-did-you-ever-want-to-set-someone-s-head-on-fire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did you ever want to set someone's head on fire, just to see what it looked like? Did you ever stand in the street and think to yourself, I could make that nun go blind just by giving her a kiss? Did you ever lay out plans for stitching babies and stray cats into a Perfect New Human? Did you ever stand naked surrounded by people who want your gleaming sperm, squirting frankincense, soma and testosterone from every pore? If so, then you're the bastard who stole my drugs Friday night. And I'll find you. Oh, yes." -- Warren Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126310-there-was-a-time-when-i-liked-a-good-riot</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 19:27:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Warren Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126310-there-was-a-time-when-i-liked-a-good-riot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was a time when I liked a good riot. Put on some heavy old street clothes that could stand a bit of sidewalk-scraping, infect myself with something good and contagious, then go out and stamp on some cops. It was great, being nine years old. " -- Warren Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2658-happiness-is-when-what-you-think-what-you-say-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 19:29:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2658-happiness-is-when-what-you-think-what-you-say-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is when what you think, what you say, and what you do are in harmony." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1066-i-don-t-want-to-achieve-immortality-through-my-work-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 19:34:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Woody Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1066-i-don-t-want-to-achieve-immortality-through-my-work-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't want to achieve immortality through my work; I want to achieve immortality through not dying. I don't want to live on in the hearts of my countrymen; I want to live on in my apartment." -- Woody Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33463-when-love-beckons-to-you-follow-him-though-his-ways</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 20:06:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33463-when-love-beckons-to-you-follow-him-though-his-ways]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When love beckons to you follow him, Though his ways are hard and steep. And when his wings enfold you yield to him, Though the sword hidden among his pinions may wound you. And when he speaks to you believe in him, Though his voice may shatter your dreams as the north wind lays waste the garden. For even as love crowns you so shall he crucify you. Even as he is for your growth so is he for your pruning. Even as he ascends to your height and caresses your tenderest branches that quiver in the sun, So shall he descend to your roots and shake them in their clinging to the earth......

But if in your fear you would seek only love's peace and love's pleasure, Then it is better for you that you cover your nakedness and pass out of love's threshing-floor, Into the seasonless world where you shall laugh, but not all of your laughter, and weep, but not all of your tears. Love gives naught but itself and takes naught but from itself.

Love possesses not nor would it be possessed; For love is sufficient unto love. And think not you can direct the course of love, if it finds you worthy, directs your course. Love has no other desire but to fulfil itself.&quot;

But if you love and must needs have desires, let these be your desires: To melt and be like a running brook that sings its melody to the night. To know the pain of too much tenderness. To be wounded by your own understanding of love; And to bleed willingly and joyfully." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115825-your-children-are-not-your-children-they-are-sons-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 20:07:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115825-your-children-are-not-your-children-they-are-sons-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your children are not your children.
They are sons and daughters of Life's longing for itself.  
They come through you but not from you.
And though they are with you yet they belong not to you.

You may give them your love but not your thoughts,
For they have their own thoughts.
You may house their bodies but not their souls,
For thir souls dwell in the house of tomorrow, which you cannot visit, not even in your dreams.
You may strive to be like them, but seek not to make them like you.
For life goes not backward nor tarries with yesterday.
You are the bows from which your children as living arrows are sent forth.
The archer sees the make upon the path of the infinite, and He bends you with His might that His arrows may go swift and far.
Let your bending in the archer's hand be for gladness.
For even as He loves the arrow that flies, so He also loves the bow that is stable." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48994-i-don-t-know-i-imagine-good-teaching-as-a-circle</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 22:50:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48994-i-don-t-know-i-imagine-good-teaching-as-a-circle]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know. I imagine good teaching as a circle of earnest people sitting down to ask each other meaningful questions. I don't see it as a handing down of answers..." -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/351226-expect-nothing-live-frugally-on-surprise</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 22:48:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/351226-expect-nothing-live-frugally-on-surprise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Expect nothing. Live frugally on surprise" -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230437-be-nobody-s-darling-be-an-outcast-take-the-contradictions-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 22:48:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230437-be-nobody-s-darling-be-an-outcast-take-the-contradictions-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be nobody's darling; 
Be an outcast. 
Take the contradictions 
Of your life 
And wrap around 
You like a shawl, 
To parry stones 
To keep you warm. 

Watch the people succumb 
To madness 
With ample cheer; 
Let them look askance at you 
And you askance reply. 

Be an outcast; 
Be pleased to walk alone 
(Uncool) 
Or line the crowded 
River beds 
With other impetuous 
Fools. 

Make a merry gathering 
On the bank 
Where thousands perished 
For brave hurt words 
They said. 

Be nobody's darling; 
Be an outcast. 
Qualified to live 
Among your dead." -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58609-the-woman-i-was-yesterday-introduced-me-to-the-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 23:25:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Poetic Evolution]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58609-the-woman-i-was-yesterday-introduced-me-to-the-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The woman I was yesterday, introduced me to the woman I am today; which makes me very excited about meeting the woman I will become tomorrow. " -- Poetic Evolution]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55536-no-wonder-these-people-don-t-believe-in-evolution-it-obviously</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 23:26:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Jeri Smith-Ready]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55536-no-wonder-these-people-don-t-believe-in-evolution-it-obviously]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No wonder these people don’t believe in evolution. It obviously hasn’t worked in their favor." -- Jeri Smith-Ready]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
