<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/61274-neil]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/61274-neil" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 10:14:33 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177007-there-are-three-things-all-wise-men-fear-the-sea</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 10:14:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177007-there-are-three-things-all-wise-men-fear-the-sea]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are three things all wise men fear: the sea in storm, a night with no moon, and the anger of a gentle man." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20603-it-s-like-everyone-tells-a-story-about-themselves-inside-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 10:13:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20603-it-s-like-everyone-tells-a-story-about-themselves-inside-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's like everyone tells a story about themselves inside their own head. Always. All the time. That story makes you what you are. We build ourselves out of that story." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28266-words-are-pale-shadows-of-forgotten-names-as-names-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 10:13:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28266-words-are-pale-shadows-of-forgotten-names-as-names-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Words are pale shadows of forgotten names. As names have power, words have power. Words can light fires in the minds of men. Words can wring tears from the hardest hearts." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350254-it-had-flaws-but-what-does-that-matter-when-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 10:44:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350254-it-had-flaws-but-what-does-that-matter-when-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It had flaws, but what does that matter when it comes to matters of the heart? We love what we love. Reason does not enter into it. In many ways, unwise love is the truest love. Anyone can love a thing &lt;i&gt;because&lt;/i&gt;. That's as easy as putting a penny in your pocket. But to love something &lt;i&gt;despite&lt;/i&gt;. To know the flaws and love them too. That is rare and pure and perfect." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116152-i-have-stolen-princesses-back-from-sleeping-barrow-kings-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 10:44:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116152-i-have-stolen-princesses-back-from-sleeping-barrow-kings-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have stolen princesses back from sleeping barrow kings. I burned down the town of Trebon. I have spent the night with Felurian and left with both my sanity and my life. I was expelled from the University at a younger age than most people are allowed in. I tread paths by moonlight that others fear to speak of during day. I have talked to gods, loved women, and written songs that make the minstrels weep. You may have heard of me." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358455-half-of-seeming-clever-is-keeping-your-mouth-shut-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 10:46:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358455-half-of-seeming-clever-is-keeping-your-mouth-shut-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Half of seeming clever is keeping your mouth shut at the right times." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350346-you-can-divide-infinity-an-infinite-number-of-times-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 10:47:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350346-you-can-divide-infinity-an-infinite-number-of-times-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can divide infinity an infinite number of times, and the resulting pieces will still be infinitely large,” Uresh said in his odd Lenatti accent. “But if you divide a non-infinite number an infinite number of times the resulting pieces are non-infinitely small. Since they are non-infinitely small, but there are an infinite number of them, if you add them back together, their sum is infinite. This implies any number is, in fact, infinite.”
“Wow,” Elodin said after a long pause. He leveled a serious finger at the Lenatti man. “Uresh. Your next assignment is to have sex. If you do not know how to do this, see me after class." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112296-chronicler-shook-his-head-and-bast-gave-a-frustrated-sigh</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 10:48:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112296-chronicler-shook-his-head-and-bast-gave-a-frustrated-sigh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chronicler shook his head and Bast gave a frustrated sigh. &quot;How about plays? Have you seen &lt;i&gt;The Ghost and the Goosegirl&lt;/i&gt; or &lt;i&gt;The Ha'penny King&lt;/i&gt;?&quot;
Chronicler frowned. &quot;Is that the one where the king sells his crown to an orphan boy?&quot;
Bast nodded. &quot;And the boy becomes a better king than the original. The goosegirl dresses like a countess and everyone is stunned by her grace and charm.&quot; He hesitated, struggling to find the words he wanted. &quot;You see, there's a fundamental connection between &lt;i&gt;seeming&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;being&lt;/i&gt;. Every Fae child knows this, but you mortals never seem to see. We understand how dangerous a mask can be. We all become what we pretend to be.&quot;
Chronicler relaxed a bit, sensing familiar ground. &quot;That's basic psychology. You dress a beggar in fine clothes, people treat him like a noble, and he lives up to their expectations.&quot;
&quot;That's only the smallest piece of it,&quot; Bast said. &quot;The truth is deeper than that. It's...&quot; Bast floundered for a moment. &quot;It's like everyone tells a story about themselves inside their own head. Always. All the time. That story makes you what you are. We build ourselves out of that story.&quot;
Frowning, Chronicler opened his mouth, but Bast held up a hand to stop him. &quot;No, listen. I've got it now. You meet a girl: shy, unassuming. If you tell her she's beautiful, she'll think you're sweet, but she won't believe you. She knows that beauty lies in your beholding.&quot; Bast gave a grudging shrug. &quot;And sometimes that's enough.&quot;
His eyes brightened. &quot;But there's a better way. You &lt;i&gt;show&lt;/i&gt; her she is beautiful. You make mirrors of your eyes, prayers of your hands against her body. It is hard, very hard, but when she truly believes you...&quot; Bast gestured excitedly. &quot;Suddenly the story she tells herself in her own head changes. She transforms. She isn't &lt;i&gt;seen as beautiful&lt;/i&gt;. She is &lt;i&gt;beautiful, seen&lt;/i&gt;.&quot;
&quot;What the hell is that supposed to mean?&quot; Chronicler snapped. &quot;You're just spouting nonsense now.&quot;
&quot;I'm spouting too much sense for you to understand,&quot; Bast said testily. &quot;But you're close enough to see my point." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350228-how-about-this-simmon-asked-me-which-is-worse-stealing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 10:49:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350228-how-about-this-simmon-asked-me-which-is-worse-stealing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How about this?' Simmon asked me. &quot;Which is worse, stealing a pie or killing Ambrose?&quot;
I gave it a moment's hard thought. &quot;A meat pie, or a fruit pie?" -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259947-only-priests-and-fools-are-fearless-and-i-ve-never-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 10:49:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259947-only-priests-and-fools-are-fearless-and-i-ve-never-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only priests and fools are fearless and I've never been on the best of terms with God." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/354460-i-ve-waited-a-long-time-to-show-these-flowers-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 10:50:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/354460-i-ve-waited-a-long-time-to-show-these-flowers-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've waited a long time to show these flowers how pretty you are." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/351749-you-never-do-things-the-easy-way-do-you-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 10:51:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/351749-you-never-do-things-the-easy-way-do-you-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You never do things the easy way, do you?&quot; she said.
&quot;There's an easy way?&quot; I asked." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169923-go-out-in-the-early-days-of-winter-after-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 10:53:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169923-go-out-in-the-early-days-of-winter-after-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Go out in the early days of winter, after the first cold snap of the season. Find a pool of water with a sheet of ice across the top, still fresh and new and clear as glass. Near the shore the ice will hold you. Slide out farther. Farther. Eventually you'll find the place where the surface just barely bears your weight. There you will feel what I felt. The ice splinters under your feet. Look down and you can see the white cracks darting through the ice like mad, elaborate spiderwebs. It is perfectly silent, but you can feel the sudden sharp vibrations through the bottoms of your feet.
That is what happened when Denna smiled at me." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/348284-the-best-lies-about-me-are-the-ones-i-told</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 10:55:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/348284-the-best-lies-about-me-are-the-ones-i-told]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best lies about me are the ones &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; told." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350230-ambrose-your-presence-is-the-horseshit-frosting-on-the-horseshit</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 10:55:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350230-ambrose-your-presence-is-the-horseshit-frosting-on-the-horseshit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ambrose, your presence is the horseshit frosting on the horseshit cake that is the admissions interview process." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350295-the-second-was-some-rather-bad-poetry-but-it-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 12:13:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350295-the-second-was-some-rather-bad-poetry-but-it-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The second was some rather bad poetry, but it was short, and I forced my way through by gritting my teeth and occasionally closing one eye so as not to damage the entirety of my brain." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218156-i-like-your-manly-bravado-she-said-do-it-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 12:15:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218156-i-like-your-manly-bravado-she-said-do-it-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like your manly bravado,&quot; she said. &quot;Do it some more." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313926-it-doesn-t-eat-meat-i-said-it-s-a-herbivore-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 12:14:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313926-it-doesn-t-eat-meat-i-said-it-s-a-herbivore-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't eat meat.&quot; I said. &quot;It's a herbivore. It's like a big cow.&quot;
Denna looked at me and started to laugh. Not hysterical laughter, but the helpless laughter of someone who's just heard something so funny they can't help but bubble over with it. She put her hands over her mouth and shook with it, the only sound was a low huffing that escaped through her fingers.
There was another flash of blue fire from below. Denna froze midlaugh, then took her hands away from her mouth. She looked at me, her eyes wide, and spoke softly with a slight quaver in her voice, &quot;Mooooo." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350877-i-walked-across-the-polished-marble-floor-and-sat-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 13:24:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350877-i-walked-across-the-polished-marble-floor-and-sat-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I walked across the polished marble floor and sat on a red velvet lounging couch. I idly wondered how exactly one was supposed to lounge. I couldn't remember ever doing it myself. After a moment's consideration, I decided lounging was probably similar to relaxing, but with more money in your pocket." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371030-what-do-you-know-of-poetry-ambrose-said-without-bothering</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 13:28:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Neil add a quote by Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371030-what-do-you-know-of-poetry-ambrose-said-without-bothering]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What do you know of poetry?” Ambrose said without bothering to turn around. “I know a limping verse when I hear it,” I said. “But this isn’t even limping. A limp has rhythm. This is more like someone falling down a set of stairs. Uneven stairs. With a midden at the bottom.” “It is a sprung rhythm,” he said, his voice stiff and offended. “I wouldn’t expect you to understand.” “Sprung?” I burst out with an incredulous laugh. “I understand that if I saw a horse with a leg this badly ‘sprung,’ I’d kill it out of mercy, then burn its poor corpse for fear the local dogs might gnaw on it and die." -- Patrick Rothfuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
