<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/613281-timothy-j]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/613281-timothy-j" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 19:37:35 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420417-it-is-hard-for-people-who-have-not-lived-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 19:37:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420417-it-is-hard-for-people-who-have-not-lived-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is hard for people who have not lived in Los Angeles to realize how radically the Santa Ana figures in the local imagination. The city burning is Los Angeles's deepest image of itself; Nathanael West perceived that, in The Day of the Locust; and at the time of the 1965 Watts riots what struck the imagination most indelibly were the fires.  For days one could drive the Harbor Freeway and see the city on fire, just as we had always known it would be in the end. Los Angeles weather is the weather of catastrophe, of apocalypse, and, just as the reliably long and bitter winters of New England determine the way life is lived there, so the violence and the unpredictability of the Santa Ana affect the entire quality of life in Los Angeles, accentuate its impermanence, its unreliability. The wind shows us how close to the edge we are." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512991-new-people-could-be-seen-by-people-like-my-grandfather</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 19:42:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512991-new-people-could-be-seen-by-people-like-my-grandfather]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["New people could be seen, by people like my grandfather, as indifferent to everything that had made California work, but the ambiguity was this: new people were also who were making California rich." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151692-california-is-a-place-in-which-a-boom-mentality-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 19:48:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151692-california-is-a-place-in-which-a-boom-mentality-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["California is a place in which a boom mentality and a sense of Chekhovian loss meet in uneasy suspension; in which the mind is troubled by some buried but ineradicable suspicion that things better work here, because here, beneath the immense bleached sky,is where we run out of continent." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/368894-psycholinguists-argue-about-whether-language-reflects-our-perception-of-reality</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 20:12:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Timothy add a quote by Hal Herzog]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/368894-psycholinguists-argue-about-whether-language-reflects-our-perception-of-reality]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Psycholinguists argue about whether language reflects our perception of reality or helps create them. I am in the latter camp. Take the names we give the animals we eat. The Patagonian toothfish is a prehistoric-looking creature with teeth like needles and bulging yellowish eyes that lives in deep waters off the coast of South America. It did not catch on with sophisticated foodies until an enterprising Los Angeles importer renamed it the considerably more palatable &quot;Chilean sea bass." -- Hal Herzog]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
