<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/61395-oliver]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/61395-oliver" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 19:58:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305878-there-is-a-quality-even-meaner-than-outright-ugliness-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 19:58:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oliver add a quote by Jane Jacobs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305878-there-is-a-quality-even-meaner-than-outright-ugliness-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a quality even meaner than outright ugliness or disorder, and this meaner quality is the dishonest mask of pretended order, achieved by ignoring or suppressing the real order that is struggling to exist and to be served." -- Jane Jacobs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1107001-it-pointed-to-an-alternative-approach-a-negative-path-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 15:00:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oliver add a quote by Oliver Burkeman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1107001-it-pointed-to-an-alternative-approach-a-negative-path-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...it pointed to an alternative approach, a ‘negative path’ to happiness, that entailed taking a radically different stance towards those things that most of us spend our lives trying to avoid. It involved learning to enjoy uncertainty, embracing insecurity, stopping trying to think positively, becoming familiar with failure, even learning to value death. In short, all these people seemed to agree that in order to be truly happy, we might actually need to be willing to experience more negative emotions—or, at the very least to learn to stop running quite so hard from them." -- Oliver Burkeman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1107008-but-sometimes-you-simply-can-t-make-yourself-feel-like-acting</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 15:02:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oliver add a quote by Oliver Burkeman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1107008-but-sometimes-you-simply-can-t-make-yourself-feel-like-acting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But sometimes you simply can't make yourself feel like acting. And in those situations, motivational advice risks making things worse, by surreptitiously strengthening your belief that you need to feel motivated before you act. By encouraging an attachment to a particular emotional state, it actually inserts an additional hurdle between you and your goal. The subtext is that if you can't make yourself feel excited and pleased about getting down to work, then you can't get down to work." -- Oliver Burkeman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1107046-who-says-you-need-to-wait-until-you-feel-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 15:11:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oliver add a quote by Oliver Burkeman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1107046-who-says-you-need-to-wait-until-you-feel-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who says you need to wait until you 'feel like' doing something in order to start doing it? The problem, from this perspective, isn't that you don't feel motivated; it's that you imagine you need to feel motivated. If you can regard your thoughts and emotions about whatever you're procrastinating on as passing weather, you'll realise that your reluctance about working isn't something that needs to be eradicated or transformed into positivity. You can coexist with it. You can note the procrastinatory feelings and act anyway." -- Oliver Burkeman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
