<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/615358-joe]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/615358-joe" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 16:19:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118450-there-are-some-upon-this-earth-of-yours-returned-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 16:19:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118450-there-are-some-upon-this-earth-of-yours-returned-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are some upon this earth of yours,' returned the Spirit, 'who lay claim to know us, and who do their deeds of passion, pride, ill-will, hatred, envy, bigotry, and selfishness in our name; who are as strange to us and all our kith and kin, as if they had never lived.  Remember that, and charge their doings on themselves, not us." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76761-it-s-possible-this-whole-why-do-latinos-love-morrisey-question</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 16:19:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76761-it-s-possible-this-whole-why-do-latinos-love-morrisey-question]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's possible this whole &quot;Why do Latinos love Morrisey?&quot; question will haunt us forever. Fortunately, Canadian academics are on the case." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269440-trust-your-luck-taran-wanderer-but-don-t-forget-to-put</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 16:19:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Lloyd Alexander]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269440-trust-your-luck-taran-wanderer-but-don-t-forget-to-put]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Trust your luck, Taran Wanderer. But don't forget to put out your nets!" -- Lloyd Alexander]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361931-a-real-friendship-ought-to-introduce-each-person-to-unexpected</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 22:05:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Jaron Lanier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361931-a-real-friendship-ought-to-introduce-each-person-to-unexpected]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A real friendship ought to introduce each person to unexpected weirdness in the other." -- Jaron Lanier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135836-you-have-some-queer-friends-dorothy-she-said-the-queerness</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 13:47:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by L. Frank Baum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135836-you-have-some-queer-friends-dorothy-she-said-the-queerness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have some queer friends, Dorothy,' she said.

The queerness doesn't matter, so long as they're friends,' was the answer" -- L. Frank Baum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116423-in-the-newspapers-the-row-about-the-prospect-of-genetically</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2008 14:17:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Rose Prince]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116423-in-the-newspapers-the-row-about-the-prospect-of-genetically]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the newspapers the row about the prospect of genetically modified food raged on, and yet here were consumers effectively demanding lambs with four back legs." -- Rose Prince]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919-the-man-who-does-not-read-has-no-advantage-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2008 07:35:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919-the-man-who-does-not-read-has-no-advantage-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who does not read has no advantage over the man who cannot read." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72385-it-struck-him-that-the-truly-characteristic-thing-about-modern</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 22:06:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72385-it-struck-him-that-the-truly-characteristic-thing-about-modern]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It struck him that the truly characteristic thing about modern life was not its cruelty and insecurity, but simply its bareness, its dinginess, its listlessness. Life, if you looked about you, bore no resemblance not only to the lies that streamed out of the telescreens, but even to the ideals that the party was trying to achieve." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131295-it-s-frustrating-to-witness-how-popular-fairtrade-bananas-coffee-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 08:27:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Rose Prince]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131295-it-s-frustrating-to-witness-how-popular-fairtrade-bananas-coffee-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's frustrating to witness how popular Fairtrade bananas, coffee and tea have become with shoppers and supermarkets while plenty of unfair trade goes on, largely unnoticed, in our own back yard." -- Rose Prince]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215314-library-stacks-from-this-perspective-are-not-a-repository-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 20:25:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Kenneth A. Bruffee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215314-library-stacks-from-this-perspective-are-not-a-repository-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Library stacks from this perspective are not a repository; they are a crowd." -- Kenneth A. Bruffee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369111-a-digital-sound-sample-in-angry-rap-doesn-t-correspond-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 16:48:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Jaron Lanier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369111-a-digital-sound-sample-in-angry-rap-doesn-t-correspond-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A digital sound sample in angry rap doesn't correspond to the graffiti but the wall." -- Jaron Lanier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/376679-nothing-save-the-hangman-s-noose-concentrates-the-mind-like-piles</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 16:48:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Tim Wu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/376679-nothing-save-the-hangman-s-noose-concentrates-the-mind-like-piles]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing, save the hangman's noose, concentrates the mind like piles of cash." -- Tim Wu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248324-problems-may-be-solved-in-the-study-which-have-baffled</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 15:06:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Arthur Conan Doyle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248324-problems-may-be-solved-in-the-study-which-have-baffled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Problems may be solved in the study which have baffled all those who have sought a solution by the aid of their senses. To carry the art, however, to its highest pitch, it is necessary that the reasoner should be able to use all the facts which have come to his knowledge; and this in itself implies, as you will readily see, a possession of all knowledge, which, even in these days of free education and encyclopaedias, is a somewhat rare accomplishment." -- Arthur Conan Doyle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44710-a-man-should-keep-his-little-brain-attic-stocked-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 16:19:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Arthur Conan Doyle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44710-a-man-should-keep-his-little-brain-attic-stocked-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man should keep his little brain attic stocked with all the furniture that he is likely to use, and the rest he can put away in the lumber room of his library, where he can get it if he wants it." -- Arthur Conan Doyle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 06:10:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29960-he-knew-everything-there-was-to-know-about-literature-except</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 06:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29960-he-knew-everything-there-was-to-know-about-literature-except]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He knew everything there was to know about literature, except how to enjoy it" -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406263-shulman-argues-that-work-that-is-valued-is-work-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2011 12:22:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Charles E. Glassick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406263-shulman-argues-that-work-that-is-valued-is-work-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Shulman argues that work that is valued is work that is presented to colleagues. The failure to make this kind of wider connection weakens the sense of community. This happens in scholarly life when such essential functions as professional service or teaching do not get discussed openly or often enough." -- Charles E. Glassick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442282-learning-often-means-changing-the-game-board-not-just-learning</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 16:32:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by David N. Perkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442282-learning-often-means-changing-the-game-board-not-just-learning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Learning often means changing the game board, not just learning fancier strategies on the same board with the same pieces." -- David N. Perkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/724222-culpable-obtuseness-he-should-know-better-that-s-one-reason-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 16:47:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Geoffrey Nunberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/724222-culpable-obtuseness-he-should-know-better-that-s-one-reason-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Culpable obtuseness. He should know better. That's one reason why we don't use the a-word, for example, of little children. They can merit the s-word, because there's a malignity that's innate in little kids sometimes, but you can't merit the a-word until you're old enough so that you ought to know better." -- Geoffrey Nunberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/569280-it-was-a-bland-tranquilized-life-adjusted-group-integrated-sort-of-face</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 16:32:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by H. Beam Piper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/569280-it-was-a-bland-tranquilized-life-adjusted-group-integrated-sort-of-face]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was a bland, tranquilized, life-adjusted, group-integrated sort of face -- the face turned out in thousands of copies every year by the educational production lines on Terra." -- H. Beam Piper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446012-assessment-in-this-spirit-does-not-concern-assignment-of-grades</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2011 07:05:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by David N. Perkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446012-assessment-in-this-spirit-does-not-concern-assignment-of-grades]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Assessment in this spirit does not concern assignment of grades or evaluation of whether instruction was effective. It's assessment designed squarely to feed into the learning process and make the learning stronger." -- David N. Perkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15124-the-state-can-t-give-you-freedom-and-the-state-can-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 13:12:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Utah Phillips]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15124-the-state-can-t-give-you-freedom-and-the-state-can-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The state can't give you freedom, and the state can't take it away. You're
born with it, like your eyes, like your ears. Freedom is something you
assume, then you wait for someone to try to take it away. The degree to
which you resist is the degree to which you are free..." -- Utah Phillips]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/450847-one-never-knows-when-one-is-going-to-get-ambushed</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 13:35:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by David N. Perkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/450847-one-never-knows-when-one-is-going-to-get-ambushed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One never knows when one is going to get ambushed into learning something." -- David N. Perkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/490592-one-of-the-most-useful-pieces-of-advice-we-ve-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 17:46:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Bill Kovach]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/490592-one-of-the-most-useful-pieces-of-advice-we-ve-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the most useful pieces of advice we've learned in our journalism careers is summed up in the phrase &quot;beware the fallacy of evil men." -- Bill Kovach]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/545992-a-dean-is-the-conductor-of-an-orchestra-made-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2012 04:10:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Mark William Roche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/545992-a-dean-is-the-conductor-of-an-orchestra-made-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A dean is the conductor of an orchestra made up entirely of composers." -- Mark William Roche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/567664-take-a-drink-because-you-pity-yourself-and-then-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2012 17:19:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by H. Beam Piper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/567664-take-a-drink-because-you-pity-yourself-and-then-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Take a drink because you pity yourself, and then the drink pities you and has a drink, and then two good drinks get together and that calls for drinks all around." -- H. Beam Piper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79031-you-live-but-once-you-might-as-well-be-amusing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 20:00:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Coco Chanel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79031-you-live-but-once-you-might-as-well-be-amusing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You live but once; you might as well be amusing." -- Coco Chanel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283628-english-is-the-product-of-a-saxon-warrior-trying-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 05:14:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by H. Beam Piper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283628-english-is-the-product-of-a-saxon-warrior-trying-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["English is the product of a Saxon warrior trying to make a date with an Angle bar-maid, and as such is no more legitimate than any of the other products of that conversation." -- H. Beam Piper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84171-critics-who-treat-adult-as-a-term-of-approval-instead</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 04:58:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84171-critics-who-treat-adult-as-a-term-of-approval-instead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Critics who treat 'adult' as a term of approval, instead of as a merely descriptive term, cannot be adult themselves. To be concerned about being grown up, to admire the grown up because it is grown up, to blush at the suspicion of being childish; these things are the marks of childhood and adolescence. And in childhood and adolescence they are, in moderation, healthy symptoms. Young things ought to want to grow. But to carry on into middle life or even into early manhood this concern about being adult is a mark of really arrested development. When I was ten, I read fairy tales in secret and would have been ashamed if I had been found doing so. Now that I am fifty I read them openly. When I became a man I put away childish things, including the fear of childishness and the desire to be very grown up." -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/721910-the-neighbor-s-flock-has-taken-advantage-of-the-chaos-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 16:46:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Jeanne Marie Laskas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/721910-the-neighbor-s-flock-has-taken-advantage-of-the-chaos-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The neighbor's flock has taken advantage of the chaos, and I think that's pretty smart." -- Jeanne Marie Laskas]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
