<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/61593-brian]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/61593-brian" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 10:46:37 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1007704-we-have-art-in-order-not-to-die-from-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 10:46:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1007704-we-have-art-in-order-not-to-die-from-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have art in order not to die from the truth. —NIETZSCHE" -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/999324-you-can-look-at-a-picture-for-a-week-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 14:21:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/999324-you-can-look-at-a-picture-for-a-week-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can look at a picture for a week and never think of it again. You can also look at a picture for a second and think of it all your life" -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1021800-you-sound-like-my-dad-well-let-s-put-it-another-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 11:31:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1021800-you-sound-like-my-dad-well-let-s-put-it-another-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You sound like my dad.” “Well—let’s put it another way. Who was it said that coincidence was just God’s way of remaining anonymous?” “Now you really sound like my dad.” “Who’s to say that gamblers don’t really understand it better than anyone else? Isn’t everything worthwhile a gamble? Can’t good come around sometimes through some strange back doors?" -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1021804-white-noise-impersonal-roar-deadening-incandescence-of-the-boarding-terminals</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 11:38:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1021804-white-noise-impersonal-roar-deadening-incandescence-of-the-boarding-terminals]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["White noise, impersonal roar. Deadening incandescence of the boarding terminals. But even these soul-free, sealed-off places are drenched with meaning, spangled and thundering with it. Sky Mall. Portable stereo systems. Mirrored isles of Drambuie and Tanqueray and Chanel No. 5. I look at the blanked-out faces of the other passengers—hoisting their briefcases, their backpacks, shuffling to disembark—and I think of what Hobie said: beauty alters the grain of reality. And I keep thinking too of the more conventional wisdom: namely, that the pursuit of pure beauty is a trap, a fast track to bitterness and sorrow, that beauty has to be wedded to something more meaningful. Only what is that thing? Why am I made the way I am? Why do I care about all the wrong things, and nothing at all for the right ones? Or, to tip it another way: how can I see so clearly that everything I love or care about is illusion, and yet—for me, anyway—all that’s worth living for lies in that charm? A great sorrow, and one that I am only beginning to understand: we don’t get to choose our own hearts. We can’t make ourselves want what’s good for us or what’s good for other people. We don’t get to choose the people we are. Because—isn’t it drilled into us constantly, from childhood on, an unquestioned platitude in the culture—? From William Blake to Lady Gaga, from Rousseau to Rumi to Tosca to Mister Rogers, it’s a curiously uniform message, accepted from high to low: when in doubt, what to do? How do we know what’s right for us? Every shrink, every career counselor, every Disney princess knows the answer: “Be yourself.” “Follow your heart." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1021921-and-increasingly-i-find-myself-fixing-on-that-refusal-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 14:02:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1021921-and-increasingly-i-find-myself-fixing-on-that-refusal-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And, increasingly, I find myself fixing on that refusal to pull back. Because I don’t care what anyone says or how often or winningly they say it: no one will ever, ever be able to persuade me that life is some awesome, rewarding treat. Because, here’s the truth: life is catastrophe. The basic fact of existence—of walking around trying to feed ourselves and find friends and whatever else we do—is catastrophe. Forget all this ridiculous ‘Our Town’ nonsense everyone talks: the miracle of a newborn babe, the joy of one simple blossom, Life You Are Too Wonderful To Grasp, &amp;c. For me—and I’ll keep repeating it doggedly till I die, till I fall over on my ungrateful nihilistic face and am too weak to say it: better never born, than born into this cesspool. Sinkhole of hospital beds, coffins, and broken hearts. No release, no appeal, no “do-overs” to employ a favored phrase of Xandra’s, no way forward but age and loss, and no way out but death. [“Complaints bureau!” I remember Boris grousing as a child, one afternoon at his house when we had got off on the vaguely metaphysical subject of our mothers: why they—angels, goddesses—had to die? while our awful fathers thrived, and boozed, and sprawled, and muddled on, and continued to stumble about and wreak havoc, in seemingly indefatigable health? “They took the wrong ones! Mistake was made! Everything is unfair! Who do we complain to, in this shitty place? Who is in charge here?”] And—maybe it’s ridiculous to go on in this vein, although it doesn’t matter since no one’s ever going to see this—but does it make any sense at all to know that it ends badly for all of us, even the happiest of us, and that we all lose everything that matters in the end—and yet to know as well, despite all this, as cruelly as the game is stacked, that it’s possible to play it with a kind of joy?" -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1021923-and-as-much-as-i-d-like-to-believe-there-s-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 14:03:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1021923-and-as-much-as-i-d-like-to-believe-there-s-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And as much as I’d like to believe there’s a truth beyond illusion, I’ve come to believe that there’s no truth beyond illusion. Because, between ‘reality’ on the one hand, and the point where the mind strikes reality, there’s a middle zone, a rainbow edge where beauty comes into being, where two very different surfaces mingle and blur to provide what life does not: and this is the space where all art exists, and all magic. And—I would argue as well—all love." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1021928-whatever-teaches-us-to-talk-to-ourselves-is-important-whatever</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 14:05:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Donna Tartt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1021928-whatever-teaches-us-to-talk-to-ourselves-is-important-whatever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever teaches us to talk to ourselves is important: whatever teaches us to sing ourselves out of despair. But the painting has also taught me that we can speak to each other across time. And I feel I have something very serious and urgent to say to you, my non-existent reader, and I feel I should say it as urgently as if I were standing in the room with you. That life—whatever else it is—is short. That fate is cruel but maybe not random. That Nature (meaning Death) always wins but that doesn’t mean we have to bow and grovel to it. That maybe even if we’re not always so glad to be here, it’s our task to immerse ourselves anyway: wade straight through it, right through the cesspool, while keeping eyes and hearts open. And in the midst of our dying, as we rise from the organic and sink back ignominiously into the organic, it is a glory and a privilege to love what Death doesn’t touch. For if disaster and oblivion have followed this painting down through time—so too has love. Insofar as it is immortal (and it is) I have a small, bright, immutable part in that immortality. It exists; and it keeps on existing. And I add my own love to the history of people who have loved beautiful things, and looked out for them, and pulled them from the fire, and sought them when they were lost, and tried to preserve them and save them while passing them along literally from hand to hand, singing out brilliantly from the wreck of time to the next generation of lovers, and the next." -- Donna Tartt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1174479-it-s-stupid-there-are-maps-to-show-you-how-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 08:13:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Anthony Marra]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1174479-it-s-stupid-there-are-maps-to-show-you-how-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s stupid. There are maps to show you how to get to the place where you want to be but no maps that show you how to get to the time when you want to be." -- Anthony Marra]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1174576-sonja-stood-and-walked-to-the-flat-afraid-of-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 10:34:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Anthony Marra]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1174576-sonja-stood-and-walked-to-the-flat-afraid-of-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sonja stood and walked to the flat, afraid of what she might hear next. At the kitchen table she examined the glass of ice. Each cube was rounded by room temperature, dissolving in its own remains, and belatedly she understood that this was how a loved one disappeared. Despite the shock of walking into an empty flat, the absence isn’t immediate, more a fade from the present tense you shared, a melting into the past, not an erasure but a conversion in form, from presence to memory, from solid to liquid, and the person you once touched now runs over your skin, now in sheets down your back, and you may bathe, may sink, may drown in the memory, but your fingers cannot hold it. She raised the glass to her lips. The water was clean." -- Anthony Marra]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/734139-life-a-constellation-of-vital-phenomena-organization-irritability-movement-growth-reproduction</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 12:52:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Anthony Marra]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/734139-life-a-constellation-of-vital-phenomena-organization-irritability-movement-growth-reproduction]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life: a constellation of vital phenomena—organization, irritability, movement, growth, reproduction, adaptation." -- Anthony Marra]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1189241-the-evidence-suggested-that-many-american-parents-treated-their-children</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 12:46:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1189241-the-evidence-suggested-that-many-american-parents-treated-their-children]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The evidence suggested that many American parents treated their children as if they were delicate flowers. In one Columbia University study, 85 percent of American parents surveyed said that they thought they needed to praise their children’s intelligence in order to assure them they were smart. However, the actual research on praise suggested the opposite was true. Praise that was vague, insincere, or excessive tended to discourage kids from working hard and trying new things. It had a toxic effect, the opposite of what parents intended. To work, praise had to be specific, authentic, and rare. Yet the same culture of self-esteem boosting extended to many U.S. classrooms. In the survey of exchange students conducted for this book, about half of U.S. and international students said that American math teachers were more likely to praise their work than math teachers abroad. (Fewer than 10 percent said that their international teachers were more likely to praise.) That finding was particularly ironic, given that American students scored below average for the developed world in math. It also suggested that whatever the intent of American teachers, their praise was probably not always specific, authentic, and rare." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1189247-around-the-world-people-who-studied-parenting-usually-divided-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 12:49:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1189247-around-the-world-people-who-studied-parenting-usually-divided-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Around the world, people who studied parenting usually divided the various styles into four basic categories: Authoritarian parents were strict disciplinarians, the “because I said so” parents. Permissive parents tended to be indulgent and averse to conflict. They acted more like friends than parents. In some studies, permissive parents tended to be wealthier and more educated than other parents. Neglectful parents were just how they sounded: emotionally distant and often absent. They were also more likely to live in poverty. Then there was the fourth option: Authoritative. The word was like a mash up of authoritarian and permissive. These parents inhabited the sweet spot between the two: they were warm, responsive, and close to their kids, but, as their children got older, they gave them freedom to explore and to fail and to make their own choices. Throughout their kids’ upbringing, authoritative parents also had clear, bright limits, rules they did not negotiate. “We’re socialized to believe that warmth and strictness are opposites,” Doug Lemov writes in his book Teach Like a Champion. “The fact is, the degree to which you are warm has no bearing on the degree to which you are strict, and vice versa.” Parents and teachers who manage to be both warm and strict seem to strike a resonance with children, gaining their trust along with their respect. When researcher Jelani Mandara at Northwestern University studied 4,754 U.S. teenagers and their parents, he found that kids with authoritative parents had higher academic achievement levels, fewer symptoms of depression, and fewer problems with aggression, disobedience, and other antisocial behaviors. Other studies have found similar benefits. Authoritative parents trained their kids to be resilient, and it seemed to work." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1190400-when-we-re-talking-about-whether-or-not-a-story-s-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 12:44:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Ann VanderMeer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1190400-when-we-re-talking-about-whether-or-not-a-story-s-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we’re talking about whether or not a story’s “time travel logic” makes sense, it is important to remember that every story builds its own framework for its own logic. In that sense, time travel is more of a fantasy-based story element than a science-based one. Time travel does not exist in the real world, and any broadly accepted rules for how it can and can’t work were derived from a bunch of “that guys” talking about time travel fiction. There is no “makes sense” in the universal sense – that is to say, criticizing a time travel story because its rules do not line up with rules in the real world is akin to dismissing the Harry Potter books because the conductive properties of wood could never sustain the energy required for spell casting. Approaching a time travel story with a dogmatic measuring stick in hand also denies the unique pleasure that the genre affords tinkerers. A good story’s internal logic is flawless, and everything in between its first and last word makes sense on its own terms. In that way, it presents the tinkerer with the literary equivalent of an Escher drawing. Internally, step by step, the logic of Escher’s staircase makes (or makes you believe it makes) nefariously perfect sense, and its dissonance with what we know to be possible is not something you have to “just accept and get over to enjoy it,” but is the very source of what’s enjoyable about it." -- Ann VanderMeer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1209237-risk-as-first-articulated-by-the-economist-frank-h-knight</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 11:15:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Nate Silver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1209237-risk-as-first-articulated-by-the-economist-frank-h-knight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Risk, as first articulated by the economist Frank H. Knight in 1921,45 is something that you can put a price on. Say that you’ll win a poker hand unless your opponent draws to an inside straight: the chances of that happening are exactly 1 chance in 11.46 This is risk. It is not pleasant when you take a “bad beat” in poker, but at least you know the odds of it and can account for it ahead of time. In the long run, you’ll make a profit from your opponents making desperate draws with insufficient odds. Uncertainty, on the other hand, is risk that is hard to measure. You might have some vague awareness of the demons lurking out there. You might even be acutely concerned about them. But you have no real idea how many of them there are or when they might strike. Your back-of-the-envelope estimate might be off by a factor of 100 or by a factor of 1,000; there is no good way to know. This is uncertainty. Risk greases the wheels of a free-market economy; uncertainty grinds them to a halt." -- Nate Silver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1209239-the-alchemy-that-the-ratings-agencies-performed-was-to-spin</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 11:16:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Nate Silver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1209239-the-alchemy-that-the-ratings-agencies-performed-was-to-spin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The alchemy that the ratings agencies performed was to spin uncertainty into what looked and felt like risk. They took highly novel securities, subject to an enormous amount of systemic uncertainty, and claimed the ability to quantify just how risky they were. Not only that, but of all possible conclusions, they came to the astounding one that these investments were almost risk-free." -- Nate Silver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1216603-it-s-a-no-win-argument-that-business-of-what-we-re-born-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2014 11:56:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1216603-it-s-a-no-win-argument-that-business-of-what-we-re-born-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s a no-win argument—that business of what we’re born with and what our environment does to us. And it’s a boring argument, because it simplifies the mysteries that attend both our birth and our growth." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1224169-someone-you-love-dies-and-you-re-not-expecting-it-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 11:23:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1224169-someone-you-love-dies-and-you-re-not-expecting-it-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["someone you love dies, and you’re not expecting it, you don’t lose her all at once; you lose her in pieces over a long time—the way the mail stops coming, and her scent fades from the pillows and even from the clothes in her closet and drawers. Gradually, you accumulate the parts of her that are gone. Just when the day comes—when there’s a particular missing part that overwhelms you with the feeling that she’s gone, forever—there comes another day, and another specifically missing part." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1231806-every-american-should-be-forced-to-live-outside-the-united</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 12:48:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1231806-every-american-should-be-forced-to-live-outside-the-united]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every American should be forced to live outside the United States for a year or two. Americans should be forced to see how ridiculous they appear to the rest of the world! They should listen to someone else’s version of themselves—to anyone else’s version! Every country knows more about America than Americans know about themselves! And Americans know absolutely nothing about any other country!" -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1237040-of-all-the-wonders-that-i-yet-have-heard-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 10:51:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1237040-of-all-the-wonders-that-i-yet-have-heard-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of all the wonders that I yet have heard, It seems to me the most strange that men should fear; Seeing that death, a necessary end, Will come when it will come." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1237061-it-is-the-well-educated-who-will-improve-society-and-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 11:20:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1237061-it-is-the-well-educated-who-will-improve-society-and-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is the well educated who will improve society—and they will improve it, at first, by criticizing it, and we are giving them the tools to criticize it. Naturally, as students, the brighter of them will begin their improvements upon society by criticizing us.” To Owen, old Archie Thorndike would sing a slightly different song: “It is your responsibility to find fault with me, it is mine to hear you out. But don’t expect me to change. I’m not going to change; I’m going to retire! Get the new headmaster to make the changes; that’s when I made changes—when I was new.” “WHAT CHANGES DID YOU MAKE?” Owen Meany asked. “That’s another reason I’m retiring!” old Thorny told Owen amiably. “My memory’s shot!" -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1238096-oh-what-a-nation-of-moralists-the-americans-are-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 09:54:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1238096-oh-what-a-nation-of-moralists-the-americans-are-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh, what a nation of moralists the Americans are! With what fervor do they relish bringing their sexual misconduct to light! A pity that they do not bring their moral outrage to bear on their president’s arrogance above the law; a pity that they do not unleash their moral zest on an administration that runs guns to terrorists. But, of course, boudoir morality takes less imagination, and can be indulged in without the effort of keeping up with world affairs—or even bothering to know “the whole story” behind the sexual adventure." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1239332-from-hester-s-bedroom-even-though-the-door-was-closed-we-could-hear</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2014 09:56:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1239332-from-hester-s-bedroom-even-though-the-door-was-closed-we-could-hear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From Hester’s bedroom—even though the door was closed—we could hear her breathing; Hester’s breathing, when she’d been drinking, was something between a snore and a moan. “Why does she drink so much?” I asked Owen. “HESTER’S AHEAD OF HER TIME,” he said. “What’s that mean?” I asked him. “Do we have a generation of drunks to look forward to?” “WE HAVE A GENERATION OF PEOPLE WHO ARE ANGRY TO LOOK FORWARD TO,” Owen said. “AND MAYBE TWO GENERATIONS OF PEOPLE WHO DON’T GIVE A SHIT,” he added. “How do you know?” I asked him. “I DON’T KNOW HOW I KNOW,” said Owen Meany. “I JUST KNOW THAT I KNOW,” he said." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1214734-you-know-the-greatest-lesson-of-history-it-s-that-history</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 14:36:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Anthony Doerr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1214734-you-know-the-greatest-lesson-of-history-it-s-that-history]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know the greatest lesson of history? It’s that history is whatever the victors say it is. That’s the lesson. Whoever wins, that’s who decides the history. We act in our own self-interest. Of course we do. Name me a person or a nation who does not. The trick is figuring out where your interests are." -- Anthony Doerr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1256754-a-line-comes-back-to-marie-laure-from-jules-verne-science</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 18:20:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Anthony Doerr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1256754-a-line-comes-back-to-marie-laure-from-jules-verne-science]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A line comes back to Marie-Laure from Jules Verne: Science, my lad, is made up of mistakes, but they are mistakes which it is useful to make, because they lead little by little to the truth." -- Anthony Doerr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1259936-for-dinner-he-orders-wild-boar-cooked-with-fresh-mushrooms</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 12:03:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Anthony Doerr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1259936-for-dinner-he-orders-wild-boar-cooked-with-fresh-mushrooms]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For dinner, he orders wild boar cooked with fresh mushrooms. And a full bottle of Bordeaux. Especially during wartime, such things remain important. They are what separate the civilized man from the barbarian. The hotel is drafty and the dining room is empty, but the waiter is excellent. He pours with grace and steps away. Once in the glass, as dark as blood, the Bordeaux seems almost as though it is a living thing. Von Rumpel takes pleasure in knowing that he is the only person in the world who will have the privilege of tasting it before it is gone." -- Anthony Doerr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1260115-to-shut-your-eyes-is-to-guess-nothing-of-blindness</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 14:56:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Anthony Doerr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1260115-to-shut-your-eyes-is-to-guess-nothing-of-blindness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To shut your eyes is to guess nothing of blindness. Beneath your world of skies and faces and buildings exists a rawer and older world, a place where surface planes disintegrate and sounds ribbon in shoals through the air. Marie-Laure can sit in an attic high above the street and hear lilies rustling in marshes two miles away. She hears Americans scurry across farm fields, directing their huge cannons at the smoke of Saint-Malo; she hears families sniffling around hurricane lamps in cellars, crows hopping from pile to pile, flies landing on corpses in ditches; she hears the tamarinds shiver and the jays shriek and the dune grass burn; she feels the great granite fist, sunk deep into the earth’s crust, on which Saint-Malo sits, and the ocean teething at it from all four sides, and the outer islands holding steady against the swirling tides; she hears cows drink from stone troughs and dolphins rise through the green water of the Channel; she hears the bones of dead whales stir five leagues below, their marrow offering a century of food for cities of creatures who will live their whole lives and never once see a photon sent from the sun. She hears her snails in the grotto drag their bodies over the rocks." -- Anthony Doerr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1275744-the-1920s-was-a-great-time-for-reading-altogether-very-possibly</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 14:52:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1275744-the-1920s-was-a-great-time-for-reading-altogether-very-possibly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The 1920s was a great time for reading altogether—very possibly the peak decade for reading in American life. Soon it would be overtaken by the passive distractions of radio, but for the moment reading remained most people’s principal method for filling idle time." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5169-what-really-knocks-me-out-is-a-book-that-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 13:24:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brian add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5169-what-really-knocks-me-out-is-a-book-that-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What really knocks me out is a book that, when you're all done reading it, you wish the author that wrote it was a terrific friend of yours and you could call him up on the phone whenever you felt like it. That doesn't happen much, though." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
