<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/616302-michael-bond]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/616302-michael-bond" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 15:07:57 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/811-for-instance-on-the-planet-earth-man-had-always-assumed</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 15:07:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/811-for-instance-on-the-planet-earth-man-had-always-assumed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For instance, on the planet Earth, man had always assumed that he was more intelligent than dolphins because he had achieved so much&amp;mdash;the wheel, New York, wars and so on&amp;mdash;whilst all the dolphins had ever done was muck about in the water having a good time. But conversely, the dolphins had always believed that they were far more intelligent than man&amp;mdash;for precisely the same reasons." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14013-the-fact-that-we-live-at-the-bottom-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 15:07:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14013-the-fact-that-we-live-at-the-bottom-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fact that we live at the bottom of a deep gravity well, on the surface of a gas covered planet going around a nuclear fireball 90 million miles away and think this to be normal is obviously some indication of how skewed our perspective tends to be." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6711-a-common-mistake-that-people-make-when-trying-to-design</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 14:56:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6711-a-common-mistake-that-people-make-when-trying-to-design]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A common mistake that people make when trying to design something completely foolproof is to underestimate the ingenuity of complete fools." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39828-i-ve-come-up-with-a-set-of-rules-that-describe</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 15:00:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39828-i-ve-come-up-with-a-set-of-rules-that-describe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've come up with a set of rules that describe our reactions to technologies:
1. Anything that is in the world when you’re born is normal and ordinary and is just a natural part of the way the world works.
2. Anything that's invented between when you’re fifteen and thirty-five is new and exciting and revolutionary and you can probably get a career in it.
3. Anything invented after you're thirty-five is against the natural order of things." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49274-if-what-s-always-distinguished-bad-writing--flat-characters-a-narrative-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 11:10:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49274-if-what-s-always-distinguished-bad-writing--flat-characters-a-narrative-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If what's always distinguished bad writing--flat characters, a narrative world that's clichéd and not recognizably human, etc.--is also a description of today's world, then bad writing becomes an ingenious mimesis of a bad world. If readers simply believe the world is stupid and shallow and mean, then [Bret] Ellis can write a mean shallow stupid novel that becomes a mordant deadpan commentary on the badness of everything. Look man, we'd probably most of us agree that these are dark times, and stupid ones, but do we need fiction that does nothing but dramatize how dark and stupid everything is? In dark times, the definition of good art would seem to be art that locates and applies CPR to those elements of what's human and magical that still live and glow despite the times' darkness. Really good fiction could have as dark a worldview as it wished, but it'd find a way both to depict this world and to illuminate the possibilities for being alive and human in it.

Postmodern irony and cynicism's become an end in itself, a measure of hip sophistication and literary savvy. Few artists dare to try to talk about ways of working toward redeeming what's wrong, because they'll look sentimental and naive to all the weary ironists. Irony's gone from liberating to enslaving. There's some great essay somewhere that has a line about irony being the song of the prisoner who's come to love his cage… The postmodern founders' patricidal work was great, but patricide produces orphans, and no amount of revelry can make up for the fact that writers my age have been literary orphans throughout our formative years.

We enter a spiritual puberty where we snap to the fact that the great transcendent horror is loneliness, excluded encagement in the self. Once we’ve hit this age, we will now give or take anything, wear any mask, to fit, be part-of, not be Alone, we young. The U.S. arts are our guide to inclusion. A how-to. We are shown how to fashion masks of ennui and jaded irony at a young age where the face is fictile enough to assume the shape of whatever it wears. And then it’s stuck there, the weary cynicism that saves us from gooey sentiment and unsophisticated naïveté. Sentiment equals naïveté on this continent.

You burn with hunger for food that does not exist.

A U. S. of modern A. where the State is not a team or a code, but a sort of sloppy intersection of desires and fears, where the only public consensus a boy must surrender to is the acknowledged primacy of straight-line pursuing this flat and short-sighted idea of personal happiness." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198946-but-when-you-talk-about-nabokov-and-coover-you-re-talking</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 11:10:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198946-but-when-you-talk-about-nabokov-and-coover-you-re-talking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But when you talk about Nabokov and Coover, you’re talking about real geniuses, the writers who weathered real shock and invented this stuff in contemporary fiction. But after the pioneers always come the crank turners, the little gray people who take the machines others have built and just turn the crank, and little pellets of metafiction come out the other end. The crank-turners capitalize for a while on sheer fashion, and they get their plaudits and grants and buy their IRAs and retire to the Hamptons well out of range of the eventual blast radius. There are some interesting parallels between postmodern crank-turners and what’s happened since post-structural theory took off here in the U.S., why there’s such a big backlash against post-structuralism going on now. It’s the crank-turners fault. I think the crank-turners replaced the critic as the real angel of death as far as literary movements are concerned, now. You get some bona fide artists who come along and really divide by zero and weather some serious shit-storms of shock and ridicule in order to promulgate some really important ideas. Once they triumph, though, and their ideas become legitimate and accepted, the crank-turners and wannabes come running to the machine, and out pour the gray pellets and now the whole thing’s become a hollow form, just another institution of fashion. Take a look at some of the critical-theory Ph.D. dissertations being written now. They’re like de Man and Foucault in the mouth of a dull child. Academia and commercial culture have somehow become these gigantic mechanisms of commodification that drain the weight and color out of even the most radical new advances. It’s a surreal inversion of the death-by-neglect that used to kill off prescient art. Now prescient art suffers death-by acceptance. We love things to death, now. Then we retire to the Hamptons." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
