<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/616750-dore]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/616750-dore" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:01:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141134-maybe-the-first-time-you-saw-her-you-were-ten</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:01:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141134-maybe-the-first-time-you-saw-her-you-were-ten]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe the first time you saw her you were ten. She was standing in the sun scratching her legs. Or tracing letters in the dirt with a stick. Her hair was being pulled. Or she was pulling someone's hair. And a part of you was drawn to her, and a part of you resisted--wanting to ride off on your bicycle, kick a stone, remain uncomplicated. In the same breath you felt the strength of a man, and a self-pity that made you feel small and hurt. Part of you thought: Please don't look at me. If you don't, I can still turn away. And part of you thought: Look at me." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171455-what-about-you-are-you-happiest-and-saddest-right-now</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:01:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171455-what-about-you-are-you-happiest-and-saddest-right-now]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What about you? Are you happiest and saddest right now that you've ever been?&quot; &quot;Of course I am.&quot; &quot;Why?&quot; &quot;Because nothing makes me happier and nothing makes me sadder than you." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71213-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-who-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:01:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71213-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-who-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time there was a boy who loved a girl, and her laughter was a question he wanted to spend his whole life answering." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140506-i-want-to-say-somewhere-i-ve-tried-to-be-forgiving</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:01:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140506-i-want-to-say-somewhere-i-ve-tried-to-be-forgiving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to say somewhere: I've tried to be forgiving. And yet. There were times in my life, whole years, when anger got the better of me. Ugliness turned me inside out. There was a certain satisfaction in bitterness. I courted it. It was standing outside, and I invited it in." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3420-even-now-all-possible-feelings-do-not-yet-exist-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:01:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3420-even-now-all-possible-feelings-do-not-yet-exist-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even now, all possible feelings do not yet exist, there are still those that lie beyond our capacity and our imagination.  From time to time, when a piece of music no one has ever written or a painting no one has ever painted, or something else impossible to predict, fathom or yet describe takes place, a new feeling enters the world.  And then, for the millionth time in the history of feeling, the heart surges and absorbs the impact." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11332-at-the-end-all-that-s-left-of-you-are-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:01:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11332-at-the-end-all-that-s-left-of-you-are-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the end, all that's left of you are your possessions.  Perhaps that's why I've never been able to throw anything away.  Perhaps that's why I hoarded the world:  with the hope that when I died, the sum total of my things would suggest a life larger than the one I lived." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62558-suicide-is-just-a-moment-lexy-told-me-this-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:01:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62558-suicide-is-just-a-moment-lexy-told-me-this-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suicide is just a moment, Lexy told me. This is how she described it to me. For just a moment, it doesn't matter that you've got people who love you and the sun is shining and there's a movie coming out this weekend that you've been dying to see. It hits you all of a sudden that nothing is ever going to be okay, ever, and you kind of dare yourself. You pick up a knife and press it gently to your skin, you look out a nineteenth-story window and you think, I could just do it. I could just do it. And most of the time, you look at the height and you get scared, or you think about the poor people on the sidewalk below - what if there are kids coming home from school and they have to spend the rest of their lives trying to forget this terrible thing you're going to make them see? And the moment's over. You think about how sad it would've been if you never got to see that movie, and you look at your dog and wonder who would've taken care of her if you had gone. And you go back to normal. But you keep it there in your mind. Even if you never take yourself up on it, it gives you a kind of comfort to know that the day is yours to choose. You tuck it away in your brain like sour candy tucked in your cheek, and the puckering memory it leaves behind, the rough pleasure of running your tongue over its strange terrain, is exactly the same.... The day was hers to choose, and perhaps in that treetop moment when she looked down and saw the yard, the world, her life, spread out below her, perhaps she chose to plunge toward it headlong. Perhaps she saw before her a lifetime of walking on the ruined earth and chose instead a single moment in the air" -- Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29121-it-s-not-the-content-of-our-dreams-that-gives-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:01:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29121-it-s-not-the-content-of-our-dreams-that-gives-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not the content of our dreams that gives our second heart its dark color; it's the thoughts that go through our heads in those wakeful moments when sleep won't come. And those are the things we never tell anyone at all." -- Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63107-all-this-to-say-i-am-forty-three-years-old-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:01:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63107-all-this-to-say-i-am-forty-three-years-old-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All this to say: I am forty-three years old. I may yet live another forty. What do I do with those years? How do I fill them without Lexy? When I come to tell the story of my life, there will be a line, creased and blurred and soft with age, where she stops. If I win the lottery, if I father a child, if I lose the use of my legs, it will be after she has finished knowing me. &quot;When I get to Heaven&quot;, my grandmother used to say, widowed at thirty-nine, &quot;your grandfather won't even recognize me." -- Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95135-there-would-be-hard-times-but-what-did-i-care</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:01:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95135-there-would-be-hard-times-but-what-did-i-care]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There would be hard times, but what did I care if we had hard times? The branches of my love were wide, and they caught the rain and the snow. We would be okay, the two of us together. We would be okay." -- Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112325-because-for-most-of-us-suicide-is-a-moment-we-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:02:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112325-because-for-most-of-us-suicide-is-a-moment-we-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because for most of us, suicide is a moment we'll never choose. It's only for people like Lexy, who know they might choose eventually, who believe they have a choice to make." -- Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385744-how-can-it-be-i-wondered-that-we-can-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:02:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385744-how-can-it-be-i-wondered-that-we-can-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How can it be, I wondered, that we can be lying in bed next to a person we love wholly and helplessly, a person we love more than our own breath, and still ache to think of the one who caused us pain all those years ago?  It's the betrayal of this second heart of ours, its flesh tied off like a fingertip twined tightly round with a single hair, blue-tinged from lack of blood.  The shameful squeeze of it." -- Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95134-i-remember-my-wife-in-white-it-just-made-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:02:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95134-i-remember-my-wife-in-white-it-just-made-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I remember my wife in white.' It just made people weep to hear it...Everybody just thought it was the saddest sentence that was ever written. And it didn't matter if I never wrote another word. This one sentence had put an end to the need for any future sentences. I had said it all." -- Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129713-my-behavior-is-nonetheless-deplorable-unfortunately-i-m-quite-prone-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:03:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129713-my-behavior-is-nonetheless-deplorable-unfortunately-i-m-quite-prone-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My behavior is nonetheless, deplorable. Unfortunately, I'm quite prone to such bouts of deplorability--take for instance, my fondness for reading books at the dinner table." -- Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149738-it-s-easy-to-believe-in-something-when-you-win-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:03:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149738-it-s-easy-to-believe-in-something-when-you-win-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's easy to believe in something when you win all the time...The losses are what define a man's faith." -- Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141304-belief-isn-t-simply-a-thing-for-fair-times-and-bright</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:03:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141304-belief-isn-t-simply-a-thing-for-fair-times-and-bright]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Belief isn't simply a thing for fair times and bright days...What is belief - what is faith - if you don't continue in it after failure?...Anyone can believe in someone, or something that always succeeds...But failure...ah, now, that is hard to believe in, certainly and truly. Difficult enough to have value. Sometimes we just have to wait long enough...then we find out why exactly it was that we kept believing...There's always another secret." -- Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159795-well-vin-says-that-there-s-something-behind-all-this-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:03:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159795-well-vin-says-that-there-s-something-behind-all-this-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well Vin says that there's something behind all this, right? Some evil force of doom or whatever? Well, if I were said force of doom, then I certainly wouldn't have used my powers to turn the land black. It just lacks flair. Red. Now, that would be an interesting color. Think of the possibilities--if the ash were red, the rivers would run like blood. Black is so monotonous that you can forget about it, but red--you'd always be thinking, 'Why, look at that. That hill is red. That evil force of doom trying to destroy me certainly has style." -- Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314089-better-to-be-the-failure-who-nobly-strived-than-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:03:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314089-better-to-be-the-failure-who-nobly-strived-than-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Better to be the failure who nobly strived than the success who never really had to." -- Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84270-accept-what-you-can-not-change-change-that-which-is-unacceptable</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:04:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Jennifer Fallon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84270-accept-what-you-can-not-change-change-that-which-is-unacceptable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Accept what you can not change-change that which is unacceptable." -- Jennifer Fallon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81150-and-try-to-stay-out-of-trouble-with-the-ladies</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:04:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Jennifer Fallon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81150-and-try-to-stay-out-of-trouble-with-the-ladies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And try to stay out of trouble with the ladies. Remember, they all have fathers and brothers and some of them have armies. " -- Jennifer Fallon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81151-belagren-i-can-t-build-a-whole-religion-on-a-probablity</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:04:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Jennifer Fallon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81151-belagren-i-can-t-build-a-whole-religion-on-a-probablity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Belagren: I can't build a whole religion on a probablity, Madalan. 

Madalan: Not when sex, drugs and human sacrifices work so much better. " -- Jennifer Fallon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293306-we-don-t-have-a-god-of-bloody-stupid-ideas</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:04:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by jennifer fallon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293306-we-don-t-have-a-god-of-bloody-stupid-ideas]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["we don't have a god of bloody stupid ideas" -- jennifer fallon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81135-never-underestimate-the-capacity-of-noble-young-men-to-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 20:04:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dore add a quote by Jennifer Fallon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81135-never-underestimate-the-capacity-of-noble-young-men-to-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never underestimate the capacity of noble young men to do incredibly foolish things for perfectly good reasons." -- Jennifer Fallon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
