<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/617289-melissa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/617289-melissa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 16:01:03 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377414-the-dismaying-truth-is-that-birtherism-is-part-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 16:01:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Hendrik Hertzberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377414-the-dismaying-truth-is-that-birtherism-is-part-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The dismaying truth is that birtherism is part of a larger pattern of rejection of reality that has taken hold of intimidating segments of one of the two political parties that alternate in power in our governing institutions.  It is akin to the view that global warming is a hoax, or that the budget can be balanced through spending cuts alone, or that contraception causes abortion, or that evolution is just another theory, on a par with the theory that the earth is six thousand years old." -- Hendrik Hertzberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90521-whenever-the-devil-harasses-you-seek-the-company-of-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2013 09:33:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Martin Luther]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90521-whenever-the-devil-harasses-you-seek-the-company-of-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever the devil harasses you, seek the company of men or drink more, or joke and talk nonsense, or do some other merry thing. Sometimes we must drink more, sport, recreate ourselves, and even sin a little to spite the devil, so that we leave him no place for troubling our consciences with trifles. We are conquered if we try too conscientiously not to sin at all. So when the devil says to you: do not drink, answer him: I will drink, and right freely, just because you tell me not to." -- Martin Luther]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
