<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/617334-madeline]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/617334-madeline" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 16:50:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102198-books-have-to-be-read-worse-luck-it-takes-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 16:50:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102198-books-have-to-be-read-worse-luck-it-takes-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books have to be read (worse luck it takes so long a time). It is the only way of discovering what they contain. A few savage tribes eat them, but reading is the only method of assimilation revealed to the West." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350957-and-without-a-doubt-it-is-more-comfortable-to-endure</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 16:50:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350957-and-without-a-doubt-it-is-more-comfortable-to-endure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And without a doubt it is more comfortable to endure blind bondage than to work for one's liberation; the dead, too, are better suited to the earth than the living." -- Simone de Beauvoir]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61787-i-would-always-rather-be-happy-than-dignified</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 16:49:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61787-i-would-always-rather-be-happy-than-dignified]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would always rather be happy than dignified." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19007-oh-how-like-a-woman-davey-said-sex-my-dear</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 14:01:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Nancy Mitford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19007-oh-how-like-a-woman-davey-said-sex-my-dear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh! How like a woman,&quot; Davey said. &quot;Sex, my dear Sadie, is not a sovereign cure for everything, you know. I only wish it were." -- Nancy Mitford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19008-then-bidding-farewell-to-the-knick-knack-i-went-to-collect</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 14:02:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Colette]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19008-then-bidding-farewell-to-the-knick-knack-i-went-to-collect]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then, bidding farewell to The Knick-Knack, I went to collect the few personal belongings which, at that time, I held to be invaluable: my cat, my resolve to travel, and my solitude." -- Colette]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19009-and-since-through-lack-of-vocation-or-from-habit-julie</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 14:03:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Colette]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19009-and-since-through-lack-of-vocation-or-from-habit-julie]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And since, through lack of vocation or from habit, [Julie] was prone to confuse pity with boredom, she felt herself practically a prisoner..." -- Colette]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19012-julie-had-lived-a-great-deal-among-lies-before-plumping</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 14:04:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Colette]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19012-julie-had-lived-a-great-deal-among-lies-before-plumping]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Julie] had lived a great deal among lies, before plumping for a small life of her own, a sincere and restricted life from which all pretense, even in matters sensual, was banished. How many crazy decisions and allegiances to successive aspects fo the truth! Had she not, one day when her costume for a fancy dress had demanded short hair, cut off the great chestnut mane that fell below her waist when she let it down? 'I could have hired a wig,' she thought. 'I might also, at a pinch, have passed the rest of my life with Becker or Espivant. If it comes to that, I could also have gone on stirring puddings in a saucepan at Carneilhan. The things &quot;one might have done&quot; are, in fact, the things one could not do..." -- Colette]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 14:10:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Groucho Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Outside of a dog, a book is man's best friend. Inside of a dog it's too dark to read." -- Groucho Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19016-if-i-ever-bore-you-it-ll-be-with-a-knife</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 14:11:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Louise Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19016-if-i-ever-bore-you-it-ll-be-with-a-knife]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I ever bore you, it'll be with a knife." -- Louise Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2044-it-is-a-defect-of-god-s-humor-that-he-directs</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 13:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2044-it-is-a-defect-of-god-s-humor-that-he-directs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a defect of God's humor that he directs our hearts everywhere but to those who have a right to them." -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57663-this-was-an-idea-peculiar-to-camille-maximilien-thought-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 13:37:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57663-this-was-an-idea-peculiar-to-camille-maximilien-thought-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This was an idea peculiar to Camille, Maximilien thought, that the worse things get, the better they get. No one else seems to think this way." -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57664-already-d-anton-did-not-believe-this-he-recognized-it-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 13:38:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57664-already-d-anton-did-not-believe-this-he-recognized-it-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Already d'Anton did not believe this. He recognized it as a disclaimer that Camille would issue from time to time in the hope of disguising the fact that he was an inveterate hell-raiser." -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57665-danton-could-you-indeed-it-s-you-idealists-who-make-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 13:39:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Hilary Mantel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57665-danton-could-you-indeed-it-s-you-idealists-who-make-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["DANTON: Could you indeed? It's you idealists who make the best tyrants.
ROBESPIERRE: It seems a bit late to be having this conversation.  I've had to take up violence now, and so much else. We should have discussed it last year." -- Hilary Mantel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16821-if-you-go-home-with-somebody-and-they-don-t-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 16:49:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by John Waters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16821-if-you-go-home-with-somebody-and-they-don-t-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you go home with somebody, and they don't have books, don't fuck 'em!" -- John Waters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110695-but-i-too-hate-long-books-the-better-the-worse</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 16:49:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Vikram Seth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110695-but-i-too-hate-long-books-the-better-the-worse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I too hate long books: the better, the worse.  If they're bad they merely make me pant with the effort of holding them up for a few minutes. But if they're good, I turn into a social moron for days, refusing to go out of my room, scowling and growling at interruptions, ignoring weddings and funerals, and making enemies out of friends. I still bear the scars of Middlemarch." -- Vikram Seth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13708-i-suggest-that-the-only-books-that-influence-us-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 14:52:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13708-i-suggest-that-the-only-books-that-influence-us-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I suggest that the only books that influence us are those for which we are ready, and which have gone a little further down our particular path than we have yet gone ourselves." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12682-it-is-fate-that-i-am-here-george-persisted-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 14:52:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by E. M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12682-it-is-fate-that-i-am-here-george-persisted-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is fate that I am here,' George persisted, 'but you can call it Italy if it makes you less unhappy." -- E. M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44629-somebody-might-have-come-along-that-way-who-would-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 14:57:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Thomas Hardy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44629-somebody-might-have-come-along-that-way-who-would-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Somebody might have come along that way who would have asked him his trouble, and might have cheered him by saying that his notions were further advanced than those of his grammarian. But nobody did come, because nobody does; and under the crushing recognition of his gigantic error Jude continued to wish himself out of the world." -- Thomas Hardy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25469-stephen-had-been-put-to-sleep-in-his-usual-room</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 20:16:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25469-stephen-had-been-put-to-sleep-in-his-usual-room]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stephen had been put to sleep in his usual room, far from children and noise, away in that corner of the house which looked down to the orchard and the bowling-green, and in spite of his long absence it was so familiar to him that when he woke at about three he made his way to the window almost as quickly as if dawn had already broken, opened it and walked out onto the balcony. The moon had set: there was barely a star to be seen. The still air was delightfully fresh with falling dew, and a late nightingale, in an indifferent voice, was uttering a routine jug-jug far down in Jack's plantations; closer at hand and more agreeable by far, nightjars churred in the orchard, two of them, or perhaps three, the sound rising and falling, intertwining so that the source could not be made out for sure. There were few birds that he preferred to nightjars, but it was not they that had brought him out of bed: he stood leaning on the balcony rail and presently Jack Aubrey, in a summer-house by the bowling-green, began again, playing very gently in the darkness, improvising wholly for himself, dreaming away on his violin with a mastery that Stephen had never heard equalled, though they had played together for years and years.

Like many other sailors Jack Aubrey had long dreamed of lying in his warm bed all night long; yet although he could now do so with a clear conscience he often rose at unChristian hours, particularly if he were moved by strong emotion, and crept from his bedroom in a watch-coat, to walk about the house or into the stables or to pace the bowling-green. Sometimes he took his fiddle with him. He was in fact a better player than Stephen, and now that he was using his precious Guarnieri rather than a robust sea-going fiddle the difference was still more evident: but the Guarnieri did not account for the whole of it, nor anything like. Jack certainly concealed his excellence when they were playing together, keeping to Stephen's mediocre level: this had become perfectly clear when Stephen's hands were at last recovered from the thumb-screws and other implements applied by French counter-intelligence officers in Minorca; but on reflexion Stephen thought it had been the case much earlier, since quite apart from his delicacy at that period, Jack hated showing away.

Now, in the warm night, there was no one to be comforted, kept in countenance, no one could scorn him for virtuosity, and he could let himself go entirely; and as the grave and subtle music wound on and on, Stephen once more contemplated on the apparent contradiction between the big, cheerful, florid sea-officer whom most people liked on sight but who would have never been described as subtle or capable of subtlety by any one of them (except perhaps his surviving opponents in battle) and the intricate, reflective music he was now creating. So utterly unlike his limited vocabulary in words, at times verging upon the inarticulate.

'My hands have now regained the moderate ability they possessed before I was captured,' observed Maturin, 'but his have gone on to a point I never thought he could reach: his hands and his mind. I am amazed. In his own way he is the secret man of the world." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234754-peace-tremulous-unexpected-sent-a-taproot-out-of-nowhere-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2010 21:27:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Patricia A. McKillip]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234754-peace-tremulous-unexpected-sent-a-taproot-out-of-nowhere-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Peace, tremulous, unexpected, sent a taproot out of nowhere into Morgan's heart." -- Patricia A. McKillip]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322432-i-came-back-suppose-you-hadn-t-i-came-back-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2010 21:28:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Patricia A. McKillip]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322432-i-came-back-suppose-you-hadn-t-i-came-back-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I came back.&quot;
&quot;Suppose you hadn't?&quot;
&quot;I came back! Why can't you understand, instead of thinking as though your brains are made of oak. Athol's son, with his hair and eyes and vision -&quot;
&quot;No!&quot; Tristan said sharply. Eliard's fist, raised and knotted, halted in midair. Morgon dropped his face again against his knees. Eliard shut his eyes.
&quot;Why do you think I'm so angry?&quot; he whispered.
&quot;I know.&quot;
&quot;Do you? Even - even after six months I still expect to hear her voice unexpectedly, or see him coming out of the barn, or in from the fields at dusk. And you? How will I know, now, that when you leave Hed, you'll come back? You could have died in that tower for the sake of a stupid crown and left us watching for the ghost of you, too. Swear you'll never do anything like that again.&quot;
&quot;I can't.&quot;
&quot;You can.&quot;
Morgon raised his head, looked at Eliard. &quot;How can I make one promise to you and another to myself? But I swear this: I will always come back.&quot;
&quot;How can you -&quot;
&quot;I swear it." -- Patricia A. McKillip]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21101-do-you-think-i-am-an-automaton-a-machine</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2011 22:04:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21101-do-you-think-i-am-an-automaton-a-machine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you think I am an automaton? — a machine without feelings? and can bear to have my morsel of bread snatched from my lips, and my drop of living water dashed from my cup? Do you think, because I am poor, obscure, plain, and little, I am soulless and heartless? You think wrong! — I have as much soul as you — and full as much heart! And if God had gifted me with some beauty and much wealth, I should have made it as hard for you to leave me, as it is now for me to leave you. I am not talking to you now through the medium of custom, conventionalities, nor even of mortal flesh: it is my spirit that addresses your spirit; just as if both had passed through the grave, and we stood at God's feet, equal — as we are!" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/355287-jerry-look-at-the-way-you-re-looking-at-me-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 19:44:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Harold Pinter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/355287-jerry-look-at-the-way-you-re-looking-at-me-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["JERRY: Look at the way you're looking at me. I can't wait for you. I'm bowled over, I'm totally knocked out, you dazzle me, you jewel, my jewel, I can't ever sleep again, no, listen, it's the truth, I won't walk, I'll be a cripple, I'll descend, I'll diminish, into total paralysis, my life is in your hands, that's what you're banishing me to, a state of catatonia, do you know the state of catatonia? do you? do you? the state of...where the reigning prince is the prince of emptiness, the prince of absence, the prince of desolation. I love you.
EMMA: My husband is at the other side of that door.
JERRY: Everyone knows. The world knows. It knows. But they'll never know, they'll never know, they're in a different world. I adore you. I'm madly in love with you. I can't believe that what anyone is at this moment saying has ever happened has ever happened. Nothing has ever happened. Nothing. Your eyes kill me. I'm lost. You're wonderful." -- Harold Pinter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102701-then-what-is-magic-for-prince-l-r-demanded-wildly-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 06:52:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102701-then-what-is-magic-for-prince-l-r-demanded-wildly-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then what is magic for?&quot; Prince Lír demanded wildly. &quot;What use is wizardry if it cannot save a unicorn?&quot; He gripped the magician's shoulder hard, to keep from falling.

Schmedrick did not turn his head. With a touch of sad mockery in his voice, he said, &quot;That's what heroes are for." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100511-the-odd-thing-about-people-who-had-many-books-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2011 13:30:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Patricia A. McKillip]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100511-the-odd-thing-about-people-who-had-many-books-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The odd thing about people who had many books was how they always wanted more." -- Patricia A. McKillip]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/389052-i-have-tried-i-said-but-he-does-not-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 20:39:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Jean Rhys]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/389052-i-have-tried-i-said-but-he-does-not-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have tried,&quot; I said, &quot;but he does not believe me. It is too late for that now&quot; (it is always too late for truth, I thought)." -- Jean Rhys]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401414-counting-on-each-other-became-automatic-when-i-found-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 10:28:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Gail Caldwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401414-counting-on-each-other-became-automatic-when-i-found-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Counting on each other became automatic. When I found a sweater in Texas I wanted, I learned to buy two, which was easier than seeing the look of disappointment on Caroline's face when I returned home with only one. When she went out from the boathouse on a windy day, she gave me her schedule in advance, which assuaged her worst-case scenario of flipping the boat, being hit on the head by an oar, and leaving Lucille stranded at home. I still have my set of keys to her house, to locks and doors that no longer exist, and I keep them in my glove compartment, where they have been moved from one car to another in the past couple of years. Someday I will throw them in the Charles, where I lost the seat to her boat and so much else." -- Gail Caldwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122425-if-i-d-stayed-there-would-i-always-have-been-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2011 08:40:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by J.L. Carr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122425-if-i-d-stayed-there-would-i-always-have-been-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I’d stayed there, would I always have been happy? No, I suppose not. People move away, grow older, die, and the bright belief that there will be another marvelous thing around each corner fades. It is now or never; we must snatch at happiness as it flies." -- J.L. Carr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15260-she-is-a-friend-of-my-mind-she-gather-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 19:16:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15260-she-is-a-friend-of-my-mind-she-gather-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She is a friend of my mind. She gather me, man. The pieces I am, she gather them and give them back to me in all the right order." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82955-condemning-nyasha-to-whoredom-making-her-a-victim-of-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 08:29:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Madeline add a quote by Tsitsi Dangarembga]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82955-condemning-nyasha-to-whoredom-making-her-a-victim-of-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...condemning Nyasha to whoredom, making her a victim of her femaleness, just as I had felt victimised at home in the days when Nhamo went to school and I grew my maize. The victimisation, I saw, was universal. It didn't depend on poverty, on lack of education or on tradition. It didn't depend on any of the things I had thought it depended on. Men took it everywhere with them. Even heroes like Babamukuru did it. And that was the problem. You had to admit Nyasha had no tact. You had to admit she was altogether too volatile and strong-willed. You couldn't ignore the fact that she had no respect for Babamukuru when she ought to have had lots of it. But what I didn't like was the way that all conflicts came back to the question of femaleness. Femaleness as opposed and inferior to maleness." -- Tsitsi Dangarembga]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
