<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/618604-marie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/618604-marie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 11:42:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21947-in-your-light-i-learn-how-to-love-in-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 11:42:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21947-in-your-light-i-learn-how-to-love-in-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In your light I learn how to love. In your beauty, how to make poems. You dance inside my chest where no-one sees you, but sometimes I do, and that sight becomes this art." -- Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85284-i-ask-the-impossible-love-me-forever-love-me-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 11:42:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Ana Castillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85284-i-ask-the-impossible-love-me-forever-love-me-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I ask the impossible: love me forever.
Love me when all desire is gone.
Love me with the single mindedness of a monk.
When the world in its entirety,
and all that you hold sacred advise you
against it: love me still more.
When rage fills you and has no name: love me.
When each step from your door to our job tires you--
love me; and from job to home again, love me, love me.
Love me when you're bored--
when every woman you see is more beautiful than the last,
or more pathetic, love me as you always have:
not as admirer or judge, but with
the compassion you save for yourself
in your solitude.
Love me as you relish your loneliness,
the anticipation of your death,
mysteries of the flesh, as it tears and mends.
Love me as your most treasured childhood memory--
and if there is none to recall--
imagine one, place me there with you.
Love me withered as you loved me new.
Love me as if I were forever--
and I, will make the impossible
a simple act,
by loving you, loving you as I do" -- Ana Castillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217657-and-i-want-to-play-hide-and-seek-and-give-you-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 11:42:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Sarah Kane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217657-and-i-want-to-play-hide-and-seek-and-give-you-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I want to play hide-and-seek and give you my clothes and tell you I like your shoes and sit on the steps while you take a bath and massage your neck and kiss your feet and hold your hand and go for a meal and not mind when you eat my food and meet you at Rudy's and talk about the day and type up your letters and carry your boxes and laugh at your paranoia and give you tapes you don't listen to and watch great films and watch terrible films and complain about the radio and take pictures of you when you're sleeping and get up to fetch you coffee and bagels and Danish and go to Florent and drink coffee at midnight and have you steal my cigarettes and never be able to find a match and tell you about the tv programme I saw the night before and take you to the eye hospital and not laugh at your jokes and want you in the morning but let you sleep for a while and kiss your back and stroke your skin and tell you how much I love your hair your eyes your lips your neck your breasts your arse your

and sit on the steps smoking till your neighbour comes home and sit on the steps smoking till &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; come home and worry when you're late and be amazed when you're early and give you sunflowers and go to your party and dance till I'm black and be sorry when I'm wrong and happy when you forgive me and look at your photos and wish I'd known you forever and hear your voice in my ear and feel your skin on my skin and get scared when you're angry and your eye has gone red and the other eye blue and your hair to the left and your face oriental and tell you you're gorgeous and hug you when you're anxious and hold you when you hurt and want you when I smell you and offend you when I touch you and whimper when I'm next to you and whimper when I'm not and dribble on your breast and smother you in the night and get cold when you take the blanket and hot when you don't and melt when you smile and dissolve when you laugh and not understand why you think I'm rejecting you when I'm not rejecting you and wonder how you could think I'd ever reject you and wonder who you are but accept you anyway and tell you about the tree angel enchanted forest boy who flew across the ocean because he loved you and write poems for you and wonder why you don't believe me and have a feeling so deep I can't find words for it and want to buy you a kitten I'd get jealous of because it would get more attention than me and keep you in bed when you have to go and cry like a baby when you finally do and get rid of the roaches and buy you presents you don't want and take them away again and ask you to marry me and you say no &lt;i&gt;again&lt;/i&gt; but keep on asking because though you think I don't mean it I do always have from the first time I asked you and wander the city thinking it's empty without you and want what you want and think I'm losing myself but know I'm safe with you and tell you the worst of me and try to give you the best of me because you don't deserve any less and answer your questions when I'd rather not and tell you the truth when I really don't want to and try to be honest because I know you prefer it and think it's all over but hang on in for just ten more minutes before you throw me out of your life and forget who I am and try to get closer to you because it's beautiful learning to know you and well worth the effort and speak German to you badly and Hebrew to you worse and make love with you at three in the morning and somehow somehow somehow communicate some of the overwhelming undying overpowering unconditional all-encompassing heart-enriching mind-expanding on-going never-ending love I have for you." -- Sarah Kane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/340404-i-can-write-the-saddest-poem-of-all-tonight-write</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 11:53:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/340404-i-can-write-the-saddest-poem-of-all-tonight-write]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can write the saddest poem of all tonight.

 Write, for instance: &quot;The night is full of stars,
 and the stars, blue, shiver in the distance.&quot;

 The night wind whirls in the sky and sings.

 I can write the saddest poem of all tonight.
 I loved her, and sometimes she loved me too.

 On nights like this, I held her in my arms.
 I kissed her so many times under the infinite sky.

 She loved me, sometimes I loved her.
 How could I not have loved her large, still eyes?

 I can write the saddest poem of all tonight.
 To think I don't have her. To feel that I've lost her.

 To hear the immense night, more immense without her.
 And the poem falls to the soul as dew to grass.

 What does it matter that my love couldn't keep her.
 The night is full of stars and she is not with me.

 That's all. Far away, someone sings. Far away.
 My soul is lost without her.

 As if to bring her near, my eyes search for her.
 My heart searches for her and she is not with me.

 The same night that whitens the same trees.
 We, we who were, we are the same no longer.

 I no longer love her, true, but how much I loved her.
 My voice searched the wind to touch her ear.

 Someone else's. She will be someone else's. As she once
 belonged to my kisses.
 Her voice, her light body. Her infinite eyes.

 I no longer love her, true, but perhaps I love her.
 Love is so short and oblivion so long.

 Because on nights like this I held her in my arms,
 my soul is lost without her.

 Although this may be the last pain she causes me,
 and this may be the last poem I write for her." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321454-cassia-i-know-which-life-is-my-real-one-now</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 11:53:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Ally Condie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321454-cassia-i-know-which-life-is-my-real-one-now]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cassia.
I know which life is my real one now, no matter what happens. It’s the one with you. For some reason, knowing that even one person knows my story makes things different. Maybe it’s like the poem says. Maybe this is my way of not going gentle.
I love you. (Ky Markham)" -- Ally Condie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142607-desiderata-go-placidly-amid-the-noise-and-the-haste-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 11:54:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Max Ehrmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142607-desiderata-go-placidly-amid-the-noise-and-the-haste-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Desiderata&quot; 
Go placidly amid the noise and the haste,
and remember what peace there may be in silence. 
As far as possible, without surrender, 
be on good terms with all persons.
Speak your truth quietly and clearly, and listen to others,
even to the dull and ignorant;
they too have their story.
Avoid loud and aggressive persons;
they are vexatious to the spirit.
If you compare yourself with others,
you may become vain or bitter,
for always there will be
greater and lesser persons than yourself.
Enjoy your achievements as well as your plans.
Keep interested in your own career
however humble;
it is a real possession in the 
changing fortunes of time.
Exercise caution in your business affairs,
for the world is full of trickery.
But let this not blind you
to what virtue there is;
many persons strive for high ideals,
and everywhere life is full of heroism.
Be yourself.
Especially do not feign affection.
Neither be cynical about love,
for in the face of all aridity and disenchantment,
it is as perennial as the grass.
Take kindly the counsel of the years,
gracefully surrendering the things of youth.
Nurture strength of spirit
to shield you in sudden misfortune.
But do not distress yourself with dark imaginings.
Many fears are born of fatigue and loneliness.

Beyond a wholesome discipline,
be gentle with yourself.
You are a child of the universe
no less than the trees and the stars;
you have a right to be here.
And whether or not it is clear to you,
no doubt the universe is unfolding as it should.
Therefore, be at peace with God,
whatever you conceive Him to be.
And whatever your labors and aspirations,
in the noisy confusion of life,
keep peace in your soul.
With all its sham,
drudgery, and broken dreams,
it is still a beautiful world.
Be cheerful.
Strive to be happy." -- Max Ehrmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65745-whoever-you-are-now-i-place-my-hand-upon-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 12:00:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65745-whoever-you-are-now-i-place-my-hand-upon-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whoever you are, now I place my hand upon you/ That you may be my poem/ I whisper with my lips close to your ear/ I have loved many women and men, but I love none better than you." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
