<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/619120-nicole]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/619120-nicole" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 07:34:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17158-the-miracle-isn-t-that-i-finished-the-miracle-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 07:34:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by John Bingham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17158-the-miracle-isn-t-that-i-finished-the-miracle-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The miracle isn't that I finished. The miracle is that I had the courage to start." -- John Bingham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739-when-i-despair-i-remember-that-all-through-history-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 11:51:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739-when-i-despair-i-remember-that-all-through-history-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I despair, I remember that all through history the way of truth and love have always won. There have been tyrants and murderers, and for a time, they can seem invincible, but in the end, they always fall. Think of it--always." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13753-people-who-claim-that-they-re-evil-are-usually-no-worse</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 11:51:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13753-people-who-claim-that-they-re-evil-are-usually-no-worse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People who claim that they're evil are usually no worse than the rest of us... It's people who claim that they're good, or any way  better than the rest of us, that you have to be wary of." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250293-evil-isn-t-the-real-threat-to-the-world-stupid-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 11:52:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Jim Butcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250293-evil-isn-t-the-real-threat-to-the-world-stupid-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Evil isn’t the real threat to the world. Stupid is just as destructive as Evil, maybe more so, and it’s a hell of a lot more common. What we really need is a crusade against Stupid. That might actually make a difference." -- Jim Butcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174047-i-know-there-s-evil-in-the-world-and-there-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 11:55:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Tess Gerritsen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174047-i-know-there-s-evil-in-the-world-and-there-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know there’s evil in the world, and there always has been. But you don’t need to believe in Satan or demons to explain it. Human beings are perfectly capable of evil all by themselves." -- Tess Gerritsen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43863-never-ascribe-to-malice-that-which-can-adequately-be-explained</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 11:56:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Napoleon Bonaparte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43863-never-ascribe-to-malice-that-which-can-adequately-be-explained]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never ascribe to malice that which can adequately be explained by incompetence." -- Napoleon Bonaparte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19968-i-live-in-the-managerial-age-in-a-world-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 11:57:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19968-i-live-in-the-managerial-age-in-a-world-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I live in the Managerial Age, in a world of &quot;Admin.&quot; The greatest evil is not now done in those sordid &quot;dens of crime&quot; that Dickens loved to paint. It is not done even in concentration camps and labour camps. In those we see its final result. But it is conceived and ordered (moved, seconded, carried, and minuted) in clean, carpeted, warmed and well-lighted offices, by quiet men with white collars and cut fingernails and smooth-shaven cheeks who do not need to raise their voices. Hence, naturally enough, my symbol for Hell is something like the bureaucracy of a police state or the office of a thoroughly nasty business concern.&quot;

&lt;i&gt;[From the Preface]&lt;/i&gt;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246717-better-to-be-strong-than-pretty-and-useless</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 06:13:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Lilith Saintcrow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246717-better-to-be-strong-than-pretty-and-useless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Better to be strong than pretty and useless." -- Lilith Saintcrow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222733-always-say-yes-to-the-present-moment-what-could-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 05:50:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222733-always-say-yes-to-the-present-moment-what-could-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Always say “yes” to the present moment. What could be more futile, more insane, than to create inner resistance to what already is? what could be more insane than to oppose life itself, which is now and always now? Surrender to what is. Say “yes” to life — and see how life suddenly starts working for you rather than against you." -- Eckhart Tolle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/340310-at-fifteen-life-had-taught-me-undeniably-that-surrender-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 05:50:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/340310-at-fifteen-life-had-taught-me-undeniably-that-surrender-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At fifteen life had taught me undeniably that surrender, in its place, was as honorable as resistance, especially if one had no choice." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4047-the-eyes-of-others-our-prisons-their-thoughts-our-cages</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 07:44:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4047-the-eyes-of-others-our-prisons-their-thoughts-our-cages]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The eyes of others our prisons; their thoughts our cages." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8054-when-i-was-a-child-my-mother-said-to-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 07:45:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Pablo Picasso]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8054-when-i-was-a-child-my-mother-said-to-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was a child my mother said to me, 'If you become a soldier, you'll be a general. If you become a monk, you'll be the pope.' Instead I became a painter and wound up as Picasso." -- Pablo Picasso]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150453-we-either-make-ourselves-miserable-or-we-make-ourselves-strong</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 07:45:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Carlos Castaneda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150453-we-either-make-ourselves-miserable-or-we-make-ourselves-strong]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We either make ourselves miserable, or we make ourselves strong. The amount of work is the same." -- Carlos Castaneda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 13:13:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 13:14:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 13:15:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 13:15:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be yourself in a world that is constantly trying to make you something else is the greatest accomplishment." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 13:17:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 13:22:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62235-i-am-good-but-not-an-angel-i-do-sin</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 13:25:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62235-i-am-good-but-not-an-angel-i-do-sin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am good, but not an angel. I do sin, but I am not the devil. I am just a small girl in a big world trying to find someone to love." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208546-the-truth-is-everyone-is-going-to-hurt-you-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 13:26:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208546-the-truth-is-everyone-is-going-to-hurt-you-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is, everyone is going to hurt you. You just got to find the ones worth suffering for." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33329-the-willingness-to-forgive-is-a-sign-of-spiritual-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 08:25:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33329-the-willingness-to-forgive-is-a-sign-of-spiritual-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The willingness to forgive is a sign of spiritual and emotional maturity.  It is one of the great virtues to which we all should aspire.  Imagine a world filled with individuals willing both to apologize and to accept an apology.  Is there any problem that could not be solved among people who possessed the humility and largeness of spirit and soul to do either -- or both -- when needed?" -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432846-there-is-no-such-thing-as-a-broken-family-family</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 08:26:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432846-there-is-no-such-thing-as-a-broken-family-family]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no such thing as a &quot;broken family.&quot; Family is family, and is not determined by marriage certificates, divorce papers, and adoption documents. Families are made in the heart. The only time family becomes null is when those ties in the heart are cut. If you cut those ties, those people are not your family. If you make those ties, those people are your family. And if you hate those ties, those people will still be your family because whatever you hate will always be with you." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144557-resentment-is-like-drinking-poison-and-then-hoping-it-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 08:27:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Nelson Mandela]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144557-resentment-is-like-drinking-poison-and-then-hoping-it-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Resentment is like drinking poison and then hoping it will kill your enemies." -- Nelson Mandela]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159464-forgiveness-in-no-way-requires-that-you-trust-the-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 08:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Wm. Paul Young]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159464-forgiveness-in-no-way-requires-that-you-trust-the-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Forgiveness in no way requires that you trust the one you forgive." -- Wm. Paul Young]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247276-offer-it-up-personally-then-right-now-i-thought-of-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 08:29:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247276-offer-it-up-personally-then-right-now-i-thought-of-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Offer it up personally,then. Right now. I thought of how many people go to their graves unforgiven and unforgiving. I thought of how many people have had siblings or friends or children or lovers disappear from their lives before precious words of clemency or absolution could be passed along. How do the survivors of terminated relationships ever endure the pain of unfinished business? From that place of meditation, I found the answer-you can finish the business yourself, from within yourself. It's not only possible, it's essential." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 08:14:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Kent M. Keith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Paradoxical Commandments

People are illogical, unreasonable, and self-centered.
Love them anyway.

If you do good, people will accuse you of selfish ulterior motives.
Do good anyway.

If you are successful, you will win false friends and true enemies.
Succeed anyway.

The good you do today will be forgotten tomorrow.
Do good anyway.

Honesty and frankness make you vulnerable.
Be honest and frank anyway.

The biggest men and women with the biggest ideas can be shot down by the smallest men and women with the smallest minds.
Think big anyway.

People favor underdogs but follow only top dogs.
Fight for a few underdogs anyway.

What you spend years building may be destroyed overnight.
Build anyway.

People really need help but may attack you if you do help them.
Help people anyway.

Give the world the best you have and you'll get kicked in the teeth.
Give the world the best you have anyway." -- Kent M. Keith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3278-i-may-not-have-gone-where-i-intended-to-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 08:14:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by douglas adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3278-i-may-not-have-gone-where-i-intended-to-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I may not have gone where I intended to go, but I think I have ended up where I needed to be." -- douglas adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19421-if-you-can-t-explain-it-to-a-six-year-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 08:15:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19421-if-you-can-t-explain-it-to-a-six-year-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can't explain it to a six year old, you don't understand it yourself." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204561-we-re-all-a-little-weird-and-life-is-a-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 08:17:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204561-we-re-all-a-little-weird-and-life-is-a-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We’re all a little weird. And life is a little weird. And when we find someone whose weirdness is compatible with ours, we join up with them and fall into mutually satisfying weirdness—and call it love—true love." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
