<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/619525-annisa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/619525-annisa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 00:31:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83017-i-like-to-see-people-reunited-i-like-to-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 00:31:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83017-i-like-to-see-people-reunited-i-like-to-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like to see people reunited, I like to see people run to each other, I like the kissing and the crying, I like the impatience, the stories that the mouth can't tell fast enough, the ears that aren't big enough, the eyes that can't take in all of the change, I like the hugging, the bringing together, the end of missing someone." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 00:31:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36501-perhaps-after-all-romance-did-not-come-into-one-s-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 00:32:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36501-perhaps-after-all-romance-did-not-come-into-one-s-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps, after all, romance did not come into one’s life with pomp and blare, like a gay knight riding down; perhaps it crept to one’s side like an old friend through quiet ways; perhaps it revealed itself in seeming prose, until some sudden shaft of illumination flung athwart its pages betrayed the rhythm and the music, perhaps . . . perhaps . . . love unfolded naturally out of a beautiful friendship, as a golden-hearted rose slipping from its green sheath." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46786-if-writers-wrote-as-carelessly-as-some-people-talk-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 00:32:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46786-if-writers-wrote-as-carelessly-as-some-people-talk-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If writers wrote as carelessly as some people talk, then adhasdh asdglaseuyt[bn[ pasdlgkhasdfasdf." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49905-does-it-break-my-heart-of-course-every-moment-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 00:32:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49905-does-it-break-my-heart-of-course-every-moment-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Does it break my heart, of course, every moment of every day, into more pieces than my heart was made of, I never thought of myself as quiet, much less silent, I never thought about things at all, everything changed, the distance that wedged itself between me and my happiness wasn't the world, it wasn't the bombs and burning buildings, it was me, my thinking, the cancer of never letting go, is ignorance bliss, I don't know, but it's so painful to think, and tell me, what did thinking ever do for me, to what great place did thinking ever bring me? I think and think and think, I've thought myself out of happiness one million times, but never once into it." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/421098-people-die-of-broken-hearts-they-have-heart-attacks-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 11:20:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/421098-people-die-of-broken-hearts-they-have-heart-attacks-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People die of broken hearts. They have heart attacks. And it's the heart that hurts most when things go wrong and fall apart." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10136-there-is-nothing-sweeter-in-this-sad-world-than-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 09:38:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Kate DiCamillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10136-there-is-nothing-sweeter-in-this-sad-world-than-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing sweeter in this sad world than the sound of someone you love calling your name." -- Kate DiCamillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110157-if-people-do-not-believe-that-mathematics-is-simple-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 06:05:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by John von Neumann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110157-if-people-do-not-believe-that-mathematics-is-simple-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If people do not believe that mathematics is simple, it is only because they do not realize how complicated life is." -- John von Neumann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64749-i-ll-tell-you-once-and-i-ll-tell-you-again-there-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 06:06:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Paul Erdos]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64749-i-ll-tell-you-once-and-i-ll-tell-you-again-there-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'll tell you once,
and I'll tell you again.
There's always a prime
between n and 2n." -- Paul Erdos]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200442-the-worst-part-of-holding-the-memories-is-not-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 07:58:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Lois Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200442-the-worst-part-of-holding-the-memories-is-not-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worst part of holding the memories is not the pain. It's the loneliness of it. Memories need to be shared." -- Lois Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10857-i-was-trying-to-feel-some-kind-of-good-bye-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 23:09:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10857-i-was-trying-to-feel-some-kind-of-good-bye-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was trying to feel some kind of good-bye.  I mean I’ve left schools and places I didn’t even know I was leaving them.  I hate that.  I don’t care if it’s a sad good-bye or a bad good-bye, but when I leave a place I like to know I’m leaving it.  If you don’t you feel even worse." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108834-there-are-so-many-fragile-things-after-all-people-break</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 01:35:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108834-there-are-so-many-fragile-things-after-all-people-break]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are so many fragile things, after all.  People break so easily, and so do dreams and hearts." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15411-actual-happiness-always-looks-pretty-squalid-in-comparison-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 00:32:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15411-actual-happiness-always-looks-pretty-squalid-in-comparison-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Actual happiness always looks pretty squalid in comparison with the overcompensations for misery. And, of course, stability isn't nearly so spectacular as instability. And being contented has none of the glamour of a good fight against misfortune, none of the picturesqueness of a struggle with temptation, or a fatal overthrow by passion or doubt. Happiness is never grand." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167031-don-t-ask-for-guarantees-and-don-t-look-to-be-saved</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 00:32:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167031-don-t-ask-for-guarantees-and-don-t-look-to-be-saved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't ask for guarantees. And don't look to be saved in any one thing, person, machine, or library. Do your own bit of saving, and if you drown, at least die knowing you were heading for shore." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25564-how-lucky-i-am-to-have-something-that-makes-saying</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 00:32:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25564-how-lucky-i-am-to-have-something-that-makes-saying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How lucky I am to have something that makes saying goodbye so hard." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/418735-tom-said-douglas-just-promise-me-one-thing-okay-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 00:32:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/418735-tom-said-douglas-just-promise-me-one-thing-okay-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tom,&quot; said Douglas, &quot;just promise me one thing, okay?&quot;
	&quot;It's a promise. What?&quot;
	&quot;You may be my brother and maybe I hate you sometimes, but stick around, all right?&quot;
	&quot;You mean you'll let me follow you and the older guys when you go on hikes?&quot;
	&quot;Well . . . sure . . . even that. What I mean is, don't go away, huh? Don't let any cars run over you or fall of a cliff.&quot;
	&quot;I should say not! Whatta you think I am, anyway?&quot;
	&quot;'Cause if worst comes to worst, and both of us are real old--say forty or forty-five some day-- we can own a gold mine out West and sit there smoking corn silk and growing bears.&quot;
	&quot;Growing beards! Boy!&quot;
	&quot;Like I say, you stick around and don't let nothing happen.&quot;
&quot;You can depend on me,&quot; said Tom.
	&quot;It's not you I worry about,&quot; said Douglas. &quot;It's the way God runs the world.&quot;
	Tom thought about this for a moment.
	&quot;He's all right, Doug,&quot; said Tom. &quot;He tries." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175155-science-can-teach-us-and-i-think-our-hearts-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 00:32:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175155-science-can-teach-us-and-i-think-our-hearts-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Science can teach us, and I think our hearts can teach us, no longer to look around for imaginary supporters, no longer to invent allies in the sky, but rather to look to our own efforts here below to make the world a fit place to live." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163344-we-inhabit-a-universe-where-atoms-are-made-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 03:12:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163344-we-inhabit-a-universe-where-atoms-are-made-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We inhabit a universe where atoms are made in the centers of stars; where each second a thousand suns are born; where life is sparked by sunlight and lightning in the airs and waters of youthful planets; where the raw material for biological evolution is sometimes made by the explosion of a star halfway across the Milky Way; where a thing as beautiful as a galaxy is formed a hundred billion times - a Cosmos of quasars and quarks, snowflakes and fireflies, where there may be black holes and other universe and extraterrestrial civilizations whose radio messages are at this moment reaching the Earth. How pallid by comparison are the pretensions of superstition and pseudoscience; how important it is for us to pursue and understand science, that characteristically human endeavor. " -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36835-there-s-always-a-moment-when-you-start-to-fall-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 18:34:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36835-there-s-always-a-moment-when-you-start-to-fall-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's always a moment when you start to fall out of love, whether it's with a person or an idea or a cause, even if it's one you only narrate to yourself years after the event: a tiny thing, a wrong word, a false note, which means that things can never be quite the same again." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/389201-it-is-sometimes-said-that-scientists-are-unromantic-that-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 01:59:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annisa add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/389201-it-is-sometimes-said-that-scientists-are-unromantic-that-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is sometimes said that scientists are unromantic, that their passion to figure out robs the world of beauty and mystery. But is it not stirring to understand how the world actually works — that white light is made of colors, that color is the way we perceive the wavelengths of light, that transparent air reflects light, that in so doing it discriminates among the waves, and that the sky is blue for the same reason that the sunset is red? It does no harm to the romance of the sunset to know a little bit about it." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
