<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/620662-marie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/620662-marie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 22:18:28 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62588-listen-you-can-be-anything-you-want-to-be-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 22:18:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Melvin Burgess]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62588-listen-you-can-be-anything-you-want-to-be-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen. You can be anything you want to be. Be careful. It's a spell. It's magic. Listen to the words. You can be anything, you can do anything, you can be anything, you can do anything. Listen to the magic.
	You are anything . . . everyone, anyone. Whatever you want. I'm showing you. So long as you stay yourself inside, you can eat dirt and it'll taste good because it's you that's eating it. You can even lick their arses if you have to. You listen to them, teachers, parents, politicians. They're always saying, if you steal you're a thief, if you sleep around you're a slut, if you take drugs you're a junkie. They want to get inside your head and control you with their fear. 
	Maybe you think your mum and dad love you but if you do the wrong things they'll try and turn you into dirt. It's your punishment for being you. Don't play their game. Nothing can touch you; you stay beautiful. 
	I've done everything. All of it. You think it, I've done it.  
	All the things you never dared, all the things you dream about, all the things you were curious about and then forgot because you knew you never would. I did 'em, I did 'em yesterday while you were still in bed,
	What about you? When's it going to be your turn?" -- Melvin Burgess]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62989-dear-friend-i-feel-great-i-really-mean-it-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2008 09:38:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62989-dear-friend-i-feel-great-i-really-mean-it-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dear friend,
I feel great! I really mean it. I have to remember his for the next time I'm having a terrible week. Have you wer done that? You feel really bad, and then it goes away, and you don't know why. I try to remind myself when I feel great like this that there will be another terrible week coming someday, so I should store up as many great details as I can, so during the next terrible week, I can remember those details and believe that I'll feel great again. It doesn't work a lot, but I think it's very important to try. " -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64356-i-believe-that-sanitizing-this-aspect-of-the-modern-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2008 20:44:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Tamora Pierce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64356-i-believe-that-sanitizing-this-aspect-of-the-modern-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that sanitizing this aspect of the modern and ancient world is at the root of our troubles as a culture now. We're bred to be smug about how peaceful we are, so we can watch television and feel safely distant from violence, when it is part of our makeup. That smugness means we don't feel we have to do anything about the violence we see, because it's obviously committed by people who aren't as educated or civilized as we are. By holding ourselves aloof from global and historical violence, we allow it to continue. If we are ever to survive as a species, we need to admit we are violent and find ways to ease the plight of the victims of violence worldwide. (No, invading a violent country and bombing it will not inspire its people to give violence up. Go figure.) We must face who we are and what creates violence: helplessness, envy, rage, even the drive to grab the good things of the world that are flaunted in the faces of the poor. We must take responsibility and protect each other from violence." -- Tamora Pierce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139311-it-s-like-the-people-who-believe-they-ll-be-happy-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 12:04:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139311-it-s-like-the-people-who-believe-they-ll-be-happy-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's like the people who believe they'll be happy if they go and live somewhere else, but who learn it doesn't work that way. Wherever you go, you take yourself with you. If you see what I mean." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 19:28:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.

So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17178-here-is-a-lesson-in-creative-writing-first-rule-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 19:30:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17178-here-is-a-lesson-in-creative-writing-first-rule-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here is a lesson in creative writing. First rule: Do not use semicolons. They are transvestite hermaphrodites representing absolutely nothing. All they do is show you've been to college." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3172-and-i-urge-you-to-please-notice-when-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 19:30:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3172-and-i-urge-you-to-please-notice-when-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I urge you to please notice when you are happy, and exclaim or murmur or think at some point, 'If this isn't nice, I don't know what is." -- Kurt Vonnegut Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10317-francois-rabelais-he-was-a-poet-and-his-last-words</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2012 21:45:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10317-francois-rabelais-he-was-a-poet-and-his-last-words]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Francois Rabelais. He was a poet. And his last words were &quot;I go to seek a Great Perhaps.&quot; That's why I'm going. So I don't have to wait until I die to start seeking a Great Perhaps." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
