<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/620884-benjamin-lupton]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/620884-benjamin-lupton" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 20:45:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171417-don-t-aim-for-success-if-you-want-it-just-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 20:45:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by David Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171417-don-t-aim-for-success-if-you-want-it-just-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't aim for success if you want it; just do what you love and believe in, and it will come naturally." -- David Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/520781-some-people-live-in-cages-with-bars-built-from-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 01:46:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/520781-some-people-live-in-cages-with-bars-built-from-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people live in cages with bars built from their own fears and doubts. Some people live in cages with bars built from other people's fears and doubts; their parents, their friends, their brothers and sisters, their families. Some people live in cages with bars built from the choices others made for them, the circumstances other people imposed upon them. And some people break free." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61119-in-truth-there-are-only-two-kinds-of-people-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 01:48:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61119-in-truth-there-are-only-two-kinds-of-people-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In truth, there are only two kinds of people; those who accept dogma and know it, and those who accept dogma and don't know it." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/910971-you-will-face-your-greatest-opposition-when-you-are-closest</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 01:50:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Shannon L. Alder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/910971-you-will-face-your-greatest-opposition-when-you-are-closest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You will face your greatest opposition when you are closest to your biggest miracle." -- Shannon L. Alder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248403-curiosity-and-irreverence-go-together-curiosity-cannot-exist-without-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 01:50:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Saul Alinsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248403-curiosity-and-irreverence-go-together-curiosity-cannot-exist-without-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Curiosity and irreverence go together. Curiosity cannot exist without the other. Curiosity asks, &quot;Is this true?&quot; &quot;Just because this has always been the way, is the best or right way of life, the best or right religion, political or economic value, morality?&quot; To the questioner, nothing is sacred. He detests dogma, defies any finite definition of morality, rebels against any repression of a free, open search of ideas no matter where they may lead. He is challenging, insulting, agitating, discrediting. He stirs unrest." -- Saul Alinsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136399-in-essentials-unity-in-non-essentials-liberty-in-all-things-charity</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 01:51:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Rupertus Meldenius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136399-in-essentials-unity-in-non-essentials-liberty-in-all-things-charity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In essentials, unity; in non-essentials, liberty; in all things, charity." -- Rupertus Meldenius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256050-belief-in-the-traditional-sense-or-certitude-or-dogma-amounts</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 01:52:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256050-belief-in-the-traditional-sense-or-certitude-or-dogma-amounts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Belief in the traditional sense, or certitude, or dogma, amounts to the grandiose delusion, &quot;My current model&quot; -- or grid, or map, or reality-tunnel -- &quot;contains the whole universe and will never need to be revised.&quot; In terms of the history of science and knowledge in general, this appears absurd and arrogant to me, and I am perpetually astonished that so many people still manage to live with such a medieval attitude." -- Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88665-the-greater-the-ignorance-the-greater-the-dogmatism</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 01:53:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Sir William Osler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88665-the-greater-the-ignorance-the-greater-the-dogmatism]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greater the ignorance the greater the dogmatism." -- Sir William Osler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97628-a-word-about-my-personal-philosophy-it-is-anchored-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 13:09:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Saul Alinsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97628-a-word-about-my-personal-philosophy-it-is-anchored-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A word about my personal philosophy.  It is anchored in optimism.  It must be, for optimism brings with it hope, a future with a purpose, and therefore, a will to fight for a better world.  Without this optimism, there is no reason to carry on.  If we think of the struggle as  aclimb up a mountain, then we must visualize a mountain with no top.  We see a top, but when we finall yreach it, the overcast rises and we find ourselves merely on a bluff.  The mountain continues on up.  Now we see the &quot;real&quot; top ahead of us, and strive for it, only to find we've reached another bluff, the top still above us. And so it goes on, interminably.
Knowing that the mountain has no top, that it is a perpetual quest from plateau to plateau, the question arises, &quot;Why the struggle, the conflict, the heartbreak, the danger, the sacrifice.  Why the constant climb?&quot;  Our answer is the same as that which a real mountain climber gives when he is asked why he does what he does.  &quot;Because it's there.&quot;  Because life is there ahead of you and either one tests oneself in its challenges or huddles in the valleys of a dreamless day-to-day existence whose only purpose is the preservation of a illusory security and safety.  The latter is what the vast majority of people choose to do, fearing the adventure into the known.  Paradocically, they give up the dream of what may lie ahead on the heighs of tomorrow for a perpetual nightmare - an endless succession of days fearing the loss of a tenuous security." -- Saul Alinsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251821-if-people-don-t-think-they-have-the-power-to-solve</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 13:10:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Saul Alinsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251821-if-people-don-t-think-they-have-the-power-to-solve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If people don't think they have the power to solve their problems, they won't even think about how to solve them." -- Saul Alinsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/348132-i-alternate-between-feeling-sympathetic-toward-humanity-and-being-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 05:16:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by John R Lindensmith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/348132-i-alternate-between-feeling-sympathetic-toward-humanity-and-being-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I alternate between feeling sympathetic toward humanity and being a misanthrope. When I'm sympathetic, it usually means I haven't been around people in awhile." -- John R Lindensmith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674201-you-call-me-a-misanthrope-because-i-avoid-society-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 05:16:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Caspar David Friedrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674201-you-call-me-a-misanthrope-because-i-avoid-society-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You call me a misanthrope because I avoid society. You err; I love society. Yet in order not to hate people, I must avoid their company." -- Caspar David Friedrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287104-pragmatically-speaking-i-like-the-fact-that-the-masses-vote</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 05:17:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Matt Paradise]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287104-pragmatically-speaking-i-like-the-fact-that-the-masses-vote]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pragmatically speaking, I like the fact that the masses vote, abuse drugs, believe in Jesus, follow sports, and worship a flag. They are tools of social engineering that keep the many-too-many sedate, pacified, and out of many people's hair (chiefly, my own)." -- Matt Paradise]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/953714-i-am-a-misanthrope-but-exceedingly-benevolent-i-am-very</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 05:18:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Alfred Bernhard Nobel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/953714-i-am-a-misanthrope-but-exceedingly-benevolent-i-am-very]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am a misanthrope, but exceedingly benevolent; I am very cranky, and am a super-idealist. ... I can digest philosophy better than food." -- Alfred Bernhard Nobel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229166-by-four-o-clock-i-ve-discounted-suicide-in-favor-of-killing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 05:31:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Warren Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229166-by-four-o-clock-i-ve-discounted-suicide-in-favor-of-killing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By four o'clock, I've discounted suicide in favor of killing everyone else in the entire world instead." -- Warren Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518525-man-was-born-for-society-however-little-he-may-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 05:34:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Matthew Gregory Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518525-man-was-born-for-society-however-little-he-may-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man was born for society. However little He may be attached to the World, He never can wholly forget it, or bear to be wholly forgotten by it. Disgusted at the guilt or absurdity of Mankind, the Misanthrope flies from it: He resolves to become an Hermit, and buries himself in the Cavern of some gloomy Rock. While Hate inflames his bosom, possibly He may feel contented with his situation: But when his passions begin to cool; when Time has mellowed his sorrows, and healed those wounds which He bore with him to his solitude, think you that Content becomes his Companion? Ah! no, Rosario. No longer sustained by the violence of his passions, He feels all the monotony of his way of living, and his heart becomes the prey of Ennui and weariness. He looks round, and finds himself alone in the Universe: The love of society revives in his bosom, and He pants to return to that world which He has abandoned. Nature loses all her charms in his eyes: No one is near him to point out her beauties, or share in his admiration of her excellence and variety. Propped upon the fragment of some Rock, He gazes upon the tumbling waterfall with a vacant eye, He views without emotion the glory of the setting Sun. Slowly He returns to his Cell at Evening, for no one there is anxious for his arrival; He has no comfort in his solitary unsavoury meal: He throws himself upon his couch of Moss despondent and dissatisfied, and wakes only to pass a day as joyless, as monotonous as the former." -- Matthew Gregory Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/557722-in-that-moment-as-he-saw-and-smelled-how-irresistible</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 05:35:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Patrick Süskind]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/557722-in-that-moment-as-he-saw-and-smelled-how-irresistible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…in that moment, as he saw and smelled how irresistible its effect was and how with lightning speed it spread and made captives of the people all around him—in that moment his whole disgust for humankind rose up again within him and completely soured his triumph, so that he felt not only no joy, but not even the least bit of satisfaction. What he had always longed for—that other people should love him—became at the moment of his achievement unbearable, because he did not love them himself, he hated them. And suddenly he knew that he had never found gratification in love, but always only in hatred—in hating and in being hated." -- Patrick Süskind]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/949380-the-one-thing-in-me-more-powerful-than-a-general</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 07:34:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Jasper Sole]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/949380-the-one-thing-in-me-more-powerful-than-a-general]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The one thing in me more powerful than a general misanthropy is an inescapable compassion for individuals." -- Jasper Sole]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/691757-pain-and-darkness-have-been-our-lot-since-the-fall</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 07:38:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Dan Simmons]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/691757-pain-and-darkness-have-been-our-lot-since-the-fall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pain and darkness have been our lot since the Fall of Man. But there must be some hope that we can rise to a higher level ... that consciousness can evolve to a plane more benevolent than its counterpoint of a universe hardwired to indifference." -- Dan Simmons]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/744245-i-know-what-cancer-was-how-is-it-like-humankind</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 07:38:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Dan Simmons]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/744245-i-know-what-cancer-was-how-is-it-like-humankind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know what cancer was.  How is it like humankind?&quot;

Sek Hardeen's perfectly modulated, softly accented tones showed a hint of agitation.  &quot;We have spread out through the galaxy like cancer cells through a living body, Duré.  We multiply without thought to the countless life forms that must die or be pushed aside so that we may breed and flourish.  We eradicate competing forms of intelligent life." -- Dan Simmons]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/744241-i-wish-we-had-the-technology-to-fight-god-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 07:39:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Dan Simmons]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/744241-i-wish-we-had-the-technology-to-fight-god-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish we had the technology to fight God on an equal basis.  To beard him in his den.  To fight back for all of the injustices heaped on humanity.  To allow him to alter his smug arrogance or be blown to hell." -- Dan Simmons]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/691765-the-great-change-is-when-humankind-accepts-its-role-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 07:39:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Dan Simmons]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/691765-the-great-change-is-when-humankind-accepts-its-role-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Great Change is when humankind accepts its role as part of the natural order of the universe instead of its role as a cancer" -- Dan Simmons]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/912666-i-d-take-cyanide-no-problem-if-it-was-that-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 07:43:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/912666-i-d-take-cyanide-no-problem-if-it-was-that-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd take cyanide no problem if it was that or throwing a cat out in the street, even a moth-eaten, mangy, caterwauling pain in the ass! I'd rather have the thing in bed with me than see it suffer on my account...though when it comes to human beings, I'm only interested in the sick...the ones who can stand up are nothing but mounds of vice and spite...I don't get mixed up in their schemes..." -- Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6406-nothing-in-the-world-is-more-dangerous-than-sincere-ignorance</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 08:19:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6406-nothing-in-the-world-is-more-dangerous-than-sincere-ignorance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing in the world is more dangerous than sincere ignorance and conscientious stupidity." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157260-the-peculiar-predicament-of-the-present-day-self-surely-came-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 22:59:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Walker Percy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157260-the-peculiar-predicament-of-the-present-day-self-surely-came-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The peculiar predicament of the present-day self surely came to pass as a consequence of the disappointment of the high expectations of the self as it entered the age of science and technology.  Dazzled by the overwhelming credentials of science, the beauty and elegance of the scientific method, the triumph of modern medicine over physical ailments, and the technological transformation of the very world itself, the self finds itself in the end disappointed by the failure of science and technique in those very sectors of life which had been its main source of ordinary satisfaction in past ages.

As John Cheever said, the main emotion of the adult Northeastern American who has had all the advantages of wealth, education, and culture is disappointment.

Work is disappointing.  In spite of all the talk about making work more creative and self-fulfilling, most people hate their jobs, and with good reason.  Most work in modern technological societies is intolerably dull and repetitive.

Marriage and family life are disappointing.  Even among defenders of traditional family values, e.g., Christians and Jews, a certain dreariness must be inferred, if only from the average time of TV viewing.  Dreary as TV is, it is evidently not as dreary as Mom talking to Dad or the kids talking to either.

School is disappointing.  If science is exciting and art is exhilarating, the schools and universities have achieved the not inconsiderable feat of rendering both dull.  As every scientist and poet knows, one discovers both vocations in spite of, not because of, school.  It takes years to recover from the stupor of being taught Shakespeare in English Lit and Wheatstone's bridge in Physics.

Politics is disappointing.  Most young people turn their backs on politics, not because of the lack of excitement of politics as it is practiced, but because of the shallowness, venality, and image-making as these are perceived through the media--one of the technology's greatest achievements.

The churches are disappointing, even for most believers.  If Christ brings us new life, it is all the more remarkable that the church, the bearer of this good news, should be among the most dispirited institutions of the age.  The alternatives to the institutional churches are even more grossly disappointing, from TV evangelists with their blown-dry hairdos to California cults led by prosperous gurus ignored in India but embraced in La Jolla.

Social life is disappointing.  The very franticness of attempts to reestablish community and festival, by partying, by groups, by club, by touristy Mardi Gras, is the best evidence of the loss of true community and festival and of the loneliness of self, stranded as it is as an unspeakable consciousness in a world from which it perceives itself as somehow estranged, stranded even within its own body, with which it sees no clear connection. 

But there remains the one unquestioned benefit of science: the longer and healthier life made possible by modern medicine, the shorter work-hours made possible by technology, hence what is perceived as the one certain reward of dreary life of home and the marketplace: recreation.

Recreation and good physical health appear to be the only ambivalent benefits of the technological revolution." -- Walker Percy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215421-the-beginning-of-love-is-the-will-to-let-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 08:01:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Thomas Merton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215421-the-beginning-of-love-is-the-will-to-let-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The beginning of love is the will to let those we love be perfectly themselves, the resolution not to twist them to fit our own image. If in loving them we do not love what they are, but only their potential likeness to ourselves, then we do not love them: we only love the reflection of ourselves we find in them" -- Thomas Merton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27688-for-me-trees-have-always-been-the-most-penetrating-preachers</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 08:01:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Herman Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27688-for-me-trees-have-always-been-the-most-penetrating-preachers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For me, trees have always been the most penetrating preachers. I revere them when they live in tribes and families, in forests and groves. And even more I revere them when they stand alone. They are like lonely persons. Not like hermits who have stolen away out of some weakness, but like great, solitary men, like Beethoven and Nietzsche. In their highest boughs the world rustles, their roots rest in infinity; but they do not lose themselves there, they struggle with all the force of their lives for one thing only: to fulfil themselves according to their own laws, to build up their own form, to represent themselves. Nothing is holier, nothing is more exemplary than a beautiful, strong tree. When a tree is cut down and reveals its naked death-wound to the sun, one can read its whole history in the luminous, inscribed disk of its trunk: in the rings of its years, its scars, all the struggle, all the suffering, all the sickness, all the happiness and prosperity stand truly written, the narrow years and the luxurious years, the attacks withstood, the storms endured. And every young farmboy knows that the hardest and noblest wood has the narrowest rings, that high on the mountains and in continuing danger the most indestructible, the strongest, the ideal trees grow.

     Trees are sanctuaries. Whoever knows how to speak to them, whoever knows how to listen to them, can learn the truth. They do not preach learning and precepts, they preach, undeterred by particulars, the ancient law of life.

     A tree says: A kernel is hidden in me, a spark, a thought, I am life from eternal life. The attempt and the risk that the eternal mother took with me is unique, unique the form and veins of my skin, unique the smallest play of leaves in my branches and the smallest scar on my bark. I was made to form and reveal the eternal in my smallest special detail.

     A tree says: My strength is trust. I know nothing about my fathers, I know nothing about the thousand children that every year spring out of me. I live out the secret of my seed to the very end, and I care for nothing else. I trust that God is in me. I trust that my labor is holy. Out of this trust I live.

     When we are stricken and cannot bear our lives any longer, then a tree has something to say to us: Be still! Be still! Look at me! Life is not easy, life is not difficult. Those are childish thoughts. Let God speak within you, and your thoughts will grow silent. You are anxious because your path leads away from mother and home. But every step and every day lead you back again to the mother. Home is neither here nor there. Home is within you, or home is nowhere at all.

     A longing to wander tears my heart when I hear trees rustling in the wind at evening. If one listens to them silently for a long time, this longing reveals its kernel, its meaning. It is not so much a matter of escaping from one's suffering, though it may seem to be so. It is a longing for home, for a memory of the mother, for new metaphors for life. It leads home. Every path leads homeward, every step is birth, every step is death, every grave is mother.

     So the tree rustles in the evening, when we stand uneasy before our own childish thoughts: Trees have long thoughts, long-breathing and restful, just as they have longer lives than ours. They are wiser than we are, as long as we do not listen to them. But when we have learned how to listen to trees, then the brevity and the quickness and the childlike hastiness of our thoughts achieve an incomparable joy. Whoever has learned how to listen to trees no longer wants to be a tree. He wants to be nothing except what he is. That is home. That is happiness." -- Herman Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28811-i-have-been-and-still-am-a-seeker-but-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 08:04:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28811-i-have-been-and-still-am-a-seeker-but-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have been and still am a seeker, but I have ceased to question stars and books; I have begun to listen to the teaching my blood whispers to me." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44379-until-you-make-the-unconscious-conscious-it-will-direct-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 08:05:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by C.G. Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44379-until-you-make-the-unconscious-conscious-it-will-direct-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until you make the unconscious conscious, it will direct your life and you will call it fate." -- C.G. Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30134-the-only-journey-is-the-one-within</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 08:06:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30134-the-only-journey-is-the-one-within]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only journey is the one within." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
