<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/622321-summer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/622321-summer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2008 20:49:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19080-once-upon-a-time-in-the-dead-of-winter-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2008 20:49:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by David McCullough]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19080-once-upon-a-time-in-the-dead-of-winter-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time in the dead of winter in the Dakota Territory, Theodore Roosevelt took off in a makeshift boat down the Little Missouri River in pursuit of a couple of thieves who had stolen his prized rowboat.  After several days on the river, he caught up and got the draw on them with his trusty Winchester, at which point they surrendered.  Then Roosevelt set off in a borrowed wagon to haul the thieves cross-country to justice.  They headed across the snow-covered wastes of the Badlands to the railhead at Dickinson, and Roosevelt walked the whole way, the entire 40 miles.  It was an astonishing feat, what might be called a defining moment in Roosevelt’s eventful life.  But what makes it especially memorable is that during that time, he managed to read all of &lt;i&gt;Anna Karenina&lt;/i&gt;.  I often think of that when I hear people say they haven’t time to read." -- David McCullough]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27372-i-felt-after-i-finished-slaughterhouse-five-that-i-didn-t-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2008 21:10:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27372-i-felt-after-i-finished-slaughterhouse-five-that-i-didn-t-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I felt after I finished Slaughterhouse-Five that I didn’t have to write at all anymore if I didn’t want to. It was the end of some sort of career. I don’t know why, exactly. I suppose that flowers, when they’re through blooming, have some sort of awareness of some purpose having been served. Flowers didn’t ask to be flowers and I didn’t ask to be me. At the end of Slaughterhouse-Five…I had a shutting-off feeling…that I had done what I was supposed to do and everything was OK ." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42717-and-lot-s-wife-of-course-was-told-not-to-look</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2008 21:11:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42717-and-lot-s-wife-of-course-was-told-not-to-look]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And Lot's wife, of course, was told not to look back where all those people and their homes had been. But she did look back, and I love her for that, because it was so human. So she was turned into a pillar of salt. So it goes." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 09:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always imagined that Paradise will be a kind of library." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5169-what-really-knocks-me-out-is-a-book-that-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 09:12:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5169-what-really-knocks-me-out-is-a-book-that-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What really knocks me out is a book that, when you're all done reading it, you wish the author that wrote it was a terrific friend of yours and you could call him up on the phone whenever you felt like it. That doesn't happen much, though." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 09:12:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I can hear my bones straining under the weight of all the lives I'm not living." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8706-life-will-break-you-nobody-can-protect-you-from-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 09:15:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8706-life-will-break-you-nobody-can-protect-you-from-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life will break you. Nobody can protect you from that, and living alone won't either, for solitude will also break you with its yearning. You have to love. You have to feel. It is the reason you are here on earth. You are here to risk your heart. You are here to be swallowed up. And when it happens that you are broken, or betrayed, or left, or hurt, or death brushes near, let yourself sit by an apple tree and listen to the apples falling all around you in heaps, wasting their sweetness. Tell yourself you tasted as many as you could." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216749-margaret-realized-the-chaotic-nature-of-our-daily-life-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 20:43:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216749-margaret-realized-the-chaotic-nature-of-our-daily-life-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Margaret realized the chaotic nature of our daily life, and its difference from the orderly sequence that has been fabricated by historians. Actual life is full of false clues and sign-posts that lead nowhere. With infinite effort we nerve ourselves for a crisis that never comes. The most successful career must show a waste of strength that might have removed mountains, and the most unsuccessful is no that of a man who is taken unprepared, but of him who has prepared and is never taken. On a tragedy of that kind our national morality is duly silent. It assumes that preparation against danger is in itself a good, and that men, like nations, are the better for staggering through life fully armed. The tragedy of preparedness has scarcely been handled, save by the Greeks. Life is indeed dangerous, but not in the way morality would have us believe. It is indeed unmanageable, but the essence of it is not a battle. It is unmanageable, but the essence of it is not a battle. It is unmanageable because it is a romance, and its essence is romantic beauty." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71689-there-is-no-justice-in-love-no-proportion-in-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2012 08:38:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71689-there-is-no-justice-in-love-no-proportion-in-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no justice in love, no proportion in it, and there need not be, because in any specific instance it is only a glimpse or parable of an embracing, incomprehensible reality. It makes no sense at all because it is the eternal breaking in on the temporal. So how could it subordinate itself to cause or consequence?" -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53417-a-man-can-know-his-father-or-his-son-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2012 08:38:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53417-a-man-can-know-his-father-or-his-son-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man can know his father, or his son, and there might still be nothing between them but loyalty and love and mutual incomprehension." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6029-in-every-important-way-we-are-such-secrets-from-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2012 08:40:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6029-in-every-important-way-we-are-such-secrets-from-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In every important way we are such secrets from one another, and I do believe that there is a separate language in each of us, also a separate aesthetics and a separate jurisprudence. Every single one of us is a little civilization built on the ruins of any number of preceding civilizations, but with our own variant notions of what is beautiful and what is acceptable - which, I hasten to add, we generally do not satisfy and by which we struggle to live. We take fortuitous resemblances among us to be actual likeness, because those around us have also fallen heir to the same customs, trade in the same coin, acknowledge, more or less, the same notions of decency and sanity. But all that really just allows us to coexist with the inviolable, intraversable, and utterly vast spaces between us." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148573-she-was-not-one-for-emptying-her-face-of-expression</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 14:12:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148573-she-was-not-one-for-emptying-her-face-of-expression]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was not one for emptying her face of expression. " -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148608-i-don-t-think-it-would-have-all-got-me-quite</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 14:13:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148608-i-don-t-think-it-would-have-all-got-me-quite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don’t think it would have all got me quite so down if just once in a while—just once in a while—there was at least some polite little perfunctory implication that knowledge should lead to wisdom, and that if it doesn't, it's just a disgusting waste of time! But there never is! You never even hear any hints dropped on a campus that wisdom is supposed to be the goal of knowledge. You hardly ever even hear the word 'wisdom' mentioned!" -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/472558-i-don-t-care-where-an-actor-acts-it-can-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 14:19:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/472558-i-don-t-care-where-an-actor-acts-it-can-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't care where an actor acts. It can be in summer stock, it can be over a radio, it can be over television, it can be in a goddam Broadway theatre, complete with the most fashionable, most well-fed, most sunburned-looking audience you can imagine. But I'll tell you a terrible secret — Are you listening to me? There isn't anyone out there who isn't Seymour's Fat Lady. That includes your Professor Tupper, buddy. And all his goddam cousins by the dozens. There isn't anyone anywhere that isn't Seymour's Fat Lady. Don't you know that? Don't you know that goddam secret yet? And don't you know — listen to me, now — don't you know who that Fat Lady really is? . . . Ah, buddy. Ah, buddy. It's Christ Himself. Christ Himself, buddy." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17931-if-you-want-to-really-hurt-you-parents-and-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 14:23:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17931-if-you-want-to-really-hurt-you-parents-and-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to really hurt you parents, and you don't have the nerve to be gay, the least you can do is go into the arts. I'm not kidding. The arts are not a way to make a living. They are a very human way of making life more bearable. Practicing an art, no matter how well or badly, is a way to make your soul grow, for heaven's sake. Sing in the shower. Dance to the radio. Tell stories. Write a poem to a friend, even a lousy poem. Do it as well as you possible can. You will get an enormous reward. You will have created something." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4490-a-man-sets-out-to-draw-the-world-as-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 14:24:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4490-a-man-sets-out-to-draw-the-world-as-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man sets out to draw the world.  As the years go by, he peoples a space with images of provinces, kingdoms, mountains, bays, ships, islands, fishes, rooms, instruments, stars, horses, and individuals. A short time before he dies, he discovers that the patient labyrinth of lines traces the lineaments of his own face." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9766-in-the-shop-window-you-have-promptly-identified-the-cover</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2013 15:35:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9766-in-the-shop-window-you-have-promptly-identified-the-cover]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the shop window you have promptly identified the cover with the title you were looking for. Following this visual trail, you have forced your way through the shop past the thick barricade of Books You Haven't Read, which are frowning at you from the tables and shelves, trying to cow you...And thus you pass the outer girdle of ramparts, but then you are attacked by the infantry of Books That If You Had More Than One Life You Would Certainly Also Read But Unfortunately Your Days Are Numbered. With a rapid maneuver you bypass them and move into the phalanxes of the Books You Mean To Read But There Are Others You Must Read First, the Books Too Expensive Now And You'll Wait Till They're Remaindered, the Books ditto When They Come Out in Paperback, Books You Can Borrow From Somebody, Books That Everybody's Read So It's As If You Had Read Them, Too. " -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
