<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/624440-tobin-elliott]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/624440-tobin-elliott" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 10:44:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/854199-q-do-you-have-any-advice-for-upcoming-writers-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 10:44:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tobin add a quote by T.E. Grau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/854199-q-do-you-have-any-advice-for-upcoming-writers-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Q: Do you have any advice for upcoming writers who want to pen weird stories?

A:  READ, damn it.  Fill your brain to the bursting point with the good stuff, starting with writers that you truly enjoy, and then work your way backward and outward, reading those writers who inspired the writers you love best.  That was my path as far as Weird/Horror Fiction, starting with Lovecraft, and then working my way backward/outward on the Weird Fiction spiderweb.   And don’t limit your reading.  Read it all, especially non-fiction and various news outlets.  You’d be surprised by how many of my story ideas were born while listening to NPR, perusing a blog, or paging through Vanity Fair.

Once you have your fuel squared away, just write what you love, in whatever style and genre.  You’ll never have fun being someone you’re not, so be yourself.  When a singer opens their mouth, what comes out is what comes out.

Also, don’t be afraid to fail, and don’t be afraid to walk away.  Writing isn’t for everyone, and that’s totally fine.  One doesn’t need to be a writer to enjoy being a reader and overall fan of genre or wider fiction." -- T.E. Grau]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
