<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/625856-maria]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/625856-maria" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 06:52:22 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206045-there-is-no-point-treating-a-depressed-person-as-though</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 06:52:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206045-there-is-no-point-treating-a-depressed-person-as-though]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no point treating a depressed person as though she were just feeling sad, saying, 'There now, hang on, you'll get over it.' Sadness is more or less like a head cold- with patience, it passes. Depression is like cancer." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11468-at-heart-i-have-always-been-a-coper-i-ve-mostly</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 06:55:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11468-at-heart-i-have-always-been-a-coper-i-ve-mostly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At heart, I have always been a coper, I've mostly been able to walk around with my wounds safely hidden, and I've always stored up my deep depressive episodes for the weeks off when there was time to have an abbreviated version of a complete breakdown.  But in the end, I'd be able to get up and on with it, could always do what little must be done to scratch by." -- Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180984-others-imply-that-they-know-what-it-is-like-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 06:55:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Kay Redfield Jamison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180984-others-imply-that-they-know-what-it-is-like-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Others imply that they know what it is like to be depressed because they have gone through a divorce, lost a job, or broken up with someone. But these experiences carry with them feelings. Depression, instead, is flat, hollow, and unendurable. It is also tiresome. People cannot abide being around you when you are depressed. They might think that they ought to, and they might even try, but you know and they know that you are tedious beyond belief: you are irritable and paranoid and humorless and lifeless and critical and demanding and no reassurance is ever enough. You're frightened, and you're frightening, and you're &quot;not at all like yourself but will be soon,&quot; but you know you won't." -- Kay Redfield Jamison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67312-choking-with-dry-tears-and-raging-raging-raging-at-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 06:57:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Stephen Fry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67312-choking-with-dry-tears-and-raging-raging-raging-at-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Choking with dry tears and raging, raging, raging at the absolute indifference of nature and the world to the death of love, the death of hope and the death of beauty, I remember sitting on the end of my bed, collecting these pills and capsules together and wondering why, why when I felt I had so much to offer, so much love, such outpourings of love and energy to spend on the world, I was incapable of being offered love, giving it or summoning the energy with which I knew I could transform myself and everything around me." -- Stephen Fry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172352-some-catastrophic-moments-invite-clarity-explode-in-split-moments-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 06:59:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172352-some-catastrophic-moments-invite-clarity-explode-in-split-moments-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some catastrophic moments invite clarity, explode in split moments: You smash your hand through a windowpane and then there is blood and shattered glass stained with red all over the place; you fall out a window and break some bones and scrape some skin. Stitches and casts and bandages and antiseptic solve and salve the wounds. But depression is not a sudden disaster. It is more like a cancer: At first its tumorous mass is not even noticeable to the careful eye, and then one day -- wham! -- there is a huge, deadly seven-pound lump lodged in your brain or your stomach or your shoulder blade, and this thing that your own body has produced is actually trying to kill you. Depression is a lot like that: Slowly, over the years, the data will accumulate in your heart and mind, a computer program for total negativity will build into your system, making life feel more and more unbearable. But you won't even notice it coming on, thinking that it is somehow normal, something about getting older, about turning eight or turning twelve or turning fifteen, and then one day you realize that your entire life is just awful, not worth living, a horror and a black blot on the white terrain of human existence. One morning you wake up afraid you are going to live.

In my case, I was not frightened in the least bit at the thought that I might live because I was certain, quite certain, that I was already dead. The actual dying part, the withering away of my physical body, was a mere formality. My spirit, my emotional being, whatever you want to call all that inner turmoil that has nothing to do with physical existence, were long gone, dead and gone, and only a mass of the most fucking god-awful excruciating pain like a pair of boiling hot tongs clamped tight around my spine and pressing on all my nerves was left in its wake.

That's the thing I want to make clear about depression: It's got nothing at all to do with life. In the course of life, there is sadness and pain and sorrow, all of which, in their right time and season, are normal -- unpleasant, but normal. Depression is an altogether different zone because it involves a complete absence: absence of affect, absence of feeling, absence of response, absence of interest. The pain you feel in the course of a major clinical depression is an attempt on nature's part (nature, after all, abhors a vacuum) to fill up the empty space. But for all intents and purposes, the deeply depressed are just the walking, waking dead.

And the scariest part is that if you ask anyone in the throes of depression how he got there, to pin down the turning point, he'll never know. There is a classic moment in The Sun Also Rises when someone asks Mike Campbell how he went bankrupt, and all he can say in response is, 'Gradually and then suddenly.' When someone asks how I love my mind, that is all I can say too" -- Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244781-it-is-not-seen-as-insane-when-a-fighter-under</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 06:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Emilie Autumn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244781-it-is-not-seen-as-insane-when-a-fighter-under]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not seen as insane when a fighter, under an attack that will inevitable lead to his death, chooses to take his own life first. In fact, this act has been encouraged for centuries, and is accepted even now as an honorable reason to do the deed. How is it any different when you are under attack by your own mind?" -- Emilie Autumn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196423-mental-illness-is-so-much-more-complicated-than-any-pill</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 06:59:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196423-mental-illness-is-so-much-more-complicated-than-any-pill]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mental illness is so much more complicated than any pill that any mortal could invent " -- Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98109-even-when-i-try-to-stir-myself-up-i-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:00:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Banana Yoshimoto]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98109-even-when-i-try-to-stir-myself-up-i-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even when I try to stir myself up, I just get irritated because I can't make anything come out. And in the middle of the night I lie here thinking about all this. If I don't get back on track somehow, I'm dead, that's the sense I get. There isn't a single strong emotion inside me." -- Banana Yoshimoto]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5099-crying-is-one-of-the-highest-devotional-songs-one-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:00:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Kripalvanandji]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5099-crying-is-one-of-the-highest-devotional-songs-one-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Crying is one of the highest devotional songs.  One who knows crying, knows spiritual practice.  If you can cry with a pure heart, nothing else compares to such a prayer.  Crying includes all the principles of Yoga." -- Kripalvanandji]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183909-one-swallow-does-not-make-a-summer-neither-does-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:01:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Aristotle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183909-one-swallow-does-not-make-a-summer-neither-does-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One swallow does not make a summer,
neither does one fine day; 
similarly one day or brief time of happiness does not make a person entirely happy." -- Aristotle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/388617-depression-is-the-most-unpleasant-thing-i-have-ever-experienced</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:02:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/388617-depression-is-the-most-unpleasant-thing-i-have-ever-experienced]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Depression is the most unpleasant thing I have ever experienced. . . .  It is that absence of being able to envisage that you will ever be cheerful again.  The absence of hope.  That very deadened feeling, which is so very different from feeling sad.  Sad hurts but it's a healthy feeling.  It is a necessary thing to feel.  Depression is very different." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353453-killing-oneself-is-anyway-a-misnomer-we-don-t-kill-ourselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:03:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Sally Brampton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353453-killing-oneself-is-anyway-a-misnomer-we-don-t-kill-ourselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Killing oneself is, anyway, a misnomer. We don't kill ourselves. We are simply defeated by the long, hard struggle to stay alive. When somebody dies after a long illness, people are apt to say, with a note of approval, &quot;He fought so hard.&quot; And they are inclined to think, about a suicide, that no fight was involved, that somebody simply gave up. This is quite wrong." -- Sally Brampton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178485-no-amount-of-love-can-cure-madness-or-unblacken-one-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:03:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Kay Redfield Jamison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178485-no-amount-of-love-can-cure-madness-or-unblacken-one-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No amount of love can cure madness or unblacken one's dark moods. Love can help, it can make the pain more tolerable, but, always, one is beholden to medication that may or may not always work and may or may not be bearable" -- Kay Redfield Jamison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367496-i-start-to-think-there-really-is-no-cure-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:05:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367496-i-start-to-think-there-really-is-no-cure-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I start to think there really is no cure for depression, that happiness is an ongoing battle, and I wonder if it isn't one I'll have to fight for as long as I live. I wonder if it's worth it." -- Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177747-i-appear-at-times-merry-and-in-good-heart-talk</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:05:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Hugo Wolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177747-i-appear-at-times-merry-and-in-good-heart-talk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I appear at times merry and in good heart, talk, too, before others quite reasonably, and it looks as if I felt, too, God knows how well within my skin. Yet the soul maintains its deathly sleep and the heart bleeds from a thousand wounds." -- Hugo Wolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167848-you-can-tell-a-lot-from-a-person-s-nails-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:05:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167848-you-can-tell-a-lot-from-a-person-s-nails-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can tell a lot from a person's nails. When a life starts to unravel, they're among the first to go." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422155-mental-pain-is-less-dramatic-than-physical-pain-but-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:06:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422155-mental-pain-is-less-dramatic-than-physical-pain-but-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mental pain is less dramatic than physical pain, but it is more common and also more hard to bear. The frequent attempt to conceal mental pain increases the burden: it is easier to say “My tooth is aching” than to say “My heart is broken." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350008-you-know-all-that-sympathy-that-you-feel-for-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:07:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Ashly Lorenzana]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350008-you-know-all-that-sympathy-that-you-feel-for-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know all that sympathy that you feel for an abused child who suffers without a good mom or dad to love and care for them? Well, they don't stay children forever. No one magically becomes an adult the day they turn eighteen. Some people grow up sooner, many grow up later. Some never really do. But just remember that some people in this world are older versions of those same kids we cry for." -- Ashly Lorenzana]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405322-he-knows-bad-days-bad-days-take-him-completely-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:07:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405322-he-knows-bad-days-bad-days-take-him-completely-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He knows bad days. Bad days take him completely by surprise. They make him not trust the good days because it's likely something is lurking twenty-four hours away." -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367327-dearest-i-feel-certain-that-i-am-going-mad-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:08:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367327-dearest-i-feel-certain-that-i-am-going-mad-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dearest, I feel certain that I am going mad again. I feel we can't go through another of those terrible times. And I shan't recover this time. I begin to hear voices, and I can't concentrate. So I am doing what seems the best thing to do. You have given me the greatest possible happiness. You have been in every way all that anyone could be. I don't think two people could have been happier 'til this terrible disease came. I can't fight any longer. I know that I am spoiling your life, that without me you could work. And you will I know. You see I can't even write this properly. I can't read. What I want to say is I owe all the happiness of my life to you. You have been entirely patient with me and incredibly good. I want to say that – everybody knows it. If anybody could have saved me it would have been you. Everything has gone from me but the certainty of your goodness. I can't go on spoiling your life any longer. I don't think two people could have been happier than we have been. V." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358133-it-s-nonverbal-i-need-love-i-need-the-thing-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:08:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358133-it-s-nonverbal-i-need-love-i-need-the-thing-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's nonverbal: I need love. I need the thing that happens when your brain shuts off and your heart turns on. And I know it's around me somewhere, but I just can't feel it." -- Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/507916-if-you-know-someone-who-s-depressed-please-resolve-never-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:10:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Stephen Fry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/507916-if-you-know-someone-who-s-depressed-please-resolve-never-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you know someone who’s depressed, please resolve never to ask them why. Depression isn’t a straightforward response to a bad situation; depression just is, like the weather.

Try to understand the blackness, lethargy, hopelessness, and loneliness they’re going through. Be there for them when they come through the other side. It’s hard to be a friend to someone who’s depressed, but it is one of the kindest, noblest, and best things you will ever do." -- Stephen Fry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488879-depression-is-like-a-bruise-that-never-goes-away-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:10:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488879-depression-is-like-a-bruise-that-never-goes-away-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Depression is like a bruise that never goes away. A bruise in your mind. You just got to be careful not to touch it where it hurts. It's always there, though." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353452-sometimes-says-a-fellow-depressive-i-wish-i-was-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:11:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Sally Brampton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353452-sometimes-says-a-fellow-depressive-i-wish-i-was-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes,&quot; says a fellow depressive, &quot;I wish I was in a full body cast, with every bone in my body broken. That's how I feel anyway. Then, maybe, people would stop minimising my illness because they can actually see what's wrong with me. They seem to need physical evidence." -- Sally Brampton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/306315-i-thought-about-suicide-all-the-time-but-it-seemed</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:13:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Helena Dela]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/306315-i-thought-about-suicide-all-the-time-but-it-seemed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I thought about suicide all the time, but it seemed toomuch effort, swallowing all those pills or jumping off things.  If I'd lived out in the country I would have found a quiet stretch of railway track, and lain on it, fallen asleep, so that I would never have known when my last moment came.  In London, the minimum tube fare had gone up so much that even to get near the line cost a fortune.  Suicide seemed an extravagance I couldn't afford.  People never leave you alone, either; I knew that if I'd tried to lie down on the line, any number of commuters would have pulled me off again, so that I didn't delay their train.  
  There must have been murderers out there who wanted to kill, with no way of finding those who wanted to be dead.  If there had been some way of contacting them, a date-with-death line, I would have called them to set up a meeting.  The current ways of death seemed too haphazard; it was all left up to chance.  Had Chance come up, tapped me on the shoulder, said &quot;Oi, you - long black tunnel, white light, off you go,&quot; I wouldn't have complained.  
It was like having frostbite all over - feeling numb and in pain at the same time." -- Helena Dela]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25411-not-waving-but-drowning-nobody-heard-him-the-dead-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:13:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Stevie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25411-not-waving-but-drowning-nobody-heard-him-the-dead-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not Waving but Drowning 

Nobody heard him, the dead man, 
But still he lay moaning: 
I was much further out than you thought 
And not waving but drowning. 

Poor chap, he always loved larking 
And now he's dead 
It must have been too cold for him his heart gave way, 
They said. 

Oh, no no no, it was too cold always 
(Still the dead one lay moaning) 
I was much too far out all my life 
And not waving but drowning." -- Stevie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180181-sometimes-they-open-it-up-like-a-package-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:14:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Julia Schumacher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180181-sometimes-they-open-it-up-like-a-package-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...Sometimes they open it up like a package in the presence of a person they can talk to,' she said. 'Someone they can trust.' She held out her hands. 'Any person who is carrying a lot of sadness,' she said, 'needs to be able to rest sometimes, and to put it down." -- Julia Schumacher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173930-sufferers-of-depression-who-can-elect-to-keep-their-feelings</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 07:14:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by David Karp]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173930-sufferers-of-depression-who-can-elect-to-keep-their-feelings]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["sufferers of depression, who can elect to keep their feelings private, experience chronic, unremitting emotional alienation. Each moment spent “passing” as normal deepens the sense of disconnection generated by depression in the first instance. In this regard, depression stands as a nearly pure case of impression-management. For depressed individuals, the social requirement to “put on a happy face” requires subjugation of an especially intense inner experience. Yet, nearly unbelievably, many severely depressed people “pull off the act” for long periods of time. The price of the performance is to further exacerbate a life condition that already seems impossibly painful  " -- David Karp]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
