<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/626626-nullifidian]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/626626-nullifidian" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 03:55:22 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34852-a-man-who-dares-to-waste-one-hour-of-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 03:55:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Charles Darwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34852-a-man-who-dares-to-waste-one-hour-of-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man who dares to waste one hour of time has not discovered the value of life." -- Charles Darwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3895-thus-from-the-war-of-nature-from-famine-and-death</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 03:55:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Charles Darwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3895-thus-from-the-war-of-nature-from-famine-and-death]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thus, from the war of nature, from famine and death, the most exalted object which we are capable of conceiving, namely, the production of the higher animals, directly follows. There is grandeur in this view of life, with its several powers, having been originally breathed into a few forms or into one; and that, whilst this planet has gone cycling on according to the fixed law of gravity, from so simple a beginning endless forms most beautiful and most wonderful have been, and are being, evolved." -- Charles Darwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18875-it-is-not-the-strongest-of-the-species-that-survives</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 03:55:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Leon C. Megginson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18875-it-is-not-the-strongest-of-the-species-that-survives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not the strongest of the species that survives, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change." -- Leon C. Megginson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24141-ignorance-more-frequently-begets-confidence-than-does-knowledge-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 03:55:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Charles Darwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24141-ignorance-more-frequently-begets-confidence-than-does-knowledge-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ignorance more frequently begets confidence than does knowledge: it is those who know little, not those who know much, who so positively assert that this or that problem will never be solved by science." -- Charles Darwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487906-the-fire-the-odor-of-burning-juniper-is-the-sweetest</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 10:02:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487906-the-fire-the-odor-of-burning-juniper-is-the-sweetest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fire. The odor of burning juniper is the sweetest fragrance on the face of the earth, in my honest judgment; I doubt if all the smoking censers of Dante's paradise could equal it. One breath of juniper smoke, like the perfume of sagebrush after rain, evokes in magical catalysis, like certain music, the space and light and clarity and piercing strangeness of the American West. Long may it burn." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/743443-it-is-one-of-the-major-tragedies-that-nothing-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 23:08:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Sinclair Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/743443-it-is-one-of-the-major-tragedies-that-nothing-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is one of the major tragedies that nothing is more discomforting than the hearty affection of the Old Friends who never were friends." -- Sinclair Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407602-new-rule-stop-asking-miss-usa-contestants-if-they-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 09:42:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Bill Maher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407602-new-rule-stop-asking-miss-usa-contestants-if-they-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["New Rule: Stop asking Miss USA contestants if they believe in evolution. It’s not their field. It’s like asking Stephen Hawking if he believes in hair scrunchies. Here’s what they know about: spray tans, fake boobs and baton twirling. Here’s what they don’t know about: everything else. If I cared about the uninformed opinions of some ditsy beauty queen, I’d join the Tea Party." -- Bill Maher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125537-those-who-do-not-move-do-not-notice-their-chains</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 09:43:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Rosa Luxemburg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125537-those-who-do-not-move-do-not-notice-their-chains]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who do not move, do not notice their chains." -- Rosa Luxemburg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293400-it-is-not-the-strongest-or-the-most-intelligent-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 09:43:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Charles Darwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293400-it-is-not-the-strongest-or-the-most-intelligent-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not the strongest or the most intelligent who will survive but those who can best manage change." -- Charles Darwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74123-responding-to-the-bishop-of-oxford-samuel-wilberforce-s-question-whether</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 09:47:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Thomas Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74123-responding-to-the-bishop-of-oxford-samuel-wilberforce-s-question-whether]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[&lt;i&gt;Responding to the Bishop of Oxford, Samuel Wilberforce's question whether he traced his descent from an ape on his mother's or his father's side&lt;/i&gt;]

A man has no reason to be ashamed of having an ape for his grandfather. If there were an ancestor whom I should feel shame in recalling it would rather be a &lt;i&gt;man&lt;/i&gt;—a man of restless and versatile intellect—who … plunges into scientific questions with which he has no real acquaintance, only to obscure them by an aimless rhetoric, and distract the attention of his hearers from the real point at issue by eloquent digressions and skilled appeals to religious prejudice." -- Thomas Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7085-the-chess-board-is-the-world-the-pieces-are-the-phenomena</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 16:15:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Thomas Henry Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7085-the-chess-board-is-the-world-the-pieces-are-the-phenomena]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The chess-board is the world; the pieces are the phenomena of the universe; the rules of the game are what we call the laws of Nature. The player on the other side is hidden from us. We know that his play is always fair, and patient. But also we know, to our cost, that he never overlooks a mistake, or makes the smallest allowance for ignorance." -- Thomas Henry Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213185-it-is-far-better-for-a-man-to-go-wrong</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 16:16:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Thomas H. Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213185-it-is-far-better-for-a-man-to-go-wrong]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is far better for a man to go wrong in freedom than to go right in chains." -- Thomas H. Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6085-we-live-in-a-world-which-is-full-of-misery</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 16:16:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Thomas Henry Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6085-we-live-in-a-world-which-is-full-of-misery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We live in a world which is full of misery and ignorance, and the plain duty of each and all of us is to try to make the little corner he can influence somewhat less miserable and somewhat less ignorant than it was before he entered." -- Thomas Henry Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328134-socialism-never-took-root-in-america-because-the-poor-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 16:16:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328134-socialism-never-took-root-in-america-because-the-poor-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Socialism never took root in America because the poor see themselves not as an exploited proletariat but as temporarily embarrassed millionaires." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20432-if-voting-changed-anything-they-d-make-it-illegal</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 16:17:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Emma Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20432-if-voting-changed-anything-they-d-make-it-illegal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If voting changed anything, they'd make it illegal." -- Emma Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2349-the-philosophy-of-atheism-represents-a-concept-of-life-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 16:17:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Emma Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2349-the-philosophy-of-atheism-represents-a-concept-of-life-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The philosophy of Atheism represents a concept of life without any metaphysical Beyond or Divine Regulator. It is the concept of an actual, real world with its liberating, expanding and beautifying possibilities, as against an unreal world, which, with its spirits, oracles, and mean contentment has kept humanity in helpless degradation." -- Emma Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/745898-inhumanity-is-the-keynote-of-stupidity-in-power</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 16:21:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Alexander Berkman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/745898-inhumanity-is-the-keynote-of-stupidity-in-power]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Inhumanity is the keynote of stupidity in power." -- Alexander Berkman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193950-companions-the-creator-seeks-not-corpses-not-herds-and-believers</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 20:46:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193950-companions-the-creator-seeks-not-corpses-not-herds-and-believers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Companions the creator seeks, not corpses, not herds and believers. Fellow creators the creator seeks -- those who write new values on new tablets. Companions the creator seeks, and fellow harvesters; for everything about him is ripe for the harvest." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62281-i-mean-d-you-know-what-eternity-is-there-s-this-big</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 20:08:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62281-i-mean-d-you-know-what-eternity-is-there-s-this-big]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I mean, d'you know what eternity is? There's this big mountain, see, a mile high, at the end of the universe, and once every thousand years there's this little bird-&quot;

&quot;What little bird?&quot; said Aziraphale suspiciously.

&quot;This little bird I'm talking about. And every thousand years-&quot;

&quot;The same bird every thousand years?&quot;

Crowley hesitated. &quot;Yeah,&quot; he said.

&quot;Bloody ancient bird, then.&quot;

&quot;Okay. And every thousand years this bird flies-&quot;

&quot;-limps-&quot;

&quot;-flies all the way to this mountain and sharpens its beak-&quot;

&quot;Hold on. You can't do that. Between here and the end of the universe there's loads of-&quot; The angel waved a hand expansively, if a little unsteadily. &quot;Loads of buggerall, dear boy.&quot;

&quot;But it gets there anyway,&quot; Crowley persevered.

&quot;How?&quot;

&quot;It doesn't matter!&quot;

&quot;It could use a space ship,&quot; said the angel.

Crowley subsided a bit. &quot;Yeah,&quot; he said. &quot;If you like. Anyway, this bird-&quot;

&quot;Only it is the end of the universe we're talking about,&quot; said Aziraphale. &quot;So it'd have to be one of those space ships where your descendants are the ones who get out at the other end. You have to tell your descendants, you say, When you get to the Mountain, you've got to-&quot; He hesitated. &quot;What have
they got to do?&quot;

&quot;Sharpen its beak on the mountain,&quot; said Crowley. &quot;And then it flies back-&quot;

&quot;-in the space ship-&quot;

&quot;And after a thousand years it goes and does it all again,&quot; said Crowley quickly.

There was a moment of drunken silence.

&quot;Seems a lot of effort just to sharpen a beak,&quot; mused Aziraphale.

&quot;Listen,&quot; said Crowley urgently, &quot;the point is that when the bird has worn the mountain down to nothing, right, then-&quot;

Aziraphale opened his mouth. Crowley just knew he was going to make some point about the relative hardness of birds' beaks and granite mountains, and plunged on quickly.

&quot;-then you still won't have finished watching The Sound of Music.&quot;

Aziraphale froze.

&quot;And you'll enjoy it,&quot; Crowley said relentlessly. &quot;You really will.&quot;

&quot;My dear boy-&quot;

&quot;You won't have a choice.&quot;

&quot;Listen-&quot;

&quot;Heaven has no taste.&quot;

&quot;Now-&quot;

&quot;And not one single sushi restaurant.&quot;

A look of pain crossed the angel's suddenly very serious face." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184384-i-have-a-friend-who-s-an-artist-and-has-sometimes</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 21:03:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Richard P. Feynman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184384-i-have-a-friend-who-s-an-artist-and-has-sometimes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have a friend who's an artist and has sometimes taken a view which I don't agree with very well. He'll hold up a flower and say &quot;look how beautiful it is,&quot; and I'll agree. Then he says &quot;I as an artist can see how beautiful this is but you as a scientist take this all apart and it becomes a dull thing,&quot; and I think that he's kind of nutty. First of all, the beauty that he sees is available to other people and to me too, I believe. Although I may not be quite as refined aesthetically as he is ... I can appreciate the beauty of a flower. At the same time, I see much more about the flower than he sees. I could imagine the cells in there, the complicated actions inside, which also have a beauty. I mean it's not just beauty at this dimension, at one centimeter; there's also beauty at smaller dimensions, the inner structure, also the processes. The fact that the colors in the flower evolved in order to attract insects to pollinate it is interesting; it means that insects can see the color. It adds a question: does this aesthetic sense also exist in the lower forms? Why is it aesthetic? All kinds of interesting questions which the science knowledge only adds to the excitement, the mystery and the awe of a flower. It only adds. I don't understand how it subtracts." -- Richard P. Feynman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/885913-the-fundamental-core-of-contemporary-darwinism-the-theory-of-dna-based</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 09:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Daniel C. Dennett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/885913-the-fundamental-core-of-contemporary-darwinism-the-theory-of-dna-based]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fundamental core of contemporary Darwinism, the theory of DNA-based reproduction and evolution, is now beyond dispute among scientists. It demonstrates its power every day, contributing crucially to the explanation of planet-sized facts of geology and meteorology, through middle-sized facts of ecology and agronomy, down to the latest microscopic facts of genetic engineering.  It unifies all of biology and the history of our planet into a single grand story.  Like Gulliver tied down in Lilliput, it is unbudgeable, not because of some one or two huge chains of argument that might–hope against hope–have weak links in them, but because it is securely tied by hundreds of thousands of threads of evidence anchoring it to virtually every other field of knowledge. New discoveries may conceivably lead to dramatic, even 'revolutionary' shifts in the Darwinian theory, but the hope that it will be 'refuted' by some shattering breakthrough is about as reasonable as the hope that we will return to a geocentric vision and discard Copernicus." -- Daniel C. Dennett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143036-if-you-can-approach-the-world-s-complexities-both-its-glories</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 09:31:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Daniel C. Dennett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143036-if-you-can-approach-the-world-s-complexities-both-its-glories]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can approach the world's complexities, both its glories and its horrors, with an attitude of humble curiosity, acknowledging that however deeply you have seen, you have only scratched the surface, you will find worlds within worlds, beauties you could not heretofore imagine, and your own mundane preoccupations will shrink to proper size, not all that important in the greater scheme of things." -- Daniel C. Dennett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214806-what-you-can-imagine-depends-on-what-you-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 09:31:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Daniel Dennett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214806-what-you-can-imagine-depends-on-what-you-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What you can imagine depends on what you know." -- Daniel Dennett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174128-if-you-want-to-teach-your-children-that-they-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 09:32:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Daniel C. Dennett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174128-if-you-want-to-teach-your-children-that-they-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to teach your children that they are the tools of God, you had better not teach them that they are God's rifles, or we will have to stand firmly opposed to you: your doctrine has no glory, no special rights, no intrinsic and inalienable merit. If you insist on teaching your children false-hoods—that the Earth is flat, that &quot;Man&quot; is not a product of evolution by natural selection—then you must expect, at the very least, that those of us who have freedom of speech will feel free to describe your teachings as the spreading of falsehoods, and will attempt to demonstrate this to your children at our earliest opportunity. Our future well-being—the well-being of all of us on the planet—depends on the education of our descendants." -- Daniel C. Dennett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140660-you-don-t-get-to-advertise-all-the-good-that-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 09:32:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nullifidian add a quote by Daniel Dennett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140660-you-don-t-get-to-advertise-all-the-good-that-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't get to advertise all the good that your religion does without first scrupulously subtracting all the harm it does and considering seriously the question of whether some other religion, or no religion at all, does better." -- Daniel Dennett]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
