<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/627502-olga]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/627502-olga" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 15:00:31 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/304420-perception-requires-imagination-because-the-data-people-encounter-in-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 15:00:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olga add a quote by Leonard Mlodinow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/304420-perception-requires-imagination-because-the-data-people-encounter-in-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perception requires imagination because the data people encounter in their lives are never complete and always equivocal.  For example, most people consider that the greatest evidence of an event one can obtain is to see it with their own eyes, and in a court of law little is held in more esteem than eyewitness testimony. Yet if you asked to display for a court a video of the same quality as the unprocessed data catptured on the retina of a human eye, the judge might wonder what you were tryig to put over.  For one thing, the view will have a blind spot where the optic nerve attaches to the retina.  Moreover, the only part of our field of vision with good resolution is a narrow area of about 1 degree of visual angle around the retina’s center, an area the width of our thumb as it looks when held at arm’s length.  Outside that region, resolution drops off sharply.  To compensate, we constantly move our eyes to bring the sharper region to bear on different portions of the scene we wish to observe. And so the pattern of raw data sent to the brain is a shaky, badly pixilated picture with a hole in it. Fortunately the brain processes the data, combining input from both eyes, filling in gaps on the assumption that the visual properties of neighboring locations are similar and interpolating.  The result - at least until age, injury, disease, or an excess of mai tais takes its toll - is a happy human being suffering from the compelling illusion that his or her vision is sharp and clear.

We also use our imagination and take shortcuts to fill gaps in patterns of nonvisual data. As with visual input, we draw conclusions and make judgments based on uncertain and incomplete information, and we conclude, when we are done analyzing the patterns, that out “picture” is clear and accurate.  But is it?" -- Leonard Mlodinow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/551352-the-cord-that-tethers-ability-to-success-is-both-loose</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 15:01:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olga add a quote by Leonard Mlodinow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/551352-the-cord-that-tethers-ability-to-success-is-both-loose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The cord that tethers ability to success is both loose and elastic. It is easy to see fine qualities in successful books or to see unpublished manuscripts, inexpensive vodkas, or people struggling in any field as somehow lacking. It is easy to believe that ideas that worked were good ideas, that plans that succeeded were well designed, and that ideas and plans that did not were ill conceived. And it is easy to make heroes out of the most successful and to glance with disdain at the least. But ability does not guarantee achievement, nor is achievement proportional to ability. And so it is important to always keep in mind the other term in the equation—the role of chance…What I’ve learned, above all, is to keep marching forward because the best news is that since chance does play a role, one important factor in success is under our control: the number of at bats, the number of chances taken, the number of opportunities seized." -- Leonard Mlodinow]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
