<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/628529-alan-wilkes]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/628529-alan-wilkes" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 01:18:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/661151-i-m-all-these-words-all-these-strangers-this-dust-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 01:18:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Samuel Beckett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/661151-i-m-all-these-words-all-these-strangers-this-dust-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm all these words, all these strangers, this dust of words, with no ground for their settling, no sky for their dispersing, coming together to say, fleeing one another to say, that I am they, all of them, those that merge, those that part, those that never meet, and nothing else, yes, something else, that I'm something quite different, a quite different thing, a wordless thing in an empty place, a hard shut dry cold black place, where nothing stirs, nothing speaks, and that I listen, and that I seek, like a caged beast born of caged beasts born of caged beasts born of caged beasts born in a cage and dead in a cage, born and then dead, born in a cage and then dead in a cage, in a word like a beast, in one of their words, like such a beast, and that I seek, like such a beast, with my little strength, such a beast, with nothing of its species left but fear and fury, no, the fury is past, nothing but fear, nothing of all its due but fear centupled, fear of its shadow, no, blind from birth, of sound then, if you like, we'll have that, one must have something, it's a pity, but there it is, fear of sound, fear of sounds, the sounds of beasts, the sounds of men, sounds in the daytime and sounds at night, that's enough, fear of sounds all sounds, more or less, more or less fear, all sounds, there's only one, continuous, day and night, what is it, it's steps coming and going, it's voices speaking for a moment, it's bodies groping their way, it's the air, it's things, it's the air among the things, that's enough, that I seek, like it, no, not like it, like me, in my own way, what am I saying, after my fashion, that I seek, what do I seek now, what it is, it must be that, it can only be that, what it is, what it can be, what what can be, what I seek, no, what I hear, I hear them, now it comes back to me, they say I seek what it is I hear, I hear them, now it comes back to me, what it can possibly be, and where it can possibly come from, since all is silent here, and the walls thick, and how I manage, without feeling an ear on me, or a head, or a body, or a soul, how I manage, to do what, how I manage, it's not clear, dear dear, you say it's not clear, something is wanting to make it clear, I'll seek, what is wanting, to make everything clear, I'm always seeking something, it's tiring in the end, and it's only the beginning." -- Samuel Beckett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100361-the-search-for-the-means-to-put-an-end-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 01:19:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Samuel Beckett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100361-the-search-for-the-means-to-put-an-end-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The search for the means to put an end to things, an end to speech, is what enables the discourse to continue." -- Samuel Beckett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278701-books-are-finite-sexual-encounters-are-finite-but-the-desire</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 02:24:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Roberto Bolano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278701-books-are-finite-sexual-encounters-are-finite-but-the-desire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are finite, sexual encounters are finite, but the desire to read and to fuck is infinite; it surpasses our own deaths, our fears, our hopes for peace." -- Roberto Bolano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136183-for-a-while-criticism-travels-side-by-side-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 02:28:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136183-for-a-while-criticism-travels-side-by-side-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For a while, Criticism travels side by side with the Work, then Criticism vanishes and it's the Readers who keep pace. The journey may be long or short. Then the Readers die one by one and the Work continues on alone, although a new Criticism and new Readers gradually fall into step with it along its path. Then Criticism dies again and the Readers die again and the Work passes over a trail of bones on its journey toward solitude. To come near the work, to sail in her wake, is a sign of certain death, but new Criticism and new Readers approach her tirelessly and relentlessly and are devoured by time and speed. Finally the Work journeys irremediably alone in the Great Vastness. And one day the Work dies, as all things must die and come to an end: the Sun and the Earth and the Solar System and the Galaxy and the farthest reaches of man's memory. Everything that begins as comedy ends in tragedy." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442672-in-a-brief-moment-of-lucidity-i-was-sure-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 02:32:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442672-in-a-brief-moment-of-lucidity-i-was-sure-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a brief moment of lucidity, I was sure that we'd all gone crazy. But then that moment of lucidity was displaced by a supersecond of superlucidity (if I can put it that way), in which I realized that this scene was the logical outcome of our ridiculous lives. It wasn't a punishment but a new wrinkle. It gave us a glimpse of ourselves in our common humanity. It wasn't proof of our idle guilt but a sign of our miraculous and pointless innocence. But that's not it. That's not it. We were still and they were in motion and the sand on the beach was moving, not because of the wind but because of what they were doing and what we were doing, which was nothing, which was watching, and all of that together was the wrinkle, the moment of superlucidity. Then, nothing." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/835541-qu-l-stima-que-pase-el-tiempo-verdad-qu-l-stima-que</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 02:37:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/835541-qu-l-stima-que-pase-el-tiempo-verdad-qu-l-stima-que]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Qué lástima que pase el tiempo ¿verdad?, qué lástima que nos muramos y que nos hagamos viejos y que las cosas buenas se vayan alejando de nosotros al galope." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/822656-dentro-del-inmenso-oc-ano-de-la-poes-a-distingu-a-varias-corrientes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 04:42:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/822656-dentro-del-inmenso-oc-ano-de-la-poes-a-distingu-a-varias-corrientes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dentro del inmenso océano de la poesía distinguía varias corrientes: maricones, maricas, mariquitas, locas, bujarrones, mariposas, ninfos y filenos. Las dos corrientes mayores, sin embargo, eran la de los maricones y la de los maricas. Walt Whitman, por ejemplo, era un poeta maricón. Pablo Neruda, un poeta marica. William Blake era maricón, sin asomo de duda, y Octavio Paz marica. Borges era fileno, es decir de improviso podía ser maricón y de improviso simplemente asexual. Rubén Darío era una loca, de hecho la reina y el paradigma de las locas. 
—En nuestra lengua, claro está —aclaró—; en el mundo ancho y ajeno el paradigma sigue siendo Verlaine el Generoso. 
Una loca, según San Epifanio, estaba más cerca del manicomio florido y de las alucinaciones en carne viva mientras que los maricones y los maricas vagaban sincopadamente de la Ética a la Estética y viceversa." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/368099-there-are-moments-in-life-when-the-heart-is-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 15:10:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Henry Wadsworth Longfellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/368099-there-are-moments-in-life-when-the-heart-is-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are moments in life, when the heart is so full of emotion
that if by chance it be shaken, or into its depths like a pebble
Drops some careless word, it overflows, and its secret,
Spilled on the ground like water, can never be gathered together." -- Henry Wadsworth Longfellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30052-a-book-is-more-than-a-verbal-structure-or-series</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2013 23:32:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30052-a-book-is-more-than-a-verbal-structure-or-series]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book is more than a verbal structure or series of verbal structures; it is the dialogue it establishes with its reader and the intonation it imposes upon his voice and the changing and durable images it leaves in his memory. A book is not an isolated being: it is a relationship, an axis of innumerable relationships." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/733334-un-hombre-se-propone-la-tarea-de-dibujar-el</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2013 23:35:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/733334-un-hombre-se-propone-la-tarea-de-dibujar-el]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["(...) Un hombre se propone la tarea de dibujar el mundo. A lo largo de los años puebla un espacio con imágenes de provincias, de reinos, de montañas, de bahías, de naves, de islas, de peces, de habitaciones, de instrumentos, de astros, de caballos y de personas. Poco antes de morir, descubre que ese paciente laberinto de líneas traza la imagen de su cara." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9593-with-her-florentino-ariza-learned-what-he-had-already-experienced</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 23:50:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9593-with-her-florentino-ariza-learned-what-he-had-already-experienced]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With her Florentino Ariza learned what he had already experienced many times without realizing it: that one can be in love with several people at the same time, feel the same sorrow with each, and not betray any of them. Alone in the midst of the crowd on the pier, he said to himself in a flash of anger: 'My heart has more rooms than a whorehouse." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512481-there-is-no-such-thing-as-moral-phenomena-but-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2013 16:56:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512481-there-is-no-such-thing-as-moral-phenomena-but-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no such thing as moral phenomena, but only a moral interpretation of phenomena" -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153555-language-is-a-skin-i-rub-my-language-against-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2013 15:04:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Roland Barthes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153555-language-is-a-skin-i-rub-my-language-against-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Language is a skin: I rub my language against the other. It is as if I had words instead of fingers, or fingers at the tip of my words. My language trembles with desire. The emotion derives from a double contact: on the one hand, a whole activity of discourse discreetly, indirectly focuses upon a single signified, which is &quot;I desire you,&quot; and releases, nourishes, ramifies it to the point of explosion (language experiences orgasm upon touching itself); on the other hand, I enwrap the other in my words, I caress, brush against, talk up this contact, I extend myself to make the commentary to which I submit the relation endure. " -- Roland Barthes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153591-besides-intercourse-when-the-image-repertoire-goes-to-the-devil-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 19:01:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Roland Barthes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153591-besides-intercourse-when-the-image-repertoire-goes-to-the-devil-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Besides intercourse (when the Image-repertoire goes to the devil), there is that other embrace, which is a motionless cradling: we are enchanted, bewitched: we are in the realm of sleep, without sleeping; we are within the voluptous infantilism of sleepiness: this is the moment for telling stories, the moment of the voice which takes me, siderates me, this is the return to the mother (&quot;in the loving calm of your arms,&quot; says a poem set to music by Duparc). In this companionable incest, everything is suspended: time, law, prohibition: nothing is exhausted, nothing is wanted: all desires are abolished, for they seem definitively fulfilled. 
Yet, within this infantile embrace, the genital unfailingly appears; it cuts off the diffuse sensuality of the incestuous embrace; the logic of desire begins to function, the will-to-possess returns, the adult is superimposed upon the child. I am then two subjects at once: I want maternity and genitality. (The lover might be defined as a child getting an erection: such was the young Eros.)" -- Roland Barthes]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
