<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/629064-patricia]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/629064-patricia" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 04:33:14 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7492-i-have-lots-of-things-to-teach-you-now-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 04:33:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7492-i-have-lots-of-things-to-teach-you-now-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have lots of things  to teach you now, in case we ever meet, concerning the message that was transmitted to me under a pine tree in North Carolina on a cold winter moonlit night. It said that Nothing Ever Happened, so don't worry. It's all like a dream. Everything is ecstasy, inside. We just don't know it because of our thinking-minds. But in our true blissful essence of mind is known that everything is alright forever and forever and forever. Close your eyes, let your hands and nerve-ends drop, stop breathing for 3 seconds, listen to the silence inside the illusion of the world, and you will remember the lesson you forgot, which was taught in immense milky way soft cloud innumerable worlds long ago and not even at all. It is all one vast awakened thing. I call it the golden eternity. It is perfect. We were never really born, we will never really die. It has nothing to do with the imaginary idea of a personal self, other selves, many selves everywhere: Self is only an idea, a mortal idea. That which passes into everything is one thing. It's a dream already ended. There's nothing to be afraid of and nothing to be glad about. I know this from staring at mountains months on end. They never show any expression, they are like empty space. Do you think the emptiness of space will ever crumble away? Mountains will crumble, but the emptiness of space, which is the one universal essence of mind, the vast awakenerhood, empty and awake, will never crumble away because it was never born." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122782-i-was-waiting-for-the-longest-time-she-said-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 04:33:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Brian Andreas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122782-i-was-waiting-for-the-longest-time-she-said-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was waiting for the longest time, she said. I thought you forgot.

It is hard to forget, I said, when there is such an empty space when you are gone." -- Brian Andreas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243780-there-s-just-something-obvious-about-emptiness-even-when-you-try</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 04:33:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243780-there-s-just-something-obvious-about-emptiness-even-when-you-try]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's just something obvious about emptiness, even when you try to convince yourself otherwise. " -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154031-this-was-something-she-would-keep-hidden-within-herself-maybe</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 04:34:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154031-this-was-something-she-would-keep-hidden-within-herself-maybe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This was something she would keep hidden within herself, maybe in place of the knot of pain and anger she had been carrying under her breastbone...a security blanket, an ace up her sleeve. She might never use it, but she would always feel its presence like a swelling secret stone, and that way when she let go of the rage, she would not feel nearly as empty." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416468-alone-i-often-fall-down-into-nothingness-i-must-push</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 04:34:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416468-alone-i-often-fall-down-into-nothingness-i-must-push]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alone, I often fall down into nothingness. I must push my foot stealthily lest I should fall off the edge of the world into nothingness. I have to bang my head against some hard door to call myself back to the body." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/517248-maybe-she-had-it-wrong-all-this-time-and-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 04:35:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Jamie Weise]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/517248-maybe-she-had-it-wrong-all-this-time-and-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe she had it wrong all this time and her empty heart could never be filled by his ingenious broken spirit. Maybe this yearning had nothing to do with him, and everything to do with her." -- Jamie Weise]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338947-if-she-spoke-she-would-tell-him-the-truth-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 04:36:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338947-if-she-spoke-she-would-tell-him-the-truth-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If she spoke, she would tell him the truth: she was not okay at all, but horribly empty, now that she knew what it was like to be filled." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/530458-she-d-cried-over-a-broken-heart-before-she-knew-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 04:36:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Ann Brashares]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/530458-she-d-cried-over-a-broken-heart-before-she-knew-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She'd cried over a broken heart before. She knew what that felt like, and it didn't feel like this. Her heart felt not so much broken as just ... empty. It felt like she was an outline empty in the middle. The outline cried senselessly for the absent middle. The past cried for the present that was nothing." -- Ann Brashares]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/486956-the-decision-to-empty-my-mind-was-a-no-brainer</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 04:36:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Jarod Kintz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/486956-the-decision-to-empty-my-mind-was-a-no-brainer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The decision to empty my mind was a no-brainer. " -- Jarod Kintz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/475399-i-d-rather-love-a-million-times-and-have-my-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 04:36:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by H.C. Paye]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/475399-i-d-rather-love-a-million-times-and-have-my-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd rather love a million times and have my heart broken every time, than hold a permanitely empty heart forever." -- H.C. Paye]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229614-when-i-was-little-i-was-out-riding-my-brand-new</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 04:37:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Chica Umino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229614-when-i-was-little-i-was-out-riding-my-brand-new]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was little, I was out riding my brand-new blue bicycle when I decided to see how far I could keep going without looking back even once. 
I could feel with my back how my neighborhood was receding, further and further away... but I kept pedaling with all my might, my mind almost going blank. All I could hear was the sound of my own heart, thumping wildly in my ears. Even now, I remember it sometimes. What exactly was I trying to do that day? What was it that I wanted to prove?

It's no good. My mind just keeps fogging over. I have this irritating sound stuck in my head. What is it? This sound... Ohh... I know what it is. 
This is... the sound of emptiness." -- Chica Umino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295785-life-is-an-empty-bottle-filled-with-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 04:38:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Santosh Kalwar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295785-life-is-an-empty-bottle-filled-with-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is an empty bottle filled with love." -- Santosh Kalwar]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
