<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/629744-olivia]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/629744-olivia" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 20:26:03 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140652-perhaps-the-greatest-challenge-to-thinking-women-is-the-challenge</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 20:26:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Gerda Lerner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140652-perhaps-the-greatest-challenge-to-thinking-women-is-the-challenge]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["perhaps the greatest challenge to thinking women is the challenge to move from the desire for safety and approval to the most &quot;unfeminine&quot; quality of all -- that of intllectual arrogance, the supreme hubris which asserts to itself the right to reorder the world. The Hubris of the god makers, the hubris of the male-system builders." -- Gerda Lerner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239710-sitting-at-the-table-doesn-t-make-you-a-diner-unless</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 20:25:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Malcolm X]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239710-sitting-at-the-table-doesn-t-make-you-a-diner-unless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sitting at the table doesn't make you a diner, unless you eat some of what's on that plate. Being here in America doesn't make you an American. Being born here in America doesn't make you an American." -- Malcolm X]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2807-as-a-woman-i-have-no-country-as-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 20:25:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by virginia woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2807-as-a-woman-i-have-no-country-as-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As a woman I have no country. As a woman I want no country. As a woman, my country is the whole world." -- virginia woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36299-one-has-a-moral-responsibility-to-disobey-unjust-laws</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 11:48:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36299-one-has-a-moral-responsibility-to-disobey-unjust-laws]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One has a moral responsibility to disobey unjust laws." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36970-history-is-not-a-procession-of-illustrious-people-it-s-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 10:45:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36970-history-is-not-a-procession-of-illustrious-people-it-s-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["History is not a procession of illustrious people. It's about what happens to a people. Millions of anonymous people is what history is about." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2008 21:05:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85172-those-who-profess-to-favor-freedom-and-yet-depreciate-agitation</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2009 18:05:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Frederick Douglass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85172-those-who-profess-to-favor-freedom-and-yet-depreciate-agitation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who profess to favor freedom and yet depreciate agitation, are people who want crops without ploughing the ground; they want rain without thunder and lightning; they want the ocean without the roar of its many waters. The struggle may be a moral one, or it may be a physical one, or it may be both. But it must be a struggle. Power concedes nothing without a demand. It never did and it never will." -- Frederick Douglass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64541-the-purpose-of-life-is-not-to-be-happy-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 20:25:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64541-the-purpose-of-life-is-not-to-be-happy-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The purpose of life is not to be happy. It is to be useful, to be honorable, to be compassionate, to have it make some difference that you have lived and lived well." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408622-at-the-risk-of-seeming-ridiculous-let-me-say-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 09:17:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Ernesto Guevara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408622-at-the-risk-of-seeming-ridiculous-let-me-say-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the risk of seeming ridiculous, let me say that the true revolutionary is guided by a great feeling of love. It is impossible to think of a genuine revolutionary lacking this quality. We must strive every day so that this love of living humanity will be transformed into actual deeds, into acts that serve as examples, as a moving force." -- Ernesto Guevara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/323126-our-problems-stem-from-our-acceptance-of-this-filthy-rotten</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 09:34:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Dorothy Day]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/323126-our-problems-stem-from-our-acceptance-of-this-filthy-rotten]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our problems stem from our acceptance of this filthy, rotten system." -- Dorothy Day]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153597-what-we-would-like-to-do-is-change-the-world--make</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 09:35:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Dorothy Day]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153597-what-we-would-like-to-do-is-change-the-world--make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What we would like to do is change the world--make it a little simpler for people to feed, clothe, and shelter themselves as God intended them to do. And, by fighting for better conditions, by crying out unceasingly for the rights of the workers, the poor, of the destitute--the rights of the worthy and the unworthy poor, in other words--we can, to a certain extent, change the world; we can work for the oasis, the little cell of joy and peace in a harried world. We can throw our pebble in the pond and be confident that its ever widening circle will reach around the world. We repeat, there is nothing we can do but love, and, dear God, please enlarge our hearts to love each other, to love our neighbor, to love our enemy as our friend." -- Dorothy Day]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 13:39:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know you're in love when you can't fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410302-a-revolutionary-woman-can-t-have-no-reactionary-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 12:46:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Assata Shakur]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410302-a-revolutionary-woman-can-t-have-no-reactionary-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A revolutionary woman can't have no reactionary man." -- Assata Shakur]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419043-tomorrow-the-revolution-will-rise-up-again-clashing-its-weapons</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 12:36:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Rosa Luxemburg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419043-tomorrow-the-revolution-will-rise-up-again-clashing-its-weapons]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tomorrow the revolution will 'rise up again, clashing its weapons,' and to your horror it will proclaim with trumpets blazing: I was, I am, I shall be!" -- Rosa Luxemburg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12425-when-i-dare-to-be-powerful-to-use-my-strength</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 20:28:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12425-when-i-dare-to-be-powerful-to-use-my-strength]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I dare to be powerful, to use my strength in the service of my vision, then it becomes less and less important whether I am afraid." -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/461414-to-love-the-one-who-loves-you-to-admire-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 23:46:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Delphine de Girardin ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/461414-to-love-the-one-who-loves-you-to-admire-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love the one who loves you, To admire the one who admires you, In a word, to be the idol of one's idol, Is exceeding the limit of human joy; It is stealing fire from heaven." -- Delphine de Girardin ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1815-do-not-believe-in-anything-simply-because-you-have-heard</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 23:53:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Buddha Siddhartha Guatama Shakyamuni]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1815-do-not-believe-in-anything-simply-because-you-have-heard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not believe in anything simply because you have heard it. Do not believe in anything simply because it is spoken and rumored by many. Do not believe in anything simply because it is found written in your religious books. Do not believe in anything merely on the authority of your teachers and elders. Do not believe in traditions because they have been handed down for many generations. But after observation and analysis, when you find that anything agrees with reason and is conducive to the good and benefit of one and all, then accept it and live up to it." -- Buddha Siddhartha Guatama Shakyamuni]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270189-what-if-by-some-miracle-this-present-turned-out-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 23:57:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Anton Pavlovich Chekhov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270189-what-if-by-some-miracle-this-present-turned-out-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What if, by some miracle, this present turned out to be a dream, a hideous nightmare, and we were to awake renewed and cleansed, strong, upright and proud? Why do we never try to stand again when once we've fallen? When we lose one thing why don't we search for another? I want our lives to be holy, sublime and solemn as the vault of heaven. Let us live! The thief on the cross had hope even though he had less than an hour left to him, and the sun only rises once a day, so take hold of what's left of your life and save it." -- Anton Pavlovich Chekhov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62588-listen-you-can-be-anything-you-want-to-be-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 23:58:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Melvin Burgess]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62588-listen-you-can-be-anything-you-want-to-be-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen. You can be anything you want to be. Be careful. It's a spell. It's magic. Listen to the words. You can be anything, you can do anything, you can be anything, you can do anything. Listen to the magic.
	You are anything . . . everyone, anyone. Whatever you want. I'm showing you. So long as you stay yourself inside, you can eat dirt and it'll taste good because it's you that's eating it. You can even lick their arses if you have to. You listen to them, teachers, parents, politicians. They're always saying, if you steal you're a thief, if you sleep around you're a slut, if you take drugs you're a junkie. They want to get inside your head and control you with their fear. 
	Maybe you think your mum and dad love you but if you do the wrong things they'll try and turn you into dirt. It's your punishment for being you. Don't play their game. Nothing can touch you; you stay beautiful. 
	I've done everything. All of it. You think it, I've done it.  
	All the things you never dared, all the things you dream about, all the things you were curious about and then forgot because you knew you never would. I did 'em, I did 'em yesterday while you were still in bed,
	What about you? When's it going to be your turn?" -- Melvin Burgess]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/436792-he-d-thought-of-fate-as-something-hostile-a-thief-moving</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 23:58:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Kay Hooper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/436792-he-d-thought-of-fate-as-something-hostile-a-thief-moving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["he'd thought of fate as something hostile, a thief moving soundlessly in the night" -- Kay Hooper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50677-who-has-never-killed-an-hour-not-casually-or-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 00:01:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50677-who-has-never-killed-an-hour-not-casually-or-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who has never killed an hour? Not casually or without thought, but carefully: a premeditated murder of minutes. The violence comes from a combination of giving up, not caring, and a resignation that getting past it is all you can hope to accomplish. So you kill the hour. You do not work, you do not read, you do not daydream. If you sleep it is not because you need to sleep. And when at last it is over, there is no evidence: no weapon, no blood, and no body. The only clue might be the shadows beneath your eyes or a terribly thin line near the corner of your mouth indicating something has been suffered, that in the privacy of your life you have lost something and the loss is too empty to share." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341193-fairy-tales-do-not-tell-children-the-dragons-exist-children</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 00:02:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341193-fairy-tales-do-not-tell-children-the-dragons-exist-children]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fairy tales do not tell children the dragons exist.  Children already know that dragons exist. Fairy tales tell children the dragons can be killed." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12280-the-illusion-of-freedom-will-continue-as-long-as-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 19:39:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12280-the-illusion-of-freedom-will-continue-as-long-as-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The illusion of freedom will continue as long as it's profitable to continue the illusion. At the point where the illusion becomes too expensive to maintain, they will just take down the scenery, they will pull back the curtains, they will move the tables and chairs out of the way and you will see the brick wall at the back of the theater." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501179-a-system-that-warehouses-people-is-not-the-cure-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 00:01:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Amiri Baraka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501179-a-system-that-warehouses-people-is-not-the-cure-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A system that warehouses people is not the cure for social ills" -- Amiri Baraka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501180-there-is-no-justice-in-america-but-it-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 00:01:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Amiri Baraka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501180-there-is-no-justice-in-america-but-it-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no justice in America, but it is the fight for justice that sustains you" -- Amiri Baraka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501181-you-must-let-suffering-speak-if-you-want-to-hear</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 00:02:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Cornell West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501181-you-must-let-suffering-speak-if-you-want-to-hear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must let suffering speak, if you want to hear the truth" -- Cornell West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35609-dare-to-change-the-world-there-is-nothing-quixotic-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 22:08:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Gioconda Belli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35609-dare-to-change-the-world-there-is-nothing-quixotic-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dare to change the world

There is nothing quixotic or romantic in wanting to change the world. It is possible. It is the age-old vocation of all humanity. I can't think of a better life than one dedicated to passion, to dreams, to the stubborness that defies chaos and disillusionment." -- Gioconda Belli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1987-where-justice-is-denied-where-poverty-is-enforced-where-ignorance</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 22:09:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Frederick Douglass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1987-where-justice-is-denied-where-poverty-is-enforced-where-ignorance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where justice is denied, where poverty is enforced, where ignorance prevails, and where any one class is made to feel that society is an organized conspiracy to oppress, rob and degrade them, neither persons nor property will be safe." -- Frederick Douglass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541838-so-many-of-my-sisters-are-so-completely-unaware-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 12:42:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Assata Shakir]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541838-so-many-of-my-sisters-are-so-completely-unaware-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many of my sisters are so completely unaware of who the real criminals and dogs are. They blame themselves for being hungry; they hate themselves for surviving the best way they know how, to see so much fear, doubt, hurt, and self hatred is the most painful part of being in this concentration camp. &quot;Anyway, in spite of all, i feel a breeze behind my neck, turning to a hurricane and when i take a deep breath I can smell freedom" -- Assata Shakir]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541839-i-believe-in-the-fire-of-love-and-the-sweat</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 12:42:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Olivia add a quote by Assata Shakur]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541839-i-believe-in-the-fire-of-love-and-the-sweat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["i Believe In The Fire Of Love And The Sweat Of Truth" -- Assata Shakur]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
