<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/629822-jinny]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/629822-jinny" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:25:14 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/397-there-is-no-flag-large-enough-to-cover-the-shame</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:25:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/397-there-is-no-flag-large-enough-to-cover-the-shame]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no flag large enough to cover the shame of killing innocent people." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17916-i-m-worried-that-students-will-take-their-obedient-place-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:26:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17916-i-m-worried-that-students-will-take-their-obedient-place-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm worried that students will take their obedient place in society and look to become successful cogs in the wheel - let the wheel spin them around as it wants without taking a look at what they're doing. I'm concerned that students not become passive acceptors of the official doctrine that's handed down to them from the White House, the media, textbooks, teachers and preachers." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88581-historically-the-most-terrible-things---war-genocide-and-slavery</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:26:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88581-historically-the-most-terrible-things---war-genocide-and-slavery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Historically, the most terrible things - war, genocide, and slavery - have resulted not from disobedience, but from obedience." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88590-the-challenge-remains-on-the-other-side-are-formidable-forces</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:27:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88590-the-challenge-remains-on-the-other-side-are-formidable-forces]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The challenge remains.  On the other side are formidable forces: money, political power, the major media.  On our side are the people of the world and a power greater than money or weapons: the truth.
Truth has a power of its own.  Art has a power of its own.  That age-old lesson – that everything we do matters – is the meaning of the people’s struggle here in the United States and everywhere.  A poem can inspire a movement.  A pamphlet can spark a revolution.  Civil disobedience can arouse people and provoke us to think, when we organize with one another, when we get involved, when we stand up and speak out together, we can create a power no government can suppress.  We live in a beautiful country.  But people who have no respect for human life, freedom, or justice have taken it over.  It is now up to all of us to take it back." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88496-we-need-to-decide-that-we-will-not-go-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:27:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88496-we-need-to-decide-that-we-will-not-go-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We need to decide that we will not go to war, whatever reason is conjured up by the politicians or the media, because war in our time is always indiscriminate, a war against innocents, a war against children" -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20797-any-humane-and-reasonable-person-must-conclude-that-if-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:27:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20797-any-humane-and-reasonable-person-must-conclude-that-if-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any humane and reasonable person must conclude that if the ends, however desireable, are uncertain and the means are horrible and certain, these means must not be employed." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27065-what-matters-most-is-not-who-is-sitting-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:28:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27065-what-matters-most-is-not-who-is-sitting-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What matters most is not who is sitting in the White House, but &quot;who is sitting in&quot; -- and who is marching outside the White House, pushing for change." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197336-history-is-important-if-you-don-t-know-history-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:28:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197336-history-is-important-if-you-don-t-know-history-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["History is important. If you don't know history it is as if you were born yesterday. And if you were born yesterday, anybody up there in a position of power can tell you anything, and you have no way of checking up on it." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88582-if-those-in-charge-of-our-society---politicians-corporate</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:28:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88582-if-those-in-charge-of-our-society---politicians-corporate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If those in charge of our society - politicians, corporate executives, and owners of press and television - can dominate our ideas, they will be secure in their power.  They will not need soldiers patrolling the streets.  We will control ourselves." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163932-civil-disobedience-is-not-our-problem-our-problem-is-civil</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:29:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163932-civil-disobedience-is-not-our-problem-our-problem-is-civil]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Civil disobedience is not our problem. Our problem is civil obedience. Our problem is that people all over the world have obeyed the dictates of leaders…and millions have been killed because of this obedience…Our problem is that people are obedient allover the world in the face of poverty and starvation and stupidity, and war, and cruelty. Our problem is that people are obedient while the jails are full of petty thieves… (and) the grand thieves are running the country. That’s our problem." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57690-if-the-gods-had-intended-for-people-to-vote-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:29:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57690-if-the-gods-had-intended-for-people-to-vote-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the gods had intended for people to vote, they would have given us candidates." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218972-how-can-you-have-a-war-on-terrorism-when-war</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:29:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218972-how-can-you-have-a-war-on-terrorism-when-war]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How can you have a war on terrorism when war itself is terrorism?" -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222336-protest-beyond-the-law-is-not-a-departure-from-democracy</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:29:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222336-protest-beyond-the-law-is-not-a-departure-from-democracy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Protest beyond the law is not a departure from democracy; it is absolutely essential to it." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128946-the-memory-of-oppressed-people-is-one-thing-that-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:29:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128946-the-memory-of-oppressed-people-is-one-thing-that-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The memory of oppressed people is one thing that cannot be taken away, and for such people, with such memories, revolt is always an inch below the surface." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214717-we-don-t-have-to-engage-in-grand-heroic-actions-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:29:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214717-we-don-t-have-to-engage-in-grand-heroic-actions-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't have to engage in grand, heroic actions to participate in the process of change. Small acts, when multiplied by millions of people, can transform the world." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88583-i-will-try-not-to-overlook-the-cruelties-that-victims</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:30:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88583-i-will-try-not-to-overlook-the-cruelties-that-victims]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will try not to overlook the cruelties that victims inflict on one another as they are jammed together in the boxcars of the system.  I don’t want to romanticize them.  But I do remember (in rough paraphrase) a statement I once read: “The cry of the poor is not always just, but if you don’t listen to it, you will never know what justice is." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226610-i-think-people-are-dazzled-by-obama-s-rhetoric-and-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:30:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226610-i-think-people-are-dazzled-by-obama-s-rhetoric-and-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think people are dazzled by Obama's rhetoric, and that people ought to begin to understand that Obama is going to be a mediocre president — which means, in our time, a dangerous president — unless there is some national movement to push him in a better direction." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88585-nations-are-not-communities-and-never-have-been-the-history</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:30:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88585-nations-are-not-communities-and-never-have-been-the-history]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nations are not communities and never have been.  The history of any country, presented as the history of a family, conceals the fierce conflicts of interest (sometimes exploding, often repressed) between conquerors and conquered, masters and slaves, capitalists and workers, dominators and dominated in race and sex.  And in such as world of conflict, a world of victims and executioners, it is the job of thinking people, as Albert Camus suggested, not to be on the side of the executioners." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176200-the-pretense-in-disputed-elections-is-that-the-great-conflict</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:30:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176200-the-pretense-in-disputed-elections-is-that-the-great-conflict]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The pretense in disputed elections is that the great conflict is between the two major parties.  The reality is that there is a much bigger conflict that the two parties jointly wage against large numbers of Americans who are represented by neither party and against powerless millions around the world.&quot; (p. 65)" -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57718-my-point-is-not-that-we-must-in-telling-history</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:31:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57718-my-point-is-not-that-we-must-in-telling-history]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My point is not that we must, in telling history, accuse, judge, condemn Columbus in absentia.  It is too late for that; it would be a useless scholarly exercise in morality.  But the easy acceptance of atrocities as a deplorable but necessary price to pay for progress (Hiroshima and Vietnam, to save Western civilization; Kronstadt and Hungary, to save socialism; nuclear proliferation, to save us all) - that is still with us.  One reason these atrocities are still with us is that we have learned to bury them in a mass of other facts, as radioactive wastes are buried in containers in the earth.  We have learned to give them exactly the same proportion of attention that teachers and writers often give them in the most respectable classrooms and textbooks.  This learned sense of moral proportion, coming from the apparent objectivity of the scholar, is accepted more easily than when it comes from politicians at press conferences.  It is therefore more deadly.
" -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226429-if-history-is-to-be-creative-to-anticipate-a-possible</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:31:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226429-if-history-is-to-be-creative-to-anticipate-a-possible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If history is to be creative, to anticipate a possible future without denying the past, it should, I believe, emphasize new possibilities by disclosing those hidden episodes of the past when, even if in brief flashes, people showed their ability to resist, to join together, occasionally to win. I am supposing, or perhaps only hoping, that our future may be found in the past's fugitive movements of compassion rather than in its solid centuries of warfare." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226427-my-viewpoint-in-telling-the-history-of-the-united-states</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 13:31:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226427-my-viewpoint-in-telling-the-history-of-the-united-states]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My viewpoint, in telling the history of the United States, is different: that we must not accept the memory of states as our own. Nations are not communities and never have been. The history of any country, presented as the history of a family, conceals fierce conflicts of interest (sometimes exploding, most often repressed) between conquerors and conquered, masters and slaves, capitalists and workers, dominators and dominated in race and sex. And in such a world of conflict, a world of victims and executioners, it is the job of thinking people, as Albert Camus suggested, not to be on the side of the executioners." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121561-if-you-think-anyone-is-sane-you-just-don-t-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 08:44:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jinny add a quote by Christopher Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121561-if-you-think-anyone-is-sane-you-just-don-t-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you think anyone is sane you just don't know enough about them." -- Christopher Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
