<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/630420-carrie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/630420-carrie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2007 14:00:59 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7342-last-month-i-was-banging-on-about-how-books-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2007 14:00:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7342-last-month-i-was-banging-on-about-how-books-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Last month I was banging on about how books were better than anything—-how just about any decent book you picked would beat up anything else, any film or painting or piece of music, you cared to match it up with. Anyway, like most theories advanced in this column, it turned out to be utter rubbish. I went to a couple of terrific exhibitions at the Royal Academy (and that’s a hole in my argument right there—one book might beat up one painting, but what chance has one book, or even four books, got against the collected works of Guston and Vuillard?)..." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7337-books-are-let-s-face-it-better-than-everything-else-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2007 14:03:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7337-books-are-let-s-face-it-better-than-everything-else-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are, let's face it, better than everything else. If we played cultural Fantasy Boxing League, and made books go 15 rounds in the ring against the best that any other art form had to offer, then books would win pretty much every time. Go on, try it. “The Magic Flute” v. Middlemarch? Middlemarch in six. “The Last Supper” v. Crime and Punishment? Fyodor on points. See? I mean, I don’t know how scientific this is, but it feels like the novels are walking it. You might get the occasional exception -– “Blonde on Blonde” might mash up The Old Curiosity Shop, say, and I wouldn’t give much for Pale Fire’s chance against Citizen Kane. And every now and again you'd get a shock, because that happens in sport, so Back to the Future III might land a lucky punch on Rabbit, Run; but I'm still backing literature 29 times out of 30." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35967-lorsque-nous-mangeons-c-est-signe-que-nous-avons-faim-de</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2008 10:06:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carrie add a quote by Valère Novarina]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35967-lorsque-nous-mangeons-c-est-signe-que-nous-avons-faim-de]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lorsque nous mangeons, c'est signe que nous avons faim de changer les choses.  Lorsque nous mangeons c'est pour changer les choses en nous." -- Valère Novarina]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
