<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/632838-diane]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/632838-diane" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 16:38:14 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46031-it-s-like-when-you-put-instant-rice-pudding-mix-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 16:38:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46031-it-s-like-when-you-put-instant-rice-pudding-mix-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s like when you put instant rice pudding mix in a bowl in the microwave and push the button, and you take the cover off when it rings, and there you’ve got ricing pudding. I mean, what happens in between the time when you push the switch and when the microwave rings? You can’t tell what’s going on under the cover. Maybe the instant rice pudding first turns into macaroni gratin in the darkness when nobody’s looking and only then turns back into rice pudding. We think it’s only natural to get rice pudding after we put rice pudding mix in the microwave and the bell rings, but to me, that is just a presumption. I would be kind of relieved if, every once in a while, after you put rice pudding mix in the microwave and it rang and you opened the top, you got macaroni gratin. I suppose I’d be shocked, of course, but I don’t know, I think I’d be kind of relieved too. Or at least I think I wouldn’t be so upset, because that would feel, in some ways, a whole lot more real." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197020-this-would-be-the-worst-birthday-of-his-life-vladimir-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 16:38:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Gary Shteyngart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197020-this-would-be-the-worst-birthday-of-his-life-vladimir-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This would be the worst birthday of his life. Vladimir's best friend Baobab was down in Florida covering his rent, doing unspeakable things with unmentionable people. Mother, roused by the meager achievements of Vladimir's first quarter-century, was officially on the warpath. And, in possibly the worst development yet, 1993 was the Year of the Girlfriend. A downcast, heavyset American girlfriend whose bright orange hair was strewn across his Alphabet City hovel as if  cadre of Angora rabbits had visited. A girlfriend whose sickly-sweet incense and musky perfume coated Vladimir's unwashed skin, perhaps to remind him of what he could expect on this, the night of his birthday: Sex. Every week, once a week, they had to have sex, as both he and this large pale woman, this Challah, perceived that without weekly sex their relationship would fold up according to some unspecified law of relationships." -- Gary Shteyngart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196006-well-i-ll-take-these-pages-and-move-on-things-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 16:37:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196006-well-i-ll-take-these-pages-and-move-on-things-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, I'll take these pages and move on. Things are happening elsewhere. Things are always happening. It seems wherever I go there is drama. People are like lice - they get under your skin and bury themselves there. You scratch and scratch until the blood comes, but you can't get permanently deloused. Everywhere I go people are making a mess of their lives. Everyone has his private tragedy. It's in the blood now - misfortune, ennui, grief, suicide. The atmosphere is saturated with disaster, frustration, futility. Scratch and scratch, until there's no skin left. However, the effect upon me is exhilarating. Instead of being discouraged or depressed, I enjoy it. I am crying for more and more disasters, for bigger calamities, grander failures. I want the whole world to be out of whack, I want every one to scratch himself to death." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196004-he-once-told-me-about-polar-bears---what-solitary</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 16:37:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196004-he-once-told-me-about-polar-bears---what-solitary]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He once told me about polar bears - what solitary animals they are. They mate just once a year. One time in a whole year. There is no such thing as a lasting male-female bond in their world. One male polar bear and one female polar bear meet by sheer chance somewhere in the frozen vastness, and they mate. It doesn't take long. And once they are finished, the male runs away from the female as if he is frightened to death: he runs from the place where they have mated. He never looks back - literally. The rest of the year he lives in deep solitude. Mutual communications - the touching of two hearts - do not exist for them. So, that is the story of polar bears - or at least it is what my employer told me about them.'

How very strange.'

Yes, it is strange. I remember asking my employer, ' Then what do polar bears exist for?' ' Yes, exactly,' he said with a big smile. 'Then what do we exist for?" -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196005-give-up-on-me-he-begged-her-i-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 16:37:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196005-give-up-on-me-he-begged-her-i-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Give up on me &quot; he begged her. &quot;I don't like people dropping in to see me without warning, I have forgotten the rules of seven tiles and kabaddi, I can't recite my prayers, I don't know what should happen at a nikah ceremony, and in this city where I grew up I get lost if I'm on my own. This isn't home. It makes me giddy because it feels like home and is not. It makes my heart tremble and my head spin.&quot;

&quot;You're a stupid, &quot; she shouted at him. &quot;A stupid. Change back! Damn fool! Of course you can.&quot; She was a vortex, a siren, tempting him back to his old self. But it was a dead self, a shadow, a ghost and he would not become a phantom. There was a return ticket to London in his wallet, and he was going to use it." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196003-they-ended-every-speech-with-the-word-hiro-which-means</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 16:37:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Leonard Cohen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196003-they-ended-every-speech-with-the-word-hiro-which-means]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They ended every speech with the word hiro, which means: like I said. Thus each man took responsibility for intruding into the inarticulate murmur of the spheres. To hiro they added the word koue, a cry of joy or distress, according to whether it was sung or howled. Thus they essayed to piece the mysterious curtain which hangs between all talking men: at the end of every utterance a man stepped back, so to speak, and attempted to interpret his words to the listener, attempted to subvert the beguiling intellect with the noise of true emotion." -- Leonard Cohen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318118-aside-from-the-possible-scientific-explanations-for-the-death-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 16:36:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Jonathan Ames]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318118-aside-from-the-possible-scientific-explanations-for-the-death-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Aside from the possible scientific explanations for the death of ballsiness, there is an economic one, which I think may be the real cause: high rents. It's very hard to be a ballsy writer when you can't afford to live anywhere. It makes you absolutely nervous and insane and takes all yours guts away. I have to say this is the case for yours truly. If I could pay a 1954 rent of fifty-eight dollars a month, I might actually be a ballsy writer. But I'm so crippled by my enormous twenty-first century rent that I can barely get out of bed, let alone raise hell, which is what you need to do to qualify as a ballsy writer. You have to be a hell-raiser. You have to care about political things and you have to be able to afford booze, not to mention days lost to hangovers. But if you're worried all the time about having to go live with your parents as a thirty-seven-year-old, then to hell with hell. You only have one goal: to come up with the rent. You don't have time for political causes or all-night orgies." -- Jonathan Ames]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46027-kumiko-and-i-felt-something-for-each-other-from-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 16:36:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46027-kumiko-and-i-felt-something-for-each-other-from-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kumiko and I felt something for each other from the beginning. It was not one of those strong, impulsive feelings that can hit two people like an electric shock when they first meet, but something quieter and gentler, like two tiny lights traveling in tandem through a vast darkness and drawing imperceptibly closer to each other as they go. As our meetings grew more frequent, I felt not so much that I had met someone new as that I had chanced upon a dear old friend." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196193-i-saw-that-sign-said-dwayne-and-i-couldn-t-help</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 16:36:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196193-i-saw-that-sign-said-dwayne-and-i-couldn-t-help]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I saw that sign,' said Dwayne, &quot;and I couldn't help wondering if that was what God put me on the earth for - to find out how much a man could take without breaking." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48373-love-is-like-falconry-he-said-don-t-you-think-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 06:30:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48373-love-is-like-falconry-he-said-don-t-you-think-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is like falconry,&quot; he said. &quot;Don't you think that's true, Cleveland?&quot;&lt;br&gt;&quot;Never say love is like anything.&quot; said Cleveland.  &quot;It isn't." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218305-anything-s-possible-in-human-nature-chacko-said-in-his-reading</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 06:30:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218305-anything-s-possible-in-human-nature-chacko-said-in-his-reading]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anything's possible in Human Nature,&quot; Chacko said in his Reading Aloud voice. Talking to the darkness now, suddenly insensitive to his little fountain-haired niece. &quot;Love. Madness. Hope. Infinite joy.&quot;
Of the four things that were Possible in Human Nature, Rahel thought that Infinnate Joy sounded the saddest. Perhaps because of the way Chacko said it.
Infinnate Joy. With a church sound to it. Like a sad fish with fins all over." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19778-the-secret-of-the-great-stories-is-that-they-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 06:30:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19778-the-secret-of-the-great-stories-is-that-they-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...the secret of the Great Stories is that they &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; no secrets. The Great Stories are the ones you have heard and want to hear again. The ones you can enter anywhere and inhabit comfortably. They don’t deceive you with thrills and trick endings. They don’t surprise you with the unforeseen. They are as familiar as the house you live in. Or the smell of your lover’s skin. You know how they end, yet you listen as though you don’t. In the way that although you know that one day you will die, you live as though you won’t. In the Great Stories you know who lives, who dies, who finds love, who doesn’t. And yet you want to know again.

&lt;i&gt;That&lt;/i&gt; is their mystery and their magic." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318121-i-live-for-coincidences-they-briefly-give-to-me-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 06:29:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Jonathan Ames]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318121-i-live-for-coincidences-they-briefly-give-to-me-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I live for coincidences. They briefly give to me the illusion or the hope that there's a pattern to my life, and if there's a pattern, then maybe I'm moving toward some kind of destiny where it's all explained." -- Jonathan Ames]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/572896-the-most-absurd-apology-for-authority-and-law-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 12:29:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Emma Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/572896-the-most-absurd-apology-for-authority-and-law-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most absurd apology for authority and law is that they serve to diminish crime. Aside from the fact that the State is itself the greatest criminal, breaking every written and natural law, stealing in the form of taxes, killing in the form of war and capital punishment, it has come to an absolute standstill in coping with crime. It has failed utterly to destroy or even minimize the horrible scourge of its own creation." -- Emma Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/632575-when-i-see-an-actual-flesh-and-blood-worker-in-conflict-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 14:22:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/632575-when-i-see-an-actual-flesh-and-blood-worker-in-conflict-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I see an actual flesh-and-blood worker in conflict with his natural enemy, the policeman, I do not have to ask myself which side I am on." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/632576-for-the-first-time-in-my-life-i-took-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 14:24:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/632576-for-the-first-time-in-my-life-i-took-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the first time in my life I took to writing things on walls. The passage-ways of several smart restaurants had ' Visca P.O.U.M.!' scrawled on them as large as I could write it. All the while, though I was technically in hiding, I could not feel myself in danger. The whole thing seemed too absurd. I had the ineradicable English belief that they cannot arrest you unless you have committed a crime. It is a most dangerous belief to have during a political pogrom." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/693155-no-american-sport-or-activity-has-been-so-consistently-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2012 16:54:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Joyce Carol Oates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/693155-no-american-sport-or-activity-has-been-so-consistently-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No American sport or activity has been so consistently and so passionately under attack as boxing, for &quot;moral&quot; as we'll as other reasons. And no American sport evokes so ambivalent a response in its defenders: when asked the familiar question &quot;How can you watch . . . ?&quot; the boxing aficionado really has no answer. He can talk about boxing only with others like himself." -- Joyce Carol Oates]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/722902-if-she-had-known-just-a-few-months-before-during</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 20:04:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Jami Attenberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/722902-if-she-had-known-just-a-few-months-before-during]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...if she had known just a few months before, during more innocent times, that she would feel that way for the rest of her life....which is to say conflicted, she would have treasured those unaware, nonjudgmental, preadolescent moments more thoroughly. (Oh, to be eleven again!) Because once you know, once you really know how the world works, you can't unknow it." -- Jami Attenberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/799622-he-was-a-fool-to-think-he-could-have-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 20:05:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Jami Attenberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/799622-he-was-a-fool-to-think-he-could-have-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was a fool to think he could have love twice in this life. Arrogance. He held her hand close his chest with both of his hands. No one was entitled to anything in this life, not the least of all love." -- Jami Attenberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/799623-but-she-never-wanted-to-be-in-a-relationship-ever</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 20:06:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Jami Attenberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/799623-but-she-never-wanted-to-be-in-a-relationship-ever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...but she never wanted to be in a relationship ever again. Because relationships were the worst. So many obligations. So many compromises. So many arguments. Someone always got destroyed in the end. Sometimes everyone got destroyed in the end." -- Jami Attenberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/799624-but-why-should-i-care-what-he-s-doing-if-i-m</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 20:08:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diane add a quote by Jami Attenberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/799624-but-why-should-i-care-what-he-s-doing-if-i-m]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But why should I care what he's doing if I'm crazy about you?'
'We are allowed to have more than one feeling at once,' said Kenneth. 'We are human beings, not ants." -- Jami Attenberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
