<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/633585-darlyne]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/633585-darlyne" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 07:04:02 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101-such-were-the-factors-that-detached-ormus-cama-from-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 07:04:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darlyne add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101-such-were-the-factors-that-detached-ormus-cama-from-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Such were the factors that detached Ormus Cama from the ordinary ties of family life. The ties that strangle us, which we call love. Because of the loosening of these ties he became, with all the attendant pain of such becoming, free.
But love is what we want, not freedom. Who then is the unluckier man? The beloved, who is given his heart's desire and must forever after fear its loss, or the free man, with his unlooked-for liberty, naked and alone between the captive armies of the earth?" -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1027523-when-we-re-incomplete-we-re-always-searching-for-somebody-to-complete</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 10:22:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darlyne add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1027523-when-we-re-incomplete-we-re-always-searching-for-somebody-to-complete]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we’re incomplete, we’re always searching for somebody to complete us. When, after a few years or a few months of a relationship, we find that we’re still unfulfilled, we blame our partners and take up with somebody more promising. This can go on and on—series polygamy—until we admit that while a partner can add sweet dimensions to our lives, we, each of us, are responsible for our own fulfillment. Nobody else can provide it for us, and to believe otherwise is to delude ourselves dangerously and to program for eventual failure every relationship we enter." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
