<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/637107-bethany]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/637107-bethany" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 16:07:37 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/707-all-you-can-do-is-hope-for-a-pattern-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 16:07:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/707-all-you-can-do-is-hope-for-a-pattern-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All you can do is hope for a pattern to emerge, and sometimes it never does. Still, with a plan, you only get the best you can imagine. I'd always hoped for something better than that." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/708-it-struck-me-as-pretty-ridiculous-to-be-called-mr</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 16:09:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Helen Fielding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/708-it-struck-me-as-pretty-ridiculous-to-be-called-mr]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It struck me as pretty ridiculous to be called Mr. Darcy and to stand on your own looking snooty at a party. It's like being called Heathcliff and insisting on spending the entire evening in the garden, shouting &quot;Cathy&quot; and banging your head against a tree." -- Helen Fielding]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/709-far-away-i-could-hear-them-lapping-up-my-brains</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 16:13:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/709-far-away-i-could-hear-them-lapping-up-my-brains]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Far away, I could hear them lapping up my brains. Like Macbeth's witches, the three lithe cats surrounded my broken head, slurping up that thick soup inside. The tips of their rough tongues licked the soft folds of my mind. And with each lick my consciousness flickered like a flame and faded away." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/710-love-knows-no-virtue-no-merit-it-loves-and-forgives</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 16:15:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Leopold von Sacher-Masoch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/710-love-knows-no-virtue-no-merit-it-loves-and-forgives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love knows no virtue, no merit; it loves and forgives and tolerates everything because it must. We are not guided by reason..." -- Leopold von Sacher-Masoch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/711-i-fear-that-with-our-current-veneration-for-the-natural</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 16:19:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/711-i-fear-that-with-our-current-veneration-for-the-natural]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I fear that, with our current veneration for the natural and the real, we have arrived at the opposite pole to all idealism, and have landed in the region of the waxworks." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/712-standing-on-an-open-hill-i-imagine-muffled-footsteps-overhead</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 16:19:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by John Champlin Gardner Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/712-standing-on-an-open-hill-i-imagine-muffled-footsteps-overhead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Standing on an open hill, I imagine muffled footsteps overhead." -- John Champlin Gardner Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/713-he-had-illuminated-the-heartbreaking-cruelty-of-war-when-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 16:21:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Patricia O'Brien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/713-he-had-illuminated-the-heartbreaking-cruelty-of-war-when-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He had illuminated the heartbreaking cruelty of war: When men who fight become nothing, only packages of bones and blood deposited in the earth with no clarion call to memory, those they love are left without a way to make such devastating loss hold meaning." -- Patricia O'Brien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47930-let-me-say-right-here-if-i-haven-t-made-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2008 10:19:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Christopher Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47930-let-me-say-right-here-if-i-haven-t-made-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me say right here, if I haven't made it clear, that I have seen as many pale, naked old-man parts in the last twenty-four hours to bruise my delicate psyche for a lifetime, so don't be surprised if you someday find me wandering the moors at midnight, a crazed look in my eye, babbling about albino Tater Tots nesting in Brillo pads and being pursued by sagging man ass, because that shit can happen when you've been traumatized." -- Christopher Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47931-tommy-had-felt-alone-in-a-crowd-before-even-inferior</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2008 10:21:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Christopher Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47931-tommy-had-felt-alone-in-a-crowd-before-even-inferior]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tommy had felt alone in a crowd before, even inferior to everyone in a crowd, but now he felt, well, different.  It wasn't just the clothes and the make up, it was the humanity. He wasn't part of it. Heightened senses or not, he felt like he had his nose pressed against the window, looking in. The problem was, it was the window of a donut shop." -- Christopher Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47933-resting-on-what-s-considered-great-has-always-been-a-recipe</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2008 10:26:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Robert K. Cooper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47933-resting-on-what-s-considered-great-has-always-been-a-recipe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Resting on what's considered great has always been a recipe for decline. I remember touring Rome with a guide who pointed out one marvelous achievement after another of the first Roman emperor, Augustus. Augustus was said to have inherited a city of brick and left a city of marble, with twelve entrances on twelve hills.  He built nearly a thousand glorious new structures - bridges, buildings, monuments, and aqueducts. As we marveled at the remnants of Augustus's grand designs, our guide exclaimed with pride that this era marked the pinnacle of Rome's greatness.
What came next?' I asked.
After an awkward silence, the guide said,  'Slow ruin." -- Robert K. Cooper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77798-they-always-do-the-same-thing---come-in-ask</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 07:24:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Patricia Wrede]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77798-they-always-do-the-same-thing---come-in-ask]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They always do the same thing - come in, ask for a meal, hide, and then run off with a harp or a bag full of money the minute I fall asleep,' Dobbilan said. 'And they're always named Jack. &lt;i&gt;Always.&lt;/i&gt; We've lived in this castle for twenty years, and every three months, regular as clockwork, one of those boys shows up, and there's never been a Tom, Dick, or Harry among 'em. Just Jacks.  The English have no imagination." -- Patricia Wrede]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105812-god-said-thou-shalt-not-kill---does-the-theft</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 15:34:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Thomas More]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105812-god-said-thou-shalt-not-kill---does-the-theft]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God said, &quot;Thou shalt not kill&quot; - does the theft of a little money make it quite all right for us to do so? If it's said that this commandment applies only to illegal killing, what's to prevent human beings from similarly agreeing among themselves to legalize certain types of rape, adultery, or perjury? Considering that God has forbidden us even to kill ourselves, can we really believe that purely human arrangements for the regulation of mutual slaughter are enough, without any divine authority, to exempt executioners from the sixth commandment?  Isn't that like saying that this particular commandment has no more validity than human laws allow it? - in which case the principle can be extended indefinitely, until in all spheres of life human beings decide just how far God's commandments may conveniently be observed." -- Thomas More]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105809-until-you-put-these-things-to-right-you-re-not-entitled</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 15:52:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Thomas More]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105809-until-you-put-these-things-to-right-you-re-not-entitled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until you put these things to right, you're not entitled to boast of the justice meted out to thieves, for it's a justice more specious than real or social desirable. You allow these people to be brought up in the worst possible way, and systematically corrupted from their earliest years. Finally, when they grow up and commit the crimes that they were obviously destined to commit, ever since they were children, you start punishing them. In other words, you create thieves, and then punish them for stealing." -- Thomas More]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118046-i-drank-lots-of-water-and-orange-juice-and-took</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 21:57:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Charlaine Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118046-i-drank-lots-of-water-and-orange-juice-and-took]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I drank lots of water and orange juice and took a multivitamin and iron supplement for breakfast, which was my regimen since Bill had come into my life and brought (along with love, adventure, and excitement) the constant threat of anemia." -- Charlaine Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 19:24:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363-it-is-better-to-remain-silent-at-the-risk-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 19:24:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Maurice Switzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363-it-is-better-to-remain-silent-at-the-risk-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to remain silent at the risk of being thought a fool, than to talk and remove all doubt of it." -- Maurice Switzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 19:25:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opposite of love is not hate, it's indifference. The opposite of art is not ugliness, it's indifference. The opposite of faith is not heresy, it's indifference. And the opposite of life is not death, it's indifference." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71-the-fool-doth-think-he-is-wise-but-the-wise</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 19:26:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71-the-fool-doth-think-he-is-wise-but-the-wise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fool doth think he is wise, but the wise man knows himself to be a fool." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 19:27:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/796-classic---a-book-which-people-praise-and-don-t-read</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 11:16:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/796-classic---a-book-which-people-praise-and-don-t-read]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Classic' - a book which people praise and don't read." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1211314-we-need-to-see-people-other-than-ourselves-in-order</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 12:16:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bethany add a quote by Charles Blow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1211314-we-need-to-see-people-other-than-ourselves-in-order]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We need to see people other than ourselves in order to empathize. If we don't live around others we do ourselves and our society damage because our ability to relate becomes impaired. It's easy to demonize, or simply dismiss, people you don't know or see...It's nearly impossible to commiserate with the unseen and unknown." -- Charles Blow]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
