<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/638424-claire]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/638424-claire" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 03:45:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63142-anyone-who-falls-in-love-is-searching-for-the-missing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 03:45:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[claire add a quote by Murakami, Haruki]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63142-anyone-who-falls-in-love-is-searching-for-the-missing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who falls in love is searching for the missing pieces of themselves. So anyone who's in love gets sad when they think of their lover. It's like stepping back inside a room you have fond memories of, one you haven't seen in a long time." -- Murakami, Haruki]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98274-fiction-is-one-of-the-few-experiences-where-loneliness-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 22:12:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[claire add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98274-fiction-is-one-of-the-few-experiences-where-loneliness-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fiction is one of the few experiences where loneliness can be both confronted and relieved. Drugs, movies where stuff blows up, loud parties -- all these chase away loneliness by making me forget my name's Dave and I live in a one-by-one box of bone no other party can penetrate or know. Fiction, poetry, music, really deep serious sex, and, in various ways, religion -- these are the places (for me) where loneliness is countenanced, stared down, transfigured, treated." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149021-fiction-s-about-what-it-is-to-be-a-fucking-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 22:12:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[claire add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149021-fiction-s-about-what-it-is-to-be-a-fucking-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fiction’s about what it is to be a fucking human being." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4786-every-day-we-slaughter-our-finest-impulses-that-is-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 22:14:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[claire add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4786-every-day-we-slaughter-our-finest-impulses-that-is-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every day we slaughter our finest impulses. That is why we get a heartache when we read those lines written by the hand of a master and recognize them as our own, as the tender shoots which we stifled because we lacked the faith to believe in our own powers, our own criterion of truth and beauty. Every man, when he gets quiet, when he becomes desperately honest with himself, is capable of uttering profound truths. We all derive from the same source. there is no mystery about the origin of things. We are all part of creation, all kings, all poets, all musicians; we have only to open up, only to discover what is already there." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11127-everything-we-shut-our-eyes-to-everything-we-run-away</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 22:14:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[claire add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11127-everything-we-shut-our-eyes-to-everything-we-run-away]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything we shut our eyes to, everything we run away from, everything we deny, denigrate, or despise, serves to defeat us in the end." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26557-this-is-what-it-means-to-be-an-adventurer-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 14:23:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[claire add a quote by Hib Chickena]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26557-this-is-what-it-means-to-be-an-adventurer-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what it means to be an adventurer in our day: to give up creature comforts of the mind, to realize the possibilities of imagination. Because everything around us says no you cannot do this, you cannot live without that, nothing is useful unless it's in service to money, to gain, to stability.  The adventurer gives in to tides of chaos, trusts the world to support her - and in doing so turns her back on the fear and obedience she has been taught.  She rejects the indoctrination of impossibility." -- Hib Chickena]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
