<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/638694-samantha]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/638694-samantha" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2007 17:53:54 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8774-there-is-no-escape-you-can-t-be-a-vagabond-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2007 17:53:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8774-there-is-no-escape-you-can-t-be-a-vagabond-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no escape. You can't be a vagabond and an artist and still be a solid citizen, a wholesome, upstanding man. You want to get drunk, so you have to accept the hangover. You say yes to the sunlight and pure fantasies, so you have to say yes to the filth and the nausea. Everything is within you, gold and mud, happiness and pain, the laughter of childhood and the apprehension of death. Say yes to everything, shirk nothing. Don't try to lie to yourself. You are not a solid citizen. You are not a Greek. You are not harmonious, or the master of yourself. You are a bird in the storm. Let it storm! Let it drive you! How much have you lied! A thousand times, even in your poems and books, you have played the harmonious man, the wise man, the happy, the enlightened man. In the same way, men attacking in war have played heroes, while their bowels twitched. My God, what a poor ape, what a fencer in the mirror man is- particularly the artist- particularly myself!" -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8776-maybe-we-all-live-life-at-too-high-a-pitch</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2007 17:59:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8776-maybe-we-all-live-life-at-too-high-a-pitch]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe we all live life at too high a pitch, those of us who absorb emotional things all day, and as mere consequence we can never feel merely content: we have to be unhappy, or ecstatically, head-over-heels happy, and those states are difficult to achieve within a stable, solid relationship." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8782-i-have-no-brakes-on-analysis-is-for-those-who-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2007 18:04:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8782-i-have-no-brakes-on-analysis-is-for-those-who-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have no brakes on...analysis is for those who are paralyzed by life." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8805-this-is-what-i-thought-for-the-most-banal-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2007 19:23:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Jean-Paul Sartre]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8805-this-is-what-i-thought-for-the-most-banal-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what I thought: for the most banal even to become an adventure, you must (and this is enough) begin to recount it. This is what fools people: a man is always a teller of tales, he sees everything that happens to him through them; and he tries to live his own life as if he were telling a story.
But you have to choose: live or tell." -- Jean-Paul Sartre]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11071-human-beings-are-perhaps-never-more-frightening-than-when-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2008 19:03:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Laurens van der Post]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11071-human-beings-are-perhaps-never-more-frightening-than-when-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human beings are perhaps never more frightening than when they are convinced beyond doubt that they are right." -- Laurens van der Post]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/830423-grown-ups-don-t-look-like-grown-ups-on-the-inside-either-outside</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2013 07:38:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/830423-grown-ups-don-t-look-like-grown-ups-on-the-inside-either-outside]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Grown-ups don't look like grown-ups on the inside either. Outside, they're big and thoughtless and they always know what they're doing. Inside, they look just like they always have. Like they did when they were your age. Truth is, there aren't any grown-ups. Not one, in the whole wide world." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
