<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/639626-bellarmin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/639626-bellarmin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 11:55:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154538-where-am-i-or-what-from-what-causes-do-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 11:55:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bellarmin add a quote by David Hume]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154538-where-am-i-or-what-from-what-causes-do-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where am I, or what? From what causes do I derive my existence, and to what condition shall I return? ... I am confounded with all these questions, and begin to fancy myself in the most deplorable condition imaginable, environed with the deepest darkness, and utterly deprived of the use of every member and faculty.

Most fortunately it happens, that since Reason is incapable of dispelling these clouds, Nature herself suffices to that purpose, and cures me of this philosophical melancholy and delirium, either by relaxing this bent of mind, or by some avocation, and lively impression of my senses, which obliterate all these chimeras. I dine, I play a game of backgammon, I converse, and am merry with my friends. And when, after three or four hours' amusement, I would return to these speculations, they appear so cold, and strained, and ridiculous, that I cannot find in my heart to enter into them any farther." -- David Hume]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113511-i-ve-thought-of-myself-a-girl-on-several-occasions-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2012 12:49:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bellarmin add a quote by Robert Walser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113511-i-ve-thought-of-myself-a-girl-on-several-occasions-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've thought of myself a girl on several occasions because I like to polish shoes and find household tasks amusing.  There was once even a time when I insisted on mending a torn suit with my own hands.  And in winter I always light the heating stoves myself, as though this were the natural course of things.  But of course I'm not a real girl.  Please give me a moment to consider all this would entail.  The first thing that comes to mind is the question of whether I might possibly be a girl has never, never, not for a single moment, troubled me, rattled my bourgeois composure or made me unhappy.  An absolutely by no means unhappy person stands before you, I'd like to put quite special emphasis on this, for I have never experienced sexual torment or distress, for I was never at a loss for quite simple methods of freeing myself from pressures.  A rather curious, that is to say, important discovery for me was that it filled me with the most delightful gaiety to imagine myself someone's servant....  My nature, then, merely inclines me to treat people well, to be helpful and so forth.  Not long ago I carried with flabbergasting zeal a shopping bag full of new potatoes for a petit bourgeoise.  She's have been perfectly able to tote it herself.  Now my situation is this: my particular nature also sometimes seeks, I've discovered, a mother, a teacher, that is, to express myself better, an unapproachable entity, a sort of goddess.  At times I find the goddess in an instant, whereas at others it takes time before I'm able to imagine her, that is, find her bright, bountiful figure and sense her power.  And to achieve a moment of human happiness, I must always first think up a story containing an encounter between myself and another person, whereby I am always the subordinate, obedient, sacrificing, scrutinized, and chaperoned party.  There's more to it, of course, quite a lot, but this still sheds light on a few things.  Many conclude it must be terribly easy to carry out a course of treatment, as it were, upon my person, but they're all gravely mistaken.  For, the moment anyone seems ready to start lording and lecturing it over me, something within me begins to laugh, to jeer, and then, of course, respect is out of the question, and within the apparently worthless individual arises a superior one whom I never expel when he appears in me...." -- Robert Walser]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
