<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/640941-micaela]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/640941-micaela" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 08:12:17 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68596-jews-have-six-senses-touch-taste-sight-smell-hearing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 08:12:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Micaela add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68596-jews-have-six-senses-touch-taste-sight-smell-hearing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["JEWS HAVE SIX SENSES
Touch, taste, sight, smell, hearing … memory.  While Gentiles experience and process the world through the traditional senses, and use memory only as a second-order means of interpreting events, for Jews memory is no less primary than the prick of a pin, or its silver glimmer, or the taste of the blood it pulls from the finger.  The Jew is pricked by a pin and remembers other pins.  It is only by tracing the pinprick back to other pinpricks – when his mother tried to fix his sleeve while his arm was still in it, when his grandfather’s fingers fell asleep from stroking his great-grandfather’s damp forehead, when Abraham tested the knife point to be sure Isaac would feel no pain – that the Jew is able to know why it hurts.
When a Jew encounters a pin, he asks:  What does it remember like?" -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103871-from-space-astronauts-can-see-people-making-love-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 08:12:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Micaela add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103871-from-space-astronauts-can-see-people-making-love-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From space, astronauts can see people making love as a tiny speck of light. Not light, exactly, but a glow that could be confused for light - a coital radiance that takes generations to pour like honey through the darkness to the astronaut's eyes.

In about one and a half centuries - after the lovers who made the glow will have long since been laid permanently on their backs - the metropolitan cities will be seen from space. They will glow all year. Smaller cities will also be seen, but with great difficulty. Towns will be virtually impossible to spot. Individual couples invisible." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
