<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/641361-annwheliss]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/641361-annwheliss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2011 14:55:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49274-if-what-s-always-distinguished-bad-writing--flat-characters-a-narrative-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2011 14:55:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AnnWheliss add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49274-if-what-s-always-distinguished-bad-writing--flat-characters-a-narrative-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If what's always distinguished bad writing--flat characters, a narrative world that's clichéd and not recognizably human, etc.--is also a description of today's world, then bad writing becomes an ingenious mimesis of a bad world. If readers simply believe the world is stupid and shallow and mean, then [Bret] Ellis can write a mean shallow stupid novel that becomes a mordant deadpan commentary on the badness of everything. Look man, we'd probably most of us agree that these are dark times, and stupid ones, but do we need fiction that does nothing but dramatize how dark and stupid everything is? In dark times, the definition of good art would seem to be art that locates and applies CPR to those elements of what's human and magical that still live and glow despite the times' darkness. Really good fiction could have as dark a worldview as it wished, but it'd find a way both to depict this world and to illuminate the possibilities for being alive and human in it.

Postmodern irony and cynicism's become an end in itself, a measure of hip sophistication and literary savvy. Few artists dare to try to talk about ways of working toward redeeming what's wrong, because they'll look sentimental and naive to all the weary ironists. Irony's gone from liberating to enslaving. There's some great essay somewhere that has a line about irony being the song of the prisoner who's come to love his cage… The postmodern founders' patricidal work was great, but patricide produces orphans, and no amount of revelry can make up for the fact that writers my age have been literary orphans throughout our formative years.

We enter a spiritual puberty where we snap to the fact that the great transcendent horror is loneliness, excluded encagement in the self. Once we’ve hit this age, we will now give or take anything, wear any mask, to fit, be part-of, not be Alone, we young. The U.S. arts are our guide to inclusion. A how-to. We are shown how to fashion masks of ennui and jaded irony at a young age where the face is fictile enough to assume the shape of whatever it wears. And then it’s stuck there, the weary cynicism that saves us from gooey sentiment and unsophisticated naïveté. Sentiment equals naïveté on this continent.

You burn with hunger for food that does not exist.

A U. S. of modern A. where the State is not a team or a code, but a sort of sloppy intersection of desires and fears, where the only public consensus a boy must surrender to is the acknowledged primacy of straight-line pursuing this flat and short-sighted idea of personal happiness." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21619-i-love-you-buttercup-said-i-know-this-must-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 15:37:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AnnWheliss add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21619-i-love-you-buttercup-said-i-know-this-must-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you,' Buttercup said. 'I know this must come as something of a surprise to you, since all I've ever done is scorn you and degrade you and taunt you, but I have loved you for several hours now, and every second, more. I thought an hour ago that I loved you more than any woman has ever loved a man, but a half hour after that I knew that what I felt before was nothing compared to what I felt then. But ten minutes after that, I understood that my previous love was a puddle compared to the high seas before a storm. Your eyes are like that, did you know? Well they are. How many minutes ago was I? Twenty? Had I brought my feelings up to then? It doesn't matter.' Buttercup still could not look at him. The sun was rising behind her now; she could feel the heat on her back, and it gave her courage. 'I love you so much more now than twenty minutes ago that there cannot be comparison. I love you so much more now then when you opened your hovel door, there cannot be comparison. There is no room in my body for anything but you. My arms love you, my ears adore you, my knees shake with blind affection. My mind begs you to ask it something so it can obey. Do you want me to follow you for the rest of your days? I will do that. Do you want me to crawl? I will crawl. I will be quiet for you or sing for you, or if you are hungry, let me bring you food, or if you have thirst and nothing will quench it but Arabian wine, I will go to Araby, even though it is across the world, and bring a bottle back for your lunch. Anything there is that I can do for you, I will do for you; anything there is that I cannot do, I will learn to do. I know I cannot compete with the Countess in skills or wisdom or appeal, and I saw the way she looked at you. And I saw the way you looked at her. But remember, please, that she is old and has other interests, while I am seventeen and for me there is only you. Dearest Westley--I've never called you that before, have I?--Westley, Westley, Westley, Westley, Westley,--darling Westley, adored Westley, sweet perfect Westley, whisper that I have a chance to win your love.' And with that, she dared the bravest thing she'd ever done; she looked right into his eyes." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27667-do-i-love-you-my-god-if-your-love-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 15:37:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AnnWheliss add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27667-do-i-love-you-my-god-if-your-love-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do I love you? My God, if your love were a grain of sand, mine would be a universe of beaches." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208362-cynics-are-simply-thwarted-romantics</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 15:45:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AnnWheliss add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208362-cynics-are-simply-thwarted-romantics]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cynics are simply thwarted romantics." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/495350-her-heart-was-a-secret-garden-and-the-walls-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 18:45:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AnnWheliss add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/495350-her-heart-was-a-secret-garden-and-the-walls-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her heart was a secret garden and the walls were very high." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
