<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/642041-sarah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/642041-sarah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 10:12:07 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118042-it-never-takes-longer-than-a-few-minutes-when-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 10:12:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118042-it-never-takes-longer-than-a-few-minutes-when-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It never takes longer than a few minutes, when they get together, for everyone to revert to the state of nature, like a party marooned by a shipwreck. That's what a family is. Also the storm at sea, the ship, and the unknown shore. And the hats and the whiskey stills that you make out of bamboo and coconuts. And the fire that you light to keep away the beasts." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3622-whenever-the-horse-stopped-which-it-did-very-often-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 10:11:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3622-whenever-the-horse-stopped-which-it-did-very-often-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever the horse stopped (which it did very often), he fell off in front; and, whenever it went on again (which it generally did rather suddenly), he fell off behind.  Otherwise he kept on pretty well, except that he had a habit of now and then falling off sideways; and, as he generally did this on the side on which Alice was walking, she soon found that it was the best plan not to walk quite close to the horse." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11676-if-you-are-very-lucky-you-re-allowed-to-be-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 12:04:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Jonathan Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11676-if-you-are-very-lucky-you-re-allowed-to-be-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are very lucky, you're allowed to be in certain places during just the right season of your life: by the sea for the summer when you're seven or eight and full of the absolute need to swim until dark and exhaustion close their hands together, cupping you in between." -- Jonathan Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8706-life-will-break-you-nobody-can-protect-you-from-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 12:04:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8706-life-will-break-you-nobody-can-protect-you-from-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life will break you. Nobody can protect you from that, and living alone won't either, for solitude will also break you with its yearning. You have to love. You have to feel. It is the reason you are here on earth. You are here to risk your heart. You are here to be swallowed up. And when it happens that you are broken, or betrayed, or left, or hurt, or death brushes near, let yourself sit by an apple tree and listen to the apples falling all around you in heaps, wasting their sweetness. Tell yourself you tasted as many as you could." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37445-every-room-i-ve-lived-in-since-i-was-given-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 13:30:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Jonathan Lethem]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37445-every-room-i-ve-lived-in-since-i-was-given-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every room I've lived in since I was given my own room at eleven was lined with, and usually overfull of, books. My employment in bookstores was always continuous with my private hours: shelving and alphabetizing, building shelves, and browsing-- in my collection and others-- in order to understand a small amount about the widest possible number of books. Such numbers of books are constantly acquired that constant culling is necessary; if I slouch in this discipline, the books erupt. I've also bricked myself in with music--vinyl records, then compact discs. My homes have been improbably information-dense, like capsules for survival of a nuclear war, or models of the interior of my own skull. That comparison--room as brain-- is one I've often reached for in describing the rooms of others, but it began with the suspicion that I'd externalized my own brain, for anyone who cared to look." -- Jonathan Lethem]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3063-a-half-read-book-is-a-half-finished-love-affair</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2008 10:42:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3063-a-half-read-book-is-a-half-finished-love-affair]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A half-read book is a half-finished love affair." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6248-book-collecting-is-an-obsession-an-occupation-a-disease-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 07:34:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6248-book-collecting-is-an-obsession-an-occupation-a-disease-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Book collecting is an obsession, an occupation, a disease, an addiction, a fascination, an absurdity, a fate. It is not a hobby. Those who do it must do it. Those who do not do it, think of it as a cousin of stamp collecting, a sister of the trophy cabinet, bastard of a sound bank account and a weak mind." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1351-he-moved-like-a-dancer-which-is-not-surprising-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 13:15:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Mark Helprin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1351-he-moved-like-a-dancer-which-is-not-surprising-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He moved like a dancer, which is not surprising; a horse is a beautiful animal, but it is perhaps most remarkable because it moves as if it always hears music." -- Mark Helprin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13797-like-so-many-americans-she-was-trying-to-construct-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 06:52:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13797-like-so-many-americans-she-was-trying-to-construct-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like so many Americans, she was trying to construct a life that made sense from things she found in gift shops." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907-when-i-was-a-child-adults-would-tell-me-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 06:52:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907-when-i-was-a-child-adults-would-tell-me-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was a child, adults would tell me not to make things up, warning me of what would happen if I did. As far as I can tell so far, it seems to involve lots of foreign travel and not having to get up too early in the morning." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177684-how-does-one-hate-a-country-or-love-one-tibe</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 05:13:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177684-how-does-one-hate-a-country-or-love-one-tibe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How does one hate a country, or love one? Tibe talks about it; I lack the trick of it. I know people, I know towns, farms, hills and rivers and rocks, I know how the sun at sunset in autumn falls on the side of a certain plowland in the hills; but what is the sense of giving a boundary to all that, of giving it a name and ceasing to love where the name ceases to apply? What is love of one's country; is it hate of one's uncountry? Then it's not a good thing. Is it simply self-love? That's a good thing, but one mustn't make a virtue of it, or a profession... Insofar as I love life, I love the hills of the Domain of Estre, but that sort of love does not have a boundary-line of hate. And beyond that, I am ignorant, I hope." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184548-olive-s-private-view-is-that-life-depends-on-what-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2009 10:46:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184548-olive-s-private-view-is-that-life-depends-on-what-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Olive's private view is that life depends on what she thinks of as &quot;big bursts&quot; and &quot;little bursts.&quot; Big bursts are things like marriage or children, intimacies that keep you afloat, but these big bursts hold dangerous, unseen currents. Which is why you need the little bursts as well: a friendly clerk at Bradlee's, let's say, or the waitress at Dunkin' Donuts who knows how you like your coffee. Tricky business, really." -- Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190528-she-still-had-all-of-her-marbles-though-every-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2009 10:34:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Ellen Klages]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190528-she-still-had-all-of-her-marbles-though-every-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She still had all of her marbles, though every one of them was a bit odd and rolled asymmetrically." -- Ellen Klages]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/779-love-doesn-t-just-sit-there-like-a-stone-it-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 09:02:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/779-love-doesn-t-just-sit-there-like-a-stone-it-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love doesn't just sit there, like a stone, it has to be made, like bread; remade all the time, made new." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183435-every-one-of-us-is-called-upon-perhaps-many-times</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2009 11:13:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183435-every-one-of-us-is-called-upon-perhaps-many-times]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every one of us is called upon, perhaps many times, to start a new life.  A frightening diagnosis, a marriage, a move, loss of a job...And onward full-tilt we go, pitched and wrecked and absurdly resolute, driven in spite of everything to make good on a new shore.  To be hopeful, to embrace one possibility after another--that is surely the basic instinct...Crying out: High tide!  Time to move out into the glorious debris.  Time to take this life for what it is." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125338-want-is-a-thing-that-unfurls-unbidden-like-fungus-opening</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2009 11:13:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125338-want-is-a-thing-that-unfurls-unbidden-like-fungus-opening]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Want is a thing that unfurls unbidden like fungus, opening large upon itself, stopless, filling the sky.
But needs, from one day to the next, are few enough to fit in a bucket, with room enough left to rattle like brittle brush in a dry wind." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218006-i-never-put-real-people-into-my-fiction----i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2009 11:15:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218006-i-never-put-real-people-into-my-fiction----i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I never put real people into my fiction -- I can't see the slightest point of that, when I have the alternative of inventing utterly subservient slave-people, whose every detail of appearance and behavior I can bend to serve my theme and plot." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218008-high-fashion-has-the-shelf-life-of-potato-salad-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2009 11:16:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218008-high-fashion-has-the-shelf-life-of-potato-salad-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["High fashion has the shelf life of potato salad. And when past its prime, it is similarly deadly." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233598-she-wanted-to-tell-him-so-mach-on-the-tarmac</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 09:49:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Colum McCann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233598-she-wanted-to-tell-him-so-mach-on-the-tarmac]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She wanted to tell him so mach, on the tarmac, the day he left. The world is run by brutal men and the surest proof is their armies. If they ask you to stand still, you should dance. If they ask you to burn the flag, wave it. If they ask you to murder, re-create. " -- Colum McCann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222015-she-s-always-thought-that-one-of-the-beauties-of-new</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2010 06:04:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Colum McCann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222015-she-s-always-thought-that-one-of-the-beauties-of-new]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She's always thought that one of the beauties of New York is that you can be from anywhere and within moments of landing its yours." -- Colum McCann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247167-when-we-got-to-the-part-where-we-had-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 15:58:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Patti Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247167-when-we-got-to-the-part-where-we-had-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we got to the part where we had to improvise an argument in a poetic language, I got cold feet. &quot;I can't do this,&quot; I said. &quot;I don't know what to say.&quot;

&quot;Say anything,&quot; he said. &quot;You can't make a mistake when you improvise.&quot;

&quot;What if I mess it up? What if I screw up the rhythm?&quot;

&quot;You can't,&quot; he said. &quot;It's like drumming. If you miss a beat, you create another.&quot;

In this simple exchange, Sam taught me the secret of improvisation, one that I have accessed my whole life." -- Patti Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270827-but-the-real-life-of-a-writer-resides-in-showing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 16:39:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Steve Almond]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270827-but-the-real-life-of-a-writer-resides-in-showing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the real life of a writer resides in showing up at the keyboard every day, with the necessary patience and mercy, and making the best decisions you can on behalf of your people. It’s a slow process. It often feels hopeless, more like an affliction than an art form.

Most of us will have to find our readers one by one, in other words, and against considerable resistance. If anything qualifies us as heroic, it’s that private perpetual struggle.

Put down the magazine, soldier. Forget about the other guy. Remember who you are." -- Steve Almond]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279518-one-of-the-most-terrible-losses-man-endures-in-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 13:25:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Jonathan Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279518-one-of-the-most-terrible-losses-man-endures-in-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the most terrible losses man endures in his lifetime is not even noticed by most people, much less mourned. Which is astonishing, because what we lose is in many ways one of the essential qualities that sets us apart from other creatures. I'm talking about the loss of the sense of wonder that is such an integral part of our world when we are children. However, as we grow older, that sense of wonder shrinks from cosmic to microscopic by the time we are adults. Kids say &quot;Wow!&quot; all the time. Opening their mouths fully, their eyes light up with genuine awe and glee. The word emanates not so much from a voice box as from an astonished soul that has once again been shown that the world is full of amazing unexpected things.
When was the last time you let fly a loud, truly heartfelt &quot;WOW?&quot;
NOt recently I bet. Because generally speaking wonder belongs to kids, with the rare exception of falling madly in love with another person, which invariably leads to a rebirth of wonder. As adults, we are not supposed to say or feel Wow, or wonder, or even true surprise because those things make us sound goofy, ingenuous, and childlike. How can you run the world if you are in constant awe of it?...
The human heart has a long memory though and remembers what it was like to live through days where it was constantly surprised and delighted by the world around it." -- Jonathan Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9748-no-long-term-marriage-is-made-easily-and-there-have-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2010 09:43:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9748-no-long-term-marriage-is-made-easily-and-there-have-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No long-term marriage is made easily, and there have been times when I've been so angry or so hurt that I thought my love would never recover. And then, in the midst of near despair, something has happened beneath the surface. A bright little flashing fish of hope has flicked silver fins and the water is bright and suddenly I am returned to a state of love again — till next time. I've learned that there will always be a next time, and that I will submerge in darkness and misery, but that I won't stay submerged. And each time something has been learned under the waters; something has been gained; and a new kind of love has grown. The best I can ask for is that this love, which has been built on countless failures, will continue to grow. I can say no more than that this is mystery, and gift, and that somehow or other, through grace, our failures can be redeemed and blessed." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41504-our-truest-response-to-the-irrationality-of-the-world-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2010 09:43:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41504-our-truest-response-to-the-irrationality-of-the-world-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our truest response to the irrationality of the world is to paint or sing or write, for only in such response do we find truth." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12315-would-it-be-possible-for-me-to-see-something-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2010 11:51:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Norton Juster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12315-would-it-be-possible-for-me-to-see-something-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Would it be possible for me to see something from up there?&quot; asked Milo politely.

&quot;You could,&quot; said Alec, &quot;but only if you try very hard to look at things as an adult does.&quot;

Milo tried as hard as he could, and, as he did, his feet floated slowly off the ground until he was standing in the air next to Alex Bings.  He looked around very quickly and, an instant later, crashed back down to the earth again.

&quot;Interesting, wasn't it?&quot; asked Alex.

&quot;Yes, it was,&quot; agreed Milo, rubbing his head and dusting himself off, &quot;but I think I'll continue to see things as a child.  It's not so far to fall." -- Norton Juster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287060-the-wrong-word-is-like-a-lie-jammed-inside-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2010 21:04:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Grace Paley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287060-the-wrong-word-is-like-a-lie-jammed-inside-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The wrong word is like a lie jammed inside the story." -- Grace Paley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292347-every-good-writer-i-know-needs-to-go-into-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 13:02:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292347-every-good-writer-i-know-needs-to-go-into-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every good writer I know needs to go into some deep, quiet place to do work that is fully imagined. And what the Internet brings is lots of vulgar data. It is the antithesis of the imagination. It leaves nothing to the imagination." -- Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314130-music-has-become-more-pervasive-and-portable-than-ever-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 08:00:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Steve Almond]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314130-music-has-become-more-pervasive-and-portable-than-ever-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Music has become more pervasive and portable than ever. But it feels less previous in the bargain. I don't want to confuse artistic and commercial value, but it's just a fact that some kid who rips an album for free isn't going to give it the same attention he would if it cost him ten bucks. At what point does convenience become spiritual indolence? I realize this makes me sound like an old fart, but sometimes I get nostalgic for the days when the universe of recorded sound wasn't at our fingertips, when we had to hunt and wait and - horror of horrors - do without, when our longing for a particular record or song made it feel sacred." -- Steve Almond]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314131-the-connection-being-that-in-my-head-all-language-began</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 08:00:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Steve Almond]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314131-the-connection-being-that-in-my-head-all-language-began]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The connection being that in my head all language began in song and that the best stories inevitably reutrn to song, to a state of rapture. For years, I had assumed that throwing beautiful words at the page would make my prose feel true. But I had the process exactly backward. It was truth that lifted the language into beauty and toward song. It was a matter of doing what Joe Henry did, of pursuing characters into moments of emotional truth and slowing down. The result was a compression of sensual and psychological detail that released the rhythm and melody in language itself, what Longfellow called &quot;the happy accidents of language." -- Steve Almond]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
