<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/642153-judy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/642153-judy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 08:26:48 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/925991-cause-i-d-rather-stay-here-with-all-the-madmen-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 08:26:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by David Bowie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/925991-cause-i-d-rather-stay-here-with-all-the-madmen-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cause I'd rather stay here
With all the madmen
Than perish with the sadmen roaming free
And I'd rather play here
With all the madmen
For I'm quite content they're all as sane
As me" -- David Bowie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12030-hold-fast-to-dreams-for-if-dreams-die-life-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 08:16:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Langston Hughes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12030-hold-fast-to-dreams-for-if-dreams-die-life-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hold fast to dreams,
For if dreams die
Life is a broken-winged bird,
That cannot fly." -- Langston Hughes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/883013-i-want-everyone-that-has-been-abused-by-someone-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 08:51:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Dauna Cole]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/883013-i-want-everyone-that-has-been-abused-by-someone-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want everyone that has been abused by someone in their childhood to know that you can get past it. Having DID is not the end of  the world; it's the beginning of your new life. DID allows the victim of exceptional abuse the ability to “forget” the abuse and continue living. Without it, I may have gone crazy as a teen and spent my life in a as a teen and spent my life in a psychiatric hospital." -- Dauna Cole]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/885832-having-did-is-for-many-people-a-very-lonely-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 08:52:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Cameron West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/885832-having-did-is-for-many-people-a-very-lonely-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Having DID is, for many people, a very lonely thing. If this book reaches some people whose experiences resonate with mine and gives them a sense that they aren't alone, that there is hope, then I will have achieved one of my goals. 
A sad fact is that people with DID spend an average of almost seven years in the mental health system before being properly diagnosed and receiving the specific help they need. During that repeatedly misdiagnosed and incorrectly treated, simply because clinicians fail to recognize the symptoms. If this book provides practicing and future clinicians certain insight into DID, then I will have accomplished another goal. 
Clinicians, and all others whose lives are touched by DID, need to grasp the fundamentally illusive nature of memory, because memory, or the lack of it, is an integral component of this condition. Our minds are stock pots which are continuously fed ingredients from many cooks: parents, siblings, relatives, neighbors, teachers, schoolmates, strangers, acquaintances, radio, television, movies, and books. These are the fixings of learning and memory, which are stirred with a spoon that changes form over time as it is shaped by our experiences. In this incredibly amorphous neurological stew, it is impossible for all memories to be exact.
But even as we accept the complex of impressionistic nature of memory, it is equally essential to recognize that people who experience persistent and intrusive memories that disrupt their sense of well-being and ability to function, have some real basis distress, regardless of the degree of clarity or feasibility of their recollections. 
We must understand that those who experience abuse as children, and particularly those who experience incest, almost invariably suffer from a profound sense of guilt and shame that is not meliorated merely by unearthing memories or focusing on the content of traumatic material. It is not enough to just remember. Nor is achieving a sense of wholeness and peace necessarily accomplished by either placing blame on others or by forgiving those we perceive as having wronged us. It is achieved through understanding, acceptance, and reinvention of the self." -- Cameron West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/866368-why-do-i-take-a-blade-and-slash-my-arms</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 08:52:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Alice Jamieson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/866368-why-do-i-take-a-blade-and-slash-my-arms]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why do I take a blade and slash my arms? Why do I drink myself into a stupor? Why do I swallow bottles of pills and end up in A&amp;E having my stomach pumped? Am I seeking attention? Showing off? The pain of the cuts releases the mental pain of the memories, but the pain of healing lasts weeks. After every self-harming or overdosing incident I run the risk of being sectioned and returned to a psychiatric institution, a harrowing prospect I would not recommend to anyone.
So, why do I do it? I don't. If I had power over the alters, I'd stop them. I don't have that power. When they are out, they're out. I experience blank spells and lose time, consciousness, dignity. If I, Alice Jamieson, wanted attention, I would have completed my PhD and started to climb the academic career ladder. Flaunting the label 'doctor' is more attention-grabbing that lying drained of hope in hospital with steri-strips up your arms and the vile taste of liquid charcoal absorbing the chemicals in your stomach. 
In most things we do, we anticipate some reward or payment. We study for status and to get better jobs; we work for money; our children are little mirrors of our social standing; the charity donation and trip to Oxfam make us feel good. Every kindness carries the potential gift of a responding kindness: you reap what you sow. There is no advantage in my harming myself; no reason for me to invent delusional memories of incest and ritual abuse. There is nothing to be gained in an A&amp;E department." -- Alice Jamieson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4959-you-don-t-have-to-burn-books-to-destroy-a-culture</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2014 09:41:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4959-you-don-t-have-to-burn-books-to-destroy-a-culture]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't have to burn books to destroy a culture. Just get people to stop reading them." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
