<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/642585-shawn]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/642585-shawn" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2009 22:08:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192986-now-he-understood-that-a-man-never-knows-for-whom</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2009 22:08:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shawn add a quote by Alejo Carpentier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192986-now-he-understood-that-a-man-never-knows-for-whom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now he understood that a man never knows for whom he suffers and hopes.  He suffers and hopes and toils for people he will never know, and who, in turn, will suffer and hope and toil for others who will not be happy either, for man always seeks a happiness far beyond that which is meted out to him.  But man's greatness consists in the very fact of wanting to be better than he is.  In laying duties upon himself.  In the Kingdom of Heaven there is no grandeur to be won, inasmuch as there all is an established hierarchy, the unknown is revealed, existence is infinite, there is no possibility of sacrifice, all is rest and joy.  For this reason, bowed down by suffering and duties, beautiful in the midst of his misery, capable of loving in the face of afflictions and trials, man finds his greatness, his fullest measure, only in the Kingdom of this World." -- Alejo Carpentier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/694108-the-problem-with-defending-the-purity-of-the-english-language</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 16:09:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shawn add a quote by James D. Nicoll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/694108-the-problem-with-defending-the-purity-of-the-english-language]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem with defending the purity of the English language is that English is about as pure as a cribhouse whore. We don't just borrow words; on occasion, English has pursued other languages down alleyways to beat them unconscious and rifle their pockets for new vocabulary." -- James D. Nicoll]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
