<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/642975-ilana]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/642975-ilana" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 04:18:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19767-grades-are-a-problem-on-the-most-general-level-they-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 04:18:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ilana add a quote by Derrick Jensen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19767-grades-are-a-problem-on-the-most-general-level-they-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Grades are a problem. On the most general level, they're an explicit acknowledgment that what you're doing is insufficiently interesting or rewarding for you to do it on your own. Nobody ever gave you a grade for learning how to play, how to ride a bicycle, or how to kiss. One of the best ways to destroy love for any of these activities would be through the use of grades, and the coercion and judgment they represent. Grades are a cudgel to bludgeon the unwilling into doing what they don't want to do, an important instrument in inculcating children into a lifelong subservience to whatever authority happens to be thrust over them." -- Derrick Jensen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21990-those-in-power-have-made-it-so-we-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 04:18:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ilana add a quote by Derrick Jensen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21990-those-in-power-have-made-it-so-we-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those in power have made it so we have to pay simply to exist on the planet. We have to pay for a place to sleep, and we have to pay for food. If we don't, people with guns come and force us to pay. That's violent." -- Derrick Jensen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21987-surely-by-now-there-can-be-few-here-who-still</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 04:18:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ilana add a quote by Derrick Jensen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21987-surely-by-now-there-can-be-few-here-who-still]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Surely by now there can be few here who still believe the purpose of government is to protect us from the destructive activities of corporations. At last most of us must understand that the opposite is true: that the primary purpose of government is to protect those who run the economy from the outrage of injured citizens." -- Derrick Jensen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21995-within-this-culture-wealth-is-measured-by-one-s-ability-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 04:18:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ilana add a quote by Derrick Jensen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21995-within-this-culture-wealth-is-measured-by-one-s-ability-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Within this culture wealth is measured by one's ability to consume and destroy." -- Derrick Jensen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 04:19:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ilana add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what you shall do; Love the earth and sun and the animals, despise riches, give alms to every one that asks, stand up for the stupid and crazy, devote your income and labor to others, hate tyrants, argue not concerning God, have patience and indulgence toward the people, take off your hat to nothing known or unknown or to any man or number of men, go freely with powerful uneducated persons and with the young and with the mothers of families, read these leaves in the open air every season of every year of your life, re-examine all you have been told at school or church or in any book, dismiss whatever insults your own soul, and your very flesh shall be a great poem and have the richest fluency not only in its words but in the silent lines of its lips and face and between the lashes of your eyes and in every motion and joint of your body." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134969-one-of-the-fables-we-live-by-is-that-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2009 01:28:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ilana add a quote by Derrick Jensen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134969-one-of-the-fables-we-live-by-is-that-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the fables we live by is that some day the killing will stop. If only we rid ourselves of Chinese, white men will have jobs and white women will have virtue, and then we can stop killing. If only we rid ourselves of Indians, we will fulfill our Manifest Destiny, and then we can stop killing. If only we rid ourselves of Canaanites, we will live in the Promised Land, and then we can stop killing. If only we rid ourselves of Jews, we can build and maintain a Thousand Year Reich, and then we can stop killing. If only we stop the Soviet Union, we can stop the killing (remember the Peace Dividend that never materialized?). If only we can take out the worldwide terrorist network of bin Laden and others like him. If only. But the killing never stops. Always a new enemy to be hated is found." -- Derrick Jensen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329613-declare-your-jihad-on-thirteen-enemies-you-cannot-see--egoism</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 06:51:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ilana add a quote by Al-Ghazzali]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329613-declare-your-jihad-on-thirteen-enemies-you-cannot-see--egoism]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Declare your jihad on thirteen enemies you cannot see -egoism, arrogance, conceit, selfishness, greed, lust, intolerance, anger, lying, cheating, gossiping and slandering. If you can master and destroy them, then you will be read to fight the enemy you can see." -- Al-Ghazzali]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
