<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/643096-robert]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/643096-robert" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 02:56:23 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169599-i-ve-never-been-lonely-i-ve-been-in-a-room---</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 02:56:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169599-i-ve-never-been-lonely-i-ve-been-in-a-room---]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've never been lonely. I've been in a room -- I've felt suicidal. I've been depressed. I've felt awful -- awful beyond all -- but I never felt that one other person could enter that room and cure what was bothering me...or that any number of people could enter that room. In other words, loneliness is something I've never been bothered with because I've always had this terrible itch for solitude. It's being at a party, or at a stadium full of people cheering for something, that I might feel loneliness. I'll quote Ibsen, &quot;The strongest men are the most alone.&quot; I've never thought, &quot;Well, some beautiful blonde will come in here and give me a fuck-job, rub my balls, and I'll feel good.&quot; No, that won't help. You know the typical crowd, &quot;Wow, it's Friday night, what are you going to do? Just sit there?&quot; Well, yeah. Because there's nothing out there. It's stupidity. Stupid people mingling with stupid people. Let them stupidify themselves. I've never been bothered with the need to rush out into the night. I hid in bars, because I didn't want to hide in factories. That's all. Sorry for all the millions, but I've never been lonely. I like myself. I'm the best form of entertainment I have. Let's drink more wine!" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217203-nobody-likes-being-alone-that-much-i-don-t-go-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 02:56:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217203-nobody-likes-being-alone-that-much-i-don-t-go-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody likes being alone that much. I don't go out of my way to make friends, that's all. It just leads to disappointment. " -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10743-loneliness-is-the-human-condition-cultivate-it-the-way-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 02:57:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Janet Fitch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10743-loneliness-is-the-human-condition-cultivate-it-the-way-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[" Loneliness is the human condition. Cultivate it. The way it tunnels into you allows your soul room to grow. Never expect to outgrow loneliness. Never hope to find people who will understand you, someone to fill that space. An intelligent, sensitive person is the exception, the very great exception. If you expect to find people who will understand you, you will grow murderous with disappointment. The best you'll ever do is to understand yourself, know what it is that you want, and not let the cattle stand in your way." -- Janet Fitch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108135-all-great-and-precious-things-are-lonely</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 02:58:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108135-all-great-and-precious-things-are-lonely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All great and precious things are lonely." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80303-are-you-angry-punch-a-pillow-was-it-satisfying-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 03:01:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Miranda July]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80303-are-you-angry-punch-a-pillow-was-it-satisfying-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Are you angry? Punch a pillow. Was it satisfying? Not hardly. These days people are too angry for punching. What you might try is stabbing. Take an old pillow and lay it on the front lawn. Stab it with a big pointy knife. Again and again and again. Stab hard enough for the point of the knife to go into the ground. Stab until the pillow is gone and you are just stabbing the earth again and again, as if you want to kill it for continuing to spin, as if you are getting revenge for having to live on this planet day after day, alone." -- Miranda July]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169340-what-is-hell-hell-is-oneself-hell-is-alone-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 03:02:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169340-what-is-hell-hell-is-oneself-hell-is-alone-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is hell? Hell is oneself. 
Hell is alone, the other figures in it 
Merely projections. There is nothing to escape from 
And nothing to escape to. One is always alone." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261833-people-use-drugs-legal-and-illegal-because-their-lives-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 03:03:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261833-people-use-drugs-legal-and-illegal-because-their-lives-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People use drugs, legal and illegal, because their lives are intolerably painful or dull.  They hate their work and find no rest in their leisure.  They are estranged from their families and their neighbors.  It should tell us something that in healthy societies drug use is celebrative, convivial, and occasional, whereas among us it is lonely, shameful, and addictive.  We need drugs, apparently, because we have lost each other." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41127-there-are-worse-things-than-being-alone-but-it-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 00:10:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41127-there-are-worse-things-than-being-alone-but-it-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["there are worse things
than being alone
but it often takes
decades to realize this
and most often when you do
it's too late
and there's nothing worse
than too late" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21505-people-with-no-morals-often-considered-themselves-more-free-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 00:18:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21505-people-with-no-morals-often-considered-themselves-more-free-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People with no morals often considered themselves more free, but mostly they lacked the ability to feel or love." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
