<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/644629-austin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/644629-austin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 09:36:25 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1065065-every-child-is-a-one-of-a-kind-mini-masterpiece-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 09:36:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Austin add a quote by Stephen Kendrick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1065065-every-child-is-a-one-of-a-kind-mini-masterpiece-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every child is a one of a kind mini-masterpiece. No known duplicates exist. They each have distinctive fingerprints, heart rhythms, eye patterns, and blood constitution. Even identical twins can be physically alike and yet light years apart in how they are mentally wired and gifted. Our children do not just grow up different; they show up different. Though circumstances and training will greatly affect their lives, the originality that is already ingrained into each of our children reflects brilliant preplanning. Every birthmark is a trademark. Every special feature is a signature of divine design." -- Stephen Kendrick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12237-the-more-i-know-of-the-world-the-more-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 08:59:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Austin add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12237-the-more-i-know-of-the-world-the-more-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The more I know of the world, the more I am convinced that I shall never see a man whom I can really love. I require so much!" -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1139031-when-you-interact-with-someone-repeatedly-over-time-it-changes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 10:00:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Austin add a quote by Truman G. Madsen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1139031-when-you-interact-with-someone-repeatedly-over-time-it-changes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you interact with someone repeatedly over time, it changes you. That's why what you watch on TV or read or see in magazines is so critical. So watch what you watch. Be careful with whom or what you are interacting. These recurrent interactions change your cells. They change your soul. They change your countenance." -- Truman G. Madsen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1142955-interestingly-mirrors-not-only-encourage-a-deceptive-self-focus-but-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 13:08:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Austin add a quote by LaNae Valentine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1142955-interestingly-mirrors-not-only-encourage-a-deceptive-self-focus-but-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Interestingly, mirrors not only encourage a deceptive self-focus but the very images they produce are themselves deceptive. The image you see in the mirror is actually a distorted representation of what you actually look like and who you are. Your mirror image is only one-half your actual size, and may be, as warned by Isaiah, an “image that is profitable for nothing” (Isaiah 44:10). The halving effect of mirrors may well be instructive in terms of representing only half of your being—in representing metaphorically only the temporal but not the spiritual. Mirrors cannot tell us much about ourselves." -- LaNae Valentine]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
