<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/644610-matt]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/644610-matt" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 20:46:51 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22727-when-you-can-t-bear-something-but-it-goes-on-anyway</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 20:46:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Austin Grossman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22727-when-you-can-t-bear-something-but-it-goes-on-anyway]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you can't bear something but it goes on anyway, the person who survives isn't you anymore; you've changed and become someone else, a new person, the one who did bear it after all." -- Austin Grossman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40086-e-l-doctorow-said-once-said-that-writing-a-novel-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 11:09:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40086-e-l-doctorow-said-once-said-that-writing-a-novel-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["E.L. Doctorow said once said that 'Writing a novel is like driving a car at night. You can see only as far as your headlights, but you can make the whole trip that way.' You don't have to see where you're going, you don't have to see your destination or everything you will pass along the way. You just have to see two or three feet ahead of you. This is right up there with the best advice on writing, or life, I have ever heard." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40088-perfectionism-is-the-voice-of-the-oppressor-the-enemy-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 11:24:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40088-perfectionism-is-the-voice-of-the-oppressor-the-enemy-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perfectionism is the voice of the oppressor, the enemy of the people. It will keep you cramped and insane your whole life, and it is the main obstacle between you and a shitty first draft. I think perfectionism is based on the obsessive belief that if you run carefully enough, hitting each stepping-stone just right, you won't have to die. The truth is that you will die anyway and that a lot of people who aren't even looking at their feet are going to do a whole lot better than you, and have a lot more fun while they're doing it." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40090-if-you-don-t-believe-in-god-it-may-help-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 11:27:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40090-if-you-don-t-believe-in-god-it-may-help-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you don't believe in God, it may help to remember this great line of Geneen Roth's: that awareness is learning to keep yourself company. And then learn to be more compassionate company, as if you were somebody you are fond of and wish to encourage. I doubt that you would read a close friend's early efforts and, in his or her presence, roll your eyes and snicker. I doubt that you would pantomime sticking your finger down your throat. I think you might say something along the lines of, 'Good for you. We can work out some of the problems later, but for now, full steam ahead!" -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40092-the-problem-is-acceptance-which-is-something-we-re-taught-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 11:36:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40092-the-problem-is-acceptance-which-is-something-we-re-taught-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem is acceptance, which is something we're taught not to do. We're taught to improve uncomfortable situations, to change things, alleviate unpleasant feelings. But if you accept the reality that you have been given- that you are not in a productive creative period- you free yourself to begin filling up again." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40093-you-are-lucky-to-be-one-of-those-people-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 11:42:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40093-you-are-lucky-to-be-one-of-those-people-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are lucky to be one of those people who wishes to build sand castles with words, who is willing to create a place where your imagination can wander.  We build this place with the sand of memories; these castles are our memories and inventiveness made tangible.  So part of us believes that when the tide starts coming in, we won't really have lost anything, because actually only a symbol of it was there in the sand.  Another part of us thinks we'll figure out a way to divert the ocean.  This is what separates artists from ordinary people: the belief, deep in our hearts, that if we build our castles well enough, somehow the ocean won't wash them away.  I think this is a wonderful kind of person to be." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40094-the-society-to-which-we-belong-seems-to-be-dying</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 11:46:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40094-the-society-to-which-we-belong-seems-to-be-dying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The society to which we belong seems to be dying or is already dead.  I don't mean to sound dramatic, but clearly the dark side is rising.  Things could not have been more odd and frightening in the Middle Ages.  But the tradition of artists will continue no matter what form the society takes.  And this is another reason to write: people need us, to mirror for them and for each other without distortion-not to look around and say, 'Look at yourselves, you idiots!,' but to say, 'This is who we are." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40095-writing-and-reading-decrease-our-sense-of-isolation-they-deepen</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 11:51:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40095-writing-and-reading-decrease-our-sense-of-isolation-they-deepen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing and reading decrease our sense of isolation.  They deepen and widen and expand our sense of life: they feed the soul.  When writers make us shake our heads with the exactness of their prose and their truths, and even make us laugh about ourselves or life, our buoyancy is restored.  We are given a shot at dancing with, or at least clapping along with, the absurdity of life, instead of being squashed by it over and over again.  It's like singing on a boat during a terrible storm at sea.  You can't stop the raging storm, but singing can change the hearts and spirits of the people who are together on that ship." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72202-success-after-all-loves-a-witness-but-failure-can-t-exist</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 10:22:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Junot Díaz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72202-success-after-all-loves-a-witness-but-failure-can-t-exist]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Success, after all, loves a witness, but failure can't exist without one." -- Junot Díaz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72205-she-would-be-a-new-person-she-vowed-they-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 10:25:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Junot Díaz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72205-she-would-be-a-new-person-she-vowed-they-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She would be a new person, she vowed.  They said no matter how far a mule travels it can never come back a horse, but she would show them all." -- Junot Díaz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72206-called-her-a-whore-and-attacked-her-walls-tearing-down</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 10:28:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Junot Díaz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72206-called-her-a-whore-and-attacked-her-walls-tearing-down]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Called her a whore and attacked her walls, tearing down her posters and throwing her books everywhere.  I found out because some whitegirl ran up and said, Excuse me, but your stupid roommate is going insane, and I had to bolt upstairs and put him in a headlock." -- Junot Díaz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72208-instead-of-finding-himself-in-nerd-heaven-where-every-nerd-gets</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 10:30:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Junot Diaz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72208-instead-of-finding-himself-in-nerd-heaven-where-every-nerd-gets]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Instead of finding himself in nerd heaven—where every nerd gets fifty-eight virgins to role-play with—he woke up in Robert Wood Johnson with two broken legs and a separated shoulder, feeling like, well, he'd jumped off the New Brunswick train bridge." -- Junot Diaz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72209-dude-you-don-t-want-to-be-dead-take-it-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 10:32:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Junot Díaz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72209-dude-you-don-t-want-to-be-dead-take-it-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dude, you don't want to be dead.  Take it from me.  No-pussy is bad.  But dead is like no-pussy times ten." -- Junot Díaz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72211-what-a-surprise-we-all-know-how-tolerant-the-tolerant</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 10:34:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Junot Díaz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72211-what-a-surprise-we-all-know-how-tolerant-the-tolerant]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...what a surprise (we all know how tolerant the tolerant are)-..." -- Junot Díaz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72212-but-if-these-years-have-taught-me-anything-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 10:36:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Junot Díaz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72212-but-if-these-years-have-taught-me-anything-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But if these years have taught me anything it is this: you can never run away.  Not ever.  The only way out is in." -- Junot Díaz]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
