<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/644848-alexander]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/644848-alexander" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 01:38:10 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2144-a-dozen-or-more-boats-on-the-lake-swung-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 01:38:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2144-a-dozen-or-more-boats-on-the-lake-swung-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A dozen or more boats on the lake swung their rosy and moon–like lanterns low on the water, that reflected as from a fire. In the distance, the steamer twanged and thrummed and washed with her faintly–splashing paddles, trailing her strings of coloured lights, and occasionally lighting up the whole scene luridly with an effusion of fireworks, Roman candles and sheafs of stars and other simple effects, illuminating the surface of the water, and showing the boats creeping round, low down. Then the lovely darkness fell again, the lanterns and the little threaded lights glimmered softly, there was a muffled knocking of oars and a waving of music.

Gudrun paddled almost imperceptibly. Gerald could see, not far ahead, the rich blue and the rose globes of Ursula’s lanterns swaying softly cheek to cheek as Birkin rowed, and iridescent, evanescent gleams chasing in the wake. He was aware, too, of his own delicately coloured lights casting their softness behind him." -- D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198-i-am-so-clever-that-sometimes-i-don-t-understand-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 01:38:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198-i-am-so-clever-that-sometimes-i-don-t-understand-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am so clever that sometimes I don't understand a single word of what I am saying." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4612-where-there-is-sorrow-there-is-holy-ground</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 01:39:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4612-where-there-is-sorrow-there-is-holy-ground]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where there is sorrow, there is holy ground." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1508-a-thing-is-not-necessarily-true-because-a-man-dies</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 01:40:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1508-a-thing-is-not-necessarily-true-because-a-man-dies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A thing is not necessarily true because a man dies for it." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2354-the-better-you-look-the-more-you-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 01:43:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2354-the-better-you-look-the-more-you-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The better you look, the more you see." -- Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2355-people-are-afraid-to-merge-on-freeways-in-los-angeles</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 02:06:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2355-people-are-afraid-to-merge-on-freeways-in-los-angeles]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People are afraid to merge on freeways in Los Angeles. This is the first thing I hear when I come back to the city. Blair picks me up from LAX and mutters this under her breath as she drives up the onramp. She says, &quot;People are afraid to merge on freeways in Los Angeles.&quot; Though that sentence shouldn't bother me, it stays in my mind for an uncomfortably long time. Nothing else seems to matter. Not the fact that I'm eighteen and it's December and the ride on the plane had been rough and the couple from Santa Barbara, who were sitting across from me in first class, had gotten pretty drunk. Not the mud that had splattered on the legs of my jeans, which felt kind of cold and loose, earlier that day at an airport in  New Hampshire. Not the stain on the arm of the wrinkled, damp shirt I wear, a shirt which looked fresh and clean this morning. Not the tear on the neck of my gray argyle vest, which seems vaguely more eastern than before, especially next to Blair's clean tight jeans and her pale-blue shirt. All of this seems irrelevant next to that one sentence. It seems easier to hear that people are afraid to merge than &quot;I'm pretty sure Muriel is anorexic&quot; or the singer on the radio crying out about magnetic waves. Nothing else seems to matter to me but those ten words. Not the warm winds, which seem to propel the car down the empty asphalt freeway, or the faded smell of marijuana which still faintly permeates Blaire's car. All it comes down to is the fact that I'm a boy coming home for a month and meeting someone whom I haven't seen for four months and people are afraid to merge." -- Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2356-you-have-a-good-heart-and-you-think-the-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 02:11:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Tony Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2356-you-have-a-good-heart-and-you-think-the-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have a good heart and you think the good thing is to be guilty and kind but it's not always kind to be gentle and soft, there's a genuine violence softness and kindness visit on people. Sometimes self-interested is the most generous thing you can be. " -- Tony Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2357-i-just-wondered-what-a-thing-it-would-be-if-overnight</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 02:15:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Tony Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2357-i-just-wondered-what-a-thing-it-would-be-if-overnight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I just wondered what a thing it would be...if overnight everything you owe anything to, justice, or love, had really gone away. Free.

It would be...heartless terror. Yes. Terrible, and...

Very great. To shed your skin, every old skin, one by one and then walk away, unemcumbered, into the morning." -- Tony Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2358-i-had-a-book-of-bible-stories-when-i-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 02:22:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Tony Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2358-i-had-a-book-of-bible-stories-when-i-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had a book of Bible stories when I was a kid. There was a picture I'd look at twenty times every day: Jacob wrestles with the angel. I don't really remember the story, or why the wrestling --just the picture. Jacob is young and very strong. The angel is...a beautiful man, with golden hair and wings, of course. I still dream about it. Many nights. I'm...It's me. In that struggle. Fierce, and unfair. The angel is not human, and it holds nothing back, so how could anyone human win, what kind of a fight is that? It's not just. Losing means your soul thrown down in the dust, your heart torn out from God's. But you can't not lose." -- Tony Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2359-harper-in-your-experience-of-the-world-how-do-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 02:28:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Tony Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2359-harper-in-your-experience-of-the-world-how-do-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Harper: In your experience of the world. How do people change?

Mormon Mother: Well it has something to do with God so it's not very nice.

God splits the skin with a jagged thumbnail from throat to belly and then plunges a huge filthy hand in, he grabs hold of your bloody tubes and they slip to evade his grasp but he squeezes hard, he insists, he pulls and pulls till all your innards are yanked out and the pain! We can't even talk about that. And then he stuffs them back, dirty, tangled and torn. It's up to you to do the stitching. 

Harper: And then up you get. And walk around.

Mormon Mother: Just mangled guts pretending.

Harper: That's how people change." -- Tony Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2361-a-the-soul-wanders-in-the-dark-until-it-finds</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 02:55:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Mary Zimmerman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2361-a-the-soul-wanders-in-the-dark-until-it-finds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A: The soul wanders in the dark, until it finds love. And so, wherever our love goes, there we find our soul.
Q: It always happens?
A: If we're lucky. And if we let ourselves be blind. 
Q: Instead of watching out?
A: Instead of always watching out." -- Mary Zimmerman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2362-let-me-die-the-moment-my-love-dies-let-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 02:59:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Mary Zimmerman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2362-let-me-die-the-moment-my-love-dies-let-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me die the moment my love dies. 
Let me not outlive my own capacity to love. 
Let me die still loving, and so, never die." -- Mary Zimmerman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33764-i-knew-my-mother-was-right-but-that-didn-t-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 16:13:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Peter Cameron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33764-i-knew-my-mother-was-right-but-that-didn-t-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I knew my mother was right, but that didn't change the way I felt about things. People always think that if they can prove they're right, you'll change your mind." -- Peter Cameron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33766-what-if-she-was-meant-to-be-or-could-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 16:14:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Peter Cameron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33766-what-if-she-was-meant-to-be-or-could-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What if she was meant to be, or could have been, someone important in my life? I think that's what scares me: the randomness of everything. That the people who could be important to you might just pass you by. Or you pass them by. How do you know...I felt that by walking away I was abandoning [them], that I spent my entire life, day after day, abandoning people." -- Peter Cameron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33767-dr-adler-had-instructed-me-to-always-say-whatever-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 16:15:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Peter Cameron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33767-dr-adler-had-instructed-me-to-always-say-whatever-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dr. Adler had instructed me to always say whatever I was thinking, but this was difficult for me, for the act of thinking and the act of articulating those thoughts were not synchronous to me, or even necessarily consecutive. I knew that I thought and spoke in the same language and that theoretically there should be no reason why I could not express my thoughts as they occurred or soon thereafter, but the language in which I thought and the language in which I spoke, though both English, often seemed divided by a gap that could not be simultaneously, or even retrospectively, bridged." -- Peter Cameron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2711-no-matter-who-you-are-no-matter-where-you-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 04:44:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2711-no-matter-who-you-are-no-matter-where-you-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No matter who you are, no matter where you live, and no matter how many people are chasing you, what you don't read is often as important as what you do read." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36217-there-s-the-ambiguity-of-human-relationships-for-instance-a-relationship</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 05:30:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Elliot Perlman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36217-there-s-the-ambiguity-of-human-relationships-for-instance-a-relationship]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's the ambiguity of human relationships, for instance. A relationship between two people, just like a sequence of words, is ambiguous if it is open to different interpretations. And if two people do have differing views about their relationship - I don't just mean about its state, I mean about its very nature - then that difference can affect the entire course of their lives." -- Elliot Perlman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144872-you-meet-a-new-person-you-go-with-him-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 23:56:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Samuel R. Delany]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144872-you-meet-a-new-person-you-go-with-him-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You meet a new person, you go with him and suddenly you get a whole new city...you go down new streets, you see houses you never saw before, pass places you didn't even know were there. Everything changes." -- Samuel R. Delany]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7407-a-great-numb-feeling-washes-over-me-as-i-let</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 23:06:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7407-a-great-numb-feeling-washes-over-me-as-i-let]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A great numb feeling washes over me as I let go of the past and look forward to the future. Pretend to be a vampire. I don't really need to pretend, because it's who I am, an emotional vampire. I've just come to expect it. Vampires are real. That I was born this way. That I feed off of other people's real emotions. Search for this night's prey. Who will it be?" -- Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72870-and-it-struck-me-then-that-i-liked-sean-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 23:07:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72870-and-it-struck-me-then-that-i-liked-sean-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And it struck me then, that I liked Sean because he looked, well, slutty. A boy who had been around. A boy who couldn't remember if he was Catholic or not." -- Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102476-it-s-not-art-for-art-s-sake-it-s-art-for-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 23:12:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102476-it-s-not-art-for-art-s-sake-it-s-art-for-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not art for art's sake, it's art for my sake. " -- D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2844-this-is-what-i-believe-that-i-am-i-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 23:13:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by DH Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2844-this-is-what-i-believe-that-i-am-i-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what I believe: That I am I. That my soul is a dark forest. That my known self will never be more than a little clearing in the forest. That gods, strange gods, come forth from the forest into the clearing of my known self, and then go back. That I must have the courage to let them come and go. That I will never let mankind put anything over me, but that I will try always to recognize and submit to the gods in me and the gods in other men and women. There is my creed." -- DH Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121894-but-better-die-than-live-mechanically-a-life-that-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 23:13:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121894-but-better-die-than-live-mechanically-a-life-that-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But better die than live mechanically a life that is a repetition of repetitions." -- D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
