<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/645261-misterdumb]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/645261-misterdumb" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 09:19:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231682-it-s-morning-time-to-get-up-so-get-up-arturo</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 09:19:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by John Fante]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231682-it-s-morning-time-to-get-up-so-get-up-arturo]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["IT'S MORNING, TIME to get up, so get up, Arturo, and look for a job. Get out there and look for what you'll never find. You're a thief and you're a crab-killer and a lover of women in clothes closets. You'll never find a job!
Every morning I got up feeling like that. Now I've got to find a job, damn it to hell. I ate breakfast, put a book under my arm, pencils in my pocket, and started out. Down the stairs I went, down the street, sometimes hot and sometimes cold, sometimes foggy and sometimes clear. It never mattered, with a book under my arm, looking for a job.
What job, Arturo? Ho ho! A job for you? Think of what you are, my boy! A crab-killer. A thief. You look at naked women in clothes closets. And you expect to get a job! How funny! But there he goes, the idiot, with a big book. Where the devil are you going, Arturo? Why do you go up this street and not that? Why go east - why not go west? Answer me, you thief! Who'll give you a job, you swine - who? But there's a park across town, Arturo. It's called Banning Park. There are a lot of beautiful eucalyptus trees in it, and green lawns. What a place to read! Go there, Arturo. Read Nietzsche. Read Schopenhauer. Get into the company of the mighty. A job? fooey! Go sit under a eucalyptus tree reading a book looking for a job. " -- John Fante]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231687-dear-woman-who-gave-me-life-the-callous-vexations-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 09:20:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by John Fante]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231687-dear-woman-who-gave-me-life-the-callous-vexations-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dear Woman Who Gave Me Life:

The callous vexations and perturbations of this night have subsequently resolved 
themselves to a state which precipitates me, Arturo Bandini, into a 
brobdingnagian and gargantuan decision. I inform you of this in no uncertain 
terms. Ergo, I now leave you and your ever charming daughter (my beloved sister 
Mona) and seek the fabulous usufructs of my incipient career in profound 
solitude. Which is to say, tonight I depart for the metropolis to the east — our 
own Los Angeles, the city of angels. I entrust you to the benign generosity of your brother, Frank Scarpi, who is, as the phrase has it, a good family man 
(sic!). I am penniless but I urge you in no uncertain terms to cease your 
cerebral anxiety about my destiny, for truly it lies in the palm of the immortal gods. I have made the lamentable discovery over a period of years that living 
with you and Mona is deleterious to the high and magnanimous purpose of Art, and I repeat to you in no uncertain terms that I am an artist, a creator beyond question. And, per se, the fumbling fulminations of cerebration and intellect find little fruition in the debauched, distorted hegemony that we poor mortals, for lack of a better and more concise terminology, call home. In no uncertain 
terms I give you my love and blessing, and I swear to my sincerity, when I say 
in no uncertain terms that I not only forgive you for what has ruefully 
transpired this night, but for all other nights. Ergo, I assume in no uncertain terms that you will reciprocate in kindred fashion. May I say in conclusion that I have much to thank you for, O woman who breathed the breath of life into my 
brain of destiny? Aye, it is, it is.

Signed.

Arturo Gabriel Bandini.

Suitcase in hand, I walked down to the depot. There was a ten-minute wait for 
the midnight train for Los Angeles. I sat down and began to think about the new novel." -- John Fante]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200584-we-never-change-neither-our-socks-nor-our-masters-nor</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 01:01:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200584-we-never-change-neither-our-socks-nor-our-masters-nor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We never change. Neither our socks nor our masters nor our opinions, or we're so slow about it that it's no use. We were born loyal and that's what killed us! Soldiers free of charge, heroes for everyone else, talking monkeys, tortured words, we are the minions of King Misery...It's not a life." -- Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/337255-i-will-exile-my-thoughts-if-they-think-of-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 01:04:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by Knut Hamsun]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/337255-i-will-exile-my-thoughts-if-they-think-of-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...I will exile my thoughts if they think of you again, and I will rip my lips out if they say your name once more. Now if you do exist, I will tell you my final word in life or in death, I tell you goodbye." -- Knut Hamsun]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269442-the-heavy-red-roses-smoldering-in-the-foggy-morning-blood-colored</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 01:09:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by Knut Hamsun]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269442-the-heavy-red-roses-smoldering-in-the-foggy-morning-blood-colored]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The heavy red roses smoldering in the foggy morning, blood-colored and uninhibited, made me greedy, and tempted me powerfully to steal one--I asked the prices merely so I could come as near them as possible." -- Knut Hamsun]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/652266-our-lives-are-not-our-own-we-are-bound-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 17:21:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/652266-our-lives-are-not-our-own-we-are-bound-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our lives are not our own. We are bound to others, past and present, and by each crime and every kindness, we birth our future." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385370-strip-back-the-beliefs-pasted-on-by-governesses-schools-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 01:26:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385370-strip-back-the-beliefs-pasted-on-by-governesses-schools-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Strip back the beliefs pasted on by governesses, schools, and states, you find indelible truths at one's core.  Rome'll decline and fall again, Cortés'll lay Tenochtitlán to waste again, and later, Ewing will sail again, Adrian'll be blown to pieces again, you and I'll sleep under the Corsican stars again, I'll come to Bruges again, fall in and out of love with Eva again, you'll read this letter again, the sun'll grow cold again.  Nietzsche's gramophone record.  When it ends, the Old One plays it again, for an eternity of eternities." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385334-how-vulgar-this-hankering-after-immortality-how-vain-how-false</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 01:26:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385334-how-vulgar-this-hankering-after-immortality-how-vain-how-false]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How vulgar, this hankering after immortality, how vain, how false.  Composers are merely scribblers of cave paintings.  One writes music because winter is eternal and because, if one didn't, the wolves and blizzards would be at one's throat all the sooner." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170254-there-is-something-sad-about-people-going-to-bed-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 01:44:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170254-there-is-something-sad-about-people-going-to-bed-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is something sad about people going to bed.  You can see they don’t give a damn whether they’re getting what they want out of life or not, you can see they don’t ever try to understand what we’re here for. They just don’t care. Americans or not, they sleep no matter what, they’re bloated mollusks, no sensibility, no trouble with their conscience.
	I’d seen too many troubling things to be easy in my mind. I knew too much and not enough. I’d better go out, I said to myself, I’d better go out again. Maybe I’ll meet Robinson.  Naturally that was an idiotic idea, but I dreamed it up as an excuse for going out again, because no matter how I tossed and turned on my narrow bed, I couldn’t snatch the tiniest scrap of sleep.  Even masturbation, at times like that, provides neither comfort nor entertainment.  Then you're really in despair." -- Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170224-a-god-who-counts-minutes-and-pennies-a-desperate-sensual</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 01:44:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170224-a-god-who-counts-minutes-and-pennies-a-desperate-sensual]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A God who counts minutes and pennies, a desperate sensual God, who grunts like a pig.  A pig with golden wings, who falls and falls, always belly side up, ready for caresses, that’s him, our master.  Come, kiss me." -- Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118970-there-is-a-loneliness-in-this-world-so-great-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 01:16:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118970-there-is-a-loneliness-in-this-world-so-great-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["there is a loneliness in this world so great
that you can see it in the slow movement of
the hands of a clock.

people so tired
mutilated
either by love or no love.

people just are not good to each other
one on one.

the rich are not good to the rich
the poor are not good to the poor.

we are afraid.

our educational system tells us
that we can all be
big-ass winners.

it hasn't told us
about the gutters
or the suicides.

or the terror of one person
aching in one place
alone

untouched
unspoken to

watering a plant." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141441-man-is-not-the-sum-of-what-he-has-already</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2013 01:04:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by Jean-Paul Sartre]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141441-man-is-not-the-sum-of-what-he-has-already]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man is not the sum of what he has already, but rather the sum of what he does not yet have, of what he could have.
" -- Jean-Paul Sartre]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3239-to-hell-with-reality-i-want-to-die-in-music</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 21:08:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by Louis-Ferdinand Celine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3239-to-hell-with-reality-i-want-to-die-in-music]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To hell with reality! I want to die in music, not in reason or in prose. People don't deserve the restraint we show by not going into delirium in front of them. To hell with them!" -- Louis-Ferdinand Celine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236225-so-many-vaginas-stomachs-cocks-snouts-and-flies-you-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 01:46:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236225-so-many-vaginas-stomachs-cocks-snouts-and-flies-you-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["so many vaginas, stomachs, cocks, snouts, and flies you don't know what to do with them ... shovelsfull! ... but hearts? ... very rare! in the last five hundred million years too many cocks and gastric tubes to count ... but hearts? ... on your fingers! ..." -- Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1215786-crime-begins-with-god-it-will-end-with-man-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 17:22:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1215786-crime-begins-with-god-it-will-end-with-man-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Crime begins with God. It will end with man, when he finds God again. Crime is everywhere, in all the fibres and roots of our being. Every minute of the day adds fresh crimes to the calendar, both those which are detected and punished, and those which are not. The criminal hunts down the criminal. The judge condemns the judger. The innocent torture the innocent. Everywhere, in every family, every tribe, every great community, crimes, crimes, crimes. War is clean by comparison. The hangman is a gentle dove by comparison. Attila, Tamerlane, Genghis Khan reckless automatons by comparison. Your father, your darling mother, your sweet sister: do you know the foul crimes they harbor in their breasts? Can you hold the mirror to iniquity when it is close at hand? Have you looked into the labyrinth of your own despicable heart? Have you sometimes envied the thug for his forthrightness? The study of crime begins with the knowledge of oneself. All that you despise, all that you loathe, all that you reject, all that you condemn and seek to convert by punishment springs from you. The source of it is God whom you place outside, above and beyond. Crime is identification, first with God, then with your own image." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1241474-by-capitulating-to-life-this-world-has-betrayed-nothingness</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 00:42:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by Emil Cioran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1241474-by-capitulating-to-life-this-world-has-betrayed-nothingness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By capitulating to life, this world has betrayed nothingness. . . . I resign from movement, and from my dreams. Absence! You shall be my sole glory. . . . Let “desire” be forever stricken from the dictionary, and from the soul! I retreat before the dizzying farce of tomorrows. And if I still cling to a few hopes, I have lost forever the faculty of hoping" -- Emil Cioran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1245326-but-where-is-the-antidote-for-lucid-despair-perfectly-articulated</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 02:41:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by Emil Cioran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1245326-but-where-is-the-antidote-for-lucid-despair-perfectly-articulated]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But where is the antidote for lucid despair, perfectly articulated, proud, and sure? All of us are miserable, but how many know it? The consciousness of misery is too serious a disease to figure in an arithmetic of agonies or in the catalogues of the Incurable. It belittles the prestige of hell, and converts the slaughterhouses of time into idyls. What sin have you committed to be born, what crime to exist? Your suffering like your fate is without motive. To suffer, truly to suffer, is to accept the invasion of ills without the excuse of causality, as a favor of demented nature, as a negative miracle. . ." -- Emil Cioran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101324-one-day-a-man-invited-him-into-a-richly-furnished</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 02:42:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by Diogenes Laertius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101324-one-day-a-man-invited-him-into-a-richly-furnished]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One day a man invited him into a richly furnished house, saying 'be careful not to spit on the floor.' Diogenes, who needed to spit, spat in his face, exclaiming that it was the only dirty place he could find where spitting was permitted." -- Diogenes Laertius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1245327-the-notion-of-nothingness-is-not-characteristic-of-laboring-humanity</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 02:45:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by Emil Cioran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1245327-the-notion-of-nothingness-is-not-characteristic-of-laboring-humanity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The notion of nothingness is not characteristic of laboring humanity: those who toil have neither time nor inclination to weigh their dust; they resign themselves to the difficulties or the doltishness of fate; they hope: hope is a slave’s virtue." -- Emil Cioran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1245328-lord-give-me-the-capacity-of-never-praying-spare-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 02:47:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by Emil Cioran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1245328-lord-give-me-the-capacity-of-never-praying-spare-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lord, give me the capacity of never praying, spare me the insanity of all worship, let this temptation of love pass from me which would deliver me forever unto You. Let the void spread between my heart and heaven! I have no desire to people my deserts by Your presence, to tyrannize my nights by Your light, to dissolve my Siberias beneath Your sun." -- Emil Cioran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/837438-do-not-forget-some-give-little-and-it-is-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2014 02:29:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misterdumb add a quote by Knut Hamsun]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/837438-do-not-forget-some-give-little-and-it-is-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not forget, some give little, and it is much for them, others give all, and it costs them no effort; who then has given most?" -- Knut Hamsun]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
