<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/645998-edward]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/645998-edward" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2007 19:26:15 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2249-there-are-a-thousand-spears-in-my-back-said-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2007 19:26:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Edith Nesbit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2249-there-are-a-thousand-spears-in-my-back-said-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are a thousand spears in my back,' said a little sharp voice, 'and they are all devoted to the Princess and to her alone." -- Edith Nesbit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2252-alpha-60-your-name-is-written-ivan-johnson-but-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2007 19:30:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Jean-Luc Godard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2252-alpha-60-your-name-is-written-ivan-johnson-but-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["ALPHA-60:  Your name is written &quot;Ivan Johnson,&quot; but it is pronounced &quot;Lemmy Caution,&quot; Secret Agent Zero Zero Three of the Outlands. You are a threat to the security of Alphaville.

CAUTION:  I refuse to become what you call &quot;normal.&quot;

...

ALPHA-60:  You cannot escape. The door is locked.

CAUTION:  Try to stop me, pal." -- Jean-Luc Godard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2483-you-may-be-sure-that-we-are-as-well-aware</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 13:20:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Thucydides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2483-you-may-be-sure-that-we-are-as-well-aware]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may be sure that we are as well aware as you of the difficulty of contending against your power and fortune, unless the terms be equal. But we trust that the gods may grant us fortune as good as yours, since we are just men fighting against unjust, and that what we want in power will be made up by the alliance of the Lacedaemonians, who are bound, if only for very shame, to come to the aid of their kindred. Our confidence, therefore, after all is not so utterly irrational.
" -- Thucydides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2638-both-destiny-s-kisses-and-its-dope-slaps-illustrate-an-individual-person-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2007 10:06:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2638-both-destiny-s-kisses-and-its-dope-slaps-illustrate-an-individual-person-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Both destiny's kisses and its dope-slaps illustrate an individual person's basic personal powerlessness over the really meaningful events in his life: i.e. almost nothing important that ever happens to you happens because you engineer it.  Destiny has no beeper; destiny always leans trenchcoated out of an alley with some sort of Psst that you usually can't even hear because you're in such a rush to or from something important you've tried to engineer." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3386-there-are-actual-monsters-in-the-world-but-when-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 14:47:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Simon Rich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3386-there-are-actual-monsters-in-the-world-but-when-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are actual monsters in the world, but when my kids ask I pretend like there aren’t." -- Simon Rich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3526-there-are-no-choices-without-personal-freedom-buckeroo-it-s-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2007 07:03:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3526-there-are-no-choices-without-personal-freedom-buckeroo-it-s-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are no choices without personal freedom, Buckeroo. It's not us who are dead inside. These things you find so weak and contemptible in us---these are just the hazards of being free." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4804-and-wherever-men-are-fighting-against-barbarism-tyranny-and-massacre</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2007 10:18:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4804-and-wherever-men-are-fighting-against-barbarism-tyranny-and-massacre]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And wherever men are fighting against barbarism, tyranny, and massacre, for freedom, law, and honour, let them remember that the fame of their deeds, even though they themselves be exterminated, may perhaps be celebrated as long as the world rolls round." -- Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4807-soyons-fermes-purs-et-fid-les-au-bout-de-nos</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2007 10:36:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Charles de Gaulle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4807-soyons-fermes-purs-et-fid-les-au-bout-de-nos]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Soyons fermes, purs et fidèles ; au bout de nos peines, il y a la plus grande gloire du monde, celle des hommes qui n'ont pas cédé. [Let us be firm, pure and faithful; at the end of our sorrow, there is the greatest glory of the world, that of the men who did not give in.]" -- Charles de Gaulle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4809-but-we-must-be-completely-clear-if-nationalism-is-truly-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2007 10:38:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Freidrich Reck-Malleczewen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4809-but-we-must-be-completely-clear-if-nationalism-is-truly-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But we must be completely clear...if nationalism is truly the hallmark of a people in the prime of its youth and energies, how does it happen that under its aegis morality decays, ancient customs die out---that men are uprooted, the steadfast derided, the thoughtful branded, the rivers poisoned, and the forests destroyed? Why, if this is a high watermark of our national life, has our speech been vulgarized in this unprecedented way?" -- Freidrich Reck-Malleczewen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5031-i-am-writing-this-because-on-that-night-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 12:06:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by John Lukacs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5031-i-am-writing-this-because-on-that-night-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am writing this because on that night of the tenth of May in the 1,940th year of Our Lord, Churchill stood for more than England. Millions of people, especially across Europe, recognized him now as the champion of their hopes. (In faraway Bengal India there was at least one man, that admirably independent writer and thinker, Nirad Chaudhuri, who fastened Churchill's picture on the wall of his room the next day.) Churchill was _the_ opponent of Hitler, the incarnation of the reaction to Hitler, the incarnation of the resistance of an old world, of old freedoms, of old standards against a man incarnating a force that was frighteningly efficient, brutal, and new." -- John Lukacs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6068-this-pain-this-dying-this-is-just-normal-this-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 19:56:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Miranda July]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6068-this-pain-this-dying-this-is-just-normal-this-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This pain, this dying, this is just normal. This is how life is. In fact, I realize, there never was an earthquake. Life is just this way, broken, and I am crazy for dreaming of something else." -- Miranda July]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6073-consider-this-every-time-a-last-thought-is-repeated-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 20:06:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by J. Sweeney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6073-consider-this-every-time-a-last-thought-is-repeated-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Consider this: every time a last thought is repeated, a story comes to an end. People need clarity, and that is what stories are for. Our own lives are complicated---nothing is ever resolved and nothing is ever over. But stories end, so they can be pure. The joy is pure and the suffering is pure and even the questions that can't be answered are precise and clear.

A lost dog has finally found his family, and they're shouting his name and they hold their arms out and he jumps into them...

It is the end of the argument, and they are more in love than ever...

The criminal has been caught at last, and punishment is waiting...

Here is the baby, born finally, healthy, and the mother is sweaty but she's okay too...

These are ends, but they are also beginnings, and in life they will end and begin again and again. Every time something happens a world of possible action opens up, and possible meanings. But in fiction, every story is an end, because we are only reading the end. Its last notes are sonorous and beautiful and final. They are beautiful. They are final.

Say a marriage is tragic. Say that the people close to the couple can find no words for the things they have done. Say at every point where the body of the world touches their bodies, people have bad dreams and lose their faith and turn their eyes away from things they once trusted. Even if this is true, it doesn't matter: it isn't the end." -- J. Sweeney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9596-it-has-been-said-that-in-every-being-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 19:15:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Philip Davison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9596-it-has-been-said-that-in-every-being-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It has been said that in every being there is another being and this being is the true self. Not a double. Not an opposite. Simply, the one each of us strives to be all our lives. Some who have suffered cruelty, violence, or abuse as children somehow short-circuit this search with their cries. They are kidnapped by the other self and abandoned in a strangely familiar place where they are victim to the same cruelty, violence, or abuse, but can remember little or none of it until such time as they are strong enough to cope." -- Philip Davison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12721-surely-for-as-long-as-there-have-been-nights-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 11:03:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12721-surely-for-as-long-as-there-have-been-nights-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Surely for as long as there have been nights as bad as this one---something to raise the possibility of another night that could actually, with love and cockcrows, light the path home, banish the Adversary, destroy the boundaries between our lands our bodies, our stories, all false, about who we are: for the one night, leaving only the clear way home and the memory of the infant you saw, almost too frail, there's too much shit in these streets, camels andother beasts stir heavily outside, each hoof a chance to wipe him out, make him only another Messiah, and sure somebody's around already taking bets on that one, while here in this town the Jewish collaborators are selling useful gossip to Imperial Intelligence, and the local hookers are keeping the foreskinned invaders happy, charging whatever the traffic will bear, just like the innkeepers who're naturally delighted with this registration thing, and up in the capital they're wondering should they, maybe, give everybody a number; yeah, something to help SPQR record-keeping...and Herod, or Hitler, fellas...what kind of a world is it...for a baby to come in tippin' those toledos at 7 pounds 8 ounces thinkin' he's gonna redeem it, why, he ought have his head examined...
 
&quot;But on the way home tonight, you wish you'd picked him up, held him a bit. Just held him, very close to your heart, his cheek by the hollow of your shoulder, full of sleep. As it it were you who could, somehow, save him. For the moment not caring who you're supposed to be registered as. For the moment, anyway, no longer who the Caesars say you are." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16422-turning-and-turning-in-the-widening-gyre-the-falcon-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 12:17:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by William Butler Yeats]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16422-turning-and-turning-in-the-widening-gyre-the-falcon-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Turning and turning in the widening gyre
The falcon cannot hear the falconer;
Things fall apart; the centre cannot hold;
Mere anarchy is loosed upon the world,
The blood-dimmed tide is loosed, and everywhere
The ceremony of innocence is drowned;
The best lack all conviction, while the worst
Are full of passionate intensity." -- William Butler Yeats]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12642-you-have-not-wasted-your-time-you-have-helped-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 12:35:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12642-you-have-not-wasted-your-time-you-have-helped-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have not wasted your time; you have helped to save the world. We are not buffoons, but very desperate men at war with a vast conspiracy." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16864-i-seem-to-remember-only-centuries-of-heroic-war-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 09:31:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by G. K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16864-i-seem-to-remember-only-centuries-of-heroic-war-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I seem to remember only centuries of heroic war, in which you were always heroes--epic on epic, Iliad on Iliad, and you always brothers in arms. Whether it was but recently (for time is nothing), or at the beginning of the world, I sent you out to war. I sat in the darkness, where there is not any created thing, and to you I was only a voice commanding valour and an unnatural virtue. You heard the voice in the dark, and you never heard it again. The sun in heaven denied it, the earth and sky denied it, all human wisdom denied it. And when I met you in the daylight I denied it myself...But you were men. You did not forget your secret honour, though the whole cosmos turned an engine of torture to tear it out of you." -- G. K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34167-pardon-if-all-the-cleanness-and-the-beauty-brave-rhythym</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 19:08:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Norman Hampson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34167-pardon-if-all-the-cleanness-and-the-beauty-brave-rhythym]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pardon if all the cleanness and the beauty
Brave rhythym and the immemorial sea
Ensare us sometimes with their siren song,
Forgetful of our murderous intentions.
Through our uneasy peacetime carnival
Cold sweat of death holds us like a dew;
Even this grey machinery of murder
Holds beauty and the promise of a future." -- Norman Hampson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35097-lavinia-oh-edward-the-point-is-that-since-i-ve-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2008 21:00:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by T. S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35097-lavinia-oh-edward-the-point-is-that-since-i-ve-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["LAVINIA: Oh Edward! 
The point is, that since I've been away
I see that I've taken you much too seriously.
And now I can see how absurd you are.
EDWARD: That is a very serious conclusion to have arrived at in...how many?...thirty-two hours." -- T. S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7038-kiss-me-and-you-will-see-how-important-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 08:44:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7038-kiss-me-and-you-will-see-how-important-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kiss me, and you will see how important I am." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35193-for-the-whole-earth-is-the-tomb-of-famous-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 08:45:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Thucydides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35193-for-the-whole-earth-is-the-tomb-of-famous-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the whole earth is the tomb of famous men; not only are they commemorated by columns and inscriptions in their own country, but in foreign lands there dwells also an unwritten memorial of them, graven not on stone but in the hearts of men. Make them your examples, and, esteeming courage to be freedom and freedom to be happiness, do not weigh too nicely the perils of war.&quot;

[Funeral Oration of Pericles]" -- Thucydides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42771-when-i-was-born-i-was-almost-fourteen-years-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 19:17:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Eugene Ionesco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42771-when-i-was-born-i-was-almost-fourteen-years-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was born, I was almost fourteen years old. That's why I was able to understand more easily than most what it was all about." -- Eugene Ionesco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23624-i-read-i-say-i-study-and-read-i-bet</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 20:21:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23624-i-read-i-say-i-study-and-read-i-bet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read,&quot; I say. &quot;I study and read. I bet I've read everything you read. Don't think I haven't. I consume libraries. I wear out spines and ROM-drives. I do things like get in a taxi and say, &quot;The library, and step on it.&quot; My instincts concerning syntax and mechanics are better than your own, I can tell, with all due respect. But it transcends the mechanics. I'm not a machine. I feel and believe. I have opinions. Some of them are interesting. I could, if you'd let me, talk and talk." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3817-are-we-not-all-of-us-fanatics-i-say-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 20:22:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3817-are-we-not-all-of-us-fanatics-i-say-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Are we not all of us fanatics?  I say only what you of the U.S.A. pretend you do not know.  Attachments are of great seriousness.  Choose your attachments carefully.  Choose your temple of fanaticism with great care.  What you wish to sing of as tragic love is an attachment not carefully chosen.  Die for one person?  This is a craziness.  Persons change, leave, die, become ill.  They leave, lie, go mad, have sickness, betray you, die.  Your nation outlives you.  A cause outlives you." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44084-two-months-after-marching-through-boston-half-the-regiment-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2008 14:44:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Robert Lowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44084-two-months-after-marching-through-boston-half-the-regiment-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two months after marching through Boston,
half the regiment was dead;
at the dedication,
William James could almost hear the bronze Negroes breathe.

Their monument sticks like a fishbone
in the city's throat.
Its Colonel is as lean
as a compass-needle.

He has an angry wrenlike vigilance,
a greyhound's gently tautness;
he seems to wince at pleasure,
and suffocate for privacy.

He is out of bounds now.  He rejoices in man's lovely,
peculiar power to choose life and die--
when he leads his black soldiers to death,
he cannot bend his back." -- Robert Lowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12843-the-fox-knows-many-things-but-the-hedgehog-knows-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 08:19:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Archilochus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12843-the-fox-knows-many-things-but-the-hedgehog-knows-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fox knows many things, but the hedgehog knows one big thing." -- Archilochus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18-3-there-are-bears-and-there-are-small-dogs-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 12:47:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18-3-there-are-bears-and-there-are-small-dogs-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["3. There are bears and there are small dogs. Be strong like bear! If they take out your teeth, sit on the dogs. Bears always forget they can just sit on the dogs. Sit on the dogs." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52467-and-now-of-a-sudden-my-illusion-vanished-what-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 17:38:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52467-and-now-of-a-sudden-my-illusion-vanished-what-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And now of a sudden my illusion vanished. What was my body to me? A kind of flunkey in my service. Let my anger wax hot, my love grow exalted, my hatred collect in me, and the boasted solidarity between me and my body was gone.

Your son is in a burning house. Nobody can hold you back. You may burn up, but what do you think of that? You are ready to bequeath the rags of your body to any man who will take them. You discover that what you set so much store by is trash. You would sell your hand, if need be, to give a hand to a friend. It is in your act that you exist, not in your body. Your act is yourself, and there is no other you. Your body belongs to you: it is not you. Are you about to strike an enemy? No threat of bodily harm can hold you back. You? It is the death of your enemy that is you. You? It is the rescue of your child that is you. In that moment you exchange yourself against something else; and you have no feeling tat you lost by the exchange. Your members? Tools. A tool snaps in your hand: how important is that tool? You exchange yourself against the death of your enemy, the rescue of your child, the recovery of your patient, the perfection of your theorem...Your true significance becomes dazzlingly evident. Your true name is duty, hatred, love, child, theorem. There is no other you than this." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42075-you-will-make-all-kinds-of-mistakes-but-as-long</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 14:44:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42075-you-will-make-all-kinds-of-mistakes-but-as-long]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You will make all kinds of mistakes; but as long as you are generous and true and also fierce you cannot hurt the world or even seriously distress her. She was meant to be wooed and won by youth." -- Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63176-wherever-in-this-city-screens-flicker-with-pornography-with-science-fiction</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2008 21:45:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Edward add a quote by Adrienne Rich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63176-wherever-in-this-city-screens-flicker-with-pornography-with-science-fiction]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wherever in this city, screens flicker
with pornography, with science-fiction vampires,
victimized hirelings bending to the lash,
we also have to walk . . . if simply as we walk
through the rainsoaked garbage, the tabloid cruelties
of our own neighborhoods.
We need to grasp our lives inseperable
from those rancid dreams, that blurt of metal, those disgraces,
and the red begonia perilously flashing
from a tenement sill six stories high,
or the long-legged young girls playing ball
in the junior highschool playground.
No one has imagined us. We want to live like trees,
sycamores blazing through the sulfuric air,
dappled with scars, still exuberantly budding,
our animal passion rooted in the city." -- Adrienne Rich]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
