<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/64627-kenneth]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/64627-kenneth" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 08:27:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44023-what-i-really-hoped-for-no-doubt-was-to-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 08:27:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44023-what-i-really-hoped-for-no-doubt-was-to-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I really hoped for, no doubt, was to come upon one of those lives which begin nowhere, which lead us through marshes and salt flats, trickling away, seemingly without plan, purpose or goal, and suddenly emerge, gushing like geysers, and never cease gushing, even in death." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44025-when-we-are-motivated-by-compassion-and-wisdom-the-results</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 08:27:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by The Dalai Lama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44025-when-we-are-motivated-by-compassion-and-wisdom-the-results]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we are motivated by compassion and wisdom, the results of our actions benefit everyone, not just our individual selves or some immediate convenience.  When we are able to recognize and forgive ignorant actions of the past, we gain strength to constructively solve the problems of the present." -- The Dalai Lama]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44020-to-show-a-child-what-has-once-delighted-you-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 08:27:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by J. B. Priestly]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44020-to-show-a-child-what-has-once-delighted-you-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To show a child what has once delighted you, to find the child's delight added to your own, so that there is now a double delight seen in the glow of trust and affection, this is happiness." -- J. B. Priestly]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44021-nothing-is-falser-than-people-s-preconceptions-and-ready-made-opinions-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 08:27:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Petronius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44021-nothing-is-falser-than-people-s-preconceptions-and-ready-made-opinions-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing is falser than people's preconceptions and ready-made opinions; nothing is sillier than their sham morality..." -- Petronius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44019-no-matter-of-difference-in-the-world-is-worth-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 08:27:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Dharma, son of righteousness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44019-no-matter-of-difference-in-the-world-is-worth-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No matter of difference in the world is worth or condones hatred, hostility, pride...Bigotry is humanity's most dangerous enemy.
Be tolerant.  Accept and love all peoples.  Be beautiful to all.
Hate is poisonous.  Anyone who teaches a child bigotry is a monster." -- Dharma, son of righteousness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 22:53:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Groucho Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Outside of a dog, a book is man's best friend. Inside of a dog it's too dark to read." -- Groucho Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 22:54:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 22:56:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Insanity is doing the same thing, over and over again, but expecting different results." -- Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13796-if-you-cannot-read-all-your-books-fondle-them---peer-into-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 19:26:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13796-if-you-cannot-read-all-your-books-fondle-them---peer-into-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you cannot read all your books...fondle them---peer into them, let them fall open where they will, read from the first sentence that arrests the eye, set them back on the shelves with your own hands, arrange them on your own plan so that you at least know where they are. Let them be your friends; let them, at any rate, be your acquaintances." -- Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/579796-it-is-a-burden-m-ake-no-mistake-about-that-any-great</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 08:28:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Susan Cooper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/579796-it-is-a-burden-m-ake-no-mistake-about-that-any-great]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a burden...(M)ake no mistake about that. Any great gift or power or talent is a burden and this more than any, and you will long to be free of it. But there is nothing to be done. If you were born with the gift, then you must serve it, and nothing in this world or out of it may stand in the way of that service, because that is why you were born and that is the Law.&quot;
- Susan Cooper (&quot;Merriman&quot; The Dark is Rising)" -- Susan Cooper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/962-develop-an-interest-in-life-as-you-see-it-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 20:59:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/962-develop-an-interest-in-life-as-you-see-it-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Develop an interest in life as you see it; the people, things, literature, music - the world is so rich, simply throbbing with rich treasures, beautiful souls and interesting people. Forget yourself." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430324-the-new-america-instead-is-fast-becoming-a-vast-ghetto</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2012 09:52:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Matt Taibbi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430324-the-new-america-instead-is-fast-becoming-a-vast-ghetto]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The new America, instead, is fast becoming a vast ghetto in which all of us, conservatives and progressives, are being bled dry by a relatively tiny oligarchy of extremely clever financial criminals and their castrato henchmen in government, whose job is to be good actors on TV and put on a good show." -- Matt Taibbi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494647-the-world-is-like-a-ride-in-an-amusement-park</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 20:54:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Bill Hicks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494647-the-world-is-like-a-ride-in-an-amusement-park]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is like a ride in an amusement park, and when you choose to go on it you think it's real because that's how powerful our minds are. The ride goes up and down, around and around, it has thrills and chills, and it's very brightly colored, and it's very loud, and it's fun for a while. Many people have been on the ride a long time, and they begin to wonder, &quot;Hey, is this real, or is this just a ride?&quot; And other people have remembered, and they come back to us and say, &quot;Hey, don't worry; don't be afraid, ever, because this is just a ride.&quot; And we … kill those people. &quot;Shut him up! I've got a lot invested in this ride, shut him up! Look at my furrows of worry, look at my big bank account, and my family. This has to be real.&quot; It's just a ride. But we always kill the good guys who try and tell us that, you ever notice that? And let the demons run amok … But it doesn't matter, because it's just a ride. And we can change it any time we want. It's only a choice. No effort, no work, no job, no savings of money. Just a simple choice, right now, between fear and love. The eyes of fear want you to put bigger locks on your doors, buy guns, close yourself off. The eyes of love instead see all of us as one. Here's what we can do to change the world, right now, to a better ride. Take all that money we spend on weapons and defenses each year and instead spend it feeding and clothing and educating the poor of the world, which it would pay for many times over, not one human being excluded, and we could explore space, together, both inner and outer, forever, in peace." -- Bill Hicks]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
