<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/647572-maria-noel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/647572-maria-noel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2007 19:51:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1986-any-transition-serious-enough-to-alter-your-definition-of-self</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2007 19:51:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Martha Beck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1986-any-transition-serious-enough-to-alter-your-definition-of-self]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any transition serious enough to alter your definition of self will require not just small adjustments in your way of living and thinking but a full-on metamorphosis." -- Martha Beck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1987-where-justice-is-denied-where-poverty-is-enforced-where-ignorance</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2007 19:51:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Frederick Douglass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1987-where-justice-is-denied-where-poverty-is-enforced-where-ignorance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where justice is denied, where poverty is enforced, where ignorance prevails, and where any one class is made to feel that society is an organized conspiracy to oppress, rob and degrade them, neither persons nor property will be safe." -- Frederick Douglass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2007 19:52:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18468-first-they-came-for-the-communists-and-i-did-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2007 19:52:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Martin Niemöller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18468-first-they-came-for-the-communists-and-i-did-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First they came for the communists, and I did not speak out—
    because I was not a communist;
Then they came for the socialists, and I did not speak out—
    because I was not a socialist;
Then they came for the trade unionists, and I did not speak out—
    because I was not a trade unionist;
Then they came for the Jews, and I did not speak out—
    because I was not a Jew;
Then they came for me—
    and there was no one left to speak out for me." -- Martin Niemöller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1990-it-is-imperative-that-the-past-of-the-pilgrims-progress</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2007 19:52:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by H. Richard Niebuhr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1990-it-is-imperative-that-the-past-of-the-pilgrims-progress]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is imperative that the past of the pilgrims' progress be intentionally carried forward into the present as we work into our future. Without it we cannot know who we are, why we are here, or where we can go. Without a common past to live out of we become aimless and wandering individuals instead of a pilgrim people." -- H. Richard Niebuhr]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
