<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/64805-katrina]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/64805-katrina" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 11:30:58 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20112-when-adults-say-teenagers-think-they-are-invincible-with-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 11:30:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katrina add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20112-when-adults-say-teenagers-think-they-are-invincible-with-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When adults say, &quot;Teenagers think they are invincible&quot; with that sly, stupid smile on their faces, they don't know how right they are. We need never be hopeless, because we can never be irreparably broken. We think that we are invincible because we are. We cannot be born, and we cannot die. Like all energy, we can only change shapes and sizes and manifestations. They forget that when they get old. They get scared of losing and failing. But that part of us greater than the sum of our parts cannot begin and cannot end, and so it cannot fail." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/503943-if-cam-finally-learned-one-lesson-before-she-died-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 20:47:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katrina add a quote by Wendy Wunder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/503943-if-cam-finally-learned-one-lesson-before-she-died-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If Cam finally learned one lesson before she died, it would be that being kind was sometimes more important than being right." -- Wendy Wunder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/564361-we-weren-t-put-on-this-earth-to-go-it-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 20:47:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katrina add a quote by Wendy Wunder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/564361-we-weren-t-put-on-this-earth-to-go-it-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We weren't put on this earth to go it alone." -- Wendy Wunder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/564367-if-you-believed-that-thoughts-were-energy-and-energy-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 20:48:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katrina add a quote by Wendy Wunder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/564367-if-you-believed-that-thoughts-were-energy-and-energy-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you believed that thoughts were energy and energy is matter (E=mc2) and matter never disappears, then a person can never truly leave you unless you stop thinking about them. Everything you shared with a person is still there swirling around in the universe. Love, Cam had to admit, might be real. And love endures. Relationships endure. Because thoughts are energy, energy is matter, and matter never disappears." -- Wendy Wunder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485442-as-he-read-i-fell-in-love-the-way-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2012 08:28:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katrina add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485442-as-he-read-i-fell-in-love-the-way-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As he read, I fell in love the way you fall asleep: slowly, and then all at once." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485841-you-don-t-get-to-choose-if-you-get-hurt-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2012 08:33:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katrina add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485841-you-don-t-get-to-choose-if-you-get-hurt-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't get to choose if you get hurt in this world...but you do have some say in who hurts you. I like my choices." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153695-it-always-shocked-me-when-i-realized-that-i-wasn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2012 08:54:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katrina add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153695-it-always-shocked-me-when-i-realized-that-i-wasn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It always shocked me when I realized that I wasn’t the only person in the world who thought and felt such strange and awful things." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63019-he-knew-only-that-his-child-was-his-warrant-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2012 08:55:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katrina add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63019-he-knew-only-that-his-child-was-his-warrant-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He knew only that his child was his warrant. He said: If he is not the word of God God never spoke." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254447-have-you-ever-heard-the-wonderful-silence-just-before-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 22:51:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katrina add a quote by Norton Juster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254447-have-you-ever-heard-the-wonderful-silence-just-before-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever heard the wonderful silence just before the dawn? Or the quiet and calm just as a storm ends? Or perhaps you know the silence when you haven't the answer to a question you've been asked, or the hush of a country road at night, or the expectant pause of a room full of people when someone is just about to speak, or, most beautiful of all, the moment after the door closes and you're alone in the whole house? Each one is different, you know, and all very beautiful if you listen carefully." -- Norton Juster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67409-as-the-cheering-continued-rhyme-leaned-forward-and-touched-milo</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 22:53:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katrina add a quote by Norton Juster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67409-as-the-cheering-continued-rhyme-leaned-forward-and-touched-milo]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As the cheering continued, Rhyme leaned forward and touched Milo gently on the shoulder. 
  &quot;They're cheering for you,&quot; she said with a smile. 
  &quot;But I could never have done it,&quot; he objected, &quot;without everyone else's help.&quot; 
  &quot;That may be true,&quot; said Reason gravely, &quot;but you had the courage to try; and what you can do is often simply a matter of what you *will* do.&quot; 
  &quot;That's why,&quot; said Azaz, &quot;there was one very important thing about your quest that we couldn't discuss until you returned. 
  &quot;I remember,&quot; said Milo eagerly. &quot;Tell me now.&quot; 
  &quot;It was impossible,&quot; said the king, looking at the Mathemagician. 
  &quot;Completely impossible,&quot; said the Mathemagician, looking at the king. 
  &quot;Do you mean----&quot; said the bug, who suddenly felt a bit faint. 
  &quot;Yes, indeed,&quot; they repeated together; &quot;but if we'd told you then, you might not have gone---and, as you've discovered, so many things are possible just as long as you don't know they're impossible.&quot; 
  And for the remainder of the ride Milo didn't utter a sound." -- Norton Juster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484846-and-remember-also-that-many-places-you-would-like-to-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 22:55:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katrina add a quote by Norton Juster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484846-and-remember-also-that-many-places-you-would-like-to-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And remember, also...that many places you would like to see are just off the map and many things you want to know are just out of sight or a little beyond your reach. But someday you'll reach them all, for what you learn today, for no reason at all, will help you discover all the wonderful secrets of tomorrow." -- Norton Juster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238648-it-is-a-miracle-if-you-can-find-true-friends</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 07:12:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katrina add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238648-it-is-a-miracle-if-you-can-find-true-friends]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a miracle if you can find true friends, and it is a miracle if you have enough food to eat, and it is a miracle if you get to spend your days and evenings doing whatever it is you like to do, and the holiday season - like all the other seasons - is a good time not only to tell stories of miracles, but to think about the miracles in your own life, and to be grateful for them, and that's the end of this particular story." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
