<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/648861-amy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/648861-amy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 21:40:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2345-i-hate-you-god-i-hate-you-as-though-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 21:40:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2345-i-hate-you-god-i-hate-you-as-though-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hate you, God. I hate you as though you actually exist." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18179-freeing-yourself-was-one-thing-claiming-ownership-of-that-freed</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 19:45:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18179-freeing-yourself-was-one-thing-claiming-ownership-of-that-freed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Freeing yourself was one thing, claiming ownership of that freed self was another." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23999-a-beautiful-woman-looking-at-her-image-in-the-mirror</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 08:12:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Simone Weil]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23999-a-beautiful-woman-looking-at-her-image-in-the-mirror]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A beautiful woman looking at her image in the mirror may very well believe the image is herself.  An ugly woman knows it is not." -- Simone Weil]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133515-when-spring-came-even-the-false-spring-there-were-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2013 13:34:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133515-when-spring-came-even-the-false-spring-there-were-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When spring came, even the false spring, there were no problems except where to be happiest.  The only thing that could spoil a day was people and if you could keep from making engagements, each day had no limits.  People were always the limiters of happiness except for the very few that were as good as spring itself." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124547-it-s-a-funny-thing-about-the-modern-world-you-hear</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2013 17:48:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124547-it-s-a-funny-thing-about-the-modern-world-you-hear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's a funny thing about the modern world. You hear girls in the toilets of clubs saying, &quot;Yeah, he fucked off and left me. He didn't love me. He just couldn't &lt;i&gt;deal&lt;/i&gt; with love. He was too fucked up to know &lt;i&gt;how&lt;/i&gt; to love me.&quot; Now, how did that happen? What was it about this unlovable century that convinced us we were, despite everything, eminently lovable as a people, as a species? What made us think that anyone who fails to love us is damaged, lacking, &lt;i&gt;malfunctioning&lt;/i&gt; in some way? And particularly if they replace us with a god, or a weeping madonna, or the face of Christ in a ciabatta roll---then we call them crazy. Deluded. Regressive. We are so convinced of the goodness of ourselves, and the goodness of our love, we cannot bear to believe that there might be something more worthy of love than us, more worthy of worship. Greeting cards routinely tell us everybody deserves love. No. Everybody deserves clean water. Not everybody deserves love all the time." -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5775-give-sorrow-words-the-grief-that-does-not-speak-knits</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2013 15:06:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5775-give-sorrow-words-the-grief-that-does-not-speak-knits]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Give sorrow words; the grief that does not speak knits up the o-er wrought heart and bids it break." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 20:52:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be patient toward all that is unsolved in your heart and try to love the questions themselves, like locked rooms and like books that are now written in a very foreign tongue. Do not now seek the answers, which cannot be given you because you would not be able to live them. And the point is, to live everything. Live the questions now. Perhaps you will then gradually, without noticing it, live along some distant day into the answer." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19562-the-point-of-marriage-is-not-to-create-a-quick</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 20:54:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19562-the-point-of-marriage-is-not-to-create-a-quick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The point of marriage is not to create a quick commonality by tearing down all boundaries; on the contrary, a good marriage is one in which each partner appoints the other to be the guardian of his solitude, and thus they show each other the greatest possible trust. A merging of two people is an impossibility, and where it seems to exist, it is a hemming-in, a mutual consent that robs one party or both parties of their fullest freedom and development. But once the realization is accepted that even between the closest people infinite distances exist, a marvelous living side-by-side can grow up for them, if they succeed in loving the expanse between them, which gives them the possibility of always seeing each other as a whole and before an immense sky." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
