<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/649149-ms-houseman]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/649149-ms-houseman" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2009 19:53:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24415-he-s-feeling-a-pull-like-gravity-of-the-approaching-tv</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2009 19:53:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ms.Houseman add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24415-he-s-feeling-a-pull-like-gravity-of-the-approaching-tv]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He's feeling a pull, like gravity, of the approaching TV news. It's a condition of the times, this compulsion to hear how it stands with the world, and be joined to the generality, to a community of anxiety. The habit's grown stronger these past two years; a different scale of news value has been set by monstrous and spectacular scenes. [...] Everyone fears it, but there's also a darker longing in the collective mind, a sickening for self-punishment and a blasphemous curiosity. Just as the hospitals have their crisis plans, so the television networks stand ready to deliver, and their audiences wait. Bigger, grosser next time. Please don't let it happen. But let me see it all the same, as it's happening and from every angle, and let me be among the first to know." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2487-maybe-the-private-life-wasn-t-forever-maybe-everyone-got-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2009 19:53:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ms.Houseman add a quote by Ann Patchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2487-maybe-the-private-life-wasn-t-forever-maybe-everyone-got-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe the private life wasn't forever. Maybe everyone got it for a little while and then spent the rest of their lives remembering." -- Ann Patchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2491-i-ll-think-of-it-tomorrow-at-tara-i-can-stand</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2009 19:53:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ms.Houseman add a quote by Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2491-i-ll-think-of-it-tomorrow-at-tara-i-can-stand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'll think of it tomorrow, at Tara. I can stand it then. Tomorrow, I'll think of some way to get him back. After all, tomorrow is another day." -- Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46513-the-lower-you-are-the-higher-your-mind-will-want</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2009 19:54:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ms.Houseman add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46513-the-lower-you-are-the-higher-your-mind-will-want]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The lower you are, the higher your mind will want to soar." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140914-i-skim-through-the-issue-of-elle-and-reach-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2009 19:54:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ms.Houseman add a quote by Jean-Dominique Bauby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140914-i-skim-through-the-issue-of-elle-and-reach-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I skim through the issue [of Elle] and reach the offending photo, a montage that ridicules rather than glorifies our idol. It is one of the mysteries of our trade. You work for weeks on a subject, it goes back and forth among the most skillful pairs of hands, and no one spots the glaring blunder that a neophyte would spot in a second." -- Jean-Dominique Bauby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129621-here-s-why-i-will-be-a-good-person-because-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 14:47:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ms.Houseman add a quote by Garth Stein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129621-here-s-why-i-will-be-a-good-person-because-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's why I will be a good person. Because I listen. I cannot talk, so I listen very well. I never deflect the course of the conversation with a comment of my own. People, if you pay attention to them, change the direction of one another's conversations constantly. It's like being a passenger in your car who suddenly grabs the steering wheel and turns you down a side street. For instance, if we met at a party and I wanted to tell you a story about the time I needed to get a soccer ball in my neighbor's yard but his dog chased me and I had to jump into a swimming pool to escape, and I began telling the story, you, hearing the words &quot;soccer&quot; and &quot;neighbor&quot; in the same sentence, might interrupt and mention that your childhood neighbor was Pele, the famous soccer player, and I might be courteous and say, Didn't he play for the Cosmos of New York? Did you grow up in New York? And you might reply that, no, you grew up in Brazil on the streets of Tres Coracoes with Pele, and I might say, I thought you were from Tennessee, and you might say not originally, and then go on to outline your genealogy at length. So my initial conversational gambit - that I had a funny story about being chased by my neighbor's dog - would be totally lost, and only because you had to tell me all about Pele. Learn to &lt;i&gt;listen&lt;/i&gt;! I beg of you. Pretend you are a dog like me and listen to other people rather than steal their stories." -- Garth Stein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2489-if-there-hadn-t-been-a-sixth-day-man-would-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 14:47:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ms.Houseman add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2489-if-there-hadn-t-been-a-sixth-day-man-would-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there hadn't been a sixth day, man would not exist; copper would always be copper; and lead just lead. It's true that everything has its Personal Legend, but one day that Personal Legend will be realized. So each thing has to transform itself into something better, and to acquire a new Personal Legend, until, someday, the Soul of the World becomes one thing only." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66570-the-blackness-would-stir-and-eventually-go-away-and-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 14:47:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ms.Houseman add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66570-the-blackness-would-stir-and-eventually-go-away-and-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The blackness would stir and eventually go away, and God would remain, a shining point of light in my heart. I would go on loving." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103741-i-still-smart-a-little-at-the-slight-when-you-ve</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 14:47:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ms.Houseman add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103741-i-still-smart-a-little-at-the-slight-when-you-ve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I still smart a little at the slight. When you've suffered a great deal in life, each additional pain is both unbearable and trifling. My life is like a memento mori painting from European art: there is always a grinning skull at my side to remind me of the folly of human ambition. I mock this skull. I look at it and I say, &quot;You've got the wrong fellow. You may not believe in life, but I don't believe in death. Move on!&quot; The skull snickers and moves ever closer, but that doesn't surprise me. The reason death sticks so closely to life isn't biological necessity -- it's envy. Life is so beautiful that death has fallen in love with it, a jealous, possessive love that grabs at what it can." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
