<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/64914-billie-rain]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/64914-billie-rain" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2009 18:35:30 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208965-reclaiming-the-sacred-is-not-simply-a-new-linguistic-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2009 18:35:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Leela Fernandes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208965-reclaiming-the-sacred-is-not-simply-a-new-linguistic-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reclaiming the sacred... is not simply a new linguistic or symbolic strategy for feminism. It goes to the heart of feminist struggles for social justice and can provide a critical foundation for social transformation. At one level, feminism becomes a means for the decolonization of the divine. At another level, the provision of spiritual strength to individuals deeply committed to social justice is more necessary than ever in a world racked by immense hatreds that feed on each other in endless cycles of retribution, always in the name of 'justice.' Finally, a spiritualization of social movements can provide a means with which to break from these cycles of retribution which perpetrate multiple and linked forms of oppression so that social movements continually find themselves appropriated by or circumscribed within the very structures they have tried wholeheartedly to resist." -- Leela Fernandes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78801-imperialism-leaves-behind-germs-of-rot-which-we-must-clinically</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:14:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Frantz Fanon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78801-imperialism-leaves-behind-germs-of-rot-which-we-must-clinically]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imperialism leaves behind germs of rot which we must clinically detect and remove from our land but from our minds as well." -- Frantz Fanon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391278-when-the-rose-is-gone-and-the-garden-faded-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2011 21:19:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391278-when-the-rose-is-gone-and-the-garden-faded-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the rose is gone and the garden faded
you will no longer hear the nightingale's song.
The Beloved is all; the lover just a veil. 
The Beloved is living; the lover a dead thing.
If love withholds its strengthening care,
the lover is left like a bird without care,
the lover is left like a bird without wings.
How will I be awake and aware
if the light of the Beloved is absent?
Love wills that this Word be brought forth." -- Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78802-the-problem-that-faces-us-is-the-problem-of-awakening</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:14:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Thich Nhat Hahn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78802-the-problem-that-faces-us-is-the-problem-of-awakening]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem that faces us is the problem of awakening. What we lack is not an ideology or doctrine that will save the world. What we lack is mindfulness of what we are, of what our situation really is. We need to wake up in order to rediscover our human sovereignty. We are riding a horse that is running out of control. The way of salvation is a new culture in which human beings are encouraged to rediscover their deepest nature." -- Thich Nhat Hahn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78803-even-in-faith-it-is-not-easy-for-me-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:15:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by David Kwang-sun Suh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78803-even-in-faith-it-is-not-easy-for-me-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even in faith, it is not easy for me to say to God, I am sorry for wanting my enemies to be destroyed and punished before my eyes. It is dishonest to say that it is easy to forgive our enemies, even to ask forgiveness for longing for revenge. " -- David Kwang-sun Suh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78804-the-refusal-to-feel-takes-a-heavy-toll-not-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:16:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Joanna Macy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78804-the-refusal-to-feel-takes-a-heavy-toll-not-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The refusal to feel takes a heavy toll. Not only is there an impoverishment of our emotional and sensory life, flowers are dimmer and less fragrant, our loves less ecstaticâ but this psychic numbing also impedes our capacity to process and respond to information. The energy expended in pushing down despair is diverted from more creative uses, depleting the resilience and imagination needed for fresh visions and strategies. " -- Joanna Macy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78805-healing-comes-not-from-being-loving-but-from-being-itself</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:16:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Stephen Levine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78805-healing-comes-not-from-being-loving-but-from-being-itself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...healing comes not from being loving but from being itself. It is not a case of being clear but of clear being. This healing is not about anything else but being itself. Nothing separate, no edges, nothing to limit healing. Entering, in moments, the realm of pure being, the gateless gate swings open-- beyond life and death, our original face shines back at us." -- Stephen Levine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78806-in-the-city-and-in-the-country-the-same-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:17:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Andrea del Moral]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78806-in-the-city-and-in-the-country-the-same-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the city and in the country, the same thing is happening to us all--we're being dispossessed of the land. Closed in by concrete, steel and gasoline, broken from the rhythms of the seasons and the soil, we've got our work to do. " -- Andrea del Moral]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78808-it-is-not-for-the-concept-but-for-the-experience</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:19:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Stephen Levine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78808-it-is-not-for-the-concept-but-for-the-experience]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not for the concept, but for the experience, that we use the term the Beloved. The experience of this enormity we falteringly label divine is unconditioned love. Absolute openness, unbounded mercy and compassion. We use this concept, not to name the unnameable vastness of being-- our greatest joy-- but to acknowledge and claim as our birthright the wonders and healings within." -- Stephen Levine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78809-around-us-life-bursts-with-miracles--a-glass-of-water-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:19:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Thich Nhat Hahn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78809-around-us-life-bursts-with-miracles--a-glass-of-water-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Around us, life bursts with miracles--a glass of water, a ray of sunshine, a leaf, a caterpillar, a flower, laughter, raindrops. If you live in awareness, it is easy to see miracles everywhere. Each human being is a multiplicity of miracles. Eyes that see thousands of colors, shapes, and forms; ears that hear a bee flying or a thunderclap; a brain that ponders a speck of dust as easily as the entire cosmos; a heart that beats in rhythm with the heartbeat of all beings. When we are tired and feel discouraged by life's daily struggles, we may not notice these miracles, but they are always there." -- Thich Nhat Hahn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78811-you-often-say-i-would-give-but-only-to-the-deserving</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:20:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78811-you-often-say-i-would-give-but-only-to-the-deserving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You often say,'I would give, but only to the deserving.'
The trees in your orchard say not so, nor the flocks in your pasture.
They give that they may live, for to withhold is to perish.
Surely he who is worthy to receive his days and his nights, is worthy of all else from you.
And he who has deserved to drink from the ocean of life deserves to fill his cup from your little stream. " -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78813-what-is-wise-in-this-world-exists-equally-inside-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:22:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Joanne Arnott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78813-what-is-wise-in-this-world-exists-equally-inside-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is wise in this world exists equally inside of us and outside of us, and it is through collaboration that wisdom, stories, songs are made manifest." -- Joanne Arnott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78814-to-acknowledge-our-ancestors-means-we-are-aware-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:23:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78814-to-acknowledge-our-ancestors-means-we-are-aware-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To acknowledge our ancestors means we are aware that we did not make ourselves, that the line stretches all the way back, perhaps to God; or to Gods. We remember them because it is an easy thing to forget: that we are not the first to suffer, rebel, fight, love and die. The grace with which we embrace life, in spite of the pain, the sorrow, is always a measure of what has gone before. " -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78815-here-and-there-in-the-barrios-and-the-favelas-among</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:23:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Mumia Abu-Jamal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78815-here-and-there-in-the-barrios-and-the-favelas-among]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["here and there
in the barrios and the favelas,
among those who have least,
beat hearts of hope,
fly sparks of Overcoming. " -- Mumia Abu-Jamal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78816-true-power-does-not-amass-through-the-pain-and-suffering</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:28:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Joy Harjo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78816-true-power-does-not-amass-through-the-pain-and-suffering]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["True power does not amass through the pain and suffering of others." -- Joy Harjo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78817-there-are-ways-in-journeys-to-the-center-of-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:29:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Linda Hogan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78817-there-are-ways-in-journeys-to-the-center-of-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are ways in, journeys to the center of life, through time; through air, matter, dream and thought. The ways are not always mapped or charted, but sometimes being lost, if there is such a thing, is the sweetest place to be. And always, in this search, a person might find that she is already there, at the center of the world. It may be a broken world, but it is glorious nonetheless." -- Linda Hogan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78818-how-do-i-know-anything-how-is-it-that-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:30:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Nalo Hopkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78818-how-do-i-know-anything-how-is-it-that-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How do I know anything? How is it that my arms stretched out in front of me are so pale? How to I even know that they should be brown like riverbank mud, as they were when I was many goddesses with many worshippers, ruling in lands on the other side of a great, salty ocean? I used to be many, but now we are one, all squeezed together, many necks in one coffle. " -- Nalo Hopkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78819-market-moralities-and-mentalities---fueled-by-economic-imperatives-to-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:31:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Cornel West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78819-market-moralities-and-mentalities---fueled-by-economic-imperatives-to-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Market moralities and mentalities-- fueled by economic imperatives to make a profit at nearly any cost-- yield unprecedented levels of loneliness, isolation, and sadness. And our public life lies in shambles, shot through with icy cynicism and paralyzing pessimism. To put it bluntly, beneath the record-breaking stock markets on Wall Street and bipartisan budget-balancing deals in the White House lurk ominous clouds of despair across this nation." -- Cornel West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78820-if-abuse-is-to-cease-and-genuine-love-respect-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:32:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Moriah S. St. Clair]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78820-if-abuse-is-to-cease-and-genuine-love-respect-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If abuse is to cease, and genuine love, respect, and trust are to be restored to the family picture- indeed to humanity's universal picture- then the ways that abuse is formed and perpetuated must be addressed. All that we deny of ourselves and bury beneath the surface, eventually becomes the rot which lays a brittle foundation for the next generation " -- Moriah S. St. Clair]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78821-the-system-is-not-working-that-is-how-a-paradigm</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:32:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Matthew Fox]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78821-the-system-is-not-working-that-is-how-a-paradigm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The system is not working. That is how a paradigm shift begins: the established way of seeing the world no longer functions." -- Matthew Fox]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78822-people-with-chronic-fatigue-who-kill-themselves-are-the-millenium-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:33:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Marta Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78822-people-with-chronic-fatigue-who-kill-themselves-are-the-millenium-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People with [Chronic Fatigue] who kill themselves are the millenium's favorite type of disabled citizens-- those who will walk quietly among the healthy, then quietly dispose of themselves. " -- Marta Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78823-the-church-says-the-body-is-a-sin-science-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:33:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Eduardo Galeano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78823-the-church-says-the-body-is-a-sin-science-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Church says: the body is a sin.
Science says: the body is a machine.
Advertising says: The body is a business.
The Body says: I am a fiesta." -- Eduardo Galeano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78824-see-me-now-your-severed-daughter-laughing-our-name-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:34:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78824-see-me-now-your-severed-daughter-laughing-our-name-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["see me now
your severed daughter
laughing our name into echo
all the world shall remember " -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78825-we-who-have-touched-war-have-a-duty-to-bring</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:35:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78825-we-who-have-touched-war-have-a-duty-to-bring]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We who have touched war have a duty to bring the truth about war to those who have not had a direct experience of it. We are the light at the tip of the candle. It is really hot, but it has the power of shining and illuminating. If we practice mindfulness, we will know how to look deeply into the nature of war and, with our insight, wake people up so that together we can avoid repeating the same horrors again and again." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78827-oftentimes-have-i-heard-you-speak-of-one-who-commits</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:37:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78827-oftentimes-have-i-heard-you-speak-of-one-who-commits]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oftentimes have I heard you speak of one who commits a wrong as though he were not one of you, but a stranger unto you and an intruder upon your world.
But I say that even as the holy and the righteous cannot rise beyond the highest which is in each one of you,
So the wicked and the weak cannot fall lower than the lowest which is in you also.
And as a single leaf turns not yellow but with the silent knowledge of the whole tree,
So the wrong-doer cannot do wrong without the hidden will of you all.
Like a procession you walk together towards your god-self.
You are the way and the wayfarers.
And when one of you falls down he falls for those behind him, a caution against the stumbling stone. " -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78828-like-most-visions-of-a-golden-age-the-traditional-family</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:38:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Stephanie Coontz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78828-like-most-visions-of-a-golden-age-the-traditional-family]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like most visions of a 'golden age', the 'traditional family' evaporates on closer examination. It is an ahistorical amalgam of structures, values, and behaviors that never coexisted in the same time and place." -- Stephanie Coontz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78829-elie-wiesel-says-that-the-greatest-evil-in-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:39:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Mumia Abu-Jamal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78829-elie-wiesel-says-that-the-greatest-evil-in-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Elie Wiesel says that the greatest evil in the world is not anger or hatred, but indifference. If that is true, then the opposite is also true: that the greatest love we can show our children is the attention we pay them, the time we take for them. Maybe we serve children the best simply by noticing them." -- Mumia Abu-Jamal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1502-facts-do-not-cease-to-exist-because-they-are-ignored</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:40:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1502-facts-do-not-cease-to-exist-because-they-are-ignored]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Facts do not cease to exist because they are ignored." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78830-goodness-will-never-win-against-evil-that-split-is-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:41:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Joanne Arnott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78830-goodness-will-never-win-against-evil-that-split-is-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Goodness will never win against evil. That split is an irresponsible division of reality." -- Joanne Arnott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78832-child-sexual-abuse-teaches-us-lessons-about-power--who-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 18:42:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Billie add a quote by Joanna Kadi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78832-child-sexual-abuse-teaches-us-lessons-about-power--who-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Child sexual abuse teaches us lessons about power- who has it and who doesn't. These lessons, experienced on a bodily level, transfer into the deepest levels of our conscious and subconscious being, and correspond with other oppressive systems. Widespread child sexual abuse supports a racist, sexist, classist and ableist society that attempts to train citizens into docility and unthinking acceptance of whatever the government and big business deem fit to hand out." -- Joanna Kadi]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
