<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/649326-hanne]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/649326-hanne" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 04:25:36 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178186-it-s-discouraging-to-think-how-many-people-are-shocked-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 04:25:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanne add a quote by Noël Coward]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178186-it-s-discouraging-to-think-how-many-people-are-shocked-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's discouraging to think how many people are shocked by honesty and how few by deceit." -- Noël Coward]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76987-the-roots-of-violence-wealth-without-work-pleasure-without-conscience</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 04:25:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanne add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76987-the-roots-of-violence-wealth-without-work-pleasure-without-conscience]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Roots of Violence: Wealth without work, Pleasure without conscience, Knowledge without character, Commerce without morality, Science without humanity, Worship without sacrifice, Politics without principles.&quot;

(&lt;i&gt;Young India&lt;/i&gt;, 22 October 1925)" -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23627-he-who-joyfully-marches-to-music-rank-and-file-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 04:27:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanne add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23627-he-who-joyfully-marches-to-music-rank-and-file-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He who joyfully marches to music rank and file has already earned my contempt. He has been given a large brain by mistake, since for him the spinal cord would surely suffice. This disgrace to civilization should be done away with at once.  Heroism at command, senseless brutality, deplorable love-of-country stance and all the loathsome nonsense that goes by the name of patriotism, how violently I hate all this, how despicable and ignoble war is; I would rather be torn to shreds than be part of so base an action!  It is my conviction that killing under the cloak of war is nothing but an act of murder." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13607-he-who-is-cruel-to-animals-becomes-hard-also-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 04:27:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanne add a quote by Emmanuel Kant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13607-he-who-is-cruel-to-animals-becomes-hard-also-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He who is cruel to animals becomes hard also in his dealings with men. We can judge the heart of a man by his treatment of animals." -- Emmanuel Kant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4976-a-person-may-cause-evil-to-others-not-only-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 04:29:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanne add a quote by John Stuart Mill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4976-a-person-may-cause-evil-to-others-not-only-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A person may cause evil to others not only by his actions but by his inaction, and in either case he is justly accountable to them for the injury." -- John Stuart Mill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116895-the-assumption-that-animals-are-without-rights-and-the-illusion</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 04:29:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanne add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116895-the-assumption-that-animals-are-without-rights-and-the-illusion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The assumption that animals are without rights and the illusion that our treatment of them has no moral significance is a positively outrageous example of Western crudity and barbarity. Universal compassion is the only guarantee of morality." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325436-we-keep-on-being-told-that-religion-whatever-its-imperfections</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 04:30:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanne add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325436-we-keep-on-being-told-that-religion-whatever-its-imperfections]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We keep on being told that religion, whatever its imperfections, at least instills morality. On every side, there is conclusive evidence that the contrary is the case and that faith causes people to be more mean, more selfish, and perhaps above all, more stupid." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267658-about-once-or-twice-every-month-i-engage-in-public</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 04:30:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanne add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267658-about-once-or-twice-every-month-i-engage-in-public]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["About once or twice every month I engage in public debates with those whose pressing need it is to woo and to win the approval of supernatural beings. Very often, when I give my view that there is no supernatural dimension, and certainly not one that is only or especially available to the faithful, and that the natural world is wonderful enough—and even miraculous enough if you insist—I attract pitying looks and anxious questions. How, in that case, I am asked, do I find meaning and purpose in life? How does a mere and gross materialist, with no expectation of a life to come, decide what, if anything, is worth caring about?

Depending on my mood, I sometimes but not always refrain from pointing out what a breathtakingly insulting and patronizing question this is. (It is on a par with the equally subtle inquiry: Since you don't believe in our god, what stops you from stealing and lying and raping and killing to your heart's content?) Just as the answer to the latter question is: self-respect and the desire for the respect of others—while in the meantime it is precisely those who think they have divine permission who are truly capable of any atrocity—so the answer to the first question falls into two parts. A life that partakes even a little of friendship, love, irony, humor, parenthood, literature, and music, and the chance to take part in battles for the liberation of others cannot be called 'meaningless' except if the person living it is also an existentialist and elects to call it so. It could be that all existence is a pointless joke, but it is not in fact possible to live one's everyday life as if this were so. Whereas if one sought to define meaninglessness and futility, the idea that a human life should be expended in the guilty, fearful, self-obsessed propitiation of supernatural nonentities… but there, there. Enough." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134283-one-of-the-greatest-tragedies-in-mankind-s-entire-history-may</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 04:30:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanne add a quote by Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134283-one-of-the-greatest-tragedies-in-mankind-s-entire-history-may]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the greatest tragedies in mankind's entire history may be that morality was hijacked by religion." -- Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22309-t-he-infliction-of-cruelty-with-a-good-conscience-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 04:31:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanne add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22309-t-he-infliction-of-cruelty-with-a-good-conscience-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[T]he infliction of cruelty with a good conscience is a delight to moralists. That is why they invented Hell." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229494-among-the-rich-you-will-never-find-a-really-generous</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 04:38:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanne add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229494-among-the-rich-you-will-never-find-a-really-generous]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Among the rich you will never find a really generous man even by accident. They may give their money away, but they will never give themselves away; they are egotistic, secretive, dry as old bones. To be smart enough to get all that money you must be dull enough to want it." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/475162-ayn-rand-s-philosophy-is-nearly-perfect-in-its-immorality-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 04:40:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanne add a quote by Gore Vidal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/475162-ayn-rand-s-philosophy-is-nearly-perfect-in-its-immorality-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ayn Rand's 'philosophy' is nearly perfect in its immorality, which makes the size of her audience all the more ominous and symptomatic as we enter a curious new phase in our society.... To justify and extol human greed and egotism is to my mind not only immoral, but evil." -- Gore Vidal]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
