<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/649848-diego-baud]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/649848-diego-baud" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2013 23:06:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286712-one-of-the-reasons-why-we-crave-love-and-seek</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2013 23:06:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Gregory David Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286712-one-of-the-reasons-why-we-crave-love-and-seek]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the reasons why we crave love, and seek it so desperately, is that love is the only cure for loneliness, and shame, and sorrow. But some feelings sink so deep into the heart that only loneliness can help you find them again. Some truths about yourself are so painful that only shame can help you live with them. And some things are just so sad that only your soul can do the crying for you." -- Gregory David Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137617-one-day-you-will-ask-me-which-is-more-important</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 01:01:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137617-one-day-you-will-ask-me-which-is-more-important]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One day you will ask me which is more important? My life or yours? I will say mine and you will walk away not knowing that you are my life." -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 01:01:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19891-marriage-is-a-fine-institution-but-i-m-not-ready-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 01:00:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19891-marriage-is-a-fine-institution-but-i-m-not-ready-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Marriage is a fine institution, but I'm not ready for an institution." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53225-ever-has-it-been-that-love-knows-not-its-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2012 14:33:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53225-ever-has-it-been-that-love-knows-not-its-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ever has it been that love knows not its own depth until the hour of separation." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135828-it-takes-a-minute-to-have-a-crush-on-someone</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2012 14:39:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Kahlil Gibran ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135828-it-takes-a-minute-to-have-a-crush-on-someone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It takes a minute to have a crush on someone, an hour to like someone, and a day to love someone... but it takes a lifetime to forget someone." -- Kahlil Gibran ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10071-time-is-a-drug-too-much-of-it-kills-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 01:46:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10071-time-is-a-drug-too-much-of-it-kills-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time is a drug.  Too much of it kills you." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97202-let-me-tell-you-this-if-you-meet-a-loner</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 02:46:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97202-let-me-tell-you-this-if-you-meet-a-loner]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me tell you this: if you meet a loner, no matter what they tell you, it's not because they enjoy solitude. It's because they have tried to blend into the world before, and people continue to disappoint them." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169599-i-ve-never-been-lonely-i-ve-been-in-a-room---</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 02:50:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169599-i-ve-never-been-lonely-i-ve-been-in-a-room---]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've never been lonely. I've been in a room -- I've felt suicidal. I've been depressed. I've felt awful -- awful beyond all -- but I never felt that one other person could enter that room and cure what was bothering me...or that any number of people could enter that room. In other words, loneliness is something I've never been bothered with because I've always had this terrible itch for solitude. It's being at a party, or at a stadium full of people cheering for something, that I might feel loneliness. I'll quote Ibsen, &quot;The strongest men are the most alone.&quot; I've never thought, &quot;Well, some beautiful blonde will come in here and give me a fuck-job, rub my balls, and I'll feel good.&quot; No, that won't help. You know the typical crowd, &quot;Wow, it's Friday night, what are you going to do? Just sit there?&quot; Well, yeah. Because there's nothing out there. It's stupidity. Stupid people mingling with stupid people. Let them stupidify themselves. I've never been bothered with the need to rush out into the night. I hid in bars, because I didn't want to hide in factories. That's all. Sorry for all the millions, but I've never been lonely. I like myself. I'm the best form of entertainment I have. Let's drink more wine!" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13733-for-those-who-believe-in-god-most-of-the-big</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 17:02:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13733-for-those-who-believe-in-god-most-of-the-big]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For those who believe in God, most of the big questions are answered. But for those of us who can't readily accept the God formula, the big answers don't remain stone-written. We adjust to new conditions and discoveries. We are pliable. Love need not be a command nor faith a dictum. I am my own god. We are here to unlearn the teachings of the church, state, and our educational system. We are here to drink beer. We are here to kill war. We are here to laugh at the odds and live our lives so well that Death will tremble to take us." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11871-that-s-the-problem-with-drinking-i-thought-as-i-poured</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 17:02:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11871-that-s-the-problem-with-drinking-i-thought-as-i-poured]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's the problem with drinking, I thought, as I poured myself a drink. If something bad happens you drink in an attempt to forget; if something good happens you drink in order to celebrate; and if nothing happens you drink to make something happen." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26093-jealousy-is-a-disease-love-is-a-healthy-condition-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 11:49:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26093-jealousy-is-a-disease-love-is-a-healthy-condition-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jealousy is a disease, love is a healthy condition. The immature mind often mistakes one for the other, or assumes that the greater the love, the greater the jealousy - in fact, they are almost incompatible; one emotion hardly leaves room for the other." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29750-i-will-love-you-as-the-iceberg-loves-the-ship</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 04:30:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29750-i-will-love-you-as-the-iceberg-loves-the-ship]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will love you as the iceberg loves the ship, and the passengers love the lifeboat and the lifeboat loves the teeth of the sperm whale, and the sperm whale loves the flavor of naval uniforms." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449778-i-will-love-you-as-we-find-ourselves-farther-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 04:54:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449778-i-will-love-you-as-we-find-ourselves-farther-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will love you as we find ourselves farther and farther from one another, where we once were so close that we could slip the curved straw, and the long, slender spoon, between our lips and fingers respectively. I will love you until the chances of us running into one another slip from slim to zero, and until your face is fogged by distant memory, and your memory faced by distant fog, and your fog memorized by a distant face, and your distance distanced by the memorized memory of a foggy fog. I will love you no matter where you go and who you see, no matter where you avoid and who you don’t see, and no matter who sees you avoiding where you go. I will love you no matter what happens to you, and no matter how I discover what happens to you, and no matter what happens to me as I discover this, and no matter how I am discovered after what happens to me as I am discovering this." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11589-i-have-absolutely-no-pleasure-in-the-stimulants-in-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 23:45:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11589-i-have-absolutely-no-pleasure-in-the-stimulants-in-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have absolutely no pleasure in the stimulants in which I sometimes so madly indulge. It has not been in the pursuit of pleasure that I have periled life and reputation and reason. It has been the desperate attempt to escape from torturing memories, from a sense of insupportable loneliness and a dread of some strange impending doom." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 23:51:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Bob Moorehead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The paradox of our time in history is that we have taller buildings but 
shorter tempers, wider Freeways, but narrower viewpoints.  We spend more, 
but have less, we buy more, but enjoy less. We have bigger houses and 
smaller families, more conveniences, but less time.  We have more degrees 
but less sense, more knowledge, but less judgment, more experts, yet more 
problems, more medicine, but less wellness.

We drink too much, smoke too much, spend too recklessly, laugh too little, 
drive too fast, get too angry, stay up too late, get up too tired, read too 
little, watch TV too much, and pray too seldom.  We have multiplied our 
possessions, but reduced our values.  We talk too much, love too seldom, and 
hate too often.

We've learned how to make a living, but not a life. We've added years to 
life not life to years.  We've been all the way to the moon and back, but 
have trouble crossing the street to meet a new neighbor.  We conquered outer 
space but not inner space.  We've done larger things, but not better things.

We've cleaned up the air, but polluted the soul. We've conquered the atom, 
but not our prejudice.  We write more, but learn less.  We plan more, but 
accomplish less.  We've learned to rush, but not to wait.  We build more 
computers to hold more information, to produce more copies than ever, but we 
communicate less and less.

These are the times of fast foods and slow digestion, big men and small 
character, steep profits and shallow relationships.

These are the days of two incomes but more divorce, fancier houses, but 
broken homes.  These are days of quick trips, disposable diapers, throwaway 
morality, one night stands, overweight bodies, and pills that do everything 
from cheer, to quiet, to kill.  It is a time when there is much in the 
showroom window and nothing in the stockroom.  A time when technology can 
bring this letter to you, and a time when you can choose either to share 
this insight, or to just hit delete...

Remember, to spend some time with your loved ones, because they are not 
going to be around forever.  Remember, say a kind word to someone who looks 
up to you in awe, because that little person soon will grow up and leave 
your side.

Remember, to give a warm hug to the one next to you, because that is the 
only treasure you can give with your heart and it doesn't cost a cent.

Remember, to say, &quot;I love you&quot; to your partner and your loved ones, but most 
of all mean it.  A kiss and an embrace will mend hurt when it comes from 
deep inside of you.

Remember to hold hands and cherish the moment for someday that person might 
not be there again.  Give time to love, give time to speak! And give time to 
share the precious thoughts in your mind." -- Bob Moorehead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315477-sometimes-i-m-terrified-of-my-heart-of-its-constant-hunger</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 23:42:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315477-sometimes-i-m-terrified-of-my-heart-of-its-constant-hunger]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I’m terrified of my heart; of its constant hunger for whatever it is it wants. The way it stops and starts." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150357-there-are-moments-when-even-to-the-sober-eye-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 23:45:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150357-there-are-moments-when-even-to-the-sober-eye-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are moments when even to the sober eye of reason, the world of our sad humanity may assume the semblance of Hell. " -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8202-most-men-lead-lives-of-quiet-desperation-and-go-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 00:42:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8202-most-men-lead-lives-of-quiet-desperation-and-go-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most men lead lives of quiet desperation and go to the grave with the song still in them." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17900-i-have-never-found-a-companion-that-was-so-companionable</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 00:45:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17900-i-have-never-found-a-companion-that-was-so-companionable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have never found a companion that was so companionable as solitude." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21291-in-the-morning-i-bathe-my-intellect-in-the-stupendous</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 00:45:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21291-in-the-morning-i-bathe-my-intellect-in-the-stupendous]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;b&gt;In the morning I bathe my intellect in the stupendous and cosmogonal philosophy of the Bhagvat-Geeta, since whose composition years of the gods have elapsed, and in comparison with which our modern world and its literature seem puny and trivial&lt;/b&gt;; and I doubt if that philosophy is not to be referred to a previous state of existence, so remote is its sublimity from our conceptions. I lay down the book and go to my well for water, and lo! there I meet the servant of the Bramin, priest of Brahma and Vishnu and Indra, who still sits in his temple on the Ganges reading the Vedas, or dwells at the root of a tree with his crust and water jug. I meet his servant come to draw water for his master, and our buckets as it were grate together in the same well. The pure Walden water is mingled with the sacred water of the Ganges." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192782-i-would-define-in-brief-the-poetry-of-words-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 23:28:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192782-i-would-define-in-brief-the-poetry-of-words-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would define, in brief, the poetry of words as the rhythmical creation of beauty." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/632563-he-was-mastered-by-the-sheer-surging-of-life-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 01:53:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Jack London]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/632563-he-was-mastered-by-the-sheer-surging-of-life-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was mastered by the sheer surging of life, the tidal wave of being, the perfect joy of each separate muscle, joint, and sinew in that it was everything that was not death, that it was aglow and rampant, expressing itself in movement, flying exultantly under the stars." -- Jack London]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141929-he-was-sounding-the-deeps-of-his-nature-and-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 01:55:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Jack London]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141929-he-was-sounding-the-deeps-of-his-nature-and-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was sounding the deeps of his nature, and of the parts of his nature that were deeper than he, going back into the womb of Time." -- Jack London]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/652-i-became-insane-with-long-intervals-of-horrible-sanity</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 22:50:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/652-i-became-insane-with-long-intervals-of-horrible-sanity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I became insane, with long intervals of horrible sanity." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260702-live-dangerously</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 21:36:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Nietzche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260702-live-dangerously]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Live dangerously." -- Nietzche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140777-therefore-dear-sir-love-your-solitude-and-try-to-sing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 15:06:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140777-therefore-dear-sir-love-your-solitude-and-try-to-sing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Therefore, dear Sir, love your solitude and try to sing out with the pain it causes you. For those who are near you are far away... and this shows that the space around you is beginning to grow vast.... be happy about your growth, in which of course you can't take anyone with you, and be gentle with those who stay behind; be confident and calm in front of them and don't torment them with your doubts and don't frighten them with your faith or joy, which they wouldn't be able to comprehend. Seek out some simple and true feeling of what you have in common with them, which doesn't necessarily have to alter when you yourself change again and again; when you see them, love life in a form that is not your own and be indulgent toward those who are growing old, who are afraid of the aloneness that you trust.... and don't expect any understanding; but believe in a love that is being stored up for you like an inheritance, and have faith that in this love there is a strength and a blessing so large that you can travel as far as you wish without having to step outside it." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1346-my-beerdrunk-soul-is-sadder-than-all-the-dead-christmas</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 18:03:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1346-my-beerdrunk-soul-is-sadder-than-all-the-dead-christmas]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["my beerdrunk soul is sadder than all the dead christmas trees of the world." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107408-we-are-like-roses-that-have-never-bothered-to-bloom</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 18:04:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Charles Bukowski ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107408-we-are-like-roses-that-have-never-bothered-to-bloom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are like roses that have never bothered to bloom when we should have bloomed and it is as if the sun has become disgusted with waiting" -- Charles Bukowski ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170390-i-was-drawn-to-all-the-wrong-things-i-liked</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 18:04:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170390-i-was-drawn-to-all-the-wrong-things-i-liked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was drawn to all the wrong things: I liked to drink, I was lazy, I didn't have a god, politics, ideas, ideals. I was settled into nothingness; a kind of non-being, and I accepted it. I didn't make for an interesting person. I didn't want to be interesting, it was too hard. What I really wanted was only a soft, hazy space to live in, and to be left alone." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
