<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/649800-lauren]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/649800-lauren" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 18:15:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10845-the-only-way-you-get-americans-to-notice-anything-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 18:15:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10845-the-only-way-you-get-americans-to-notice-anything-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only way you get Americans to notice anything is to tax them or draft them or kill them." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10840-your-memory-is-a-monster-you-forget-it-doesn-t-it-simply</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 18:19:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10840-your-memory-is-a-monster-you-forget-it-doesn-t-it-simply]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your memory is a monster; you forget—it doesn't. It simply files things away. It keeps things for you, or hides things from you—and summons them to your recall with will of its own. You think you have a memory; but it has you!" -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2529-hindus-in-their-capacity-for-love-are-indeed-hairless-christians</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 19:33:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2529-hindus-in-their-capacity-for-love-are-indeed-hairless-christians]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hindus, in their capacity for love, are indeed hairless Christians, just as Muslims, in the way they see God in everything, are bearded Hindus, and Christians, in their devotion to God, are hat wearing Muslims." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46179-i-must-say-a-word-about-fear-it-is-life-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 19:39:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46179-i-must-say-a-word-about-fear-it-is-life-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I must say a word about fear. It is life's only true opponent. Only fear can defeat life. It is a clever, treacherous adversary, how well I know. It has no decency, respects no law or convention, shows no mercy. It goes for your weakest spot, which it finds with unnerving ease. It begins in your mind, always ... so you must fight hard to express it. You must fight hard to shine the light of words upon it. Because if you don't, if your fear becomes a wordless darkness that you avoid, perhaps even manage to forget, you open yourself to further attacks of fear because you never truly fought the opponent who defeated you." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20347-a-nything-worth-dying-for-is-certainly-worth-living-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 19:43:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20347-a-nything-worth-dying-for-is-certainly-worth-living-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...[A]nything worth dying for ... is certainly worth living for." -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49018-i-m-not-a-drug-salesman-i-m-a-writer-what-makes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 20:14:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49018-i-m-not-a-drug-salesman-i-m-a-writer-what-makes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not a drug salesman. I'm a writer.&quot;

&quot;What makes you think a writer isn't a drug salesman?" -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51475-i-always-say-waste-not-want-not-which-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 14:25:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Plum Sykes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51475-i-always-say-waste-not-want-not-which-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I always say, waste not, want not, which is a terrible cliche the British invented during the war to get kids to eat their whole-wheat bread, but when I say it I mean, waste not money on boring old rent when it can be un-wasted on Chloe jeans." -- Plum Sykes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59103-we-are-all-worthy-of-one-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 15:50:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Edward P. Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59103-we-are-all-worthy-of-one-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all worthy of one another." -- Edward P. Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114832-saeed-quickly-found-employment-at-a-banana-republic-where-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 18:16:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Kiran Desai]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114832-saeed-quickly-found-employment-at-a-banana-republic-where-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Saeed quickly found employment at a Banana Republic, where he would sell to urban sophisticates the black turtleneck of the season, in a shop whose name was synonymous with colonial exploitation and the rapacious ruin of the third world." -- Kiran Desai]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114838-whenever-people-in-that-part-of-the-world-asked-patterson</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 18:31:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Edward P. Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114838-whenever-people-in-that-part-of-the-world-asked-patterson]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever people in that part of the world asked Patterson about the wonders of America, the possibilities and the hope of America, Patterson would say that it was a good and fine place but all the Americans were running it into the ground and that it would be a far better place if it had no Americans." -- Edward P. Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114843-a-man-does-not-learn-very-well-mr-robbins-women</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 18:37:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Edward P. Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114843-a-man-does-not-learn-very-well-mr-robbins-women]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man does not learn very well, Mr. Robbins. Women, yes, because they are used to bending with whatever wind comes along.  A woman, no matter the age, is always learning, always becoming.  But a man, if you will pardon me, stops learning at fourteen or so.  He shuts it all down, Mr. Robbins.  A log is capable of learning more than a man.  To teach a man would be a battle, a war, and I would lose." -- Edward P. Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114845-she-went-through-her-memory-for-the-time-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 18:42:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Edward P. Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114845-she-went-through-her-memory-for-the-time-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She went through her memory for the time, for the day, she and and her husband told him all about what he should and should not do.  No goin out into them woods without Papa or me knowin about it.  No steppin foot out this house without them free papers, not even to go to the well or the privy. Say your prayers every night...Pick the blueberries close to the ground, son.  Them the sweetest, I find.  If a white man say the trees can talk, can dance, you just say yes right along, that you done seen em do it plenty of times.  Don't look them people in the eye.  You see a white woman riding toward you, get way off the road and go stand behind a tree.  The uglier the white woman, the farther you go and the broader the tree.  But where, in all she taught her son, was it about thou shall own no one, havin been owned once your own self.  Don't go back to Egypt after God done took you outa there." -- Edward P. Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114846-calvin-had-long-been-uneasy-in-his-own-person-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 18:45:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Edward P. Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114846-calvin-had-long-been-uneasy-in-his-own-person-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Calvin had long been uneasy in his own person and so lived to put everyone else at ease." -- Edward P. Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114847-he-knew-he-was-going-to-die-but-he-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 18:48:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Edward P. Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114847-he-knew-he-was-going-to-die-but-he-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He knew he was going to die but he thought this little thing might provide him with a nothing stool way off in the corner of heaven reserved for fools, people too stupid to come out of the rain.  People got to that corner by heaven's back door." -- Edward P. Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114848-best-hurry-he-thought-best-get-outa-this-weather-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 18:50:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Edward P. Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114848-best-hurry-he-thought-best-get-outa-this-weather-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Best hurry, he thought. Best get outa this weather.  He wanted to die but he really didn't want to catch a cold to do it." -- Edward P. Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114855-now-i-began-to-understand-art-as-a-kind-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 19:13:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114855-now-i-began-to-understand-art-as-a-kind-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now I began to understand art as a kind of black box the reader enters.  He enters in one state of mind and exits in another.  The writer gets no points just because what's inside the box bears some linear resemblance to &quot;real life&quot; -- he can put whatever he wants in there.  What's important is that something undeniable and nontrivial happens to the reader between entry and exit." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53201-humor-is-what-happens-when-we-re-told-the-truth-quicker</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 19:14:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53201-humor-is-what-happens-when-we-re-told-the-truth-quicker]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humor is what happens when we're told the truth quicker and more directly than we're used to." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114860-at-times-they-re-so-right-and-i-m-so-left-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 19:20:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114860-at-times-they-re-so-right-and-i-m-so-left-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At times, they're so Right and I'm so Left, we agree." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114863-america-is-and-always-has-been-undecided-about-whether-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 19:28:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114863-america-is-and-always-has-been-undecided-about-whether-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["America is, and always has been, undecided about whether it will be the United States of Tom or the United States of Huck.  The United States of Tom looks at misery and says: Hey, I didn't do it.  It looks at inequity and says: All my life I busted my butt to get where I am, so don't come crying to me.  Tom likes kings, codified nobility, unquestioned privilege.  Huck likes people, fair play, spreading the truck around.  Whereas Tom knows, Huck wonders.  Whereas Huck hopes, Tom presumes.  Whereas Huck cares, Tom denies.  These two parts of the American Psyche have been at war since the beginning of the nation, and come to think of it, these two parts of the World Psyche have been at war since the beginning of the world, and the hope of the nation and of the world is to embrace the Huck part and send the Tom part back up the river, where it belongs." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10046-there-did-not-have-to-be-a-moral-she-need</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 23:10:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10046-there-did-not-have-to-be-a-moral-she-need]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There did not have to be a moral. She need only show separate minds, as alive as her own, struggling with the idea that other minds were equally alive. It wasn't only wickedness and scheming that made people unhappy, it was confusion and misunderstanding, above all, it was the failure to grasp the simple truth that other people are as real as you. And only in a story could you enter these different minds and show how they had an equal value. That was the only moral a story need have." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65836-it-is-quite-impossible-these-days-to-assume-anything-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 23:12:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65836-it-is-quite-impossible-these-days-to-assume-anything-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is quite impossible these days to assume anything about people's educational level from the way they talk or dress or from their taste in music. Safest to treat everyone you meet as a distinguished intellectual." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72202-success-after-all-loves-a-witness-but-failure-can-t-exist</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 21:04:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Junot Díaz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72202-success-after-all-loves-a-witness-but-failure-can-t-exist]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Success, after all, loves a witness, but failure can't exist without one." -- Junot Díaz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72208-instead-of-finding-himself-in-nerd-heaven-where-every-nerd-gets</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 21:04:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Junot Diaz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72208-instead-of-finding-himself-in-nerd-heaven-where-every-nerd-gets]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Instead of finding himself in nerd heaven—where every nerd gets fifty-eight virgins to role-play with—he woke up in Robert Wood Johnson with two broken legs and a separated shoulder, feeling like, well, he'd jumped off the New Brunswick train bridge." -- Junot Diaz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65054-the-road-now-stretched-across-open-country-and-it-occured</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 11:23:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65054-the-road-now-stretched-across-open-country-and-it-occured]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The road now stretched across open country, and it occured to me - not by way of protest, not as a symbol, or anything like that, but merely as a novel experience - that since I had disregarded all laws of humanity, I might as well disregard the rules of traffic. So I crossed to the left side of the highway and checked the feeling, and the feeling was good. It was a pleasant diaphragmal melting, with elements of diffused tactility, all this enhanced by the thought that nothing could be nearer to the elimination of basic physical laws than deliberately driving on the wrong site of the road." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71510-the-history-of-every-major-galactic-civilization-tends-to-pass</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2009 19:58:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71510-the-history-of-every-major-galactic-civilization-tends-to-pass]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The History of every major Galactic Civilization tends to pass through three distinct and recognizable phases, those of Survival, Inquiry and Sophistication, otherwise known as the How, Why, and Where phases.  For instance, the first phase is characterized by the question 'How can we eat?' the second by the question 'Why do we eat?' and the third by the question 'Where shall we have lunch?" -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185811-can-o-beans-was-to-remark-that-a-comparison-between-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 14:54:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185811-can-o-beans-was-to-remark-that-a-comparison-between-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Can o'Beans was to remark that a comparison between the American Cowpoke and, say, the Japanese samurai, left the cowboy looking rather shoddy. 'Before a samurai went into battle,' Can o' Beans was to say, 'he would burn incense in his helmet so that if his enemy took his head, he would find it pleasant to his nose. Cowboys, on the other hand, hardly ever bathed or changed their crusty clothing.  If a samurai's enemy lost his sword, the samurai gave him his extra one so that the fight might continue in a manner honorable and fair.  The cowboy's specialty was to shoot enemies in the back from behind a bush.  Do you begin to see the difference?'  Spoon and Dirty Sock would wonder how Can o' Beans knew so much about samurai. 'Oh, I sat on the shelf next to a box of imported rice crackers for over a month,' Can o' Beans would explain. 'One can learn a lot conversing with foreigners." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185812-the-inability-to-correctly-perceive-reality-is-often-responsible-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 14:58:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185812-the-inability-to-correctly-perceive-reality-is-often-responsible-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The inability to correctly perceive reality is often responsible for humans' insane behavior.  And every time they substitute an all-purpose, sloppy slang word for words that would accurately describe an emotion or a situation, it lowers their reality orientations, pushes them farther from shore, out onto the foggy waters of alienation and confusion." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185813-what-mattered-to-abu-was-the-music-of-the-sentence</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 15:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185813-what-mattered-to-abu-was-the-music-of-the-sentence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What mattered to Abu was the music of the sentence.  'A shadow does not belong to the object that casts it.'  To Abu, it was a little poem.  And in general, it was the poetics, the music of things that tossed his confetti." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214704-information-about-time-cannot-be-imparted-in-a-straightforward-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 15:18:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214704-information-about-time-cannot-be-imparted-in-a-straightforward-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Information about time cannot be imparted in a straightforward way.  Like furniture, it has to be tipped and tilted to get it through the door.  If the past is a solid oak buffet whose legs must be unscrewed and whose drawers must be removed before, in an altered state, it can be upended into the entryway of our minds, then the future is a king-size waterbed that hardly stands a chance, especially if it needs to be brought up in an elevator.

Those billions who persist in perceiving time as the pursuit of the future are continually buying waterbeds that will never make it beyond the front porch or the lobby.  And if man's mission is to reside in the fullness of the present, then he's got no space for the waterbed, anyhow, not even if he could lower it through a skylight." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185816-summer-had-come-to-sit-on-new-york-s-face</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 15:19:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185816-summer-had-come-to-sit-on-new-york-s-face]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Summer had come to sit on New York's face." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
