<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/650459-doug]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/650459-doug" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2009 13:10:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16821-if-you-go-home-with-somebody-and-they-don-t-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2009 13:10:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by John Waters]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16821-if-you-go-home-with-somebody-and-they-don-t-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you go home with somebody, and they don't have books, don't fuck 'em!" -- John Waters]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164628-america-hadn-t-really-been-suited-for-its-long-and-tiresome</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2010 14:40:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by Bruce Sterling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164628-america-hadn-t-really-been-suited-for-its-long-and-tiresome]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["America hadn't really been suited for its long and tiresome role as the Last Superpower, the World's Policeman. As a patriotic American, Oscar was quite content to watch other people's military coming home in boxes for a while. The American national character wasn't suited for global police duties. It never had been. Tidy and meticulous people such as the Swiss and the Swedes were the types who made good cops. America was far better suited to be the World's Movie Star. The world's tequila-addled pro-league bowler. The world's acerbic, bipolar stand-up comedian. Anything but a somber and tedious nation of socially responsible centurions." -- Bruce Sterling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309633-toska---noun-t--sk---russian-word-roughly-translated-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 22:23:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309633-toska---noun-t--sk---russian-word-roughly-translated-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Toska - noun /ˈtō-skə/ - Russian word roughly translated as sadness, melancholia, lugubriousness.

&quot;No single word in English renders all the shades of toska. At its deepest and most painful, it is a sensation of great spiritual anguish, often without any specific cause. At less morbid levels it is a dull ache of the soul, a longing with nothing to long for, a sick pining, a vague restlessness, mental throes, yearning. In particular cases it may be the desire for somebody of something specific, nostalgia, love-sickness. At the lowest level it grades into ennui, boredom." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/450012-in-the-beginning-god-became-the-heaven-and-the-earth</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 16:55:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/450012-in-the-beginning-god-became-the-heaven-and-the-earth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the beginning, God became the Heaven and the Earth... And God said, 'Let Me be light,&quot; and He was light." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117664-mr-constant-he-said-right-now-you-re-as-easy-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 16:55:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117664-mr-constant-he-said-right-now-you-re-as-easy-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mr. Constant,&quot; he said, &quot;right now you’re as easy for the Bureau of Internal Revenue to watch as a man on a street corner selling apples and pears. But just imagine how hard you would be to watch if you had a whole office building jammed to the rafters with industrial bureaucrats—men who lose things and use the wrong forms and create new forms and demand everything in quintuplicate, and who understand perhaps a third of what is said to them; who habitually give misleading answers in order to gain time in which to think, who make decisions only when forced to, and who then cover their tracks; who make perfectly honest mistakes in addition and subtraction, who call meetings whenever they feel lonely, who write memos whenever they feel unloved; men who never throw anything away unless they think it could get them fired. A single industrial bureaucrat, if he is sufficiently vital and nervous, should be able to create a ton of meaningless papers a year for the Bureau of Internal Revenue to examine." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172489-oh-lord-most-high-creator-of-the-cosmos-spinner-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 16:55:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172489-oh-lord-most-high-creator-of-the-cosmos-spinner-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh Lord Most High, Creator of the Cosmos, Spinner of Galaxies, Soul of Electromagnetic Waves, Inhaler and Exhaler of Inconceivable Volumes of Vacuum, Spitter of Fire and Rock, Trifler with Millennia — what could we do for Thee that Thou couldst not do for Thyself one octillion times better? Nothing. What could we do or say that could possibly interest Thee? Nothing. Oh, Mankind, rejoice in the apathy of our Creator, for it makes us free and truthful and dignified at last. No longer can a fool point to a ridiculous accident of good luck and say, 'Somebody up there likes me.' And no longer can a tyrant say, 'God wants this or that to happen, and anyone who doesn't help this or that to happen is against God.' O Lord Most High, what a glorious weapon is Thy Apathy, for we have unsheathed it, have thrust and slashed mightily with it, and the claptrap that has so often enslaved us or driven us into the madhouse lies slain!&quot; -The prayer of the Reverend C. Horner Redwine" -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161972-the-first-thing-you-notice-about-new-orleans-are-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 12:23:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by Bob Dylan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161972-the-first-thing-you-notice-about-new-orleans-are-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first thing you notice about New Orleans are the burying grounds - the cemeteries - and they're a cold proposition, one of the best things there are here. Going by, you try to be as quiet as possible, better to let them sleep. Greek, Roman, sepulchres- palatial mausoleums made to order, phantomesque, signs and symbols of hidden decay - ghosts of women and men who have sinned and who've died and are now living in tombs. The past doesn't pass away so quickly here. You could be dead for a long time.

The ghosts race towards the light, you can almost hear the heavy breathing spirits, all determined to get somewhere. New Orleans, unlike a lot of those places you go back to and that don't have the magic anymore, still has got it. Night can swallow you up, yet none of it touches you. Around any corner, there's a promise of something daring and ideal and things are just getting going. There's something obscenely joyful behind every door, either that or somebody crying with their head in their hands. A lazy rhythm looms in the dreamy air and the atmosphere pulsates with bygone duels, past-life romance, comrades requesting comrades to aid them in some way. You can't see it, but you know it's here. Somebody is always sinking. Everyone seems to be from some very old Southern families. Either that or a foreigner. I like the way it is.

There are a lot of places I like, but I like New Orleans better. There's a thousand different angles at any moment. At any time you could run into a ritual honoring some vaguely known queen. Bluebloods, titled persons like crazy drunks, lean weakly against the walls and drag themselves through the gutter. Even they seem to have insights you might want to listen to. No action seems inappropriate here. The city is one very long poem. Gardens full of pansies, pink petunias, opiates. Flower-bedecked shrines, white myrtles, bougainvillea and purple oleander stimulate your senses, make you feel cool and clear inside.

Everything in New Orleans is a good idea. Bijou temple-type cottages and lyric cathedrals side by side. Houses and mansions, structures of wild grace. Italianate, Gothic, Romanesque, Greek Revival standing in a long line in the rain. Roman Catholic art. Sweeping front porches, turrets, cast-iron balconies, colonnades- 30-foot columns, gloriously beautiful- double pitched roofs, all the architecture of the whole wide world and it doesn't move. All that and a town square where public executions took place. In New Orleans you could almost see other dimensions. There's only one day at a time here, then it's tonight and then tomorrow will be today again. Chronic melancholia hanging from the trees. You never get tired of it. After a while you start to feel like a ghost from one of the tombs, like you're in a wax museum below crimson clouds. Spirit empire. Wealthy empire. One of Napoleon's generals, Lallemaud, was said to have come here to check it out, looking for a place for his commander to seek refuge after Waterloo. He scouted around and left, said that here the devil is damned, just like everybody else, only worse. The devil comes here and sighs. New Orleans. Exquisite, old-fashioned. A great place to live vicariously. Nothing makes any difference and you never feel hurt, a great place to really hit on things. Somebody puts something in front of you here and you might as well drink it. Great place to be intimate or do nothing. A place to come and hope you'll get smart - to feed pigeons looking for handouts" -- Bob Dylan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53993-i-think-if-it-is-true-that-there-are-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 10:38:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53993-i-think-if-it-is-true-that-there-are-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think... if it is true that 
there are as many minds as there 
are heads, then there are as many 
kinds of love as there are hearts." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7142-all-happy-families-are-alike-each-unhappy-family-is-unhappy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 10:38:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by Leo Tolstoy  ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7142-all-happy-families-are-alike-each-unhappy-family-is-unhappy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All happy families are alike; each unhappy family is unhappy in its own way." -- Leo Tolstoy  ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74804-if-you-look-for-perfection-you-ll-never-be-content</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 10:38:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74804-if-you-look-for-perfection-you-ll-never-be-content]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you look for perfection, you'll never be content." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74807-respect-was-invented-to-cover-the-empty-place-where-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 10:38:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74807-respect-was-invented-to-cover-the-empty-place-where-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Respect was invented to cover the empty place where love should be." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74808-is-it-really-possible-to-tell-someone-else-what-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 10:38:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74808-is-it-really-possible-to-tell-someone-else-what-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is it really possible to tell someone else what one feels?" -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391485-it-s-much-better-to-do-good-in-a-way-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 10:39:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391485-it-s-much-better-to-do-good-in-a-way-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["it's much better to do good in a way that no one knows anything about it." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74797-it-s-hard-to-love-a-woman-and-do-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 10:39:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74797-it-s-hard-to-love-a-woman-and-do-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's hard to love a woman and do anything." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193078-when-i-die-nieces-i-want-to-be-cremated-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 16:05:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by Joseph Boyden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193078-when-i-die-nieces-i-want-to-be-cremated-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I die, nieces, I want to be cremated, my ashes taken up in a bush plane and sprinkled onto the people in town below. Let them think my body is snowflakes, sticking in their hair and on their shoulders like dandruff." -- Joseph Boyden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/568233-this-memory-this-pretty-little-stone-i-examine-it-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 16:05:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by Joseph Boyden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/568233-this-memory-this-pretty-little-stone-i-examine-it-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This memory, this pretty little stone, I examine it with my eyes closed tight. Turn it over in my fingers." -- Joseph Boyden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361705-there-s-something-sexy-in-cooking-for-a-man-who-likes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 16:05:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Doug add a quote by Joseph Boyden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361705-there-s-something-sexy-in-cooking-for-a-man-who-likes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There’s something sexy in cooking for a man who likes my food. Am I growing up?" -- Joseph Boyden]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
