<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/651378-jill]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/651378-jill" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 22:24:19 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/462036-i-saw-a-werewolf-drinking-a-pina-colada-at-trader</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 22:24:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jill add a quote by Martha Stout]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/462036-i-saw-a-werewolf-drinking-a-pina-colada-at-trader]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I saw a werewolf drinking a pina colada at Trader Vic's.  His hair was perfect." -- Martha Stout]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/848668-and-so-without-our-primordial-attachments-to-others-what-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 22:24:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jill add a quote by Martha Stout]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/848668-and-so-without-our-primordial-attachments-to-others-what-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And so without our primordial attachments to others, what would we be?
Evidently, we would be the players of a game, one that resembled a giant chess match, with our fellow human beings as the rooks, the knights, and the pawns. For this is the essence of sociopathic behavior, and desire." -- Martha Stout]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541065-as-a-counterpoint-to-sociopathy-the-condition-of-narcissism-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 22:36:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jill add a quote by Martha Stout]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541065-as-a-counterpoint-to-sociopathy-the-condition-of-narcissism-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As a counterpoint to sociopathy, the condition of narcissism is particularly interesting and instructive. Narcissism is, in a metaphorical sense, one half of what sociopathy is. Even clinical narcissists are able to feel most emotions are strongly as anyone else does, from guilt to sadness to desperate love and passion. The half that is missing is the crucial ability to understand what other people are feeling. Narcissism is a failure not of conscience but of empathy, which is the capacity to perceive emotions in others and so react to them appropriately. The poor narcissist cannot see past his own nose, emotionally speaking, and as with the Pillsbury Doughboy, any input from the outside will spring back as if nothing had happened. Unlike sociopaths, narcissists often are in psychological pain, and may sometimes seek psychotherapy. When a narcissist looks for help, one of the underlying issues is usually that, unbeknownst to him, he is alienating his relationships on account of his lack of empathy with others, and is feeling confused, abandoned, and lonely. He misses the people he loves, and is ill-equipped to get them back. Sociopaths, in contrast, do not care about other people, and so do not miss them when they are alienated or gone, except as one might regret the absence of a useful appliance that one has somehow lost." -- Martha Stout]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
