<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/651521-esther-ure]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/651521-esther-ure" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2011 14:53:14 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111166-baby-i-said-i-m-a-genius-but-nobody-knows-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2011 14:53:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111166-baby-i-said-i-m-a-genius-but-nobody-knows-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Baby,&quot; I said, &quot;I'm a genius but nobody knows it but me." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215366-i-carry-death-in-my-left-pocket-sometimes-i-take</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2011 14:53:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215366-i-carry-death-in-my-left-pocket-sometimes-i-take]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I carry death in my left pocket. Sometimes I take it out and talk to it: &quot;Hello, baby, how you doing? When you coming for me? I'll be ready." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152661-how-come-you-re-so-ugly-my-life-has-hardly-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2011 14:54:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152661-how-come-you-re-so-ugly-my-life-has-hardly-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["how come you're so ugly?&quot;

&quot;my life has hardly been pretty — the hospitals, the jails, the jobs, the women, the drinking. some of my critics claim that i have deliberately inflicted myself with pain. i wish that some of my critics had been along with me for the journey. it’s true that i haven't always chosen easy situations but that's a hell of a long ways from saying that i leaped into the oven and locked the door. hangover, the electric needle, bad booze, bad women, madness in small rooms, starvation in the land of plenty, god knows how i got so ugly, i guess it just comes from being slugged and slugged again and again, and not going down, still trying to think, to feel, still trying to put the butterfly back together again…it’s written a map on my face that nobody would ever want to hang on their wall.

sometimes i’ll see myself somewhere…suddenly…say in a large mirror in a supermarket…eyes like little mean bugs…face scarred, twisted, yes, i look insane, demented, what a mess…spilled vomit of skin…yet, when i see the “handsome” men i think, my god my god, i’m glad i’m not them" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112187-it-was-wintertime-i-was-starving-to-death-trying-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2011 14:56:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112187-it-was-wintertime-i-was-starving-to-death-trying-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was wintertime. I was starving to death trying to be a writer in New York. I hadn't eaten for three or four days. So, I finally said, &quot;I'm gonna have a big bag of popcorn.&quot; And God, I hadn't tasted food for so long, it was so good. Each kernel, you know, each one was like a steak! I chewed and it would just drop into my poor stomach. My stomach would say, &quot;THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU!&quot; I was in heaven, just walking along, and two guys happened by, and one said to the other, &quot;Jesus Christ!&quot; The other one said, &quot;What was it?&quot; &quot;Did you see that guy eating popcorn? God, it was awful!&quot; And so I couldn't enjoy the rest of the popcorn. I thought; what do you mean, &quot;it was awful?&quot; I'm in heaven here. I guess I was kinda dirty. They can always tell a fucked-up guy." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276116-he-asked-what-makes-a-man-a-writer-well-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2011 14:57:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276116-he-asked-what-makes-a-man-a-writer-well-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He asked, &quot;What makes a man a writer?&quot; &quot;Well,&quot; I said, &quot;it's simple. You either get it down on paper, or jump off a bridge." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
