<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/652191-lain]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/652191-lain" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2007 23:30:37 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7420-life-is-not-easy-for-any-of-us-but-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2007 23:30:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lain add a quote by Marie Curie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7420-life-is-not-easy-for-any-of-us-but-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is not easy for any of us. But what of that? We must have perseverance and above all confidence in ourselves. We must believe that we are gifted for something and that this thing must be attained." -- Marie Curie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35817-we-work-so-hard-to-avoid-death-because-life-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 22:30:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lain add a quote by Daniel Gottlieb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35817-we-work-so-hard-to-avoid-death-because-life-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We work so hard to avoid death because life is precious. That is why we clutch to this life so tightly. That's why we have so much anxiety, even anger, when something threatens us or our loved ones. But here's the contradiction: If you work TOO HARD to avoid death, then you're not going to have time to feel how precious life really is. You won't be able to feel it. You'll know it in your head but not in your heart." -- Daniel Gottlieb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35820-hope-is-always-about-the-future-and-it-isn-t-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 22:32:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lain add a quote by Daniel Gottlieb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35820-hope-is-always-about-the-future-and-it-isn-t-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hope is always about the future. And it isn't always good news. Sometimes, hope can imprison us with belief or expectation that something will happen in the future to change our lives. Similarly hopelessness isn't always about despair. Hopelessness can bring us right into this very moment and answer all of life's most difficult questions. Who am I? Where am I? What does this mean? And what now?" -- Daniel Gottlieb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47070-there-is-a-vitality-a-life-force-an-energy-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 13:19:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lain add a quote by Martha Graham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47070-there-is-a-vitality-a-life-force-an-energy-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a vitality, a life force, an energy, a quickening that is translated through you into action, and because there is only one of you in all of time, this expression is unique. And if you block it, it will never exist through any other medium and it will be lost. The world will not have it. It is not your business to determine how good it is nor how valuable nor how it compares with other expressions. It is your business to keep it yours clearly and directly, to keep the channel open. You do not even have to believe in yourself or your work. You have to keep yourself open and aware to the urges that motivate you. Keep the channel open. ... No artist is pleased. [There is] no satisfaction whatever at any time. There is only a queer divine dissatisfaction, a blessed unrest that keeps us marching and makes us more alive than the others" -- Martha Graham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9717-time-stands-still-best-in-moments-that-look-suspiciously-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 18:03:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lain add a quote by Brian Andreas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9717-time-stands-still-best-in-moments-that-look-suspiciously-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time stands still best in moments that look suspiciously like ordinary life." -- Brian Andreas]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
