<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/653432-kristeeeee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/653432-kristeeeee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 08:57:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/857-those-who-dream-by-day-are-cognizant-of-many-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 08:57:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristeeeee add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/857-those-who-dream-by-day-are-cognizant-of-many-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who dream by day are cognizant of many things which escape those who dream only by night." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13897-i-will-fight-with-all-the-weapons-within-my-reach</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 09:01:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristeeeee add a quote by Ernesto &quot;Che&quot; Guevara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13897-i-will-fight-with-all-the-weapons-within-my-reach]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will fight with all the weapons within my reach rather than let myself be nailed to a cross or whatever." -- Ernesto &quot;Che&quot; Guevara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96426-nothing-can-replace-the-feel-of-the-paper-against-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 14:07:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristeeeee add a quote by CrimethInc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96426-nothing-can-replace-the-feel-of-the-paper-against-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing can replace the feel of the paper against your fingers, the ink soaked up by paper, the sensation of turning a page with the wind rustling your hair, or the deliberate and intricate presentation of images and text that you can only get in the real world, on real pages. And few things can be as torturous as sitting in front of a computer screen for hours on end." -- CrimethInc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106005-for-there-is-a-growing-apprehension-that-existence-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 07:43:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristeeeee add a quote by Alan Watts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106005-for-there-is-a-growing-apprehension-that-existence-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For there is a growing apprehension that existence is a rat-race in a trap: living organisms, including people,are merely tubes which put things in at one end and let them out at the other, which both keeps them doing it and in the long run wears them out. So to keep the farce going, the tubes find ways of making new
tubes, which also put things in at one end and let them out at the other. At the input end they even develop ganglia of nerves called brains, with eyes and ears, so that they can more easily scrounge around for things to swallow. As and when they get enough to eat, they use up their surplus energy by wiggling in complicated patterns, making all sorts of noises by blowing air in and out of the input hole, and gathering together in groups to fight with other groups. In time, the tubes grow such an
abundance of attached appliances that they are hardly recognizable as mere tubes, and they manage to do this in a staggering variety of forms. There is a vague rule not to eat tubes of your own form, but in general there is serious competition as to who is going to be the top type of tube. All this seems marvelously futile, and yet, when you begin to think about it, it begins to be more marvelous than futile. Indeed, it seems extremely odd." -- Alan Watts]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
