<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/653510-sarah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/653510-sarah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 05:51:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/301542-but-there-i-was-surrendering-to-a-most-extraordinary-call</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 05:51:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/301542-but-there-i-was-surrendering-to-a-most-extraordinary-call]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But there I was, surrendering to a most extraordinary call from the grave, the mass-grave-to-be of Europe, as if somewhere ahead lay an iron gateway, slightly ajar, leading to a low and sombre country, with an incalculable crowd on sides &lt;i&gt;eager to pass into it,&lt;/i&gt; and bearing me along." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/752072-can-you-make-a-house-of-cards-she-asked-yes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 11:03:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by John Crowley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/752072-can-you-make-a-house-of-cards-she-asked-yes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Can you make a house of cards?&quot; she asked.
&quot;Yes,&quot; Violet said, and went on looking. This way Violet had of seizing first not the most obvious sense of what people said to her but some other, interior echo or reverse side of it was a thing that baffled and frustrated her husband, who sought in her sybilline responses to ordinary questions some truth he was sure Violet knew but couldn't quite enunciate. With his father-in-law's help, he had filled volumes with his searchings. Her children, though, hardly noticed it. Nora shifted from foot to foot for a moment waiting for the promised structure, and when it didn't appear forgot it. The clock on the mantelpiece chimed." -- John Crowley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/752078-almost-as-soon-as-it-was-lit-it-began-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 11:17:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by John Crowley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/752078-almost-as-soon-as-it-was-lit-it-began-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Almost as soon as it was lit it began to sound as though it were running down, but in fact it would continue to run down for a long time. He knew the feeling." -- John Crowley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1245616-n-early-every-creationist-debater-will-mention-the-second-law-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 08:40:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Donald R. Prothero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1245616-n-early-every-creationist-debater-will-mention-the-second-law-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[N]early every creationist debater will mention the second law of thermodynamics and argue that complex systems like the earth and life cannot evolve, because the second law seems to say that everything in nature is running down and losing energy, not getting more complex. But that's NOT what the second law says; every creationist has heard this but refuses to acknowledge it. The second law &lt;i&gt;only applies to closed systems&lt;/i&gt;, like a sealed jar of heated gases that gradually cools down and loses energy. But the earth is &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; a closed system -- it constantly gets new energy from the sun, and this (through photosynthesis) is what powers life and makes it possible for life to become more complex and evolve. It seems odd that the creationists continue to misuse the second law of thermodynamics when they have been corrected over and over again, but the reason is simple: it sounds impressive to their audience with limited science education, and if a snow job works, you stay with it." -- Donald R. Prothero]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
