<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/655826-micah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/655826-micah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 20:36:24 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197986-no-relationship-is-without-its-difficulties-and-this-is-certainly</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 20:36:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Micah add a quote by Daniel Tammet]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197986-no-relationship-is-without-its-difficulties-and-this-is-certainly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No relationship is without its difficulties and this is certainly true when one or both of the persons involved has an autistic spectrum disorder. Even so, I believe what is truly essential to the success of any relationship is not so much compatibility, but love. When you love someone, virtually anything is possible." -- Daniel Tammet]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199151-he-had-in-his-bronx-apartment-a-lodger-less-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2009 16:54:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Micah add a quote by Herman Wouk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199151-he-had-in-his-bronx-apartment-a-lodger-less-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He had in his Bronx apartment a lodger less learned than himself, and much fiercer in piety. One day when we were studying the laws of repentance together, the lodger burst from his room. &quot;What!&quot; he said. &quot;The atheists guzzles his whiskey and eats pork and wallows with women all his life long, and then repents the day before he dies and stands guiltless? While I spend a lifetime trying to please God?&quot; My grandfather pointed to the book. &quot;So it is written,&quot; he said gently.—&quot;Written!&quot; the lodger roared. &quot;There are books and there are books.&quot; And he slammed back into his room.

The lodger's outrage seemed highly logical. My grandfather pointed out afterward that cancelling the past does not turn it into a record of achievement. It leaves it blank, a waste of spilled years. A man had better return, he said, while time remains to write a life worth scanning. And since no man knows his death day, the time to get a grip on his life is the first hour when the impulse strikes him." -- Herman Wouk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205992-we-instinctively-feel-an-overwhelming-desire-to-take-sides-organic</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 08:48:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Micah add a quote by James McWilliams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205992-we-instinctively-feel-an-overwhelming-desire-to-take-sides-organic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We instinctively feel an overwhelming desire to take sides: organic or conventional, fair or free trade, &quot;pure&quot; or genetically engineered food, wild or farm-raised fish. Like most things in life, though, the sensible answer lies somewhere between the extremes, somewhere in that dull but respectable placed called the pragmatic center. To be a centrist when it comes to food is, unfortunately, to be a radical." -- James McWilliams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204396-oh-that-s-lovely-said-bunny-olive-you-ve-got-a-date</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 08:56:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Micah add a quote by Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204396-oh-that-s-lovely-said-bunny-olive-you-ve-got-a-date]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh that's lovely,&quot; said Bunny. &quot;Olive, you've got a date.&quot;

&quot;Why would you say something so foolish?&quot; Olive asked, really annoyed. &quot;We're two lonely people having supper.&quot;

&quot;Exactly,&quot; said Bunny. &quot;That's a date." -- Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377759-the-cosmos-extends-for-all-practical-purposes-forever-after-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 08:56:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Micah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377759-the-cosmos-extends-for-all-practical-purposes-forever-after-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Cosmos extends, for all practical purposes, forever. After a brief sedentary hiatus, we are resuming our ancient nomadic way of life. Our remote descendants, safely arrayed on many worlds throughout the Solar System and beyond, will be unified by their common heritage, by their regard for their home planet, and by the knowledge that, whatever other life may be, the only humans in all the Universe come from Earth. They will gaze up and strain to find the blue dot in their skies. They will love it no less for its obscurity and fragility. They will marvel at how vulnerable the repository of all our potential once was, how perilous our infancy, how humble our beginnings, how many rivers we had to cross before we found our way." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121616-these-were-the-lovely-bones-that-had-grown-around-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 08:56:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Micah add a quote by Alice Sebold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121616-these-were-the-lovely-bones-that-had-grown-around-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These were the lovely bones that had grown around my absence: the connections-sometimes tenuous, sometimes made at great cost, but often magnificent-that happened after I was gone. And I began to see things in a way that let me hold the world without me in it. The events that my death wrought were merely the bones of a body that would become whole at some unpredictable time in the future. The price of what I came to see as this miraculous body had been my life." -- Alice Sebold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219096-in-addition-to-its-role-in-facilitating-change-conflict-serves</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 09:29:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Micah add a quote by Jeffrey Kottler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219096-in-addition-to-its-role-in-facilitating-change-conflict-serves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In addition to its role in facilitating change, conflict serves a number of other constructive functions—as a releaser of tension, a promoter of growth, a regulator of distance between people, a path to intimacy and to personal gain, and a preventer of stagnation. The intention here is not to convince you to go looking for opportunities to argue at every turn, but rather to help you realize that what makes fighting so intolerable is the belief that it serves no useful purpose. It is extremely important when you find yourself embroiled in controversy to ask yourself what functions the conflict is serving." -- Jeffrey Kottler]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
