<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/658216-nancy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/658216-nancy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 17:23:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 17:23:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I went to the woods because I wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and see if I could not learn what it had to teach, and not, when I came to die, discover that I had not lived. I did not wish to live what was not life, living is so dear; nor did I wish to practise resignation, unless it was quite necessary. I wanted to live deep and suck out all the marrow of life, to live so sturdily and Spartan-like as to put to rout all that was not life, to cut a broad swath and shave close, to drive life into a corner, and reduce it to its lowest terms." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62173-winter-came-to-an-end-and-spring-arrived-in-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 17:24:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by Henry Orenstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62173-winter-came-to-an-end-and-spring-arrived-in-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Winter came to an end, and spring arrived, in its fully glory. I remember looking at the blooming trees and flowers and thinking of how incongruous is the beauty of nature against the ugliness of man." -- Henry Orenstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62174-let-us-be-the-ones-who-say-we-do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 17:25:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by Brad Pitt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62174-let-us-be-the-ones-who-say-we-do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let us be the ones who say we do not accept that a child dies every three seconds simply because he does not have the drugs you and I have. Let us be the ones to say we are not satisfied that your place of birth determines your right for life. Let us be outraged, let us be loud, let us be bold." -- Brad Pitt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62175-pity-can-purge-us-of-hostility-and-arouse-feelings-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 17:27:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by Richard Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62175-pity-can-purge-us-of-hostility-and-arouse-feelings-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pity can purge us of hostility and arouse feelings of identification with the characters, but it can also be a consoling reassurance which leads us to believe that we have understood, and that, in pitying, we have even done something to right a wrong." -- Richard Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62176-violence-is-a-personal-necessity-for-the-oppressed-it-is-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 17:28:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by Richard Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62176-violence-is-a-personal-necessity-for-the-oppressed-it-is-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Violence is a personal necessity for the oppressed...It is not a strategy consciously devised. It is the deep, instinctive expression of a human being denied individuality." -- Richard Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43813-the-enemy-of-the-black-is-not-the-white-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 17:47:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43813-the-enemy-of-the-black-is-not-the-white-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The enemy of the black is not the white. The enemy of capitalist is not communist, the enemy of homosexual is not heterosexual, the enemy of Jew is not Arab, the enemy of youth is not the old, the enemy of hip is not redneck, the enemy of Chicano is not gringo and the enemy of women is not men.

We all have the same enemy.

The enemy is the tyranny of the dull mind.

The enemy is every expert who practices technocratic manipulation, the enemy is every proponent of standardization and the enemy is every victim who is so dull and lazy and weak as to allow himself to be manipulated and standardized." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62426-and-also--to-add-to-my-problems--my-parents-and-relatives-kept</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 13:10:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by Victor Villasenor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62426-and-also--to-add-to-my-problems--my-parents-and-relatives-kept]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And also--to add to my problems--my parents and relatives kept telling me how they'd grown up feeling so close to the Almighty that they'd spoken to Him on a daily basis as one would speak to a friend and how, now and then, God had actually spoken back to them in the form of miracles." -- Victor Villasenor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63952-jaguars-afterall-were-fairly-common-and-so-people-were-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2008 22:08:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by Victor Villasenor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63952-jaguars-afterall-were-fairly-common-and-so-people-were-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jaguars, afterall, were fairly common, and so people were more respectful than afraid of them, just as they were of any other natural force." -- Victor Villasenor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106058-it-is-perfectly-understandable-in-a-world-where-the-media</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 10:52:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by Prunier, Gérard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106058-it-is-perfectly-understandable-in-a-world-where-the-media]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is perfectly understandable, in a world where the media shout in the same vulgar way about genocides and sexual scandals, to think that silence is the ultimate form of respect for the victims. But the danger is that this honest search for decency, paradoxically in the same way as the screaming media headlines, will end up obscuring the tragedies, turning them into chaotic convulsions in the primeval mud." -- Prunier, Gérard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106059-and-this-author-thinks-that-understanding-why-they-died-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 10:53:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by Prunier, Gérard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106059-and-this-author-thinks-that-understanding-why-they-died-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And this author thinks that understanding why they died is the best and most fitting memorial we can raise for the victims. Letting their deaths go unrecorded, or distorted by propaganda, or misunderstood through simplified clichés, would in fact bring the last touch to the killers' work in completing the victims' dehumanisation. Man is largely a social construct and to deny a man the social meaning of his death is to kill him twice, first in the flesh, then in the spirit." -- Prunier, Gérard]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
