<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/65913-tim]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/65913-tim" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 21:09:32 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/615843-ever-since-this-day-i-have-dreamt-sometimes-i-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 21:09:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by E.L. Doctorow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/615843-ever-since-this-day-i-have-dreamt-sometimes-i-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ever since this day I have dreamt sometimes... I, a street rat in my soul, dream even now... that if it were possible to life this littered, paved Manhattan from the earth... and all its torn and dripping pipes and conduits and tunnels and tracks and cables--all of it, like a scab from new skin underneath--how seedlings would sprout and freshets bubble up, and brush and grasses would grow over the rolling hills..." -- E.L. Doctorow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/836891-your-grandfather-were-a-quiet-and-secret-man-he-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 21:09:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Peter Carey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/836891-your-grandfather-were-a-quiet-and-secret-man-he-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your grandfather were a quiet and secret man he had been ripped from his home in Tipperary and transported to the prisons of Van Diemen's Land I do not know what was done to him he never spoke of it. When they had finished with their tortures they set him free and he crossed the sea to the colony of Victoria. He were by this time 30 yr. of age red headed and freckled with his eyes always slitted against the sun. My da had sworn an oath to evermore avoid the attentions of the law so when he saw the streets of Melbourne was crawling with policemen worse than flies he walked 28 mi. to the township of Donnybrook and then or soon thereafter he seen my mother. Ellen Quinn were 18 yr. old she were dark haired and slender the prettiest figure on a horse he ever saw but your grandma was like a snare laid out by God for Red Kelly. She were a Quinn and the police would never leave the Quinns alone." -- Peter Carey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706890-somehow-molly-he-heard-her-in-the-entryway-mol-molly</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 14:43:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706890-somehow-molly-he-heard-her-in-the-entryway-mol-molly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Somehow: Molly.
He heard her in the entryway. Mol, Molly, oh boy. When they were first married they used to fight. Say the most insane things. Afterward, sometimes there would be tears. Tears in bed? And then they would - Molly pressing her hot wet face against his hot wet face. They were sorry, they were saying with their bodies, they were accepting each other back, and that feeling, that feeling of being accepted back again and again, of someone's affection for you expanding to encompass whatever new flawed thing had just manifested in you, that was the deepest, dearest thing he'd ever -
She came in flustered and apologetic, a touch of anger in her face. He'd embarrassed her. He saw that. He'd embarrassed her by doing something that showed she hadn't sufficiently noticed him needing her. She'd been too busy nursing him to notice how scared he was. She was angry at him for pulling this stunt and ashamed of herself for feeling angry at him in his hour of need, and was trying to put the shame and anger behind her now so she could do what might be needed.
All of this was in her face. He knew her so well.
Also concern.
Overriding everything else in that lovely face was concern.
She came to him now, stumbling a bit on a swell in the floor of this stranger's house." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407926-it-is-said-the-sesta-is-one-of-the-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 19:53:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Ann Patchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407926-it-is-said-the-sesta-is-one-of-the-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is said the sesta is one of the only gifts the Europeans brought to South America, but I imagine the Brazilians could have figured out how to sleep in the afternoon without having to endure centuries of murder and enslavement." -- Ann Patchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/787893-i-don-t-want-to-be-a-simile-anymore-i-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 10:39:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by China Miéville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/787893-i-don-t-want-to-be-a-simile-anymore-i-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't want to be a simile anymore,' I said. &quot;I want to be a metaphor." -- China Miéville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214813-what-i-am-telling-you-before-you-begin-my-story</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2014 08:50:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Tana French]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214813-what-i-am-telling-you-before-you-begin-my-story]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I am telling you, before you begin my story, is this -- two things: I crave truth. And I lie. " -- Tana French]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
