<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/659798-jen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/659798-jen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 09:45:56 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34022-why-do-you-do-up-your-hair-in-those-tortured</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 09:45:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Angela Carter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34022-why-do-you-do-up-your-hair-in-those-tortured]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why do you do up your hair in those tortured plaits, now, Melanie? Why?
Because, she said.
You know that's no answer.  You're spoiling your pretty looks, pet.  Come here.
She did not move.  He ground out his cigarette on the window-ledge and laughed.
Come here, he said again, softly.
So she went." -- Angela Carter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44542-he-no-longer-wished-to-be-dead-at-the-same</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 06:37:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Paul Auster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44542-he-no-longer-wished-to-be-dead-at-the-same]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He no longer wished to be dead.  At the same time, it cannot be said that he was glad to be alive.  But at least he did not resent it.  He was alive, and the stubbornness of this fact had little by little begun to fascinate him - as if he had managed to outlive himself, as if he were somehow living a posthumous life." -- Paul Auster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38116-in-depression-this-faith-in-deliverance-in-ultimate-restoration-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2008 15:59:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by William Styron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38116-in-depression-this-faith-in-deliverance-in-ultimate-restoration-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In depression this faith in deliverance, in ultimate restoration, is absent. The pain is unrelenting, and what makes the condition intolerable is the foreknowledge that no remedy will come- not in a day, an hour, a month, or a minute. If there is mild relief, one knows that it is only temporary; more pain will follow. It is hopelessness even more than pain that crushes the soul. So the decision-making of daily life involves not, as in normal affairs, shifting from one annoying situation to another less annoying- or from discomfort to relative comfort, or from boredom to activity- but moving from pain to pain. One does not abandon, even briefly, one’s bed of nails, but is attached to it wherever one goes. And this results in a striking experience- one which I have called, borrowing military terminology, the situation of the walking wounded. For in virtually any other serious sickness, a patient who felt similar devistation would by lying flat in bed, possibly sedated and hooked up to the tubes and wires of life-support systems, but at the very least in a posture of repose and in an isolated setting. His invalidism would be necessary, unquestioned and honorably attained. However, the sufferer from depression has no such option and therefore finds himself, like a walking casualty of war, thrust into the most intolerable social and family situations. There he must, despite the anguish devouring his brain, present a face approximating the one that is associated with ordinary events and companionship. He must try to utter small talk, and be responsive to questions, and knowingly nod and frown and, God help him, even smile. But it is a fierce trial attempting to speak a few simple words." -- William Styron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55133-i-am-not-as-you-will-have-observed-a-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 20:42:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Patrick McGrath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55133-i-am-not-as-you-will-have-observed-a-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am not, as you will have observed, a man greatly enamored of his fellow human beings.  I do not enter lightly into the foibles and whimsicalities of others, I do not suffer fools gladly, I seem able, in conversation, only to needle or be needled.  My relationships, as a result, are few, and those few are tenuous, prickly sorts of arrangements, altogether lacking in the spontaneity and intimacy for which humans, I'm told, have an instinctive need.  I am aware of no such instincts myself.  " -- Patrick McGrath]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
