<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/659984-nick]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/659984-nick" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 16:47:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3394-i-also-think-there-are-prices-too-high-to-pay</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 16:47:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by Heinlein Robert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3394-i-also-think-there-are-prices-too-high-to-pay]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I also think there are prices too high to pay to save the United States. Conscription is one of them. Conscription is slavery, and I don't think that any people or nation has a right to save itself at the price of slavery for anyone, no matter what name it is called. We have had the draft for twenty years now; I think this is shameful. If a country can't save itself through the volunteer service of its own free people, then I say: Let the damned thing go down the drain!" -- Heinlein Robert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3396-the-wild-worship-of-lawlessness-and-the-materialist-worship-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 16:52:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nick add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3396-the-wild-worship-of-lawlessness-and-the-materialist-worship-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The wild worship of lawlessness and the materialist worship of law end in the same void. Nietzsche scales staggering mountains, but he turns up ultimately in Tibet. He sits down beside Tolstoy in the land of nothing and Nirvana. They are both helpless—one because he must not grasp anything, and the other because he must not let go of anything. The Tolstoyan’s will is frozen by a Buddhist instinct that all special actions are evil. But the Nietzscheite’s will is quite equally frozen by his view that all special actions are good; for if all special actions are good, none of them are special. They stand at the crossroads, and one hates all the roads and the other likes all the roads. The result is—well, some things are not hard to calculate. They stand at the cross-roads." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
