<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/660043-aileen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/660043-aileen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 19:14:40 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35398-romance-takes-place-in-the-middle-distance-romance-is-looking</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 19:14:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aileen add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35398-romance-takes-place-in-the-middle-distance-romance-is-looking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Romance takes place in the middle distance. Romance is looking in at yourself through a window clouded with dew. Romance means leaving things out: where life grunts and shuffles, romance only sighs." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35399-people-only-get-married-when-they-ve-no-other-option-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 19:17:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aileen add a quote by Javier Marias]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35399-people-only-get-married-when-they-ve-no-other-option-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People only get married when they've no other option, out of panic or desperation or so as not to lose someone they couldn't bear to lose.  It's always the most conventional things that contain the largest measure of madness." -- Javier Marias]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35402-if-a-man-has-committed-wrong-in-life-i-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 19:20:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aileen add a quote by William Makepeace Thackeray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35402-if-a-man-has-committed-wrong-in-life-i-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a man has committed wrong in life, I don't know any moralist more anxious to point his errors out to the world than his own relations..." -- William Makepeace Thackeray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57711-you-re-blindly-following-a-tradition-that-says-because-women-didn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 16:07:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aileen add a quote by Christi Phillips]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57711-you-re-blindly-following-a-tradition-that-says-because-women-didn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're blindly following a tradition that says because women didn't leave behind voluminous records of their thoughts and deeds, then they didn't have any thoughts and deeds - they were just standing on the sidelines while history was made by men. Just because a woman didn't have a vote doesn't mean that she didn't have an informed opinion. It doesn't mean she was incapable of thinking or acting." -- Christi Phillips]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57712-the-evil-that-is-in-the-world-almost-always-comes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 16:09:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aileen add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57712-the-evil-that-is-in-the-world-almost-always-comes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The evil that is in the world almost always comes from ignorance, and good intentions may do as much harm as malevolence if they lack understanding." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57713-a-pious-man-explained-to-his-followers-it-is-evil</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 16:13:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aileen add a quote by Amy Tan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57713-a-pious-man-explained-to-his-followers-it-is-evil]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A pious man explained to his followers: 'It is evil to take lives and noble to save them.  Each day I pledge to save a hundred lives.  I drop my net in the lake and scoop out a hundred fishes.  I place the fishes on the bank, where they flop and twirl. &quot;Don't be scared,&quot; I tell those fishes.  &quot;I am saving you from drowning.&quot;  Soon enough, the fishes grow calm and lie still.  Yet, sad to say, I am always too late.  The fishes expire.  And because it is evil to waste anything, I take those dead fishes to market and I sell them for a good price.  With the money I receive, I buy more nets so I can save more fishes." -- Amy Tan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57716-we-did-not-undertake-systematic-interviews-with-people-now-below</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 16:46:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aileen add a quote by Patricia Marchak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57716-we-did-not-undertake-systematic-interviews-with-people-now-below]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We did not undertake systematic interviews with people now below the age of thirty-five, but in many of the interviews with their parents' generation we heard a bemused recognition that younger people who did not experience these events have very little interest in what happened in that long-ago time; and may even express hostility toward parents who dreamed of a new society. They are interested in the same activities and ideas as young people the world over - dancing, loving, listening to (mostly American) music, dressing in fashion, buying the latest gadgets, attending school and developing career ambitions. The past - even though it is the immediate past of their parents - holds for them no appeal, and they have little sympathy for its victims. Consumerism, not politics, is their passion; consumption, not citizenship, motivates them." -- Patricia Marchak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57718-my-point-is-not-that-we-must-in-telling-history</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 16:56:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aileen add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57718-my-point-is-not-that-we-must-in-telling-history]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My point is not that we must, in telling history, accuse, judge, condemn Columbus in absentia.  It is too late for that; it would be a useless scholarly exercise in morality.  But the easy acceptance of atrocities as a deplorable but necessary price to pay for progress (Hiroshima and Vietnam, to save Western civilization; Kronstadt and Hungary, to save socialism; nuclear proliferation, to save us all) - that is still with us.  One reason these atrocities are still with us is that we have learned to bury them in a mass of other facts, as radioactive wastes are buried in containers in the earth.  We have learned to give them exactly the same proportion of attention that teachers and writers often give them in the most respectable classrooms and textbooks.  This learned sense of moral proportion, coming from the apparent objectivity of the scholar, is accepted more easily than when it comes from politicians at press conferences.  It is therefore more deadly.
" -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
