<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/661025-nancy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/661025-nancy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2014 08:14:15 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1046642-a-lutheran-church-in-nebraska-is-typically-a-place-where</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2014 08:14:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by Timothy Schaffert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1046642-a-lutheran-church-in-nebraska-is-typically-a-place-where]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A Lutheran church in Nebraska is typically a place where any mad passion for Christ is politely concealed. Men and women recite the various creeds in hypnotic monotone; the hymns, pumped from wheezy organ pipes, are sung with no lilt or musicality. The members of the choirs not only don't dance, they don't sway. That's not to say no one is ever smacked hard with God's love or filled up to the eyeballs with the Holy Spirit, but when you are, you keep it to yourself.&quot; (48)" -- Timothy Schaffert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1046638-i-thought-it-such-a-shame-that-our-culture-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2014 08:14:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nancy add a quote by Timothy Schaffert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1046638-i-thought-it-such-a-shame-that-our-culture-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I thought it such a shame that our culture had not devised a way to defang old age. A sophisticated civilization wouldn't ridicule senility, it would elevate it, worship it, wouldn't it? We would train ourselves to see poetry in the nonsense of dementia, to actually look forward to becoming so untethered from the world. We'd make a ceremony of casting off our material goods and confining ourselves to a single room, leaving all our old, abandoned space to someone new, someone young, so that we could die alone, indifferent to our own decay and lost beauty.&quot; (127" -- Timothy Schaffert]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
