<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/661198-lori-rader-day]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/661198-lori-rader-day" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 07:05:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32856-i-don-t-teach-writing-i-teach-patience-toughness-stubbornness-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 07:05:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Richard Bausch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32856-i-don-t-teach-writing-i-teach-patience-toughness-stubbornness-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't teach writing.  I teach patience.  Toughness.  Stubbornness.  The willingness to fail.  I teach the life.  The odd thing is most of the things that stop an inexperienced writer are so far from the truth as to be nearly beside the point.  When you feel glosbal doubt about your talent, that is your talent.  People who have no talent don't have any doubt." -- Richard Bausch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6606-running-a-close-second-as-a-writing-lesson-was-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2010 14:21:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6606-running-a-close-second-as-a-writing-lesson-was-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Running a close second [as a writing lesson] was the realization that stopping a piece of work just because it's hard, either emotionally or imaginatively, is a bad idea. Sometimes you have to go on when you don't feel like it, and sometimes you're doing good work when it feels like all you're managing is to shovel shit from a sitting position." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6604-writing-is-a-dog-s-life-but-the-only-one-worth</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 08:35:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6604-writing-is-a-dog-s-life-but-the-only-one-worth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing is a dog’s life, but the only one worth living." -- Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6605-being-in-an-m-f-a-is-like-living-in-a-sci-fi</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 08:36:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Adam Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6605-being-in-an-m-f-a-is-like-living-in-a-sci-fi]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being in an M.F.A. is like living in a sci-fi biosphere on an alien planet, where everyone shares your obscure visionary notions: namely, that literature matters, that English professors know more than other people, that typing, alone, in a library, is what everyone should be doing on a Friday night. Better to tell strangers that speaking Klingon is what turns you on." -- Adam Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6607-a-good-short-story-would-take-me-out-of-myself</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 08:36:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6607-a-good-short-story-would-take-me-out-of-myself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A good [short story] would take me out of myself and then stuff me back in, outsized, now, and uneasy with the fit." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22057-that-kind-of-thinking-that-writers-must-alleviate-their-guilt</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 08:50:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Ariel Gore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22057-that-kind-of-thinking-that-writers-must-alleviate-their-guilt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That kind of thinking [that writers must alleviate their guilt for leading a creative life] is based on the idea that the creative life is somehow self-indulgent. Artists and writers have to understand and live the truth that what we are doing is nourishing the world. William Carlos Williams said, &quot;It is difficult to get the news from poems yet men die miserably every day for lack of what is found there.&quot; You can't eat a book, right, but books have saved my life more often than sandwiches. And they've saved your life... But we don't say, oh, Maya Angelou should have silenced herself because other people have other destinies. It's interesting, because artists are always encouraged to feel guilty about their work. Why? Why don't we ask predatory bankers how they alleviate their guilt? " -- Ariel Gore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155236-a-writer-with-her-work-needs-to-be-like-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 13:38:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Dani Shapiro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155236-a-writer-with-her-work-needs-to-be-like-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A writer with her work needs to be like a dog with a bone all the time. She needs to know where she's hidden it. Where she's stored the good stuff. She needs to keep gnawing at it, even after all the meat seems to be gone. When a student of mine says (okay, whines) that she's impatient, or tired, or the worst: isn't it good enough? this may be harsh, but she loses just a little bit of my respect. Because there is no room for impatience, or exhaustion, or self-satisfaction, or laziness. All of these really mean, simply, that the inner censor has won the day." -- Dani Shapiro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20477-quite-often-somebody-will-say-what-year-do-your-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2011 13:44:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Beverly Cleary]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20477-quite-often-somebody-will-say-what-year-do-your-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Quite often somebody will say, 'What year do your books take place?' and the only answer I can give is, in childhood." -- Beverly Cleary]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446081-t-he-only-means-i-have-to-stop-ignorant-snobs-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2011 16:42:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446081-t-he-only-means-i-have-to-stop-ignorant-snobs-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...[T]he only means I have to stop ignorant snobs from behaving towards genre fiction with snobbish ignorance is to not reinforce their ignorance and snobbery by lying and saying that when I write SF it isn't SF, but to tell them more or less patiently for forty or fifty years that they are wrong to exclude SF and fantasy from literature, and proving my arguments by writing well." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1718-the-very-least-you-can-do-in-your-life-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 14:30:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1718-the-very-least-you-can-do-in-your-life-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The very least you can do in your life is figure out what you hope for. And the most you can do is live inside that hope. Not admire it from a distance but live right in it, under its roof." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30541-i-don-t-like-people-who-have-never-fallen-or-stumbled</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 11:34:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Boris Pasternak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30541-i-don-t-like-people-who-have-never-fallen-or-stumbled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't like people who have never fallen or stumbled. Their virtue is lifeless and it isn't of much value. Life hasn't revealed its beauty to them. " -- Boris Pasternak]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
