<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/662261-lindsay]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/662261-lindsay" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 08:48:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 08:48:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384301-really-being-a-librarian-is-a-much-more-dangerous-job</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2012 07:38:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384301-really-being-a-librarian-is-a-much-more-dangerous-job]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Really, being a librarian is a much more dangerous job than you realize." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233-i-don-t-know-half-of-you-half-as-well-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 09:03:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233-i-don-t-know-half-of-you-half-as-well-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know half of you half as well as I should like; and I like less than half of you half as well as you deserve." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58946-sometimes-when-i-look-at-you-i-feel-i-m-gazing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 06:46:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58946-sometimes-when-i-look-at-you-i-feel-i-m-gazing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes when I look at you, I feel I'm gazing at a distant star. 
It's dazzling, but the light is from tens of thousands of years ago.
Maybe the star doesn't even exist any more. Yet sometimes that light seems more real to me than anything." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224163-we-are-homesick-most-for-the-places-we-have-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 06:46:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Carson McCullers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224163-we-are-homesick-most-for-the-places-we-have-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are homesick most for the places we have never known." -- Carson McCullers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/634013-my-library-is-an-archive-of-longings</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 06:49:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Susan Sontag]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/634013-my-library-is-an-archive-of-longings]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My library is an archive of longings." -- Susan Sontag]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/686557-i-like-being-on-my-own-better-than-i-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 06:52:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/686557-i-like-being-on-my-own-better-than-i-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like being on my own better than I like anything else, but I can't give up love. Maybe it's the tension between longing and aloneness that I need. My own funicular railway, holding in balance the two things most likely to destroy me." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16949-a-friend-is-someone-who-knows-all-about-you-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 06:56:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16949-a-friend-is-someone-who-knows-all-about-you-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A friend is someone who knows all about you and still loves you." -- Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 06:57:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 06:59:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We accept the love we think we deserve." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 07:00:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that's what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that is holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life.  

A true soul mate is probably the most important person you'll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake.  But to live with a soul mate forever?  Nah. Too painful.  Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then leave.  

A soul mates purpose is to shake you up, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light can get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you have to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28571-if-i-had-a-flower-for-every-time-i-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 07:02:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28571-if-i-had-a-flower-for-every-time-i-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I had a flower for every time I thought of you...I could walk through my garden forever." -- Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57741-dumbledore-watched-her-fly-away-and-as-her-silvery-glow</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 07:03:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57741-dumbledore-watched-her-fly-away-and-as-her-silvery-glow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dumbledore watched her fly away, and as her silvery glow faded he turned back to Snape, and his eyes were full of tears.
&quot;After all this time?&quot;
&quot;Always,&quot; said Snape." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38436-there-s-nowhere-you-can-be-that-isn-t-where-you-re-meant</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 07:06:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38436-there-s-nowhere-you-can-be-that-isn-t-where-you-re-meant]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's nowhere you can be that isn't where you're meant to be..." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360-good-friends-good-books-and-a-sleepy-conscience-this-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 08:16:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360-good-friends-good-books-and-a-sleepy-conscience-this-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good friends, good books, and a sleepy conscience: this is the ideal life." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 21:25:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.

So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
