<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/662209-dana]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/662209-dana" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 13:23:41 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15548-the-best-attitude-to-take-toward-back-talk-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 13:23:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Gay Hendricks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15548-the-best-attitude-to-take-toward-back-talk-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best attitude to take toward back talk is to reach out and embrace it with love, compassion, and understanding.  No need to criticize it for its shortcomings or to waste time in recriminations.  Just give a loving nod and a hug to any back talk you get, and move on to the joyful creation of your fulfilled life. " -- Gay Hendricks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15551-welcome-the-back-talk-because-it-s-completely-natural-and-normal</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 13:25:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Gay Hendricks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15551-welcome-the-back-talk-because-it-s-completely-natural-and-normal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Welcome the back talk, because it's completely natural and normal. It's actually a sign that the new idea you've planted in your mind is taking root." -- Gay Hendricks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81379-the-millions-of-vacationers-who-came-here-every-year-before</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 14:10:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Billy Sothern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81379-the-millions-of-vacationers-who-came-here-every-year-before]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The millions of vacationers who came here every year before Katrina were mostly unaware of this poverty.  French Quarter tourists were rarely exposed to the reality beneath the Disneyland Gomorrah that is projected as 'N'Awlins,' a phrasing I have never heard a local use and a place, as far as I can tell, that I have never encountered despite my years in the city. The seemingly average, white, middle-class Americans whooped it up on Bourbon Street without any thought of the third-world lives of so many of the city's citizens that existed under their noses. The husband and wife, clad in khaki shorts, feather boa, and Mardi Gras beads well out of season, beheld a child tap-dancing on the street for money and clapped along to his beat without considering the obvious fact that this was an early school-day afternoon and that the child should be learning to read, not dancing for money.  Somehow they did not see their own child beneath the dancer's black visage. Nor, perhaps, did they see the crumbling buildings where the city's poor live as they traveled by cab from the French Quarter to Commander's Palace. They were on vacation and this was not their problem. " -- Billy Sothern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81381-if-people-are-troubled-by-their-view-they-ought-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 14:16:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Billy Sothern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81381-if-people-are-troubled-by-their-view-they-ought-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If people are troubled by their view, they ought to offer these New Orleanians, and black and poor people in the places like the Lower Ninth Ward around the country, a reason to believe otherwise." -- Billy Sothern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81382-i-met-two-young-guys-from-the-oregon-national-guard</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 14:34:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Billy Sothern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81382-i-met-two-young-guys-from-the-oregon-national-guard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["..I met two young guys from the Oregon National Guard... The lieutenant told me about their temporary barracks in an old neighborhood high school. He told me that he was disgusted that kids ever went to school there, and that in Oregon the place would have been bulldozed and rebuilt so that kids could have a proper place to learn. He seemed troubled that all of this was happening in America. He realized that many of the problems he was seeing in New Orleans existed before the storm, and he wanted to know why people had put up with it and why they hadn't voted out of office the people who had let this happen. I told him I didn't know, but maybe we could change things in New Orleans in the future. He seemed hopeful. I felt less certain." -- Billy Sothern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81385-i-began-speaking-first-i-took-issue-with-the-media-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 14:45:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Billy Sothern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81385-i-began-speaking-first-i-took-issue-with-the-media-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["..I began speaking.. First, I took issue with the media's characterization of the post-Katrina New Orleans as resembling the third world as its poor citizens clamored for a way out. I suggested that my experience in New Orleans working with the city's poorest people in the years before the storm had reflected the reality of third-world conditions in New Orleans, and that Katrina had not turned New Orleans into a third-world city but had only revealed it to the world as such. I explained that my work, running Reprieve, a charity that brought lawyers and volunteers to the Deep South from abroad to work on death penalty issues, had made it clear to me that much of the world had perceived this third-world reality, even if it was unnoticed by our own citizens. 

  To try answer Ryan's question, I attempted to use my own experience to explain that for many people in New Orleans, and in poor communities across the country, the government was merely an antagonist, a terrible landlord, a jailer, and a prosecutor. As a lawyer assigned to indigent people under sentence of death and paid with tax dollars, I explained the difficulty of working with clients who stand to be executed and who are provided my services by the state, not because they deserve them, but because the Constitution requires that certain appeals to be filed before these people can be killed. The state is providing my clients with my assistance, maybe the first real assistance they have ever received from the state, so that the state can kill them. 

  I explained my view that the country had grown complacent before Hurricane Katrina, believing that the civil rights struggle had been fought and won, as though having a national holiday for Martin Luther King, or an annual march by politicians over the bridge in Selma, Alabama, or a prosecution - forty years too late - of Edgar Ray Killen for the murder of civil rights workers in Philadelphia, Mississippi, were any more than gestures. Even though President Bush celebrates his birthday, wouldn't Dr. King cry if he could see how little things have changed since his death? If politicians or journalists went to Selma any other day of the year, they would see that it is a crumbling city suffering from all of the woes of the era before civil rights were won as well as new woes that have come about since. And does anyone really think that the Mississippi criminal justice system could possibly be a vessel of social change when it incarcerates a greater percentage of its population than almost any place in the world, other than Louisiana and Texas, and then compels these prisoners, most of whom are black, to work prison farms that their ancestors worked as chattel of other men? 
...
I hoped, out loud, that the post-Katrina experience could be a similar moment [to the Triangle Shirtwaist factory fiasco], in which the American people could act like the children in the story and declare that the emperor has no clothes, and hasn't for a long time. That, in light of Katrina, we could be visionary and bold about what people deserve. We could say straight out that there are people in this country who are racist, that minorities are still not getting a fair shake, and that Republican policies heartlessly disregard the needs of individual citizens and betray the common good. As I stood there, exhausted, in front of the thinning audience of New Yorkers, it seemed possible that New Orleans's destruction and the suffering of its citizens hadn't been in vain." -- Billy Sothern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39541-these-people-fail-to-realize-that-it-is-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 23:58:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39541-these-people-fail-to-realize-that-it-is-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These people fail to realize that it is on the inside that God must be defended, not on the outside. They should direct their anger at themselves. For evil in the open is but evil from within that has been let out. The main battlefield for good is not the open ground of the public arena but the small clearing of each heart." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123964-things-didn-t-turn-out-the-way-they-were-supposed-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 00:01:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123964-things-didn-t-turn-out-the-way-they-were-supposed-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things didn't turn out the way they were supposed to, but what can you do? You must take life the way it comes at you and make the best of it." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123967-you-can-get-used-to-anything---haven-t-i-already</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 00:07:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123967-you-can-get-used-to-anything---haven-t-i-already]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can get used to anything - haven't I already said that? Isn't that what all survivors say?" -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123969-high-calls-low-and-low-calls-high-i-tell-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 00:11:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123969-high-calls-low-and-low-calls-high-i-tell-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["High calls low and low calls high. I tell you, if you were in such dire straits as I was, you too would elevate your thoughts. The lower you are, the higher your mind will want to soar. " -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123970-what-a-terrible-thing-it-is-to-botch-a-farewell</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 00:16:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123970-what-a-terrible-thing-it-is-to-botch-a-farewell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a terrible thing it is to botch a farewell. I am a person who believes in form, in the harmony of order. Where we can, we must give things a meaningful shape. For example - I wonder - could you tell my jumbled story in exactly one hundred chapters, not one more, not one less? I'll tell you, that's one thing I have about my nickname, the way the number runs on forever. It's important in life to conclude things properly. Only then can you let go. Otherwise you are left with words you should have said but never did, and your heart is heavy with remorse. That bungled goodbye hurts me to this day. I wish so much that I'd had one last look at him in the lifeboat, that I'd provoked him a little, so that I was on his mind. I wish I had said to him then - yes, I know, to a tiger, but still - I wish I had said, &quot;Richard Parker, it's over. We  have survived. Can you believe it? I owe you more gratitude than I can express I couldn't have done it without you. I would like to say it formally: Richard Parker, thank you. Thank you for saving my life. And now go where you must. You have known the confined freedom of a zoo most of your life; now you will know the free confinement of a jungle. I wish you all the best with it. Watch out for Man. He is not your friend. But I hope you will remember me as a friend. I will never forget you , that is certain. You will always be with me, in my heart. What is that hiss? Ah, our boat has touched sand. So farewell, Richard Parker, farewell. God be with you." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5325-if-we-citizens-do-not-support-our-artists-then-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 00:17:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5325-if-we-citizens-do-not-support-our-artists-then-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we, citizens, do not support our artists, then we sacrifice our imagination on the altar of crude reality and we end up believing in nothing and having worthless dreams." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129095-oncoming-death-is-terrible-enough-but-worse-still-is-oncoming</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 11:08:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129095-oncoming-death-is-terrible-enough-but-worse-still-is-oncoming]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oncoming death is terrible enough, but worse still is oncoming death with time to spare, time in which all the happiness that was yours and all the happiness that might have been yours becomes clear to you. You see with utter lucidity all that you are losing." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58252-why-do-people-move-what-makes-them-uproot-and-leave</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 11:11:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58252-why-do-people-move-what-makes-them-uproot-and-leave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why do people move? What makes them uproot and leave everything they've known for a great unknown beyond the horizon? Why climb this Mount Everest of formalities that makes you feel like a beggar? Why enter this jungle of foreignness where everything is new, strange and difficult? The answer is the same the world over: people move in hope of a better life." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120628-all-living-things-contain-a-measure-of-madness-that-moves</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 11:12:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120628-all-living-things-contain-a-measure-of-madness-that-moves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All living things contain a measure of madness that moves them in strange, sometimes inexplicable ways. This madness can be saving; it is part and parcel of the ability to adapt. Without it, no species would survive." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81380-according-to-the-2003-data-from-the-u-s-census-bureau</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 11:20:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Billy Sothern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81380-according-to-the-2003-data-from-the-u-s-census-bureau]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["According to the 2003 data from the U.S. Census Bureau, 25.8 percent of [New Orleans] population lives below the poverty line... This is more than twice the national average, but is close tot he percentages in other American cities such as Miami (28.5), Los Angeles (22.1), Atlanta (24.4), and New York City (21.2). " -- Billy Sothern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/859283-and-in-my-heart-i-despised-the-life-i-led</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 17:51:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Tobias Wolff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/859283-and-in-my-heart-i-despised-the-life-i-led]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And in my heart I despised the life I led in Seattle. I was sick of it and had no idea how to change it. I thought that in Chinook, away from Taylor and Silver, away from Marian, away from people who had already made up their minds about me, I could be different. I could introduce myself as a scholar-athlete, a boy of dignity and consequence, and without any reason to doubt me people would believe I was that boy, and thus allow me to be that boy. I recognized no obstacle to miraculous change but the incredulity of others. This was an idea that died hard, if it ever really died at all." -- Tobias Wolff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158271-knowing-that-everything-comes-to-an-end-is-a-gift</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 17:52:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Tobias Wolff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158271-knowing-that-everything-comes-to-an-end-is-a-gift]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Knowing that everything comes to an end is a gift of experience, a consolation gift for knowing that we ourselves are coming to an end.  Before we get it we live in a continuous present, and imagine the future as more of that present.  Happiness is endless happiness, innocent of its own sure passing.  Pain is endless pain." -- Tobias Wolff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175711-when-we-are-green-still-half-created-we-believe-that-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 17:55:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dana add a quote by Tobias Wolff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175711-when-we-are-green-still-half-created-we-believe-that-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we are green, still half-created, we believe that our dreams are rights, that the world is disposed to act in our best interests, and that falling and dying are for quitters. We live on the innocent and monstrous assurance that we alone, of all the people ever born, have a special arrangement whereby we will be allowed to stay green forever" -- Tobias Wolff]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
