<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/662439-jo]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/662439-jo" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2008 18:51:42 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11984-most-of-us-are-called-on-to-perform-tasks-far</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2008 18:51:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by Lloyd Alexander]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11984-most-of-us-are-called-on-to-perform-tasks-far]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most of us are called on to perform tasks far beyond what we can do. Our capabilities seldom match our aspirations, and we are often woefully unprepared. To this extent, we are all Assistant Pig-Keepers at heart." -- Lloyd Alexander]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28690-aravis-also-had-many-quarrels-and-i-m-afraid-even-fights</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 18:42:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28690-aravis-also-had-many-quarrels-and-i-m-afraid-even-fights]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Aravis also had many quarrels (and, I'm afraid even fights) with Cor, but they always made it up again: so that years later, when they were grown up they were so used to quarreling and making it up again that they got married so as to go on doing it more conveniently." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6019-i-wanted-you-to-see-what-real-courage-is-instead</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 10:28:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6019-i-wanted-you-to-see-what-real-courage-is-instead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted you to see what real courage is, instead of getting the idea that courage is a man with a gun in his hand. It's when you know you're licked before you begin, but you begin anyway and see it through no matter what.
- Atticus Finch" -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28702-evil-conquered-said-gwydion-you-have-learned-much-but-learn</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 19:05:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by Lloyd Alexander]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28702-evil-conquered-said-gwydion-you-have-learned-much-but-learn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Evil conquered?' said Gwydion. 'You have learned much, but learn this last and hardest of lessons. You have conquered only the enchantments of evil. That was the easiest of your tasks, only a beginning, not an ending. Do you believe evil itself to be so quickly overcome? Not so long as men still hate and slay each other, when greed and anger goad them. Against these even a flaming sword cannot prevail, but only that portion of good in all men's hearts whose flame can never be quenched." -- Lloyd Alexander]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33882-i-will-keep-the-law-given-by-god-sanctioned-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 20:15:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33882-i-will-keep-the-law-given-by-god-sanctioned-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will keep the law given by God; sanctioned by man. Laws and principles are not for the times when there is no temptation: they are for such moments as this, when body and soul rise in mutiny against their rigour; stringent are they; inviolate they shall be. If at my individual convenience I might break them, what would be their worth?" -- Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54763-and-i-don-t-know-if-batty-s-gotten-over-it-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 20:54:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by Jeanne Birdsall]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54763-and-i-don-t-know-if-batty-s-gotten-over-it-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I don't know if Batty's gotten over it yet,' said Skye.

Mr. Penderwick looked out the window to where Batty was playing vampires with Hound. Hound was on his back, trying to wiggle out of the black towel Batty had tied around his neck. Batty was leaping over Hound's water bowl, shrieking, 'Blood, blood!'

'She looks all right,' he said." -- Jeanne Birdsall]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23295-mama-s-love-had-always-been-the-kind-that-acted-itself</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2008 14:21:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by Corrie Ten Boom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23295-mama-s-love-had-always-been-the-kind-that-acted-itself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mama's love had always been the kind that acted itself out with soup pot and sewing basket. But now that these things were taken away, the love seemed as whole as before. She sat in her chair at the window and loved us. She loved the people she saw in the street-- and beyond: her love took in the city, the land of Holland, the world. And so I learned that love is larger than the walls which shut it in. " -- Corrie Ten Boom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76585-jane-she-said-climbing-down-from-the-chair-remember-last</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2008 18:05:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by Jeanne Birdsall]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76585-jane-she-said-climbing-down-from-the-chair-remember-last]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jane,' she said, climbing down from the chair. 'Remember last year when I built that model wind tower for you and you wrote those poems for me?' 

And you said you'd never switch homework assignments with me again.'

For good reason. My teacher had a hard time believing I wrote &lt;i&gt;Tra-la the joy of tulips blooming, Ha-ha the thrill of bumblebees zooming. I'm alive and I dance, I'm alive though death is always looming. &lt;/i&gt; When I finally convinced her that I had, she asked me if I needed to talk to the school counselor." -- Jeanne Birdsall]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9467-alice-laughed-there-s-no-use-trying-she-said-one-can-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 09:35:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9467-alice-laughed-there-s-no-use-trying-she-said-one-can-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alice laughed. 'There's no use trying,' she said. 'One can't believe impossible things.'

I daresay you haven't had much practice,' said the Queen. 'When I was your age, I always did it for half-an-hour a day. Why, sometimes I've believed as many as six impossible things before breakfast. There goes the shawl again!" -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175073-i-liked-the-feeling-of-love-jonas-confessed-he-glanced</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2009 13:25:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by Lois Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175073-i-liked-the-feeling-of-love-jonas-confessed-he-glanced]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I liked the feeling of love,' [Jonas] confessed. He glanced nervously at the speaker on the wall, reassuring himself that no one was listening. 'I wish we still had that,' he whispered. 'Of course,' he added quickly, 'I do understand that it wouldn't work very well. And that it's much better to be organized the way we are now. I can see that it was a dangerous way to live.'

...'Still,' he said slowly, almost to himself, 'I did like the light they made. And the warmth." -- Lois Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62307-here-is-edward-bear-coming-downstairs-now-bump-bump-bump</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 12:26:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62307-here-is-edward-bear-coming-downstairs-now-bump-bump-bump]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here is Edward Bear, coming downstairs now, bump, bump, bump, on the back of his head, behind Christopher Robin. It is, as far as he knows, the only way of coming downstairs, but sometimes he feels that there really is another way, if only he could stop bumping for a moment and think of it. And then he feels that perhaps there isn't." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175954-i-suppose-next-time-i-come-home-i-shall-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 21:51:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by Agatha Christie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175954-i-suppose-next-time-i-come-home-i-shall-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I suppose next time I come home I shall find you wearing false moustaches—or are you doing so now?'
   Poirot winced. His moustaches had always been his sensitive point. He was inordinately proud of them. My words touched him on the raw.
   'No, no, indeed, mon ami. That day, I pray the good God, is still far off. The false moustaches!  Quelle Horreur!’
   He tugged at them vigorously to assure me of their genuine character.
   'Well, they are very luxuriant still,' I said.
   'N’est-ce pas? Never, in the whole of London, have I seen a pair of moustaches to equal mine.'
   A good job too, I thought privately." -- Agatha Christie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184163-the-only-chains-god-wants-us-to-wear-are-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2009 13:05:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by Kevin DeYoung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184163-the-only-chains-god-wants-us-to-wear-are-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only chains God wants us to wear are the chains of righteousness--not the chains of hopeless subjectivism, not the shackles of risk-free living, not the fetters of horoscope decision making--just the chains befitting a bond servant of Christ Jesus. Die to self. Live for Christ. And then do what you want, and go where you want, for God's glory." -- Kevin DeYoung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186360-if-a-rhinoceros-were-to-enter-this-restaurant-now-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2009 17:19:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186360-if-a-rhinoceros-were-to-enter-this-restaurant-now-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a rhinoceros were to enter this restaurant now, there is no denying he would have great power here. But I should be the first to rise and assure him that he had no authority whatever." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167441-imagine-a-poem-written-with-such-enormous-three-dimensional-words-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 11:35:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by N.D. Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167441-imagine-a-poem-written-with-such-enormous-three-dimensional-words-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine a poem written with such enormous three-dimensional words that we had to invent a smaller word to reference each of the big ones; that we had to rewrite the whole thing in shorthand, smashing it into two dimensions, just to talk about it. Or don’t imagine it. Look outside. Human language is our attempt at navigating God’s language; it is us running between the lines of His epic, climbing on the vowels and building houses out of the consonants." -- N.D. Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11796-i-m-on-aslan-s-side-even-if-there-isn-t-any-aslan</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2009 20:44:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11796-i-m-on-aslan-s-side-even-if-there-isn-t-any-aslan]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm on Aslan's side even if there isn't any Aslan to lead it. I'm going to live as like a Narnian as I can even if there isn't any Narnia." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58811-what-ho-i-said-what-ho-said-motty-what-ho</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 22:30:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by Wodehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58811-what-ho-i-said-what-ho-said-motty-what-ho]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What ho!&quot; I said.
&quot;What ho!&quot; said Motty.
&quot;What ho! What ho!&quot;
&quot;What ho! What ho! What ho!&quot;
After that it seemed rather difficult to go on with the conversation." -- Wodehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405597-yet-if-we-would-know-god-and-for-other-s-sake</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 21:23:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by A.W. Tozer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405597-yet-if-we-would-know-god-and-for-other-s-sake]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yet if we would know God and for other's sake tell what we know we must try to speak of his love. All Christians have tried but none has ever done it very well. I can no more do justice to that awesome and wonder-filled theme than a child can grasp a star. Still by reaching toward the star the child may call attention to it and even indicate the direction one must look to see it. So as I stretch my heart toward the high shining love of God someone who has not before known about it may be encouraged to look up and have hope." -- A.W. Tozer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5550-let-me-not-to-the-marriage-of-true-minds-admit</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 20:22:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5550-let-me-not-to-the-marriage-of-true-minds-admit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me not to the marriage of true minds 
Admit impediments. Love is not love 
Which alters when it alteration finds, 
Or bends with the remover to remove. 
O no, it is an ever-fixed mark 
That looks on tempests and is never shaken; 
It is the star to every wand'ring barque, 
Whose worth's unknown, although his height be taken. 
Love's not Time's fool, though rosy lips and cheeks 
Within his bending sickle's compass come; 
Love alters not with his brief hours and weeks, 
But bears it out even to the edge of doom. 
If this be error and upon me proved, 
I never writ, nor no man ever loved." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27777-love-of-music-of-sunsets-and-sea-a-liking-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 20:22:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27777-love-of-music-of-sunsets-and-sea-a-liking-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love of music, of sunsets and sea; a liking for the same kind of people; political opinions that are not radically divergent; a similar stance as we look at the stars and think of the marvelous strangeness of the universe - these are what build a marriage. And it is never to be taken for granted." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263668-your-question-is-the-most-difficult-in-the-world-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 12:49:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263668-your-question-is-the-most-difficult-in-the-world-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your question is the most difficult in the world. It is not a question I can answer simply with yes or no. I am not an Atheist. I do not know if I can define myself as a Pantheist. The problem involved is too vast for our limited minds. May I not reply with a parable? The human mind, no matter how highly trained, cannot grasp the universe. We are in the position of a little child, entering a huge library whose walls are covered to the ceiling with books in many different tongues. The child knows that someone must have written those books. It does not know who or how. It does not understand the languages in which they are written. The child notes a definite plan in the arrangement of the books, a mysterious order, which it does not comprehend, but only dimly suspects. That, it seems to me, is the attitude of the human mind, even the greatest and most cultured, toward God. We see a universe marvelously arranged, obeying certain laws, but we understand the laws only dimly. Our limited minds cannot grasp the mysterious force that sways the constellations. I am fascinated by Spinoza's Pantheism. I admire even more his contributions to modern thought. Spinoza is the greatest of modern philosophers, because he is the first philosopher who deals with the soul and the body as one, not as two separate things." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204561-we-re-all-a-little-weird-and-life-is-a-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 19:22:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204561-we-re-all-a-little-weird-and-life-is-a-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We’re all a little weird. And life is a little weird. And when we find someone whose weirdness is compatible with ours, we join up with them and fall into mutually satisfying weirdness—and call it love—true love." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/549476-we-know-from-myths-and-fairy-tales-that-there-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 21:31:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jo add a quote by Susan Cain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/549476-we-know-from-myths-and-fairy-tales-that-there-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We know from myths and fairy tales that there are many different kinds of powers in the world. One child is given a light saber, another a wizard's education. The trick is not to amass all the different kinds of available power, but to use well the kind you've been granted. Introverts are offered keys to private gardens full of riches. To possess such a key is to tumble like Alice down her rabbit hole. She didn't choose to go to Wonderland -- but she made of it an adventure that was fresh and fantastic and very much her own." -- Susan Cain]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
