<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/662669-vicki-tan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/662669-vicki-tan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 10:00:53 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260402-once-in-a-dream-i-saw-a-snake-swallowing-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 10:00:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vicki add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260402-once-in-a-dream-i-saw-a-snake-swallowing-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once in a dream I saw a snake swallowing its own tail, it swallowed and swallowed until it got halfway round, and there it stopped and there it stayed, it was stuffed with its own self. Some fix, that.
We only have ourselves to go on, and it’s enough…" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260403-at-loch-mor-we-walked-down-a-spongy-hill-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 10:01:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vicki add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260403-at-loch-mor-we-walked-down-a-spongy-hill-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At Loch Mor we walked down a spongy hill to a valley. The sun was dropping then dropped, leaving a sky of frilly reds. The moon appeared too soon. The valley sloped around a teardrop-shaped lake, pink with the bizarre fuchsia bursts of the late-coming sunset. Violet heather bruised the green weedy ground as we jumped down. This was a place conceived in a burst of emotion by a melancholy boy." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260404-a-question-so-what-are-people-supposed-to-do-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 10:02:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vicki add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260404-a-question-so-what-are-people-supposed-to-do-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A question.

So what are people supposed to do if they want to avoid a collision (thud!) but still lie in the field, enjoying the clouds drifting by, listening to the grass grow—not thinking, in other words? Sound hard? Not at all. Logically, it’s easy. C’est simple. The answer is dreams. Dreaming on and on. Entering the world of dreams, and never coming out. Living in dreams for the rest of time.

In dreams you don’t need to make any distinctions between things. Not at all. Boundaries don’t exist. So in dreams there are hardly any collisions. Even if there are, they don’t hurt. Reality is different. Reality bites.

Reality, reality." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260405-everybody-has-some-one-thing-they-do-not-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 10:03:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vicki add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260405-everybody-has-some-one-thing-they-do-not-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody has some one thing they do not want to lose,&quot; began the man. &quot;You included. And we are professionals at finding out that very thing. Humans by necessity must have a midway point between their desires and their pride. Just as all objects must have a center of gravity. This is something we can pinpoint. Only when it is gone do people realize it even existed." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260406-the-voice-of-the-nickly-reflection-of-the-moon-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 10:03:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vicki add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260406-the-voice-of-the-nickly-reflection-of-the-moon-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The voice of the nickly reflection of the moon was not as deep as you might expect. It was a singer’s voice, though, a tenor, one that loved itself without reservation.

“I feel time like you dream. Your dreams are jumbled. You can’t remember the order of your dreams, and when you recall them, the memories bend. Faces change. It’s all in puddles and ripples. That’s what time is for me." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260407-i-used-to-have-nightmare-about-having-petrol-poured-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 10:05:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vicki add a quote by Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260407-i-used-to-have-nightmare-about-having-petrol-poured-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I used to have nightmare about having petrol poured over me, and being set on fire, and nowadays I have nightmares that I have wooden teeth and that they are continually falling out, as if I had an infinite number of them. It seems that everyone has their own inexplicable fear to have nightmares about. We need nightmares to keep ourselves entertained, and fend off the contentment that we all fear and abhor so much." -- Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260409-all-you-have-to-do-is-wait-i-explained-sit</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 10:12:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vicki add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260409-all-you-have-to-do-is-wait-i-explained-sit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All you have to do is wait,” I explained. “Sit tight and wait for the right moment. Not try to change anything by force, just watch the drift of things. Make an effort to cast a fair eye on everything. If you do that, you just naturally know what to do. But everyone’s always too busy. They’re too talented, their schedules are too full. They’re too interested in themselves to think about what’s fair." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
