<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/662819-the-story-girl]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/662819-the-story-girl" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2008 17:47:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61423-i-know-better-than-most-people-that-a-criminal-isn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2008 17:47:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61423-i-know-better-than-most-people-that-a-criminal-isn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know better than most people that a criminal isn't always a thug in a black leather jacket with a big brand on his forehead to warn us away. Criminals sit next to us on the bus. They pack our groceries and cash our paychecks for us and teach our children. They look no different from you or me. And that's why they get away with it." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61424-remembering-is-only-a-new-form-of-suffering</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2008 17:48:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by Charles Baudelaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61424-remembering-is-only-a-new-form-of-suffering]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remembering is only a new form of suffering." -- Charles Baudelaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61425-bad-is-not-an-absolute-but-a-relative-term-ask</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2008 17:48:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61425-bad-is-not-an-absolute-but-a-relative-term-ask]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bad is not an absolute, but a relative term. Ask the robber who used the cash he stole to feed his infant; the rapist who was sexually abused as a child; the kidnapper who truly believed he was saving a life. And just because you break the law doesn't mean you have intentionally crossed the line into evil. Sometimes the line creeps up on you, and before you know it, you're standing on the other side." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22971-the-real-things-haven-t-changed-it-is-still-best-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 21:56:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by Laura Ingalls Wilder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22971-the-real-things-haven-t-changed-it-is-still-best-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The real things haven't changed.  It is still best to be honest and truthful; to make the most of what we have; to be happy with simple pleasures; and have courage when things go wrong." -- Laura Ingalls Wilder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1629-it-is-the-mark-of-an-educated-mind-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 18:39:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by Aristotle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1629-it-is-the-mark-of-an-educated-mind-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it." -- Aristotle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34350-look-at-that-sea-girls--all-silver-and-shadow-and-vision</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 21:31:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34350-look-at-that-sea-girls--all-silver-and-shadow-and-vision]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look at that sea, girls--all silver and shadow and vision of things not seen. We couldn't enjoy its loveliness any more if we had millions of dollars and ropes of diamonds." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30181-if-you-take-a-book-with-you-on-a-journey</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2013 07:59:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by Cornelia Funke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30181-if-you-take-a-book-with-you-on-a-journey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you take a book with you on a journey,&quot; Mo had said when he put the first one in her box, &quot;an odd thing happens: The book begins collecting your memories. And forever after you have only to open that book to be back where you first read it. It will all come into your mind with the very first words: the sights you saw in that place, what it smelled like, the ice cream you ate while you were reading it... yes, books are like flypaper—memories cling to the printed page better than anything else." -- Cornelia Funke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18014-the-earth-laughs-in-flowers</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 16:06:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18014-the-earth-laughs-in-flowers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The earth laughs in flowers." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/879875-i-m-going-home-to-an-old-country-farmhouse-once-green</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 17:55:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/879875-i-m-going-home-to-an-old-country-farmhouse-once-green]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’m going home to an old country farmhouse, once green, rather faded now, set among leafless apple orchards. There is a brook below and a December fir wood beyond, where I’ve heard harps swept by the fingers of rain and wind. There is a pond nearby that will be gray and brooding now. There will be two oldish ladies in the house, one tall and thin, one short and fat; and there will be two twins, one a perfect model, the other what Mrs. Lynde calls a ‘holy terror.’ There will be a little room upstairs over the porch, where old dreams hang thick, and a big, fat, glorious feather bed which will almost seem the height of luxury after a boardinghouse mattress. How do you like my picture, Phil?&quot;

&quot;It seems a very dull one,&quot; said Phil, with a grimace.

&quot;Oh, but I’ve left out the transforming thing,&quot; said Anne softly. &quot;There’ll be love there, Phil—faithful, tender love, such as I’ll never find anywhere else in the world—love that’s waiting for me. That makes my picture a masterpiece, doesn’t it, even if the colors are not very brilliant?&quot;

Phil silently got up, tossed her box of chocolates away, went up to Anne, and put her arms about her. &quot;Anne, I wish I was like you,&quot; she said soberly." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79687-we-pay-a-price-for-everything-we-get-or-take</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:55:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79687-we-pay-a-price-for-everything-we-get-or-take]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We pay a price for everything we get or take in this world; and although ambitions are well worth having, they are not to be cheaply won, but exact their dues of work and self denial, anxiety and discouragement." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440154-you-can-be-the-most-beautiful-person-in-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:57:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440154-you-can-be-the-most-beautiful-person-in-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can be the most beautiful person in the world and everybody sees light and rainbows when they look at you, but if you yourself don't know it, all of that doesn't even matter. Every second that you spend on doubting your worth, every moment that you use to criticize yourself; is a second of your life wasted, is a moment of your life thrown away. It's not like you have forever, so don't waste any of your seconds, don't throw even one of your moments away." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25777-it-is-difficult-to-make-a-man-miserable-while-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:59:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25777-it-is-difficult-to-make-a-man-miserable-while-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is difficult to make a man miserable while he feels worthy of himself and claims kindred to the great God who made him." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/798708-i-agree-with-proust-in-this-he-says-that-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 11:06:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by Gabriel Josipovici]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/798708-i-agree-with-proust-in-this-he-says-that-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I agree with Proust in this, he says, that books create their own silences in ways that friends rarely do. And the silence that grows palpable when one has finished a canto of Dante, he says, is quite different from the silence that grows palpable when one has reached the end of Oedipus at Colonus. The most terrible thing that has happened to people today, he says, is that they have grown frightened of silence. Instead of seeking it as a friend and as a source of renewal they now try in every way they can to shut it out... the fear of silence is the fear of loneliness, he says, and the fear of loneliness is the fear of silence. People fear silence, he says, because they have lost the ability to trust the world to bring about renewal. Silence for them means only the recognition that they have been abandoned... How can people find the strength to be happy if they are so terrified of silence?" -- Gabriel Josipovici]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148310-three-percent-of-all-males-are-deemed-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 16:35:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by Ann Rule]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148310-three-percent-of-all-males-are-deemed-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[". . .three percent of all males are deemed to be antisocial and without conscience, while only one percent of females seem to lack compassion for others. But the icy manipulations of that one percent are utterly fascinating. No one can be crueler than a woman without a conscience." -- Ann Rule]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607098-the-american-college-of-sports-medicine-found-that-the-productivity</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2014 14:13:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by Chalene Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607098-the-american-college-of-sports-medicine-found-that-the-productivity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The American College of Sports Medicine found that the productivity of people after exercise was an average of 65 percent higher than those who did not exercise. If I have something that's really bothering me, so much that it almost hurts my head to try to sort it out, I always find the solution in a puddle of sweat! Intense exercise is like taking a magic pill that gives you the ability to solve problems like a superhero." -- Chalene Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/769-books-are-the-quietest-and-most-constant-of-friends-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 13:19:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by Charles W. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/769-books-are-the-quietest-and-most-constant-of-friends-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are the quietest and most constant of friends; they are the most accessible and wisest of counselors, and the most patient of teachers." -- Charles W. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23452-isn-t-it-odd-how-much-fatter-a-book-gets-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 13:21:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Story Girl add a quote by Cornelia Funke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23452-isn-t-it-odd-how-much-fatter-a-book-gets-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't it odd how much fatter a book gets when you've read it several times?&quot; Mo had said...&quot;As if something were left between the pages every time you read it.  Feelings, thoughts, sounds, smells...and then, when you look at the book again many years later, you find yourself there, too, a slightly younger self, slightly different, as if the book had preserved you like a pressed flower...both strange and familiar." -- Cornelia Funke]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
