<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/66383-arthur-lewis]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/66383-arthur-lewis" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 12:01:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339655-journeys-are-the-midwives-of-thought-few-places-are-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 12:01:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arthur add a quote by Alain de Botton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339655-journeys-are-the-midwives-of-thought-few-places-are-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Journeys are the midwives of thought. Few places are more conducive to internal conversations than a moving plane, ship or train. There is an almost quaint correlation between what is in front of our eyes and the thoughts we are able to have in our heads: large thoughts at times requiring large views, new thoughts new places.  Introspective reflections which are liable to stall are helped along by the flow of the landscape. The mind may be reluctant to think properly when thinking is all it is supposed to do.

At the end of hours of train-dreaming, we may feel we have been returned to ourselves - that is, brought back into contact with emotions and ideas of importance to us. It is not necessarily at home that we best encounter our true selves. The furniture insists that we cannot change because it does not; the domestice setting keeps us tethered to the person we are in ordinary life, but who may not be who we essentially are.

If we find poetry in the service station and motel, if we are drawn to the airport or train carriage, it is perhaps because, in spite of their architectural compromises and discomforts, in spite of their garish colours and harsh lighting, we implicitly feel that these isolated places offer us a material setting for an alternative to the selfish ease, the habits and confinement of the ordinary, rooted world." -- Alain de Botton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456687-there-is-a-cult-of-ignorance-in-the-united-states</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 12:59:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arthur add a quote by Issac Asimov ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456687-there-is-a-cult-of-ignorance-in-the-united-states]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a cult of ignorance in the United States, and there has always been. The strain of anti-intellectualism has been a constant thread winding its way through our political and cultural life, nurtured by the false notion that  democracy means that 'my ignorance is just as good as your knowledge." -- Issac Asimov ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480127-happiness-ceases-to-be-a-normal-condition-of-being-alive</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 12:13:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arthur add a quote by Jean Liedloff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480127-happiness-ceases-to-be-a-normal-condition-of-being-alive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness ceases to be a normal condition of being alive, and becomes a goal." -- Jean Liedloff]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
