<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/664326-jenna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/664326-jenna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 23:57:21 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9380-a-status-not-freely-chosen-or-entered-into-by-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 23:57:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Lorraine Hansberry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9380-a-status-not-freely-chosen-or-entered-into-by-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A status not freely chosen or entered into by an individual or a group is necessarily one of oppression and the oppressed are by their nature (i.e., oppressed) forever in ferment and agitation against their condition and what they understand to be their oppressors.  If not by overt rebellion or revolution, then in the thousand and one ways they will devise with and without consciousness to alter their condition" -- Lorraine Hansberry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9384-brewster-place-became-especially-fond-of-its-colored-daughters-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 00:14:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Gloria Naylor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9384-brewster-place-became-especially-fond-of-its-colored-daughters-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Brewster Place became especially fond of its colored daughters as they milled like determined spirits among its decay, trying to make it home. Nutmeg arms leaned over windowsills, gnarled ebony legs carried groceries up double flights of steps, and saffron hands strung out wet laundry on backyard lines. Their perspiration mingled with the steam from boiling pots of smoked pork greens, and it curled on the edges of the aroma of vinegar douches and Evening in Paris cologne that drifted through the street where they stood together - hands on hips, straight-backed, round-bellied, high-behinded women who threw their heads back when they laughed and exposed strong teeth and dark gums. They cursed, badgered, worshiped, and shared their men.  Their love drove them to fling dishcloths in someone else's kitchen to help him make the rent, or to fling hot lye to help him forget that bitch behind the counter at the five-and-dime. They were hard-edged, soft-centered, brutally demanding, and easily pleased, these women of Brewster Place. They came, they went, grew up, and grew old beyond their years. Like an ebony phoenix, each in her own time and with her own season had a story." -- Gloria Naylor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11239-justification-after-all-confers-value-on-an-activity-from-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 13:57:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Stanley Fish]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11239-justification-after-all-confers-value-on-an-activity-from-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Justification, after all, confers value on an activity from a perspective outside its performance. An activity that cannot be justified is an activity that refuses to regard itself as instrumental to some larger good. The humanities are their own good. There is nothing more to say, and anything that is said – even when it takes the form of Kronman’s inspiring cadences – diminishes the object of its supposed praise." -- Stanley Fish]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
