<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/664515-patricia]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/664515-patricia" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 12:00:52 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125244-as-long-as-you-have-a-garden-you-have-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 12:00:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125244-as-long-as-you-have-a-garden-you-have-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As long as you have a garden you have a future and as long as you have a future you are alive." -- Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104408-he-turned-and-looked-at-the-boy-maybe-he-understood</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 12:26:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104408-he-turned-and-looked-at-the-boy-maybe-he-understood]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He turned and looked at the boy. Maybe he understood for the first time that to the boy he was himself an alien. A being from a planet that no longer existed. The tales of which were suspect. He could not construct for the child's pleasure the world he'd lost without constructing the loss as well and he thought perhaps the child  had known this better than he. He tried to remember the dream but he could not. All that was left was the feeling of it. He thought perhaps they'd come to warn him. Of what? That he could not enkindle in the heart of the child what was ashes in his own. Even now some part of him wished they'd never found this refuge. Some part of him always wished it to be over." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130992-on-the-tv-screen-right-now-it-s-1975-and-jimmy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2009 07:17:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Dan Kennedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130992-on-the-tv-screen-right-now-it-s-1975-and-jimmy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the TV screen right now, it's 1975, and Jimmy Page is playing like a man who answers to nobody.  A man existing in that seductive state of extended adolescence that rock legends bask in, a man connected to something in the universe larger than even the sum total of the legendary Led Zeppelin, playing guitar because that is so clearly what he was put here to do.  And it's wrong to expect that kind of divine moment to last forever, and to expect an artist to stay in 1975.  Fact is, ten minutes ago I saw the guy onscreen right downstairs, coming off the trading floor of the stock exchange with a banker carrying his guitar cases for him.  I sit cross-legged on the floor on a workday staring into my cereal bowl, thinking about how we all change.  We all grow up.  We all move on, one way or another, whether we want to or not." -- Dan Kennedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135672-i-failed-to-understand-what-was-so-enviable-about-having</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2009 09:02:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Pete Jordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135672-i-failed-to-understand-what-was-so-enviable-about-having]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I failed to understand what was so enviable about having a position that a pack of phonies sucked up to.  Dishwashing suited me because nice people were nice to me and assholes were assholes to me, yet no one ever sucked up to me." -- Pete Jordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138407-expanding-your-notion-of-fun-beyond-a-two-week-vacation-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2009 06:38:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Karen Karbo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138407-expanding-your-notion-of-fun-beyond-a-two-week-vacation-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Expanding your notion of fun beyond a two-week vacation in Maui increases the chances you'll have more of it." -- Karen Karbo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167499-did-he-really-want-to-know-that-at-any-given</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2009 07:35:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Alisa Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167499-did-he-really-want-to-know-that-at-any-given]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did he really want to know?  That at any given moment I see everyday life as only _this big_, the space between my finger and thumb.  The rest of my mind is occupied with five, a dozen, three dozen other potential lives, each representing some opportunity never taken or currently within reach.  Without those worlds of possibility, my life immediately begins to seem boring and drab.  I'm thirty-three years old, always broke, and merely _existing_ in what, without having been sealed by formal wedding vows, had become a traditional marriage.  I had no blues to lament, not really.  My only drama was in my daydreams. They reminded me that any day, at any moment, I could change everything, and while many of those alternate lives featured James at my side--the truth was that some of them did not." -- Alisa Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167500-way-back-when-i-was-four-i-became-increasingly-sickly</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2009 07:39:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Alisa Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167500-way-back-when-i-was-four-i-became-increasingly-sickly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Way back when I was four, I became increasingly sickly and spiritless.  My mother took me to the doctor, who poked and prodded and deliberated.  In the end, he pronounced, &quot;She's depressed.&quot;  Depressed at four years old.  Why?  No one had an answer....I have long evaded the real reasons for my discontentment.  I still can't tell what they are, precisely, but I feel their presence most acutely in moments like this one with my grandmother, imagining a day in a big-box store that had replaced an old farm." -- Alisa Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170295-she-assumes-that-skill-will-guide-her-fingertips-that-shapely</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 07:12:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170295-she-assumes-that-skill-will-guide-her-fingertips-that-shapely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She assumes that skill will guide her fingertips, that shapely lines will uncoil out of the pencil the moment she starts.  Surely talent is a thing curled deep inside, just waiting to be exercised, and at the slightest invitation it will stretch, shake itself, make itself known?

Talent, it seems, is not so insistent." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191903-truely-was-a-mississippi-boy-still-he-didn-t-have-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 16:33:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Nanci Kincaid]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191903-truely-was-a-mississippi-boy-still-he-didn-t-have-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Truely was a Mississippi boy still.  He didn't have a thing against religion, especially in the gentle hands of somebody like his daddy--or his mother either.  But he wasn't too much persuaded when salvation was fired out of a double-barrel shotgun aimed point-blank at his skull." -- Nanci Kincaid]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191904-unlike-some-of-his-buddies-truely-had-never-been-afraid</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 16:39:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Nanci Kincaid]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191904-unlike-some-of-his-buddies-truely-had-never-been-afraid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Unlike some of his buddies, Truely had never been afraid of books.  Following his daddy's example, he had read the newspaper every day of his life since the sixth grade, starting with the sports page.  He had a vague idea what was going on in the world.  It was true that Truely could generally nail a test, took a certain pride in it, but he was also a guy who like to dance all night to throbbing music in makeshift clubs off unlit country roads.  He liked to drink a cold beer on a hot day, maybe a flask of Jack Daniel's on special occasions.  He wore his baseball cap backwards, his jeans ripped and torn--because they were old and practically worn-out, not because he bought them that way. His hair was a little too long, his boots a little too big, his aspirations modest.  He preferred listening to talking--and wasn't all that great at either.  He like barbecue joints more than restaurants.  Catfish and hush puppies or hot dogs burned black over a campfire were his favorites. He preferred simple food dished out in large helpings.  He liked to serve himself and go for seconds." -- Nanci Kincaid]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193145-when-you-are-a-high-school-girl-there-is-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 20:06:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193145-when-you-are-a-high-school-girl-there-is-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you are a high school girl, there is nothing more miraculous than a high school boy." -- Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193146-but-the-truth-was-that-i-didn-t-want-to-stay</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 20:09:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193146-but-the-truth-was-that-i-didn-t-want-to-stay]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the truth was that I didn't want to stay in Riley.  The pulls of familial love and obligation could not, for the moment, compete with the promise of early-relationship sex.  Starlight and beer and our twisting, naked bodies--that was what I wanted, not a seat at a dining room table with two old women eating breaded veal cutlets and Vienna torte." -- Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193148-i-noticed-then-that-the-red-haired-woman-was-buying-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 20:14:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193148-i-noticed-then-that-the-red-haired-woman-was-buying-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I noticed then that the red-haired woman was buying the food you eat when you live alone: a box of cereal, a few apples, a plastic container of plain yogurt....With an abrupt clarity, I saw how I had been launched into another category.  I had been the red-haired woman; for a decade of my adult life, I had bought cereal and yogurt, I'd stood near couples and watched them nuzzle, and now I was part of such a couple.  And I would not be launched back, I was certain. But I recognized her life, I knew it so well!  I wanted to clasp her freckled hand, to say to her--surely we understood some shared code (or surely not, surely she'd have thought me preposterous)--It's good on the other side, but it's good on your side too.  Enjoy it there.  The loneliness is harder and the loneliness is the biggest part; but some things are easier." -- Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193149-well---my-mother-paused-and-her-tone-was-reflective-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 20:16:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193149-well---my-mother-paused-and-her-tone-was-reflective-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well--&quot; My mother paused, and her tone was reflective in that way that is inevitably sad, because the past is sad. &quot;What I remember,&quot; she said, &quot;is that you were always such a dear little girl." -- Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214080-she-left-for-the-mercury-but-i-stayed-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2009 16:20:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Robert Kaplow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214080-she-left-for-the-mercury-but-i-stayed-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She left for the Mercury, but I stayed on the roof for a while.  I breathed in the city: its warming wind, its noise.  And I was one young man on a roof who had just spent the night with a beautiful woman...and the sunlight suggested winter and hard days to come, but we would all survive somehow, and the seasons were bigger than any of us anyway--and we were all tumbling along on the breeze of something enormous and eternal and gloriously busy." -- Robert Kaplow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218571-people-left-a-lot-of-things-behind-when-they-went</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 18:59:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Ann Brashares]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218571-people-left-a-lot-of-things-behind-when-they-went]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People left a lot of things behind when they went in the water.  Their clothes, their stuff, their makeup, their fixed-up hair, their voices, their hearing, their sight--at least as they normally experienced them....Some people lost their individuality in the water, but Riley always felt most herself.  Water was supposed to symbolize renewal, she knew, but when Riley swam, pared down, alone, and unreachable--she felt a deeper sense of who she already was." -- Ann Brashares]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218572-i-hated-motorcycles-i-said-to-my-mother-i-ll-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 19:02:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Ann Brashares]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218572-i-hated-motorcycles-i-said-to-my-mother-i-ll-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hated motorcycles.  I said to my mother, 'I'll never get a motorcycle.' And she said, 'You never know what you'll want when you are older.'

After that, the thing that scared me was not so much the motorcycle itself, but that I could turn into a person who would want one.  I was scared of the idea that I could become an entirely different person, a stranger to myself." -- Ann Brashares]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357763-the-tea-ritual-such-a-precise-repetition-of-the-same</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 07:56:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Muriel Barbery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357763-the-tea-ritual-such-a-precise-repetition-of-the-same]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The tea ritual:  such a precise repetition of the same gestures and the same tastes; accession to simple,authentic and refined sensations, a license given to all, at little cost, to become aristocrats of taste, because tea is he beverage of the wealthy and of the poor; the tea ritual, therefore, has the extraordinary virtue of introducing into the absurdity of our lives an aperture of serene harmony." -- Muriel Barbery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417480-the-following-afternoon-alone-in-their-room-and-oppressed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 18:01:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417480-the-following-afternoon-alone-in-their-room-and-oppressed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The following afternoon, alone in their room, and oppressed by not yet having made the promised call to Connie..." -- Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417481-they-gathered-not-in-anger-but-in-celebration-of-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 18:03:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417481-they-gathered-not-in-anger-but-in-celebration-of-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They gathered not in anger but in celebration of their having found, as a generation, a gentler and more respectful way of being.  A way, not incidentally, more in harmony with consuming." -- Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417483-well-and-that-s-what-really-counts-isn-t-it-i-ve-become</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 18:05:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417483-well-and-that-s-what-really-counts-isn-t-it-i-ve-become]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, and that's what really counts, isn't it?  I've become one of those women who put a ton of work into looking OK.  If I can just go on and make a beautiful corpse, I'll have the whole problem pretty well licked." -- Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/342200-he-became-another-data-point-in-the-american-experiment-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 18:07:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/342200-he-became-another-data-point-in-the-american-experiment-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He became another data point in the American experiment of self-government, an experiment statistically skewed from the outset, because it wasn't the people with sociable genes who fled the crowded Old World for the new continent; it was the people who didn't get along well with others." -- Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417486-he-had-three-ancient-candy-thermometers-whose-metal-casings-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 18:09:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417486-he-had-three-ancient-candy-thermometers-whose-metal-casings-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He had three ancient candy thermometers whose metal casings were shaped like fraternity paddles and whose nature it was to show no increase in temperature for several hours and the, and all at once and all together, to register temperatures at which fudge burned and toffee hardened like epoxy." -- Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417487-why-the-conservatives-who-controlled-all-three-branches-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 18:14:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417487-why-the-conservatives-who-controlled-all-three-branches-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why the conservatives, who controlled all three branches of the federal government, were still so enraged--at respectful skeptics of the Iraq War, at gay couples who wanted to get married, at bland Al Gore and cautious Hillary Clinton, at endangered species and their advocates, at taxes and gas prices that were among the lowest of any industrialized nation, at a mainstream media whose corporate owners were themselves conservatives, at the Mexicans who cut their grass and washed their dishes--was somewhat mysterious to Walter." -- Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/421671-it-was-a-good-speech-but-the-reaction-was-due</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 18:03:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Mark Helprin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/421671-it-was-a-good-speech-but-the-reaction-was-due]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was a good speech, but the reaction was due to the fact that politics are madness, and even if one does not know it, a country in electoral season experiences flares of lunacy like the great storms that sometimes march across the golden surface of the sun." -- Mark Helprin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296683-kizzy-wanted-to-be-a-woman-who-would-dive-off</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 19:52:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Laini Taylor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296683-kizzy-wanted-to-be-a-woman-who-would-dive-off]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kizzy wanted to be a woman who would dive off the prow of a sailboat into the sea, who would fall back in a tangle of sheets, laughing, and who could dance a tango, lazily stroke a leopard with her bare foot, freeze an enemy's blood with her eyes, make promises she couldn't possibly keep, and then shift the world to keep them. She wanted to write memoirs and autograph them at a tiny bookshop in Rome, with a line of admirers snaking down a pink-lit alley. She wanted to make love on a balcony, ruin someone, trade in esoteric knowledge, watch strangers as coolly as a cat. She wanted to be inscrutable, have a drink named after her, a love song written for her, and a handsome adventurer's small airplane, champagne-christened Kizzy, which would vanish one day in a windstorm in Arabia so that she would have to mount a rescue operation involving camels, and wear an indigo veil against the stinging sand, just like the nomads.
Kizzy wanted." -- Laini Taylor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/556648-though-his-classmates-supposedly-hailed-form-all-fifty-states-guam</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 09:05:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Chad Harbach]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/556648-though-his-classmates-supposedly-hailed-form-all-fifty-states-guam]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Though his classmates supposedly hailed form &quot;all fifty states, Guam, and twenty-two foreign lands,&quot; as President Affenlight said in his convocation address, they all seemed to Henry to come from the same close-knit high school, or at least to have attended some crucial orientation session he'd missed.  They traveled in large packs, constantly texting the other packs, and when two packs converged there was always a tremendous amount of hugging and kissing on the cheek." -- Chad Harbach]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/556649-henry-had-never-felt-so-happy-freshperson-year-had-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 09:09:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Chad Harbach]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/556649-henry-had-never-felt-so-happy-freshperson-year-had-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Henry had never felt so happy.  Freshperson year had been one thing, an adventure, an exhilaration, all in all a success, but it had also been exhausting, a constant struggle and adjustment and tumult.  Now he was locked in.  Every day that summer had the same framework, the alarm at the same time, meals and workouts and shifts and SuperBoost at the same times, over and over, and it was that sameness, that repetition, that gave life meaning.  He savored the tiny variations, the incremental improvements--tuna fish on his salad instead of turkey; tow extra reps on the bench press.  Every move he made had purpose." -- Chad Harbach]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/556654-opentoe-college-had-some-sort-of-evangelical-mission-that-involved</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 09:13:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Chad Harbach]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/556654-opentoe-college-had-some-sort-of-evangelical-mission-that-involved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Opentoe College had some sort of evangelical mission that involved perpetual kindness and hopelessly outdated uniforms. The Harpooners hated them for it.  It was unspeakably infuriating that the one school in the UMSCAC that spent less money on its baseball program than Westish always managed to kick their ass.  The Opentoe players never talked even the mildest forms of smack.  If you worked a walk, the first baseman would say, &quot;Good eye.&quot;  If you ripped a three-run triple, the third baseman would say, &quot;Nice rip.&quot; They smiled when they were behind, and when they were ahead they looked pensive and slightly sad.  Their team name was the Holy Poets." -- Chad Harbach]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/556659-baseball-was-an-art-but-to-excel-at-it-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 09:18:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patricia add a quote by Chad Harbach]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/556659-baseball-was-an-art-but-to-excel-at-it-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Baseball was an art, but to excel at it you had to become a machine.  It didn't matter how beautifully you performed _sometimes_, what you did on your best day, how many spectacular plays you made.  You weren't a painter or a writer--you didn't work in private and discard your mistakes, and it wasn't just your masterpieces that counted.  What mattered, as for any machine, was repeatability.  Moments of inspiration were nothing compared to elimination of error.  The scouts cared little for Henry's superhuman grace; insofar as they cared they were suckered-in aesthetes and shitty scouts.  Can you perform on demand, like a car, a furnace, a gun?  Can you make that throw one hundred times out of a hundred? If it can't be a hundred, it had better be ninety-nine." -- Chad Harbach]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
