<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/664567-aria]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/664567-aria" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 19:13:12 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3806-his-philosophy-was-a-mixture-of-three-famous-schools---</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 19:13:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aria add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3806-his-philosophy-was-a-mixture-of-three-famous-schools---]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His philosophy was a mixture of three famous schools -- the Cynics, the Stoics and the Epicureans -- and summed up all three of them in his famous phrase, 'You can't trust any bugger further than you can throw him, and there's nothing you can do about it, so let's have a drink." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73022-the-battlefields-where-the-dice-of-world-history-have-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 19:13:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aria add a quote by Goran Schildt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73022-the-battlefields-where-the-dice-of-world-history-have-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The battlefields where the dice of world history have been thrown can never be ordinary fields again and no god from a vanished civilization is so dead that he does not live on in his ruined temple." -- Goran Schildt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73023-no-there-s-going-to-be-no-even-tenor-with-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 19:13:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aria add a quote by Richard Halliburton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73023-no-there-s-going-to-be-no-even-tenor-with-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No, there's going to be no even tenor with me. The more uneven it is the happier I shall be. And when my time comes to die, I'll be able to die happy, for I will have done and seen and heard and experienced all the joy, pain, thrills — every emotion that any human ever had — and I'll be especially happy if I am spared a stupid, common death in bed." -- Richard Halliburton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39926-in-great-deeds-something-abides-on-great-fields-something-stays</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 19:13:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aria add a quote by Joshua Lawrence Chamberlain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39926-in-great-deeds-something-abides-on-great-fields-something-stays]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In great deeds, something abides. On great fields, something stays. Forms change and pass; bodies disappear; but spirits linger, to consecrate ground for the vision-place of souls… generations that know us not and that we know not of, heart-drawn to see where and by whom great things were suffered and done for them, shall come to this deathless field, to ponder and dream; and lo! the shadow of a mighty presence shall wrap them in its bosom, and the power of the vision pass into their souls." -- Joshua Lawrence Chamberlain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9787-i-have-heard-there-are-troubles-of-more-than-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 19:13:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aria add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9787-i-have-heard-there-are-troubles-of-more-than-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have heard there are troubles of more than one kind. Some come from ahead and some come from behind. But I've bought a big bat. I'm all ready you see. Now my troubles are going to have troubles with me!" -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213722-learn-to-like-what-doesn-t-cost-much-learn-to-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 13:22:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aria add a quote by Lowell Bennion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213722-learn-to-like-what-doesn-t-cost-much-learn-to-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Learn to like what doesn't cost much.
Learn to like reading, conversation, music.
Learn to like plain food, plain service, plain cooking.
Learn to like fields, trees, brooks, hiking, rowing, climbing hills.
Learn to like people, even though some of them may be different...different from you.
Learn to like to work and enjoy the satisfaction doing your job as well as it can be done.
Learn to like the song of birds, the companionship of dogs.
Learn to like gardening, puttering around the house, and fixing things.
Learn to like the sunrise and sunset, the beating of rain on the roof and windows, and the gentle fall of snow on a winter day.
Learn to keep your wants simple and refuse to be controlled by the likes and dislikes of others." -- Lowell Bennion]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
