<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/664997-tena]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/664997-tena" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 14:49:32 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200442-the-worst-part-of-holding-the-memories-is-not-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 14:49:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tena add a quote by Lois Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200442-the-worst-part-of-holding-the-memories-is-not-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worst part of holding the memories is not the pain. It's the loneliness of it. Memories need to be shared." -- Lois Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62064-the-man-that-i-named-the-giver-passed-along-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 14:50:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tena add a quote by Lois Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62064-the-man-that-i-named-the-giver-passed-along-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man that I named the Giver passed along to the boy knowledge, history, memories, color, pain, laughter, love, and truth.  Every time you place a book in the hands of a child, you do the same thing.  It is very risky.  But each time a child opens a book, he pushes open the gate that separates him from Elsewhere.  It gives him choices.  It gives him freedom.  Those are magnificent, wonderfully unsafe things.

[from her Newberry Award acceptance speech]" -- Lois Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100460-it-is-much-easier-to-be-brave-if-you-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 14:50:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tena add a quote by Lois Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100460-it-is-much-easier-to-be-brave-if-you-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is much easier to be brave if you do not know everything." -- Lois Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242875-we-re-all-on-our-own-aren-t-we-that-s-what-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 14:54:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tena add a quote by Lois Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242875-we-re-all-on-our-own-aren-t-we-that-s-what-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're all on our own, aren't we? That's what it boils down to. 

We come into this world on our own- in Hawaii, as I did, or New York, or China, or Africa or Montana- and we leave it in the same way, on our own, wherever we happen to be at the time- in a plane, in our beds, in a car, in a space shuttle, or in a  field of flowers. 

And between those times, we try to connect along the way with others who are also on their own. 

If we're lucky, we have a mother who reads to us. 

We have a teacher or two along the way who make us feel special. 

We have dogs who do the stupid dog tricks we teach them and who lie on our bed when we're not looking, because it smells like us, and so we pretend not to notice the paw prints on the bedspread. 

We have friends who lend us their favorite books. 

Maybe we have children, and grandchildren, and funny mailmen and eccentric great-aunts, and uncles who can pull pennies out of their ears.

   All of them teach us stuff. They teach us about combustion engines and the major products of Bolivia, and what poems are not boring, and how to be kind to each other, and how to laugh, and when the vigil is in our hands, and when we have to make the best of things even though it's hard sometimes.

    Looking back together, telling our stories to one another, we learn how to be on our own." -- Lois Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411663-then-recalling-what-he-had-said-she-turned-to-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 14:56:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tena add a quote by Lois Lowry (Author)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411663-then-recalling-what-he-had-said-she-turned-to-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then, recalling what he had said, she turned to him eagerly. “What’s my surprise?”

Most Ancient turned and reached for something that was behind him. He picked it up and placed it in her arms, and it looked up at her with wide, curious eyes. It was what she had once been: tiny, a wisp of a thing, with a mischievous smile and a trusting, visible heart.

“Oh!” she cried. She hugged it to her, against her badge. “What’s its name?”

“Ask it,” Most Ancient suggested.

“Who are you?” she asked the diminutive, transparent creature in her arms, keeping her voice calm so that it wouldn’t be scared.

“New Littlest,” it told her.

She was puzzled and almost frightened at first. The she thought, Of course! Most Ancient could not have always have been Most Ancient, and Thin Elderly must once have been something else. Even Fastidious – well, maybe not. Perhaps she had always been Fastidious.

She cradled New Littlest, moving her hands as gently as possible around the fragile little thing, and turned back to ask Most Ancient what she needed to know.

“Who am I now?”

“Gossamer,” he told her." -- Lois Lowry (Author)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5504-once-you-have-tasted-flight-you-will-forever-walk-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 12:37:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tena add a quote by Leonardo da Vinci]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5504-once-you-have-tasted-flight-you-will-forever-walk-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once you have tasted flight, you will forever walk the earth with your eyes turned skyward, for there you have been, and there you will always long to return." -- Leonardo da Vinci]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
