<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/665193-maureen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/665193-maureen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 06:29:07 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405909-teenagers-read-millions-of-books-every-year-they-read-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 06:29:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Sherman Alexie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405909-teenagers-read-millions-of-books-every-year-they-read-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Teenagers read millions of books every year. They read for entertainment and for education. They read because of school assignments and pop culture fads.
&lt;p&gt;
 And there are millions of teens who read because they are sad and lonely and enraged. They read because they live in an often-terrible world. They read because they believe despite the callow protestations of certain adults that books-especially the dark and dangerous ones-will save them." -- Sherman Alexie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122956-suffering-does-not-ennoble-it-destroys-to-resist-destruction</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 04:37:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Dorothy Allison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122956-suffering-does-not-ennoble-it-destroys-to-resist-destruction]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["... suffering does not ennoble. It destroys. To resist destruction, self-hatred, or lifelong hopelessness, we have to throw off the conditioning of being despised, the fear of becoming the they that is talked about so dismissively, to refuse lying myths and easy moralities, to see ourselves as human, flawed, and extraordinary. All of us extraordinary" -- Dorothy Allison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/337202-why-write-stories-to-join-the-conversation</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 04:40:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Dorothy Allison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/337202-why-write-stories-to-join-the-conversation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why write stories? To join the conversation." -- Dorothy Allison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/698412-the-qualities-that-make-for-excellence-in-children-s-literature-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 19:23:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Maurice Sendak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/698412-the-qualities-that-make-for-excellence-in-children-s-literature-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The qualities that make for excellence in children's literature can be summed up in a single word: imagination. And imagination as it relates to the child is, to my mind, synonymous with fantasy. Contrary to most of the propaganda in books for the young, childhood is only partly a time of innocence. It is, in my opinion, a time of seriousness, bewilderment, and a good deal of suffering. It's also possibly the best of all times. Imagination for the child is the miraculous, freewheeling device he uses to course his way through the problems of every day....It's through fantasy that children achieve catharsis." -- Maurice Sendak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/710239-before-the-bat-could-answer-the-mockingbird-exclaimed-angrily-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 07:13:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Randall Jarrell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/710239-before-the-bat-could-answer-the-mockingbird-exclaimed-angrily-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Before the bat could answer, the mockingbird exclaimed angrily: &quot;You sound as if there were something wrong with imitating things!&quot;

&quot;Oh no,&quot; the bat said.

&quot;Well then, you sound as if there something wrong with driving them off. It's my territory, isn't it? If you can't drive things off your own territory what can you do?&quot;

The bat didn't know what to say; after a minute the chipmunk said uneasily, &quot;He just meant it's odd to drive them all off and then imitate them so well too.&quot;

&quot;Odd!&quot; cried the mockingbird. &quot;Odd! If I didn't it really would be odd. Did you ever hear of a mockingbird that didn't?&quot;

The bat said politely, &quot;No indeed. No, it's just what mockingbirds do do. That's really why I made up the poem about it--I admire mockingbirds so much, you know.&quot;

The chipmunk said, &quot;He talks about them all the time.&quot;

&quot;A mockingbird's sensitive,&quot; said the mockingbird; when he said sensitive his voice went way up and way back down. &quot;They get on my nerves. You just don't understand how much they get on my nerves. Sometimes I think if I can't get rid of them I'll go crazy.&quot;

&quot;If they didn't get on your nerves so, maybe you wouldn't be able to imitate them so well, the chipmunk said in a helpful, hopeful voice." -- Randall Jarrell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/519525-in-my-old-age-i-see-that-life-is-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 06:04:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Eowyn Ivey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/519525-in-my-old-age-i-see-that-life-is-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In my old age, I see that life is often more fantastic and terrible than stories we believed as children, and that perhaps there is no harm in finding magic among the trees." -- Eowyn Ivey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131294-i-can-t-go-back-to-yesterday-because-i-was-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 05:30:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131294-i-can-t-go-back-to-yesterday-because-i-was-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can't go back to yesterday because I was a different person then." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10111-we-don-t-need-a-list-of-rights-and-wrongs-tables</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 09:50:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10111-we-don-t-need-a-list-of-rights-and-wrongs-tables]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don’t need a list of rights and wrongs, tables of dos and don’ts: we need books, time, and silence. &lt;I&gt;Thou shalt not&lt;/I&gt; is soon forgotten, but &lt;I&gt;Once upon a time&lt;/I&gt; lasts forever." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/495172-kiss-me-hardy-kiss-me-quick</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 08:50:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Elizabeth Wein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/495172-kiss-me-hardy-kiss-me-quick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["KISS ME, HARDY! Kiss me, QUICK!" -- Elizabeth Wein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258846-life-s-a-freaking-mess-in-fact-i-m-going-to-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 14:25:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Jandy Nelson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258846-life-s-a-freaking-mess-in-fact-i-m-going-to-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life's a freaking mess. In fact, I'm going to tell Sarah we need to start a new philosophical movement: messessentialism instead of existentialism: For those who revel in the essential mess that is life. Because Gram's right, there's not one truth ever, just a bunch of stories, all going on at once, in our heads, in our hearts, all getting in the way of each other. It's all a beautiful calamitous mess. It's like the day Mr. James took us into the woods and cried triumphantly, &quot;That's it! That's it!&quot; to the dizzying cacophony of soloing instruments trying to make music together. That is it." -- Jandy Nelson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/817534-i-wanted-a-perfect-ending-now-i-ve-learned-the-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 07:52:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Gilda Radner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/817534-i-wanted-a-perfect-ending-now-i-ve-learned-the-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted a perfect ending. Now I've learned, the hard way, that some poems don't rhyme, and some stories don't have a clear beginning, middle, and end." -- Gilda Radner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20171-there-are-three-rules-for-writing-a-novel-unfortunately-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 08:26:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20171-there-are-three-rules-for-writing-a-novel-unfortunately-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are three rules for writing a novel. Unfortunately, no one knows what they are." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315932-once-a-little-boy-sent-me-a-charming-card-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 08:36:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Maurice Sendak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315932-once-a-little-boy-sent-me-a-charming-card-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once a little boy sent me a charming card with a little drawing on it. I loved it. I answer all my children’s letters — sometimes very hastily — but this one I lingered over. I sent him a card and I drew a picture of a Wild Thing on it. I wrote, “Dear Jim: I loved your card.” Then I got a letter back from his mother and she said, “Jim loved your card so much he ate it.” That to me was one of the highest compliments I’ve ever received. He didn’t care that it was an original Maurice Sendak drawing or anything. He saw it, he loved it, he ate it." -- Maurice Sendak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252292-there-s-real-trouble-in-the-world-the-kind-that-can-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 18:49:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Barb Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252292-there-s-real-trouble-in-the-world-the-kind-that-can-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's real trouble in the world. The kind that can't be fixed. The kind we lie awake keeping vigil against. Love is not trouble. It's all we have to light our days, to bring music to the time we've been given." -- Barb Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/842371-laugh-and-cry-and-tell-stories-sad-stories-about-bodies</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2013 06:17:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Eli Clare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/842371-laugh-and-cry-and-tell-stories-sad-stories-about-bodies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Laugh and cry and tell stories. Sad stories about bodies stolen, bodies no longer here. Enraging stories about the false images, devastating lies, untold violence. Bold, brash stories about reclaiming our bodies and changing the world." -- Eli Clare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10466-we-are-focusing-on-the-small-details-and-hiding-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 04:53:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Marjane Satrapi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10466-we-are-focusing-on-the-small-details-and-hiding-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are focusing on the small details and hiding the misery in the world. Look at the smoker and we miss global warming, war, and the crap we eat--not the bad guys but smoking. I smoke and they talk about cancer, I eat and they talk about cholesterol, I make love, it's AIDS. Before AIDS and cholesterol and cancer there's the pleasure of making love and eating and smoking. I have to die someday, so if the thing that gave me pleasure all of my life kills me instead of me going under a truck, that's fine. Besides, why should I live so that when I die I give fresh meat to the worms? I hope that I am rotted and they don't want to eat me. F@#$ck the worms." -- Marjane Satrapi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399896-people-say-that-which-doesn-t-kill-you-makes-you-stronger</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 12:09:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Tayari Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399896-people-say-that-which-doesn-t-kill-you-makes-you-stronger]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People say, That which doesn't kill you makes you stronger.  But they are wrong.  What doesn't kill you doesn't kill you.  That's all you get.  Sometimes, you just have to hope that's enough." -- Tayari Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/595436-that-s-what-being-shy-feels-like-like-my-skin-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2014 09:03:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maureen add a quote by Carol Rifka Brunt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/595436-that-s-what-being-shy-feels-like-like-my-skin-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's what being shy feels like. Like my skin is too thin, the light too bright. Like the best place I could possibly be is in a tunnel far under the cool, dark earth. Someone asks me a question and I stare at them, empty-faced, my brain jammed up with how hard I'm trying to find something interesting to say. And in the end, all I can do is nod or shrug, because the light of their eyes looking at me, waiting for me, is just too much to take. And then it's over and there's one more person in the world who thinks I'm a complete and total waste of space. 
The worst thing is the stupid hopefulness. Every new party, every new bunch of people, and I start thinking that maybe this is my chance. That I'm going to be normal this time. A new leaf. A fresh start. But then I find myself at the party, thinking, Oh, yeah. This again. 
So I stand on the edge of things, crossing my fingers, praying nobody will try to look me in the eye. And the good thing is, they usually don't." -- Carol Rifka Brunt]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
