<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/665331-nikki-li]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/665331-nikki-li" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 18:04:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 18:04:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nikki Li add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that's what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that is holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life.  

A true soul mate is probably the most important person you'll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake.  But to live with a soul mate forever?  Nah. Too painful.  Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then leave.  

A soul mates purpose is to shake you up, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light can get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you have to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53259-among-other-things-you-ll-find-that-you-re-not-the-first</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 06:34:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nikki Li add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53259-among-other-things-you-ll-find-that-you-re-not-the-first]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Among other things, you'll find that you're not the first person who was ever confused and frightened and even sickened by human behavior. You're by no means alone on that score, you'll be excited and stimulated to know. Many, many men have been just as troubled morally and spiritually as you are right now. Happily, some of them kept records of their troubles. You'll learn from them—if you want to. Just as someday, if you have something to offer, someone will learn something from you. It's a beautiful reciprocal arrangement. And it isn't education. It's history. It's poetry." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70234-i-am-always-saying-glad-to-ve-met-you-to-somebody</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 06:35:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nikki Li add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70234-i-am-always-saying-glad-to-ve-met-you-to-somebody]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am always saying &quot;Glad to've met you&quot; to somebody I'm not at all glad I met. If you want to stay alive, you have to say that stuff, though." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/572109-people-who-ve-been-to-hell-and-back-develop-a-certain</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 14:35:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nikki Li add a quote by Marya Hornbacher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/572109-people-who-ve-been-to-hell-and-back-develop-a-certain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People who’ve Been to Hell and Back develop a certain sort of self-righteousness. There is a tendency to say: I have an addictive personality, I am terribly sensitive, I’m touched with fire, I have Scars. There is a self-perpetuating belief that one simply cannot help it, and this is very dangerous. It becomes an identity in and of itself. It becomes its own religion, and you wait for salvation, and you wait, and wait, and wait, and do not save yourself. If you saved yourself and did not wait for salvation, you’d be self-sufficient. How dull." -- Marya Hornbacher]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
