<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/665982-astraea]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/665982-astraea" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 21:11:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770888-some-of-them-stole-off-to-those-cryptical-realms-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 21:11:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770888-some-of-them-stole-off-to-those-cryptical-realms-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some of them stole off to those cryptical realms which are known only to cats and which villagers say are on the moon's dark side, whither the cats leap from tall housetops; but one small black kitten crept upstairs and sprang in Carter's lap to purr and play, and curled up near his feet when he lay down at last on the little couch whose pillows were stuffed with fragrant drowsy herbs." -- H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22755-why-should-a-man-be-scorned-if-finding-himself-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 14:43:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22755-why-should-a-man-be-scorned-if-finding-himself-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why should a man be scorned, if, finding himself in prison, he tries to get out and go home? Or if, when he cannot do so, he thinks and talks about other topics than jailers and prison-walls? The world outside has not become less real because the prisoner cannot see it. In using Escape in this way the critics have chosen the wrong word, and, what is more, they are confusing, not always by sincere error, the Escape of the Prisoner with the Flight of the Deserter. just so a Party-spokesman might have labeled departure from the misery of the Fuhrer's or any other Reich and even criticism of it as treachery .... Not only do they confound the escape of the prisoner with the flight of the deserter; but they would seem to prefer the acquiescence of the &quot;quisling&quot; to the resistance of the patriot." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19189-in-ancient-times-cats-were-worshipped-as-gods-they-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 14:43:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19189-in-ancient-times-cats-were-worshipped-as-gods-they-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In ancient times cats were worshipped as gods; they have not forgotten this." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10284-i-have-dwelt-ever-in-realms-apart-from-the-visible</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 14:42:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10284-i-have-dwelt-ever-in-realms-apart-from-the-visible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have dwelt ever in realms apart from the visible world; spending my youth and adolescence in ancient and little-known books, and in roaming the fields and groves of the region near my ancestral home. I do not think that what I read in these books or saw in these fields and groves was exactly what other boys read and saw there; but of this I must say little, since detailed speech would but confirm those cruel slanders upon my intellect which I sometimes overhear from the whispers of the stealthy attendants around me." -- H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50268-there-are-not-many-persons-who-know-what-wonders-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 14:42:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by Howard Phillips Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50268-there-are-not-many-persons-who-know-what-wonders-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are not many persons who know what wonders are opened to them in the stories and visions of their youth; for when as children we learn and dream, we think but half-formed thoughts, and when as men we try to remember, we are dulled and prosaic with the poison of life. But some of us awake in the night with strange phantasms of enchanted hills and gardens, of fountains that sing in the sun, of golden cliffs overhanging murmuring seas, of plains that stretch down to sleeping cities of bronze and stone, and of shadowy companies of heroes that ride caparisoned white horses along the edges of thick forests; and then we know that we have looked back through the ivory gates into that world of wonder which was ours before we were wise and unhappy." -- Howard Phillips Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1205-it-seemed-to-him-that-he-had-stepped-through-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 14:44:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by J. R. R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1205-it-seemed-to-him-that-he-had-stepped-through-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seemed to him that he had stepped through a high window that looked on a vanished world. A light was upon it for which his language had no name. All that he saw was shapely, but the shapes seemed at once clear cut, as if they had been first conceived and drawn at the uncovering of his eyes, and ancient as if they had endured for ever. He saw no colour but those he knew, gold and white and blue and green, but they were fresh and poignant, as if he had at that moment first perceived them and made names for them new and wonderful. In winter here no heart could mourn for summer or for spring. No blemish or sickness or deformity could be seen in anything that grew upon the earth. On the land of Lorien there was no stain." -- J. R. R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233-i-don-t-know-half-of-you-half-as-well-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2010 23:41:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233-i-don-t-know-half-of-you-half-as-well-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know half of you half as well as I should like; and I like less than half of you half as well as you deserve." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 23:49:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't see things as they are, we see them as we are." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2216-luxury-is-not-a-necessity-to-me-but-beautiful-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 23:49:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2216-luxury-is-not-a-necessity-to-me-but-beautiful-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Luxury is not a necessity to me, but beautiful and good things are." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7915-each-friend-represents-a-world-in-us-a-world-possibly</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 23:49:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7915-each-friend-represents-a-world-in-us-a-world-possibly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each friend represents a world in us, a world possibly not born until they arrive, and it is only by this meeting that a new world is born." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1124-in-sorrow-we-must-go-but-not-in-despair-behold</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 14:43:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1124-in-sorrow-we-must-go-but-not-in-despair-behold]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In sorrow we must go, but not in despair. Behold! we are not bound for ever to the circles of the world, and beyond them is more than memory." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22754-in-the-world-of-the-dreamer-there-was-solitude-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 14:29:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22754-in-the-world-of-the-dreamer-there-was-solitude-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the world of the dreamer there was solitude: all the exaltations and joys came in the moment of preparation for living. They took place in solitude. But with action came anxiety, and the sense of insuperable effort made to match the dream, and with it came weariness, discouragement, and the flight into solitude again. And then in solitude, in the opium den of remembrance, the possibility of pleasure again." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425869-well-did-the-traveler-know-those-garden-lands-that-lie</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 14:46:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425869-well-did-the-traveler-know-those-garden-lands-that-lie]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well did the traveler know those garden lands that lie betwixt the wood of the Cerenerian Sea, and blithely did he follow the singing river Oukranos that marked his course. The sun rose higher over gentle slopes of grove and lawn, and heightened the colors of the thousand flowers that starred each knoll and dangle. A blessed haze lies upon all this region, wherein is held a little more of the sunlight than other places hold, and a little more of the summer's humming music of birds and bees; so that men walk through it as through a faery place, and feel greater joy and wonder than they ever afterward remember." -- H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425870-by-noon-carter-reached-the-jasper-terraces-of-kiran-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 14:47:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425870-by-noon-carter-reached-the-jasper-terraces-of-kiran-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By noon Carter reached the jasper terraces of Kiran which slope down to the river's edge and bear that temple of loveliness wherein the King of Ilek-Vad comes from his far realm on the twilight sea once a year in a golden palanquin to pray to the god of Oukranos, who sang to him in youth when he dwelt in a cottage by its banks. All of jasper is that temple, and covering an acre of ground with its walls and courts, its seven pinnacled towers, and its inner shrine where the river enters through hidden channels and the god sings softly in the night. Many times the moon hears strange music as it shines on those courts and terraces and pinnacles, but whether that music be the song of the god or the chant of the cryptical priests, none but the King of Ilek-Vad may say; for only he had entered the temple or seen the priests. Now, in the drowsiness of day, that carven and delicate fane was silent, and Carter heard only the murmur of the great stream and the hum of the birds and bees as he walked onward under the enchanted sun." -- H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425871-down-through-this-verdant-land-carter-walked-at-evening-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 14:49:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425871-down-through-this-verdant-land-carter-walked-at-evening-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Down through this verdant land Carter walked at evening, and saw twilight float up from the river to the marvelous golden spires of Thran. And just at the hour of dusk he came to the southern gate, and was stopped by a red-robed sentry till he had told three dreams beyond belief, and proved himself a dreamer worthy to walk up Thran's steep mysterious streets and linger in the bazaars where the wares of the ornate galleons were sold. Then into that incredible city he walked; through a wall so thick that the gate was a tunnel, and thereafter amidst curved and undulant ways winding deep and narrow between the heavenward towers. Lights shone through grated and balconied windows, and, the sound of lutes and pipes stole timid from inner courts where marble fountains bubbled. Carter knew his way, and edged down through darker streets to the river, where at an old sea tavern he found the captains and seamen he had known in myriad other dreams. There he bought his passage to Celephais on a great green galleon, and there he stopped for the night after speaking gravely to the venerable cat of that inn, who blinked dozing before an enormous hearth and dreamed of old wars and forgotten gods." -- H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21030-if-you-follow-every-dream-you-might-get-lost</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 19:57:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by Neil Young]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21030-if-you-follow-every-dream-you-might-get-lost]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you follow every dream, you might get lost." -- Neil Young]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33043-keep-on-rockin-in-the-free-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 19:58:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by neil young]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33043-keep-on-rockin-in-the-free-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Keep on rockin' in the free world." -- neil young]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/466456-as-soon-as-you-start-talking-about-mystique-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 19:59:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by Neil Young]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/466456-as-soon-as-you-start-talking-about-mystique-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As soon as you start talking about mystique, you have none." -- Neil Young]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/466464-i-love-it-when-people-yell-at-me-about-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 20:03:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by Neil Young]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/466464-i-love-it-when-people-yell-at-me-about-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love it when people yell at me about the environment and then I tell 'em I'm burning 90% cleaner than them." -- Neil Young]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/509485-i-judge-a-novel-by-whether-or-not-it-turns</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2012 14:40:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by Bryan Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/509485-i-judge-a-novel-by-whether-or-not-it-turns]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I judge a novel by whether or not it turns my blood into starlight." -- Bryan Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19786-tomorrow-you-re-all-going-to-wake-up-in-a-brave</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2012 13:01:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Astraea add a quote by Stephen Colbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19786-tomorrow-you-re-all-going-to-wake-up-in-a-brave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tomorrow you're all going to wake up in a brave new world, a world where the Constitution gets trampled by an army of terrorist clones, created in a stem-cell research lab run by homosexual doctors who sterilize their instruments over burning American flags. Where tax-and-spend Democrats take all your hard-earned money and use it to buy electric cars for National Public Radio, and teach evolution to illegal immigrants. Oh, and everybody's high!" -- Stephen Colbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
