<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/666841-chris-palmer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/666841-chris-palmer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 05:59:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266303-audiences-see-personalities-on-shows-interacting-with-wild-animals-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 05:59:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Chris Palmer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266303-audiences-see-personalities-on-shows-interacting-with-wild-animals-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Audiences see personalities on shows interacting with wild animals as if they were not dangerous or, at the other extreme, provoking them to give viewers an adrenaline rush. Mostly, the animals just want to be left alone, so it’s not surprising that these entertainers are seriously hurt or even killed on rare occasions. On one level, it’s that very possibility the shows are selling." -- Chris Palmer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266305-in-this-image-driven-age-wildlife-filmmakers-carry-a-heavy-responsibility</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 06:03:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Chris Palmer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/266305-in-this-image-driven-age-wildlife-filmmakers-carry-a-heavy-responsibility]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In this image-driven age, wildlife filmmakers carry a heavy responsibility. They can influence how we think and behave when we’re in nature. They can even influence how we raise our kids, how we vote and volunteer in our communities, as well as the future of our wildlands and wildlife. If the stories they create are misleading or false in some way, viewers will misunderstand the issues and react in inappropriate ways. People who consume a heavy diet of wildlife films filled with staged violence and aggression, for example, are likely to think about nature as a circus or a freak show. They certainly won’t form the same positive connections to the natural world as people who watch more thoughtful, authentic, and conservation-oriented films." -- Chris Palmer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
