<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/6669-jack-babalon]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/6669-jack-babalon" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 18:33:08 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302476-there-are-four-kinds-of-people-in-this-world-cretins</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 18:33:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302476-there-are-four-kinds-of-people-in-this-world-cretins]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are four kinds of people in this world: cretins, fools, morons, and lunatics…Cretins don’t even talk; they sort of slobber and stumble…Fools are in great demand, especially on social occasions. They embarrass everyone but provide material for conversation…Fools don’t claim that cats bark, but they talk about cats when everyone else is talking about dogs. They offend all the rules of conversation, and when they really offend, they’re magnificent…Morons never do the wrong thing. They get their reasoning wrong. Like the fellow who says that all dogs are pets and all dogs bark, and cats are pets, too, therefore cats bark…Morons will occasionally say something that’s right, but they say it for the wrong reason…A lunatic is easily recognized. He is a moron who doesn’t know the ropes. The moron proves his thesis; he has logic, however twisted it may be. The lunatic on the other hand, doesn’t concern himself at all with logic; he works by short circuits. For him, everything proves everything else. The lunatic is all idée fixe, and whatever he comes across confirms his lunacy. You can tell him by the liberties he takes with common sense, by his flashes of inspiration, and by the fact that sooner or later he brings up the Templars…There are lunatics who don’t bring up the Templars, but those who do are the most insidious. At first they seem normal, then all of a sudden…" -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189083-danger-is-a-biologic-necessity-like-dreams-if-you-face</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 19:28:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189083-danger-is-a-biologic-necessity-like-dreams-if-you-face]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["danger is a biologic necessity, like dreams. if you face death, for that time, for the period of
direct confrontation, you are immortal." -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62777-silence-is-only-frightening-to-people-who-are-compulsively-verbalizing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 16:39:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62777-silence-is-only-frightening-to-people-who-are-compulsively-verbalizing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Silence is only frightening to people who are compulsively verbalizing." -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/539025-it-is-far-easier-to-write-an-angry-letter-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 13:35:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Colin Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/539025-it-is-far-easier-to-write-an-angry-letter-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is far easier to write an angry letter than to go and say angry things to another person - because as soon as we look in one another's faces we can see the other point of view." -- Colin Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/539048-man-is-not-a-fixed-and-limited-animal-whose-nature</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 13:37:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Colin Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/539048-man-is-not-a-fixed-and-limited-animal-whose-nature]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man is not a 'fixed and limited animal whose nature is absolutely constant'. He changed drastically when he developed 'divided consciousness' to cope with complexities of civilisation, and has been changing steadily ever since. His greatest problem, the problem that has caused most of his agonies and miseries, has been his attempt to compensate for the narrowing of cinsciousness and the entrapment in the left-brain ego. His favorite method of compensation has been to seek out excitement. He feels most free in moments of conquest; so for the past three thousand years or so, most of the greatest man have led armies into their neighbours' territority, and turned order into chaos. This has plainly been a retrogressive step; the evolutionary urge has been defeating its own purpose." -- Colin Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335830-surely-all-art-is-the-result-of-one-s-having-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 13:45:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335830-surely-all-art-is-the-result-of-one-s-having-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Surely all art is the result of one's having been in danger, of having gone through an experience all the way to the end, where no one can go any further." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
