<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/667194-jessica]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/667194-jessica" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 19:18:36 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321540-how-you-can-sit-there-calmly-eating-muffins-when-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 19:18:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321540-how-you-can-sit-there-calmly-eating-muffins-when-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How you can sit there, calmly eating muffins when we are in this horrible trouble, I can’t make out. You seem to me to be perfectly heartless.&quot;

&quot;Well, I can’t eat muffins in an agitated manner. The butter would probably get on my cuffs. One should always eat muffins quite calmly. It is the only way to eat them.&quot;

&quot;I say it’s perfectly heartless your eating muffins at all, under the circumstances." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120699-but-whenever-i-meet-dynamic-nonretarded-americans-i-notice-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 14:18:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120699-but-whenever-i-meet-dynamic-nonretarded-americans-i-notice-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But whenever I meet dynamic, nonretarded Americans, I notice that they all seem to share a single unifying characteristic: the inability to experience the kind of mind-blowing, transcendent romantic relationship they perceive to be a normal part of living. And someone needs to take the fall for this. So instead of blaming no one for this (which is kind of cowardly) or blaming everyone (which is kind of meaningless), I'm going to blame John Cusack." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 14:33:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40501-enjoy-the-power-and-beauty-of-your-youth-oh-nevermind</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 14:40:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Baz Luhrmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40501-enjoy-the-power-and-beauty-of-your-youth-oh-nevermind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Enjoy the power and beauty of your youth; oh nevermind; you will not 
understand the power and beauty of your youth until they have faded. 
But trust me, in 20 years you’ll look back at photos of yourself and 
recall in a way you can’t grasp now how much possibility lay before 
you and how fabulous you really looked….You’re not as fat as you 
imagine. Don’t worry about the future; or worry, but know that worrying is as 
effective as trying to solve an algebra equation by chewing 
bubblegum. The real troubles in your life are apt to be things that 
never crossed your worried mind; the kind that blindside you at 4pm 
on some idle Tuesday. Do one thing everyday that scares you Sing Don’t be reckless with other people’s hearts, don’t put up with 
people who are reckless with yours. Floss Don’t waste your time on jealousy; sometimes you’re ahead, sometimes 
you’re behind…the race is long, and in the end, it’s only with 
yourself. Remember the compliments you receive, forget the insults; if you 
succeed in doing this, tell me how. Keep your old love letters, throw away your old bank statements. Stretch Don’t feel guilty if you don’t know what you want to do with your 
life…the most interesting people I know didn’t know at 22 what they 
wanted to do with their lives, some of the most interesting 40 year 
olds I know still don’t. Get plenty of calcium. Be kind to your knees, you’ll miss them when they’re gone. Maybe you’ll marry, maybe you won’t, maybe you’ll have children,maybe 
you won’t, maybe you’ll divorce at 40, maybe you’ll dance the funky 
chicken on your 75th wedding anniversary…what ever you do, don’t 
congratulate yourself too much or berate yourself either – your 
choices are half chance, so are everybody else’s. Enjoy your body, 
use it every way you can…don’t be afraid of it, or what other people 
think of it, it’s the greatest instrument you’ll ever 
own.. Dance…even if you have nowhere to do it but in your own living room. Read the directions, even if you don’t follow them. Do NOT read beauty magazines, they will only make you feel ugly. Get to know your parents, you never know when they’ll be gone for 
good. Be nice to your siblings; they are the best link to your past and the 
people most likely to stick with you in the future. Understand that friends come and go,but for the precious few you 
should hold on. Work hard to bridge the gaps in geography and 
lifestyle because the older you get, the more you need the people you 
knew when you were young." -- Baz Luhrmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21401-anybody-can-become-angry-that-is-easy-but-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 14:41:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Aristotle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21401-anybody-can-become-angry-that-is-easy-but-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anybody can become angry — that is easy, but to be angry with the right person and to the right degree and at the right time and for the right purpose, and in the right way — that is not within everybody's power and is not easy." -- Aristotle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68927-the-greatest-enemy-of-knowledge-is-not-ignorance-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 14:57:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Daniel J. Boorstin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68927-the-greatest-enemy-of-knowledge-is-not-ignorance-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greatest enemy of knowledge is not ignorance, it is the illusion of knowledge." -- Daniel J. Boorstin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122020-the-truth-is-you-can-be-orphaned-again-and-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 17:17:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122020-the-truth-is-you-can-be-orphaned-again-and-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is you can be orphaned again and again and again. The truth is, you will be. And the secret is, this will hurt less and less each time until you can't feel a thing. Trust me on this." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6655-don-t-go-around-saying-the-world-owes-you-a-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 18:03:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6655-don-t-go-around-saying-the-world-owes-you-a-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don’t go around saying the world owes you a living. The world owes you nothing. It was here first." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174533-never-allow-someone-to-be-your-priority-while-allowing-yourself</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 18:04:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174533-never-allow-someone-to-be-your-priority-while-allowing-yourself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never allow someone to be your priority while allowing yourself to be their option." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47069-education-the-path-from-cocky-ignorance-to-miserable-uncertainty</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 18:05:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47069-education-the-path-from-cocky-ignorance-to-miserable-uncertainty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Education: the path from cocky ignorance to miserable uncertainty." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135111-don-t-wake-up-a-woman-in-love-let-her-dream</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 18:12:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135111-don-t-wake-up-a-woman-in-love-let-her-dream]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't wake up a woman in love. Let her dream, so that she does not weep when she returns to her bitter reality" -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161762-anyone-who-can-only-think-of-one-way-to-spell</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 18:18:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161762-anyone-who-can-only-think-of-one-way-to-spell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who can only think of one way to spell a word obviously lacks imagination." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/348792-really-great-people-make-you-feel-that-you-too-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 18:48:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/348792-really-great-people-make-you-feel-that-you-too-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Really great people make you feel that you, too, can become great." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/336052-what-a-wee-little-part-of-a-person-s-life-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 19:05:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/336052-what-a-wee-little-part-of-a-person-s-life-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a wee little part of a person's life are his acts and his words! His real life is lead in his head, and is known to none but himself. All day long, and every day, the mill of his brain is grinding, and his thoughts, (which are but the mute articulation of his feelings,) not those other things are his history. His acts and his words are merely the visible thin crust of his world, with its scattered snow summits and its vacant wastes of water-and they are so trifling a part of his bulk! a mere skin enveloping it. The mass of him is hidden-it and its volcanic fires that toss and boil, and never rest, night nor day.  These are his life, and they are not written, and cannot be written." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71299-the-more-stupid-one-is-the-closer-one-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 20:26:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71299-the-more-stupid-one-is-the-closer-one-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The more stupid one is, the closer one is to reality.  The more stupid one is, the clearer one is.  Stupidity is brief and artless, while intelligence squirms and hides itself.  Intelligence is unprincipled, but stupidity is honest and straightforward." -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353807-that-a-greater-fool-than-jane-eyre-had-never-breathed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 19:43:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353807-that-a-greater-fool-than-jane-eyre-had-never-breathed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That a greater fool than Jane Eyre had never breathed the breath of life; that a more fantastic idiot had never surfeited herself on sweet lies, and swallowed poison as if it were nectar." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278722-live-each-day-as-if-it-s-our-last-that-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 09:24:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by David Nicholls]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278722-live-each-day-as-if-it-s-our-last-that-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Live each day as if it's our last', that was the conventional advice, but really who had the energy for that? What if it rained or you felt a bit glandy? It just wasn't practical. Better by far to simply try and be good and courageous and bold and to make a difference. Not change the world exactly, but the bit around you. Go out there with your passion and you relectric typewriter and work hard at...something. Change lives through art maybe. Cherish your friends, stay true to your principles, live passionately and fully and well. Experience new things. Love and be loved, if you ever get the chance." -- David Nicholls]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286272-you-can-trust-us-to-stick-to-you-through-thick</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 09:29:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286272-you-can-trust-us-to-stick-to-you-through-thick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can trust us to stick to you through thick and thin – to the bitter end. And you can trust us to keep any secret of yours – closer than you yourself keep it. But you cannot trust us to let you face trouble alone, and go off without a word. We are your friends, Frodo. Anyway: there it is. We know most of what Gandalf has told you. We know a good deal about the ring. We are horribly afraid–but we are coming with you; or following you like hounds." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27324-here-s-to-alcohol-the-rose-colored-glasses-of-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 19:45:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27324-here-s-to-alcohol-the-rose-colored-glasses-of-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to alcohol, the rose colored glasses of life." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/347843-the-victor-belongs-to-the-spoils</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 19:51:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/347843-the-victor-belongs-to-the-spoils]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the victor belongs to the spoils" -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4853-in-spite-of-everything-i-loved-you-and-will-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 20:03:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4853-in-spite-of-everything-i-loved-you-and-will-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In spite of everything I loved you, and will go on loving you―on my knees, with my shoulders drawn back, showing my heels to the headsman and straining my goose neck―even then.  And afterwards―perhaps most of all afterwards―I shall love you, and one day we shall have a real, all-embracing explanation, and then perhaps we shall somehow fit together, you and I, and turn ourselves in such a way that we form one pattern, and solve the puzzle: draw a line from point A to point B... without looking, or, without lifting the pencil... or in some other way... we shall connect the points, draw the line, and you and I shall form that unique design for which I yearn.  If they do this kind of thing to me every morning, they will get me trained and I shall become quite wooden." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225210-i-don-t-care-about-anyone-and-the-feeling-is-quite</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 20:05:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225210-i-don-t-care-about-anyone-and-the-feeling-is-quite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don’t care about anyone, and the feeling is quite obviously mutual." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21101-do-you-think-i-am-an-automaton-a-machine</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 20:08:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21101-do-you-think-i-am-an-automaton-a-machine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you think I am an automaton? — a machine without feelings? and can bear to have my morsel of bread snatched from my lips, and my drop of living water dashed from my cup? Do you think, because I am poor, obscure, plain, and little, I am soulless and heartless? You think wrong! — I have as much soul as you — and full as much heart! And if God had gifted me with some beauty and much wealth, I should have made it as hard for you to leave me, as it is now for me to leave you. I am not talking to you now through the medium of custom, conventionalities, nor even of mortal flesh: it is my spirit that addresses your spirit; just as if both had passed through the grave, and we stood at God's feet, equal — as we are!" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52202-true-love-is-not-so-much-a-matter-of-romance</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 20:09:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52202-true-love-is-not-so-much-a-matter-of-romance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["True love is not so much a matter of romance as it is a matter of anxious concern for the well-being of one's companion." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198195-it-is-a-long-way-to-ireland-janet-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 20:10:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198195-it-is-a-long-way-to-ireland-janet-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a long way to Ireland, Janet, and I am sorry to send my little friend on such weary travels: but if I can't do better, how is it to be helped? Are you anything akin to me, do you think, Jane?&quot;

I could risk no sort of answer by this time: my heart was still. 

&quot;Because, he said, &quot;I sometimes have a queer feeling with regard to you - especially when you are near me, as now: it is as if I had a string somewhere under my left ribs, tightly and inextricably knotted to a similar string situated in the corresponding quarter of your little frame. And if that boisterous channel, and two hundred miles or so of land some broad between us, I am afraid that cord of communion will be snapt; and then I've a nervous notion I should take to bleeding inwardly. As for you, - you'd forget me." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66560-i-care-for-myself-the-more-solitary-the-more-friendless</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 20:11:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66560-i-care-for-myself-the-more-solitary-the-more-friendless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; care for myself. The more solitary, the more friendless, the more unsustained I am, the more I will respect myself." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247223-i-liked-my-name-pronounced-by-your-lips-in-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 20:18:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247223-i-liked-my-name-pronounced-by-your-lips-in-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I liked my name pronounced by your lips in a grateful, happy accent." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4815-life-appears-to-me-too-short-to-be-spent-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 20:22:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4815-life-appears-to-me-too-short-to-be-spent-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life appears to me too short to be spent in nursing animosity or registering wrongs." -- Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74718-they-ve-got-no-idea-what-happiness-is-they-don-t-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 20:31:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74718-they-ve-got-no-idea-what-happiness-is-they-don-t-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They've got no idea what happiness is, they don't know that without this love there is no happiness or unhappiness for us--there is no life." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74708-everything-intelligent-is-so-boring</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 20:33:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74708-everything-intelligent-is-so-boring]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything intelligent is so boring." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
