<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/667494-shazia]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/667494-shazia" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 18:01:53 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/595436-that-s-what-being-shy-feels-like-like-my-skin-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 18:01:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shazia add a quote by Carol Rifka Brunt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/595436-that-s-what-being-shy-feels-like-like-my-skin-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's what being shy feels like. Like my skin is too thin, the light too bright. Like the best place I could possibly be is in a tunnel far under the cool, dark earth. Someone asks me a question and I stare at them, empty-faced, my brain jammed up with how hard I'm trying to find something interesting to say. And in the end, all I can do is nod or shrug, because the light of their eyes looking at me, waiting for me, is just too much to take. And then it's over and there's one more person in the world who thinks I'm a complete and total waste of space. 
The worst thing is the stupid hopefulness. Every new party, every new bunch of people, and I start thinking that maybe this is my chance. That I'm going to be normal this time. A new leaf. A fresh start. But then I find myself at the party, thinking, Oh, yeah. This again. 
So I stand on the edge of things, crossing my fingers, praying nobody will try to look me in the eye. And the good thing is, they usually don't." -- Carol Rifka Brunt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/609134-i-really-wondered-why-people-were-always-doing-what-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 18:02:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shazia add a quote by Carol Rifka Brunt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/609134-i-really-wondered-why-people-were-always-doing-what-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I really wondered why people were always doing what they didn't like doing. It seemed like life was a sort of narrowing tunnel. Right when you were born, the tunnel was huge. You could be anything. Then, like, the absolute second after you were born, the tunnel narrowed down to about half that size. You were a boy, and already it was certain you wouldn't be a mother and it was likely you wouldn't become a manicurist or a kindergarten teacher. Then you started to grow up and everything you did closed the tunnel in some more. You broke your arm climbing a tree and you ruled out being a baseball pitcher. You failed every math test you ever took and you canceled any hope of ever being a scientist. Like that. On and on through the years until you were stuck. You'd become a baker or a librarian or a bartender. Or an accountant. And there you were. I figured that on the day you died, the tunnel would be so narrow, you'd have squeezed yourself in with so many choices, that you just got squashed." -- Carol Rifka Brunt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/586716-the-sun-kept-on-with-its-slipping-away-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 18:02:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shazia add a quote by Carol Rifka Brunt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/586716-the-sun-kept-on-with-its-slipping-away-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sun kept on with its slipping away, and I thought how many small good things in the world might be resting on the shoulders of something terrible." -- Carol Rifka Brunt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/750010-if-my-life-was-a-film-i-d-have-walked-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 18:27:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shazia add a quote by Carol Rifka Brunt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/750010-if-my-life-was-a-film-i-d-have-walked-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If my life was a film, I’d have walked out by now." -- Carol Rifka Brunt]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
