<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/667926-judy-king]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/667926-judy-king" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2011 18:00:25 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138581-there-is-probably-no-better-or-more-reliable-measure-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2011 18:00:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Clarissa Pinkola Estes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138581-there-is-probably-no-better-or-more-reliable-measure-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is probably no better or more reliable measure of whether a woman has spent time in ugly duckling status at some point or all throughout her life than her inability to digest a sincere compliment. Although it could be a matter of modesty, or could be attributed to shyness- although too many serious wounds are carelessly written off as &quot;nothing but shyness&quot;- more often a compliment is stuttered around about because it sets up an automatic and unpleasant dialogue in the woman's mind.

If you say how lovely she is, or how beautiful her art is, or compliment anything else her soul took part in, inspired, or suffused, something in her mind says she is undeserving and you, the complimentor, are an idiot for thinking such a thing to begin with. Rather than understand that the beauty of her soul shines through when she is being herself, the woman changes the subject and effectively snatches nourishment away from the soul-self, which thrives on being acknowledged.&quot;

&quot;I must admit, I sometimes find it useful in my practice to delineate the various typologies of personality as cats and hens and ducks and swans and so forth. If warranted, I might ask my client to assume for a moment that she is a swan who does not realzie it. Assume also for a moment that she has been brought up by or is currently surrounded by ducks.

There is nothing wrong with ducks, I assure them, or with swans. But ducks are ducks and swans are swans. Sometimes to make the point I have to move to other animal metaphors. I like to use mice. What if you were raised by the mice people? But what if you're, say, a swan. Swans and mice hate each other's food for the most part. They each think the other smells funny. They are not interested in spending time together, and if they did, one would be constantly harassing the other.

But what if you, being a swan, had to pretend you were a mouse? What if you had to pretend to be gray and furry and tiny? What you had no long snaky tail to carry in the air on tail-carrying day? What if wherever you went you tried to walk like a mouse, but you waddled instead? What if you tried to talk like a mouse, but insteade out came a honk every time? Wouldn't you be the most miserable creature in the world?

The answer is an inequivocal yes. So why, if this is all so and too true, do women keep trying to bend and fold themselves into shapes that are not theirs? I must say, from years of clinical observation of this problem, that most of the time it is not because of deep-seated masochism or a malignant dedication to self-destruction or anything of that nature. More often it is because the woman simply doesn't know any better. She is unmothered." -- Clarissa Pinkola Estes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3347-writing-historical-fiction-is-a-legitimate-use-of-multiple-personality</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2011 21:15:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Peggy Ullman Bell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3347-writing-historical-fiction-is-a-legitimate-use-of-multiple-personality]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing historical fiction is a legitimate use of Multiple Personality disorder." -- Peggy Ullman Bell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192640-you-is-kind-you-is-smart-you-is-important</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:45:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192640-you-is-kind-you-is-smart-you-is-important]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You is kind. You is smart. You is important." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205769-i-always-thought-insanity-would-be-a-dark-bitter-feeling</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:45:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205769-i-always-thought-insanity-would-be-a-dark-bitter-feeling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I always thought insanity would be a dark, bitter feeling, but it is drenching and delicious if you really roll around in it." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232859-ever-morning-until-you-dead-in-the-ground-you-gone</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:45:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232859-ever-morning-until-you-dead-in-the-ground-you-gone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ever morning, until you dead in the ground, you gone have to make this decision. You gone have to ask yourself, &quot;Am I gone believe what them fools say about me today?" -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225030-truth-it-feels-cool-like-water-washing-over-my-sticky-hot</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:46:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225030-truth-it-feels-cool-like-water-washing-over-my-sticky-hot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Truth.
It feels cool, like water washing over my sticky-hot body.  Cooling a heat that's been burning me up all my life.
Truth, I say inside my head again, just for that feeling." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225033-out-of-the-blue-he-kissed-me-right-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:46:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225033-out-of-the-blue-he-kissed-me-right-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...out of the blue, he kissed me.  Right in the middle of the Robert E. Lee Hotel Restaurant, he kissed me so slowly with an open mouth and every single thing in my body-my skin, my collarbone, the hollow backs of my knees, everything inside of me filled up with light." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284440-she-s-wearing-a-tight-red-sweater-and-a-red-skirt</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:46:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284440-she-s-wearing-a-tight-red-sweater-and-a-red-skirt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She's wearing a tight red sweater and a red skirt and enough makeup to scare a hooker." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300855-i-m-sorry-but-were-you-dropped-on-your-head-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:47:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300855-i-m-sorry-but-were-you-dropped-on-your-head-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm sorry, but were you dropped on your head as an infant?" -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155659-everyone-knows-how-we-white-people-feel-the-glorified-mammy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:47:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155659-everyone-knows-how-we-white-people-feel-the-glorified-mammy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone knows how we white people feel, the glorified Mammy figure who dedicates her whole life to a white family. Margaret Mitchell covered that. But no one ever asked Mammy how she felt about it." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287364-and-you-call-yourself-a-christian-were-hilly-s-words-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:47:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287364-and-you-call-yourself-a-christian-were-hilly-s-words-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And you call yourself a Christian,' were Hilly's words to me and I thought, God. When did I ever do that?" -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384876-womens-they-ain-t-like-men-a-woman-ain-t-gone-beat</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:48:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384876-womens-they-ain-t-like-men-a-woman-ain-t-gone-beat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Womens, they ain't like men. A woman ain't gone beat you with a stick. Miss Hilly wouldn't pull no pistol on me. Miss Leefolt wouldn't come burn my house down. No, white womens like to keep they hands clean. They got a shiny little set of tools they use, sharp as witches' fingernails, tidy and laid out neat, like the picks on a dentist tray. They gone take they time with em." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300853-she-s-got-so-many-azalea-bushes-her-yard-s-going-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:48:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300853-she-s-got-so-many-azalea-bushes-her-yard-s-going-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She's got so many azalea bushes, her yard's going to look like Gone With the Wind come spring. I don't like azaleas and I sure didn't like that movie, the way they made slavery look like a big happy tea party. If I'd played Mammy, I'd of told Scarlett to stick those green draperies up her white little pooper. Maker her own damn man-catching dress." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410949-once-upon-a-time-they-was-two-girls-i-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:49:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410949-once-upon-a-time-they-was-two-girls-i-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time they was two girls,&quot; I say. &quot;one girl had black skin, one girl had white.&quot;
Mae Mobley look up at me. She listening.
&quot;Little colored girl say to little white girl, 'How come your skin be so pale?' White girl say, 'I don't know. How come your skin be so black? What you think that mean?'
&quot;But neither one a them little girls knew. So little white girl say, 'Well, let's see. You got hair, I got hair.'&quot;I gives Mae Mobley a little tousle on her head.
&quot;Little colored girl say 'I got a nose, you got a nose.'&quot;I gives her little snout a tweak. She got to reach up and do the same to me.
&quot;Little white girl say, 'I got toes, you got toes.' And I do the little thing with her toes, but she can't get to mine cause I got my white work shoes on.
&quot;'So we's the same. Just a different color', say that little colored girl. The little white girl she agreed and they was friends. The End.&quot;
Baby Girl just look at me. Law, that was a sorry story if I ever heard one. Wasn't even no plot to it. But Mae Mobley, she smile and say, &quot;Tell it again." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407747-this-woman-talk-like-she-from-so-deep-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:49:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407747-this-woman-talk-like-she-from-so-deep-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This woman talk like she from so deep in the country she got corn growing in her shoes." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410960-today-i-m-on-tell-you-bout-a-man-from-outer</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:50:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410960-today-i-m-on-tell-you-bout-a-man-from-outer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today I'm on tell you bout a man from outer space.&quot; She just loves hearing about peoples from outer space. Her favorite show on the tee-vee is My Favorite Martian, I pull on my antennae hats I shaped last night out a tin foil, fasten em on our heads. One for her and one for me. We look like we a couple a crazy people in them things.
&quot;One day, a wise Martian come down to Earth to teach us people a thing or two,&quot; I say.
&quot;Martian? How big?&quot;
&quot;oh, he about six-two.&quot;
&quot;What's his name?&quot;
&quot;Martian Luther King.&quot;
She take a deep breath and lean her head down on my shoulder. I feel her three-year-old heart racing against mine, flapping like butterflies on  my white uniform.
&quot;He was a real nice Martian, Mister King. Looked just like us, nose, mouth, hair up on his head, but sometime people looked at him funny and sometime, well, I guess sometime people was just downright mean.&quot;
I coul get in a lot a trouble telling her these little stories, especially with Mister Leefolt. But Mae Mobley know these our &quot;secret stories&quot;.
&quot;Why Aibee? Why was they so mean to him?&quot; she ask.
&quot;Cause he was green." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417329-now-i-had-babies-confuse-before-john-green-dudley-first</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:50:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417329-now-i-had-babies-confuse-before-john-green-dudley-first]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now I had babies confuse before. John Green Dudley, first word out a that boy's mouth was &lt;i&gt;Mama&lt;/i&gt; and he was looking straight at me. But then pretty soon he calling everybody including hisself Mama and calling his daddy Mama too... Nobody worry bout it. Course when he start playing dress-up in his sister's Jewel Taylor twirl skirts and wearing Chanel No. 5, we all get a little concern." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410955-we-go-on-in-her-room-where-we-like-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:51:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410955-we-go-on-in-her-room-where-we-like-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We go on in her room, where we like to set. I get up in the big chair and she get up on me and smile, bounce a little. &quot;Tell me bout the brown wrapping. And the present.&quot; She so excited, she squirming. She has to jump off my lap, squirm a little to get it out. Then she crawl back up. 
That's her favorite story cause when I tell it, she get two presents. I take the brown wrapping from my Piggly Wiggly grocery bag and wrap up a little something, like piece a candy, inside. Then I use the white paper from my Cole's Drug Store bag and wrap another one just like it. She take it real serious, the unwrapping, letting me tell the story bout how it ain't the color a the wrapping that count, it's what we is inside." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417335-i-looked-after-that-dudley-family-for-too-long-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:51:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417335-i-looked-after-that-dudley-family-for-too-long-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I looked after that Dudley family for too long, over six years. His daddy would take him to the garage and whip him with a rubber hose-pipe trying to beat the girl out a that boy until I couldn't stand it no more.... I wish to God I'd told John Green Dudley he ain't going to hell. That he ain't no sideshow freak cause he like boys. I wish to God I'd filled his ears with good things like I'm trying to do with Mae Mobley. Instead, I just sat in the kitchen, waiting to put the salve on them hose-pipe welts." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384877-with-other-people-hilly-hands-out-lies-like-the-presbyterians</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:51:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384877-with-other-people-hilly-hands-out-lies-like-the-presbyterians]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With other people, Hilly hands out lies like the Presbyterians hand out guilt, but it's our own silent agreement, this strict honesty, perhaps the one thing that has kept us friends" -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429308-lord-i-never-seen-blue-hair-on-a-black-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:52:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429308-lord-i-never-seen-blue-hair-on-a-black-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lord, I never seen blue hair on a black woman before or since.  Leroy say you look like a cracker from outer space." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403679-week-after-clyde-left-you-i-heard-that-cocoa-wake</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:52:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403679-week-after-clyde-left-you-i-heard-that-cocoa-wake]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Week after Clyde left you I heard that Cocoa wake up to her cootchie spoilt like a rotten oyster. Didn't get better for three months. Bertrina she good friends with Cocoa She knows your prayer works." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427861-president-kennedy-s-assassination-less-than-two-weeks-ago-has-struck</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:53:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427861-president-kennedy-s-assassination-less-than-two-weeks-ago-has-struck]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["President Kennedy’s assassination, less than two weeks ago, has struck the world dumb. It’s like no one wants to be the first to break the silence. Nothing seems important." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425432-bosoms-are-for-bedrooms-and-breastfeeding-not-for-occasions-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:53:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425432-bosoms-are-for-bedrooms-and-breastfeeding-not-for-occasions-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bosoms, are for bedrooms and breastfeeding.  Not for occasions with dignity." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/500920-amnesty-n-the-state-s-magnanimity-to-those-offenders-whom-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2012 20:37:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/500920-amnesty-n-the-state-s-magnanimity-to-those-offenders-whom-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["AMNESTY, n.  The state's magnanimity to those offenders whom it would be too expensive to punish." -- Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360419-because-spanish-is-a-feeling-based-language-that-comes-first-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 11:59:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Victor Villaseñor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360419-because-spanish-is-a-feeling-based-language-that-comes-first-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because Spanish is a feeling-based language that comes first from the heart, just as English is a thinking-based language that comes first from the head." -- Victor Villaseñor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/443616-everybody-knew-that-being-dead-could-put-you-in-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 06:58:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Luis Alberto Urrea]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/443616-everybody-knew-that-being-dead-could-put-you-in-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody knew that being dead could put you in a terrible mood." -- Luis Alberto Urrea]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/443619-this-is-how-heaven-works-they-re-practical-we-are-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 06:59:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Luis Alberto Urrea]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/443619-this-is-how-heaven-works-they-re-practical-we-are-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is how Heaven works. They're practical. We are always looking for rays of light. For lightning bolts or burning bushes. But God is a worker, like us. He made the world — He didn't hire poor Indios to build it for him! God has worker's hands. Just remember — angels carry no harps. Angels carry hammers." -- Luis Alberto Urrea]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/555525-i-can-t-write-without-a-reader-it-s-precisely-like-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 20:05:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by John Cheever]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/555525-i-can-t-write-without-a-reader-it-s-precisely-like-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can’t write without a reader. It’s precisely like a kiss—you can’t do it alone." -- John Cheever]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5183-if-you-obey-all-of-the-rules-you-miss-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 16:55:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Judy add a quote by Katharine Hepburn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5183-if-you-obey-all-of-the-rules-you-miss-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you obey all of the rules, you miss all of the fun." -- Katharine Hepburn]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
