<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/668302-jami]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/668302-jami" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 10:11:44 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3763-every-relationship-is-fundamentally-a-power-struggle-and-the-individual</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 10:11:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jami add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3763-every-relationship-is-fundamentally-a-power-struggle-and-the-individual]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every relationship is fundamentally a power struggle, and the individual in power is whoever likes the other person less." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6184-a-work-that-aspires-however-humbly-to-the-condition-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 10:18:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jami add a quote by Joseph Conrad]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6184-a-work-that-aspires-however-humbly-to-the-condition-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A work that aspires, however humbly, to the condition of art should carry its justification in every line...To snatch in a moment of courage, from the remorseless rush of time, a passing phase of life is only the beginning of the task. The task approached in tenderness and faith is to hold up unquestioningly, without choice and without fear, the rescued fragment before all eyes and in the light of a sincere mood. It is to show its vibration, its colour, its form; and through its movement, its form, and its colour, reveal the substance of its truth -- disclose its inspiring secret: the stress and passion within the core of each convincing moment. In a single-minded attempt of that kind, if one be deserving and fortunate, one may perchance attain to such clearness of sincerity that at last the presented vision of regret or pity, of terror or mirth, shall awaken in the hearts of the beholders that feeling of unavoidable solidarity; of the solidarity in mysterious origin, in toil, in joy, in hope, in uncertain fate, which binds men to each other and all mankind to the visible world." -- Joseph Conrad]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2244-his-very-existence-was-improbable-inexplicable-and-altogether-bewildering-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 10:18:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jami add a quote by Joseph Conrad]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2244-his-very-existence-was-improbable-inexplicable-and-altogether-bewildering-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His very existence was improbable, inexplicable, and altogether bewildering. He was an insoluble problem. It was inconceivable how he had existed, how he had succeeded in getting so far, how he had managed to remain -- why he did not instantly disappear." -- Joseph Conrad]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2005-my-skin-is-kind-of-sort-of-brownish-pinkish-yellowish</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 10:19:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jami add a quote by Shel Silverstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2005-my-skin-is-kind-of-sort-of-brownish-pinkish-yellowish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My skin is kind of sort of brownish pinkish yellowish white. My eyes are greyish blueish green, but I'm told they look orange in the night. My hair is reddish blondish brown, but its silver when its wet, and all the colors I am inside have not been invented yet." -- Shel Silverstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
