<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/669275-drew]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/669275-drew" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 19:24:28 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4441-i-wanted-to-become-the-seeker-the-aroused-and-passionate</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 19:24:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Drew add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4441-i-wanted-to-become-the-seeker-the-aroused-and-passionate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted to become the seeker, the aroused and passionate explorer, and it was better to go at it knowing nothing at all, always choosing the unmarked bottle, always choosing your own unproven method, armed with nothing but faith and a belief in astonishment." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4448-if-the-case-isn-t-plea-bargained-dismissed-or-placed-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 19:56:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Drew add a quote by David Simon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4448-if-the-case-isn-t-plea-bargained-dismissed-or-placed-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the case isn't plea bargained, dismissed or placed on the inactive docket for an indefinite period of time, if by some perverse twist of fate it becomes a trial by jury, you will then have the opportunity of sitting on the witness stand and reciting under oath the facts of the case-a brief moment in the sun that clouds over with the appearance of the aforementioned defense attorney who, at worst, will accuse you of perjuring yourself in a gross injustice or, at best, accuse you of conducting an investigation so incredibly slipshod that the real killer has been allowed to roam free.
   Once both sides have argued the facts of the case, a jury of twelve men and women picked from computer lists of registered voters in one of America's most undereducated cities will go to a room and begin shouting. If these happy people manage to overcome the natural impulse to avoid any act of collective judgement, they just may find one human being guilty of murdering another. Then you can go to Cher's Pub at Lexington and Guilford, where that selfsame assistant state's attorney, if possessed of any human qualities at all, will buy you a bottle of domestic beer.
   And you drink it. Because in a police department of about three thousand sworn souls, you are one of thirty-six investigators entrusted with the pursuit of that most extraordinary of crimes: the theft of a human life. You speak for the dead. You avenge those lost to the world. Your paycheck may come from fiscal services but, goddammit, after six beers you can pretty much convince yourself that you work for the Lord himself. If you are not as good as you should be, you'll be gone within a year or two, transferred to fugitive, or auto theft or check and fraud at the other end of the hall. If you are good enough, you will never do anything else as a cop that matters this much. Homicide is the major leagues, the center ring, the show. It always has been. When Cain threw a cap into Abel, you don't think The Big Guy told a couple of fresh uniforms to go down and work up the prosecution report. Hell no, he sent for a fucking detective. And it will always be that way, because the homicide unit of any urban police force has for generations been the natural habitat of that rarefied species, the thinking cop." -- David Simon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4450-a-look-passed-between-recevo-and-karras-they-could-hear</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 20:24:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Drew add a quote by George Pelecanos]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4450-a-look-passed-between-recevo-and-karras-they-could-hear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A look passed between Recevo and Karras. They could hear the rest of them crowded outside the door.
Karras cradled the Thompson gun, pressed the butt tight against his ribs.
&quot;Well,&quot; he whispered. &quot;Come on if you're gonna come.&quot;
They charged into the room.
Karras saw white fire as he heard the reports, heard Joey's gun explode, saw one man fall, heard Joey scream, watched Joey's fedora tumble by as if it had been blown by a strong wind. Karras squeezed the trigger, saw men diving through the gunsmoke, the doorframe disintegrating in spark and dust. He fell back to the floor from a blunt shock that felt like a hammer blow to his chest.
Karras winced, got himself up onto the balls of his feet. He leaned his face against the table, rested it there, caught his breath. He listened to the others move about the room.
Swim, you Greek bastard.
And he was over the table, landing on his feet as softly as if he had landed in water. And they were there, the Welshman and the others, moving toward him, emptying their guns at once, the sound deafening now and riding over their caterwauling screams and the bottomless scream coming from his own mouth.
Karras went forward, humming as his finger locked down on the trigger, the Tommy gun dancing crazily in his arms, the gunmen falling before him through the smoke and ejecting shells and the white gulls gliding against the perfect blue sky.
Red flowers bloomed on the chests of the men who had come to take Peter Karras to the place where he was always meant to be." -- George Pelecanos]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4451-suenos-dulces-suenos-he-must-be-painting-upstairs-i-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 20:44:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Drew add a quote by Rafael Alvarez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4451-suenos-dulces-suenos-he-must-be-painting-upstairs-i-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suenos. Dulces Suenos.
He must be painting upstairs.
I can feel it.
I remember when his father was just a baby and I called her Mama for the first time and she became Mama for all of us; Mama de la casa and his father would wake up in the middle of the night and scream in his crib and nothing would make him stop, nada, and Mama would get so exhausted she would turn her back to me and cry in her pillow.
I would smooth her hair-it was black, Basilio, as black as an olive-and I would turn on the radio (electricity, Basilio, in the middle of the night), to maybe calm the baby and listen to something besides the screaming.
Mama liked the radio, Basilio, and we listened while your father cried-cantante negra, cantante de almas azules-and it made us feel a little better, helped us make it through.
I had to get up early to catch the streetcar to the shipyard, but when the crying finally stopped sometimes the sun would be ready to pop and Mama's breathing would slow down and her shoulders would move like gentle waves, sleeping but still listening, like I can hear her now on this good bed, and Basilio-Mira, hombre, I will not tell you this again-if I moved very close and kissed her shoulders, she would turn to face me and we would have to be quiet Basilio, under the music, very, very quiet....
So this I want to know, Basilio.
This, if you want to live on Macon Street for another minute.
Can you paint an apple baked soft in the oven, an apple filled with cinnamon and raisins?
Can you paint such a woman?
Are you good enough yet with those brushes so that she will step out of your pictures to turn on the radio in the middle of the night?
Will she visit an old man on his death bed?
If you cannot do that, Basilio, there is no need for you to live here anymore." -- Rafael Alvarez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4456-i-would-prefer-pat-said-his-voice-a-little-stiff</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 21:00:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Drew add a quote by Laura Lippman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4456-i-would-prefer-pat-said-his-voice-a-little-stiff]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would prefer,&quot; Pat said, his voice a little stiff, as if he expected resistance, &quot;that I be the cosigner on the loan, if you go through with this. I know I'm not a famous billionaire, but I think my credit's just as good.&quot;
No, you're wrong about that,&quot; Tess said, shaking her head.
What?&quot;
As far as I'm concerned, it's better. I'd much rather do business with you.&quot;
They shook on it. It was a deal, after all, not a time for hugging.
Favors, Arnie Vasso had once said. Your father knows all about favors. He had meant it as an insult, a sly reference to the corners the Monaghans and Weinsteins cut here and there. Now Tess saw it for the simple truth it was: Her father understood favors. How to do them, how to accept them, how to walk away when the price was too steep. It was a lesson she wouldn't mind learning someday.
Maybe this was the place to start." -- Laura Lippman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4472-you-heard-me-let-someone-else-send-you-to-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 22:11:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Drew add a quote by Dennis Lehane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4472-you-heard-me-let-someone-else-send-you-to-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You heard me. Let someone else send you to your blaze of glory. You're a speck, man. You're nothing. You're not worth the bullet or the mark on my soul for taking you out.&quot;
You trying to piss me off again, Patrick?&quot; He removed Campbell Rawson from his shoulder and held him aloft.
I tilted my wrist so the cylinder fell into my palm, shrugged. &quot;You're a joke, Gerry. I'm just calling it like I see it.&quot;
That so?&quot;
Absolutely.&quot; I met his hard eyes with my own. &quot;And you'll be replaced, just like everything else, in maybe a week, tops. Some other dumb, sick shit will come along and kill some people and he'll be all over the papers, and all over Hard Copy and you'll be yesterday's news. Your fifteen minutes are up, Gerry. And they've passed without impact.&quot;
They'll remember this,&quot; Gerry said. &quot;Believe me.&quot;
Gerry clamped back on the trigger. When he met my finger, he looked at me and then clamped down so hard that my finger broke.
I depressed the trigger on the one-shot and nothing happened.
Gerry shrieked louder, and the razor came out of my flesh, then swung back immediately, and I clenched my eyes shut and depressed the trigger frantically three times.
And Gerry's hand exploded.
And so did mine.
The razor hit the ice by my knee as I dropped the one shot and fire roared up the electrical tape and gasoline on Gerry's arm and caught the wisps of Danielle's hair.
Gerry threw his head back and opened his mouth wide and bellowed in ecstasy.
I grabbed the razor, could barely feel it because the nerves in my hand seemed to have stopped working.
I slashed into the electric tape at the end of the shotgun barrel, and Danielle dropped away toward the ice and rolled her head into the frozen sand.
My broken finger came back out of the shotgun and Gerry swung the barrels toward my head.
The twin shotgun bores arced through the darkness like eyes without mercy or soul, and I raised my head to meet them, and Gerry's wail filled my ears as the fire licked at his neck.
Good-bye, I thought. Everyone. It's been nice.
Oscar's first two shots entered the back of Gerry's head and exited through the center of his forehead and a third punched into his back.
The shotgun jerked upward in Gerry's flaming arm and then the shots came from the front, several at once, and Gerry spun like a marionette and pitched toward the ground. The shotgun boomed twice and punched holes through the ice in front of him as he fell.
He landed on his knees and, for a moment, I wasn't sure if he was dead or not. His rusty hair was afire and his head lolled to the left as one eye disappeared in flames but the other shimmered at me through waves of heat, and an amused derision shone in the pupil.
Patrick, the eye said through the gathering smoke, you still know nothing.
Oscar rose up on the other side of Gerry's corpse, Campbell Rawson clutched tight to his massive chest as it rose and fell with great heaving breaths. The sight of it-something so soft and gentle in the arms of something so thick and mountaineous-made me laugh.
Oscar came out of the darkness toward me, stepped around Gerry's burning body, and I felt the waves of heat rise toward me as the circle of gasoline around Gerry caught fire.
Burn, I thought. Burn. God help me, but burn.
Just after Oscar stepped over the outer edge of the circle, it erupted in yellow flame, and I found myself laughing harder as he looked at it, not remotely impressed.
I felt cool lips smack against my ear, and by the time I looked her way, Danielle was already past me, rushing to take her child from Oscar.
His huge shadow loomed over me as he approached, and I looked up at him and he held the look for a long moment.
How you doing, Patrick?&quot; he said and smiled broadly.
And, behind him, Gerry burned on the ice.
And everything was so goddamned funny for some reason, even though I knew it wasn't. I knew it wasn't. I did. But I was still laughing when they put me in the ambulance." -- Dennis Lehane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4475-but-then-something-happened-ray-something-amazing-something-that-white</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 22:38:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Drew add a quote by Richard Price]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4475-but-then-something-happened-ray-something-amazing-something-that-white]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But then something happened, Ray, something amazing. Something...

&quot;That white cop sitting next to me? He took a long look at my mother when she came in, just like, absorbed her, and then without even turning to me, he just put his hand on my back, up between my neck and shoulder...

&quot;And all he did was squeeze. Give me a little squeeze of sympathy, then rubbed that same spot with his palm for maybe two, three seconds, and that was it.

&quot;But I swear to you, nobody, in my entire life up to that point had ever touched me with that kind of tenderness. I had never experienced a sympathetic hand like that, and Ray, it felt like lightning.

&quot;I mean, the guy did it without thinking, I'm sure. And when dinnertime rolled around he had probably forgotten all about it. Forgot about me, too, for that matter... But I didn't forget.

&quot;I didn't walk around thinking about it nonstop either, but something like seven years later when I was at community college? The recruiting officer for the PD came on campus for Career Day, and I didn't really like college all that much to begin with, so I took the test for the academy, scored high, quit school and never looked back.

&quot;And usually when I tell people why I became a cop I say because it would keep Butchie and Antoine out of my life, and there's some truth in that.

&quot;But I think the real reason was because that recruiting officer on campus that day reminded me, in some way, you know, conscious or not, of that housing cop who had sat on the bench with me when I was thirteen.

&quot;In fact, I don't think it, I know it. As sure as I'm standing here, I know I became a cop because of him. For him. To be like him. God as my witness, Ray. The man put his hand on my back for three seconds and it rerouted my life for the next twenty-nine years.

&quot;It's the enormity of small things... Adults, grown-ups, us, we have so much power... And sometimes when we find ourselves coming into contact with certain kinds of kids? Needy kids? We have to be ever so careful..." -- Richard Price]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
